Hm...
Kujou
I've got it!
It's a Hokkaido squirrel!
Incorrect.
It's a Taiwanese squirrel.
What?
The fact that you recognized it as a squirrel
shows you've made great progress, young master.
In the beginning, you'd have
just run away to the kitchen.
You're right.
It's true that I've become
somewhat used to seeing all this.
I guess I've come a little way.
By the way...
Because you're at our house,
you must be done with your finals.
Oh, yes!
I have some business in Touma tomorrow.
Would you like to come along, boy?
Is this from Shouko-san?
Yes, she said it was for the young master.
What's wrong?
You don't want it?
So you're back to calling me "boy."
Of course.
You're still a minor, aren't you?
That's not the issue.
I mean, the other day you called
me by my name, "Shoutarou"!
I don't recall.
So are you coming or not?
Come to think of it,
Densuke watermelons will be in season
in Touma right about now.
You're quite fond of them, aren't you?
Yes, indeed.
I don't feel it's truly summer
until I've had one.
Once you take a mouthful of
that crisp, ice-cold watermelon,
its shockingly sweet juices
just burst in your mouth—
Fine, I'll go!
I'll go with you!
I see.
But...
in return...
The Third Bone
The Bones that Slumber in Summer
Because it's summer and all...
- A Story Dedicated to Those Trapped by the Past -
de
Searching for a way out, I surround myself with trains of thought
I think about where to run, but I don't know which way to turn
Even words that feel like unstoppable forces
Can't do anything to shake my resolve
Can't do anything to shake my resolve
Can't do anything to shake my resolve
Can't do anything to shake my resolve
Can't do anything to shake my resolve
Front and back are two sides of the same coin
Together, they become pieces of the same puzzle
My heart woven tight, I'm headed for a future spun by fate
As time continues to pass,
I'll adorn this neverending pain with beautiful lies
But as long as I have a hope that may flutter by
It'll be fine that you're my answer
Seriously.
I didn't expect you to
be into this sort of thing.
Are you all right?
Sorry about that.
L-Let's go.
It may well be that I'm
just a boy to Sakurako-san.
Because she doesn't like others
and avoids human interaction,
it's doubtful that she even
thinks of me as a friend.
It wouldn't hurt for her to
count on me a bit more, though.
The metabolism of human cells increases
when they're exposed to sunlight.
Let's go, boy.
Go? Go where?
Welcome to Limestone Cave Green Park
For a little walk.
Wait. Are you sure this is a good idea?
This is totally a game trail!
So what?
A game trail means we
might find animals along it.
The same goes for their remains!
Don't go, Soutarou!
Who's Soutarou?
Soutarou... Shoutarou...
His name is just one letter from mine.
Um, Sakurako-san?
What?
Well, um...
If you need to go,
just do it in the bushes.
That's not it!
Then what?
Um, is Soutarou—
S-Someone's...
Someone's bones!
Please don't!
What if you go alone and
something happens to you?
If that were to happen,
having you with me wouldn't change much.
This is wonderful!
Look, boy!
I don't want to!
No, you should.
This is one of the mysteries of nature!
Listen, when a body is left exposed,
flies are quickly drawn to
the smell and lay eggs in it.
Once the larvae hatch, maggots feast
on the flesh and grow at an incredible rate.
In turn, the maggots attract their predators,
insects and small animals,
transforming the body into
a paradise of life for a short time!
Isn't it wonderful, boy?
The great circle of life known as the
food chain continues to enfold us all,
even after the body ceases all metabolic
activity and its cells are destroyed.
What? You don't find it awe-inspiring?
I'm going to report this to the authorities now.
I have a feeling your left lung
is larger than average.
My what?
Typically, the left lung is smaller
because it has to accommodate the heart.
But you are totally lacking in empathy.
You lack any heart!
Oh, hello?
Is this the police?
Hokkaido Police
Oh, come on! Not you two again!
NO  ENTRY
Well, some couple found it before we did, but...
Well, I have to ask.
Do you have any idea who this is?
No, but I can speculate.
Sakurako-san!
Now, let's clear up this mystery.
From the clothing, we can deduce that
the individual died in spring or autumn.
In spring, residual snow would
have made it difficult to come here,
so I'd say autumn.
Please, ma'am...
Quiet! You're disturbing my train of thought!
Hey, you! No one gave you
permission this time either.
Not to mention,
the body is partially mummified.
Saponification occurred over the winter,
then dehydration as the temperature rose.
As such, I recommend looking into missing
persons during or prior to last autumn.
Yeah?
The teeth indicate that
the individual was rather elderly.
Also, there's a fracture in the upper
cervical spine—that is, the neck.
I suspect the individual
fell from that cliff there.
However, the direct cause of death
would have been suffocation.
The cervical fracture severed the nerve,
preventing autonomous breathing.
Okay.
Still, it's quite miraculous
that the bones are so intact!
Normally, animals would have taken them.
How extremely fortunate!
Well, this individual wouldn't
think that, of course.
Hm?
What? Do you want more specifics?
Yes, that would be very helpful.
Upon finding a corpse, the first order
of business is determining its sex.
One approach is to examine
the ridge of the skull's orbit...
Please continue.
but the best method is to look at the pelvis.
Kujou
And Sakurako-san's been sulking ever since?
Yes. Naoe-sama scolded her rather harshly.
I'm sorry I couldn't stop her.
It's not your fault, young master.
Ever since she was a little girl,
bones have sent her off on a tear.
Since she was a little girl?
Yes. I believe it was her uncle's influence.
Now, why don't you take these to her...
while they're still cold?
Sakurako-san, it's me.
I'm coming in.
Miss, I've brought you some
ice-cold Densuke watermelon.
Like I thought, she's sulking.
That's Soutarou.
Huh?
My dead younger brother.
You've wanted to ask me that
for a while, haven't you?
Done!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Now, let's dig in while it's still ice-cold.
Because of that,
I completely forgot about
the bones we'd found.
I forgot that bones always
belonged to someone,
and that they had a family.
Meisei High School
All right, enjoy your summer break.
Opening
Ceremony
Day Duty
Katou
&
Minakawa
Don't you dare cause any trouble.
I won't be around to bail you out.
Huh?
And you call yourself a teacher?
Opening
Ceremony
Day Duty
Katou
&
Minakawa
Dismissed.
Hey, Shoutarou.
Huh?
You have a visitor.
Sorry, it was difficult
to bring this up at school.
FIRE
Um, the chiffon cake
here is pretty good.
Want to try some?
Then let's split it.
This silky smooth texture...
just melts along with
the light whipped cream.
You know, Tatewaki-kun...
Yeah?
My grandma loved
the chiffon cake here too.
Oh, really?
FIRE
Why...
Why couldn't we have thought more
about how she was doing?
Kougami-san?
Thank you, Tatewaki-kun.
Huh?
The police told me.
It was you, wasn't it?
You found my grandma's bones.
She'd been missing since last autumn.
She up and vanished one day,
as if she'd just had the idea
to walk out around the block.
Everything had been left as it was.
She'd even left her lights on.
And she didn't leave a single note.
People who knew her said a lot of things,
like how she must've grown tired of caring
for Grandpa and just run away on a whim.
But I believed in her.
She wasn't that kind of person!
She'd never kill herself!
Your grandmother...
committed suicide?
Yeah.
The police told me
that it's pretty common.
And why must I come along?
I was planning to assemble
a monkey skeleton today.
She'd like to see you and thank you.
I don't need any thanks.
That's just a bother.
She helped you with Ii-chan, didn't she?
Thanks for coming all the way out here.
Kujou-san came, too?
Yeah.
She's a little unusual,
but she's not a bad person.
I know.
I could hear Kujou-san
talking at Ii-chan's place.
She's kind.
Yeah, I guess.
By the way, are the two of you, uh...
Huh?
No, no, no!
That's not how it is at all!
Really?
That's how it seemed to me.
We're what you might call, like...
in a guardian relationship.
She's your guardian?
No, I'm hers.
This is a nice painting.
My grandfather painted it.
The horse's muscles are depicted
with great accuracy and beauty.
He must've studied the subject
very carefully before painting this.
I wish I could've told him that
when he could still understand.
S-Speaking of that, where's your family?
Sorry, my mom's picking up
my grandfather from daycare.
Oh, was this a bad time?
No, not at all.
But I guess we're only just realizing
how tough my grandma had it every day.
She said it'd be best to
let him stay somewhere familiar,
so she took care of him in their home
in Touma when he was bedridden.
When we called her from time to time,
she only said everything was fine.
But it wasn't fine at all.
Grandpa's dementia was getting worse.
Isn't that horrible?
We didn't even know about that.
We took Grandma at her word
and let her handle everything.
No, maybe we did know...
and just pretended not to notice.
Kougami-san, that's not—
We put her in a desperate position!
We...
It's my fault!
Tears are blood without
the plasma component.
In other words,
when you cry, you lose water,
and your blood temporarily thickens.
It's not good for your health.
Drink.
It's lukewarm, so it probably
won't taste good anymore.
That's the way.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Um, if you'd like,
please take this with you.
Are you sure?
Yeah, we still have lots of his paintings.
We brought them all over from Touma,
thinking they'd be good therapy for him.
Lucky you, Sakurako-san!
Hm?
Thank you.
I'll take good care of it.
No, thank you.
I'm sure Grandpa
would want you to have it.
Well, let's go, boy.
Okay.
Um,  Kujou-san!
May I ask you for a favor?
What is it?
Could you tell me where
and how Grandma died?
She came all the way out here,
into the mountains?
If she was taking care of her
bedridden husband alone,
she must have been strong.
Nursing someone isn't an easy task,
even for young people like you.
Sakurako-san...
It's all right, Tatewaki-kun.
Nursing really is tough.
Of course it is.
You're supporting a living human being.
There's no way it could be easy.
You're right.
It's up ahead.
Here.
Your grandmother was found
lying face-down over there.
She must have fallen from up there.
She died in such a lonely place.
It isn't lonely.
It's sunny, and it has a good view.
But there's nothing here!
The police told me that Grandma
left in the middle of the night,
because the lights were still on,
and the morning newspaper was in the mailbox.
Why?
Why did she walk
all the way here in the dark?
Why?
All I can say from examining
her remains is that, at the very least,
your grandmother did not suffer for long
before succumbing to death.
Are you...
Are you saying that's why
she jumped from the cliff?
So she could die quickly?
What are you talking about?
Your grandmother didn't choose
this place to be her grave.
What do you mean?
It's self-explanatory.
Most people wouldn't die
of a fall from that height.
There are any number of places
where death would be more certain.
But the police said—
Nonsense!
Your grandmother did fall from that cliff.
But it wasn't intentional.
She only died because
she fell in a bad way.
It was an accident.
What?
Then why was she here?
Wasn't that what
you came here to learn?
Climb up there, and you'll find out.
I have to go!
Kougami-san!
Grandma...
What were you trying to do, Grandma?
Please tell me.
What were you thinking at the end?
Now do you understand?
Understand?
Understand what?
Look.
Those mountains? What about them?
Honestly...
You guys don't see anything, do you?
Look at this view.
It's Grandpa's painting.
I get it.
That painting was the
sunset he saw from here.
I didn't recognize it,
even though I looked at it every day.
Good grief.
Boy, I'm surprised you got
into high school like that.
Huh?
Check your bearings.
Whoa!
Jeez...
If this way is north, then...
Grandpa didn't paint the sunset.
He painted the sunrise... in the east.
Bingo.
That's why your grandmother
left in the middle of the night.
She came here to see the same sunrise
that her husband had painted.
The sunrise...
When people bask in the morning sun,
serotonin is released in the brain.
Serotonin, also known
as the happy hormone,
calms and lightens the heart.
In other words,
the morning sun cheers people up.
Your grandmother
came here to gain something,
to rally herself.
She did not come here to die.
She was not in despair.
She chose to come here
because she wanted to live.
She wanted to live...
Of course, this is only
speculation on my part.
But if I were you, I would trust...
in the grandmother I knew, not the police.
My grandmother was an early riser.
She liked to go out to the fields
first thing in the morning.
She said it was the source of her energy.
I see.
So that was why.
Grandma wanted to see the sunrise,
so she could keep living with Grandpa.
Grandma?
You were right, Grandma.
It really does cheer you up!
Waves of fragmented memories break at my feet
memories
Lies crumble and are washed away, trickling like sand
kyou
ni
These echoes of memories fade away
echoes
But your gentle touch gives them shape once more
Surely what lies behind that beautiful smile
shi
roi
mo
shin
Are pure and delicate truths that will remain forever
truths
Faraway voices of prayer strip me of my defences
And continue to echo
voices