Dammit! We won't get anywhere like this!
What the hell's going on?
Are you confused?
Wait, how is he...
There's nothing much to it.
It's as simple as this.
This footage is merely a review of the results.
Nothing more and nothing less.
Th-Then... the King of Distortion
and everything he's been doing...
It was a collaboration.
Between that man and myself.
Though I must say, I am thankful
to him for setting all this up for me.
Sorry. I can't let you open the Moon Temple yet.
Shirou, your eyes look just like...
That's right.
I'm the real King of Distortion.
Oh? Does that mean you finally get it, President?
Yes.
I should have figured it out
the moment you showed up.
Did Masami Saotome say something to you?
I had completely forgotten about it,
but yes, he did.
To put it in your terms,
I might have pretended it never happened,
blamed it on a separate personality,
and tried to forget about it.
I see.
Impressive.
No matter how much you care for someone,
there's no guarantee that
they'll return your feelings.
I didn't want to admit it, but that's the truth.
Are you talking about yourself?
Specifically, about your
romantic feelings for Keiji Takeda?
I'm not sure. It still hurts, you know.
Well, aren't you honest?
Maybe.
I'm the disciplinary committee president.
But...
But I don't want to run away anymore.
Who knows? I'm not certain myself,
but I would guess she sees
the same things in him that you do.
That's right. I have nothing to be ashamed of.
Well done, Kei Niitoki.
You truly are an impressive one.
Kei Niitoki? So our paths have crossed yet again.
What brings you here?
I'm sure you wouldn't have
climbed all this way simply for fun.
Then again, maybe you did.
It's you we're talking about, after all.
T-Tanaka?!
Y-You're the real deal, right?
I've already had enough of these illusions.
I see. So that's how you knew about me.
We were once comrades in battle.
So it's only natural that you'd remember,
isn't it, King of Distortion?
Wh-What are you talking about?
I have no intention of hurting anyone.
This is simply an experiment.
I want to learn how to heal
the distortion in people's hearts.
All human hearts contain distortion.
Far too much of it, in fact.
All I have done today was
to draw their attention to this fact.
I see. That's the nature of your power.
It pinpoints the distortion in one's heart
in order to draw it out completely.
An ability to resonate with the mind
and amplify a certain portion of it.
Not bad for one so recently born.
Isn't that right, King of Distortion?
You first appeared only a short time ago.
If I'm not mistaken, it was just as you
arrived at the Moon Temple this morning.
That's why you are as of yet too inexperienced
to use your power properly.
This is also what caused Zouragi to appear.
Why were you born?
Do you yourself even know?
Yes, I do.
A deep feeling of guilt had wormed its way
into the core of Shirou Tanaka's being.
Because he had never understood
what she was thinking.
"She"?
Would that be Naoko Kamikishiro?
Should he have been more receptive of her feelings?
When thoughts like that took shape,
the result was this ability.
I see.
So, inexperienced or not,
I have to keep going. For her sake.
No matter how arduous the path may be.
Well, isn't that noble?
What are you going to do, Boogiepop?
Do you intend to stop me?
H-Hey! Hang on, you two!
I would have thought you'd understand, Kei.
Huh?
Because you managed to find
your own way through the distortion.
Well, tell me this.
What's going to happen to Tanaka's pain?
I'm sure that Tanaka was deeply hurt
by the guilt he felt when Naoko died.
What's going to happen to that suffering?
That's...
You have to change all that pain into gold.
You're the one who said that!
This is a story about a boy.
This boy was an ordinary person who
certainly could not have been called evil.
But in the end, he became an enemy of the world.
Through a caprice of fate, he met a man-eater
and realized that he harbored
a deep hatred of life itself within him.
Because of this, he became a man-eater himself.
This next story is about a girl.
She could see people's deaths.
This ability was harmless,
but it caused her to see death as something absolute.
She became obsessed with the idea of drawing out
the deaths of many people and putting them
together into something greater.
The girl believed that this was
the key to surpassing humanity,
and so she became an enemy of the world.
What are you talking about?
I was merely reminiscing about a few
of those who ended up as my enemies.
Sadly for them, they had no other path
available to them, and thus no future.
It's unclear whether that was for
good or ill to each of them personally.
Then again, it's quite possible
it didn't matter to them at all.
They could be, like me, mere possibilities
that took form and appeared in this world.
Existences with no bodies of their own.
But you...
Are you really the same way?
What do you mean?
You mentioned earlier that it didn't matter
how arduous your path might be.
The fact that you're willing
to adapt to any future events
indicates a certain level of flexibility.
Do you think I'm still unsure?
There do exist those who have
never known uncertainty.
Those who see only despair for this world.
When I meet such a person,
I must cut off their path
before they can go any further.
But you are not among them.
Any wounds you suffer here
will appear in reality too.
I'm quite aware. As you should know,
the same goes for you.
I'm of the opinion that you're
simply being a bit stubborn.
Even if you were to halt this experiment right now,
you would probably escape with very few regrets.
That isn't...
I get the impression that
you consider me your enemy.
But what exactly led you to believe that?
Are you saying you're not my enemy?
Let me be a little more precise.
What makes you think you're evil?
Have you done anything wrong here today?
You said it yourself earlier.
You haven't hurt anyone.
Are you the one who trapped
them inside this building?
You aren't, are you?
So why do you believe there must
be an enemy coming for you?
Was it that painful?
Did Shirou Tanaka really believe
he was that bad of a person?
Niitoki...
What do you think?
What?
Do you know what she was thinking?
I don't know.
But I do remember how excited she
always sounded when she would tell me,
"Kei, I'm in love with this guy."
I was a little jealous of how
honestly she could say that.
Tanaka, did you really care for Naoko?
Were you in love with her?
I can tell now.
I don't think your feelings were the same as hers.
Naoko was really in love with you,
but you were never sure of how
you felt about her, right up to the end.
And then when Naoko passed away,
you didn't know what to do, and that guilt
eventually became the King of Distortion.
But that really just means—
Yes. That is the nature of your own distortion.
It appears that it's not me
you should be trying to defeat.
But Tanaka, I'm sure that if Naoko could see you,
she'd say this with a big smile on her face.
"You'd better take care of yourself first
before you start worrying about anyone else!"
Tanaka!
Tanaka?
Boogie?
Niitoki... Th-The password...
Tanaka? Is it really you?
Niitoki, please go type the password
into that keyboard over there.
I'm betting this is what you'd choose, Boogie.
Oh? Is this classical?
Yes.
Not the most fitting score for an epilogue,
but I suppose it'll have to do.
An epilogue? Are you leaving?
Yes. This is where we say goodbye.
The distortion will return
to its origin, just as it should.
I see... That's too bad.
I was really enjoying myself.
I'm glad to hear it.
I mean it. I feel like a weight's been lifted from me.
I'm sure even if I'd been able to talk to the real him,
it wouldn't have gone this well.
I won't forget you.
Oh, but you will.
Once the distortion is gone from their hearts,
people just can't seem to remember
what it was that used to torment them.
I see... I don't really understand, but...
It's for the best.
You and your son pulled through.
Won't you feel a little lonely,
being forgotten like that?
The path you all must walk is a long one.
You can't afford to be worrying about my loneliness.
Hey... Where are you?
I am at once everywhere and nowhere.
Makoto! Wake up, Makoto!
Huh? Mom?
Where's Boogiepop?!
He—He beat the crap out of Zouragi!
Boogiepop was so awesome!
That's nice.
Hello there.
Is it over?
Yes. It appears that my work here is done.
I see...
Farewell.
U-Um...
Will I ever see you again?
I would think you should hope
never to meet the likes of me again.
Th-Then...
Wh-What if I...
If I, um...
end up your enemy...
You? End up my enemy?
Yeah. If that happens—
Finally! There you are!
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
Huh? What do you mean, what do I mean?
Don't you realize what just happened?
And it happened, like, immediately
after you got mad and ran off, too...
I looked everywhere for you!
If that time ever comes, I promise I won't hold back.
Where did she run off to?
This was supposed to be a date!
Niitoki! You were here too?
Oh, Takeda,
what brings you here?
Well, uh...
That's kind of what I wanted to ask you.
What are you doing here, Niitoki?
I just followed someone who caught
my eye and ended up here somehow.
And I got wrapped up in all this mess.
I-I see...
I guess today sucked for both of us.
No kidding. But it did let me see him again.
What, did you think I was
talking about you, Takeda?
Huh?
You think too highly of yourself.
Th-That's not really it...
Don't worry. It had nothing to do with you.
So, what are you doing here, Takeda?
O-Oh, yeah, Niitoki!
This might be a weird question,
but do you know who put this song on?
Of course I do.
Really? Where are they?
Right here.
Huh?
I'm the one who put it on.
Is there something wrong with that?
N-No...
You're looking for Miyashita, aren't you?
Huh? Uh, well, yeah...
I knew it. Well, I saw her not too long ago.
Down below.
But—
Touka Miyashita
Okay!
Good morning!
Super excited for today!
'Morning
Read
Touka Miyashita
I should be able to make
it on time for sure!
Touka Miyashita
Good morning!
Super excited for today!
Touka Miyashita
Okay!
Good morning!
Super excited for today!
'Morning
Read
Touka Miyashita
I should be able to make
it on time for sure!
Okay!
Good morning!
Super excited for today!
Okay!
Touka Miyashita
Good morning!
Super excited for today!
'Morning
Read
Touka Miyashita
I should be able to make
it on time for sure!
Touka Miyashita
Good morning!
Super excited for today!
'Morning
Read
Touka Miyashita
I should be able to make
it on time for sure!
Touka Miyashita
Good morning!
Super excited for today!
'Morning
Read
Touka Miyashita
I should be able to make
it on time for sure!
Touka Miyashita
Good morning!
Super excited for today!
'Morning
Read
Touka Miyashita
I should be able to make
it on time for sure!
Touka Miyashita
Good morning!
Super excited for today!
'Morning
Read
Touka Miyashita
I should be able to make
it on time for sure!
Touka Miyashita
Sorry
I'm running super late!
Touka Miyashita
Good morning!
Super excited for today!
'Morning
Read
Touka Miyashita
I should be able to make
it on time for sure!
Touka Miyashita
Sorry
I'm running super late!
Good morning!
Super excited for today!
'Morning
Read
Touka Miyashita
I should be able to make
it on time for sure!
Touka Miyashita
Sorry
I'm running super late!
Touka Miyashita
Good morning!
Super excited for today!
'Morning
Read
Touka Miyashita
I should be able to make
it on time for sure!
Touka Miyashita
Sorry
I'm running super late!
Touka Miyashita
Good morning!
Super excited for today!
'Morning
Read
Touka Miyashita
I should be able to make
it on time for sure!
Touka Miyashita
Sorry
I'm running super late!
Touka Miyashita
'Morning
Read
Touka Miyashita
I should be able to make
it on time for sure!
Touka Miyashita
Sorry
I'm running super late!
Touka Miyashita
On my way now!
Almost there!
'Morning
Read
Touka Miyashita
I should be able to make
it on time for sure!
Touka Miyashita
Sorry
I'm running super late!
Touka Miyashita
On my way now!
Almost there!
Touka Miyashita
I should be able to make
it on time for sure!
Touka Miyashita
Sorry
I'm running super late!
Touka Miyashita
On my way now!
Almost there!
Touka Miyashita
I should be able to make
it on time for sure!
Touka Miyashita
Sorry
I'm running super late!
Touka Miyashita
On my way now!
Almost there!
Touka Miyashita
I should be able to make
it on time for sure!
Touka Miyashita
Sorry
I'm running super late!
Touka Miyashita
On my way now!
Almost there!
Touka Miyashita
Made it!
Sorry
I'm running super late!
Touka Miyashita
On my way now!
Almost there!
Touka Miyashita
Made it!
Sorry
I'm running super late!
Touka Miyashita
On my way now!
Almost there!
Touka Miyashita
Made it!
Did you already
go home
?
Touka Miyashita
Did you already
go home
?
Touka Miyashita
Did you already
go home
?
You probably missed each other
because there's no cell signal in here.
You should probably hurry if you want to catch her.
Y-You think so? I'd better go now, then.
A-Also, Niitoki...
I'm sorry.
For what?
W-Well, I mean...
You know.
I told you. You're not the one I followed in here.
Right.
I have a better handle on my own
feelings after what happened today.
Thanks. I'll see you later, Takeda.
Yeah. See you later.
Goodbye.
I bet they'll sweep this whole thing under the rug as
"Kyouichirou Teratsuki's heinous crime".
But man, something about that feels so wrong.
That's just how it is.
True.
Boogiepop.
How did you know it was me?
Of course I knew.
How could I mistake the face of a friend?
The threat has passed, Mr. Takeda.