- Jurgen's House -
I never knew my parents.
Monika.
Go get some firewood.
I'll go get it!
It's so cold!
Right?
What should we do today?
Bullseye!
Seriously?
My life was filled with light.
My father,
he died.
Was it my fault?
Some people think so.
The forest is singing the song of your sweet warm memories
What about my mother?
Your mother's far from the only
woman to have died in childbirth.
Yes, you, and only you, can hear this angelic chorus
Am I...
Am I a little disaster?
Look up… let them hold your hands, so they can show you the way
Now cheer up and share your happiness
Leaves slowly float along the river
I lost everything.
No, it was taken from me.
Who knows where they came from?
- Ruins -
As if they’re telling you to leave all of your pain and tragedy behind
There's only one person I want to see.
Capital of the
Former Territory of Kal-o
Slowly breathe in the air around you
So that's the new duke, Ray Dawn.
He seems like a kind man.
Be sure to look after yourself, madam.
Listen to the serene sound of the wind blowing
Such gracious words, coming from our new king.
Please, I am no king.
If you smile, then the sky will shine, slowly but surely...
A gun!
There's a gun!
Run!
Your Grace!
Even though I can never get it back...
You'll be able to see your tomorrow...
Ray Dawn!
Drop the gun!
The forest is singing the song of your sweet warm memories
All of it!
It's all your fault!
Yes, you, and only you, can hear this angelic chorus
Look up… let them hold your hands, so they can show you the way
Several Months Later
Now cheer up and share your happiness...
Where is she?
The forest is singing the song of your sweet warm memories
I have to take the same amount
that was taken from me.
Yes, you, and only you, can hear this angelic chorus
Because I'm still empty.
Look up… let them hold your hands, so they can show you the way
Now cheer up and share your happiness...
Where are you?
I wake up, tired
So sick, bored, and fed up
I was never like this, I even had dreams, too
No one can stop me, bully me or suppress me
Can we ever break free of this miserable life we're living?
We'll never stop, we'll find our way, always, if we pray
I hear them coming for me now
Trying to lure me out
And all this time, I knew where it was
So I'm fired up and ready, looking for a good fight
So break it down and never give up
This is your only chance to change the world, so rise up!
It's your life!
Now is the time!
Fight for your life!
So don't cry out to stop! Not until you've won!
Break free of these chains
And give it all you've got!
Episode 05
Black Moon and Lost Child's Song
Ver!
Oh?
I don't know who you are,
but do you think you can stand in the way of my art?
Art? Is that what you call it?
Ver!
A fairy?
Daddy, this is the fairy you envisioned.
Ah, I can hear Mommy's song!
Creep...
Oh, yes!
Take this!
Guess you're not really a big deal at all!
Damn it... she's good.
Boo!
How ideal.
You specialize in parlor tricks?
It's art! Maybe you can't tell!
How can I be so powerless?
I'm not the old me anymore!
Seriously?!
Quit screwing around!
I'm not the old me anymore!
You're...
Ver! Get back!
How divine!
Ver.
Quickly.
Damn mongrel.
Yo.
Use it.
You dropped one hell of
a job on my lap, Bitter Sweet.
Stop!
The Black Fairy Tome!
Bye!
Ver?
Thanks...
for saving me.
I'm amazed you survived.
Deep down, I always believed you were safe.
I mean, I survived, after all.
"Safe"...
You're the one who tried
to kill Ray Dawn, aren't you?
I messed up.
Don't tell me you still haven't given up?
Do you still plan to kill him?!
Don't do it, Ver! Doing such a thing won't—
Mommy, let me hear you sing.
Daddy, I can paint so well.
He's still...!
Oh, my art!
Yes!
Ver!
Don't try to find me.
Don't get involved with me.
I just wanted to tell you that.
But...!
The Veronica Thorn you know is dead.
That is what you must believe.
Ver!
Your Grace.
You're going?
Yes.
Things are probably going
to get busier from here on out.
I will do what I can.
Wolfran Row.
For what purpose do you live?
This is the only path I can choose.
Me too.
Dorothea HQ
Ow!
Darn it...
That might leave a scar.
I'll worry about that when the time comes.
Medical Technology Department
Fairy regulatory agency Dorothea
Elenoa Need
Free was with you, and yet this still happened.
He's not my guardian.
He's a man, so he's got to protect women.
I don't really get stuff like that.
That so?
Oh, hang on.
Health Certificate Report for Marlya Noel
Looks good.
Is there anything else on your mind?
Nothing I can think of, really.
Health Certificate Report for Marlya Noel
Fairy possession, huh?
Jangri'la
Pie &      Mash
Hello, hello! How goes?
That rookie's as noisy as ever.
I'll say.
Over here! Marlya!
Right here, this seat!
He's too loud.
Here you are.
Oh, thanks.
Sir!
You sit there.
Aw...
Are they...
Those three gentlemen there?
Are they affiliated with us?
You said "us". Now you're fully one of the gang.
I thought maybe I should
avoid mentioning the name.
It's generally okay in this pub.
Unit 1
Fairy regulatory agency Dorothea
Robert Chase
It's local, and we come here often.
Those old men are just regulars here.
We're outstanding regulars!
I'm a hero of the great war.
That he is!
Gonny here was a captain in the military!
"Gonny"?
I was one of the captain's men.
He may not look it, but he was a good soldier.
Wow.
Ray Dawn.
History is written by the victors.
Jangri'la
Pie &      Mash
And so,
late as it may be, this is both Marlya's welcome party
and a celebration of her successful mission!
Cheers!
Good stuff!
Can I get another, please?
She chugged it?
Why so down, sir?
Is it because the Gui Carlin cleaner who
attacked during your mission got away?
Maybe you do need me there
for things to go well, after all.
Yeah, keep dreaming.
Are you all right?
You were wounded, so you should take it easy.
No, I'm fine. Really.
Despite appearances, she's actually quite tough.
Does that mean I look weak?
You mean she looks sweet, right?
I said nothing of the sort!
Well!
I think Marlya's cute, though.
Be on your guard.
He says that to everyone.
Right.
Commander of Unit 3
Fairy regulatory agency Dorothea
Lily Heinemann
He's never said it to me.
Well, you see, that's because
you're beautiful and dignified!
How about the director?
The director?!
Director Nein, huh?
Let's see...
Unit 1
Fairy regulatory agency Dorothea
Ozz Mare
Ozz, you're already drinking something else?
Didn't you invite the director?
I did tell her about it.
But she said no way.
The director is always busy.
But if you don't at least invite her,
she might take it personally.
Yeah.
Surprisingly enough, she can be like that.
She's not that kind of person.
No, you just don't know her true nature.
Yes, I very well do.
Klara owes the director her life, after all.
That's right.
If the director hadn't saved me, right now I'd be...
He's moved on to yet another drink.
Well!
You could say I technically owe her my life as well.
Didn't you beg her for your life?
That's another way to put it, I suppose.
Long live the director! Three cheers for Nein Auler!
Everyone has a history. And no two are the same.
Each one is unique.
Don't tell me you're drunk already?
What are you talking about?
Hey, you guys!
This one's on me!
You really are a hero, Gonny!
Aren't you guys the security
for the anniversary of the war's end?
Make us proud.
Will do!
Steve! Bring us some glasses!
Yes, sir! Right away, sir!
Give it a rest.
Don't order Steve around.
Slow down.
Come on, Ozz! It's Marlya's welcome party.
Don't drink so much without the rest of us!
Come on, Steve!
Glasses for everyone, on the double!
Sure thing!
I just told you not to order him around.
Chop-chop!
Pace yourselves with the drinking.
Nice.
Deep in the forest
A quiet song is sung
Carrying fate upon its shoulders
A song of life
Said the lying crow
"Only calamity awaits beyond"
The fox asks, in hushed tones,
"Is there such a thing as happiness?"
Vanishing as quickly as it gathers
Drawn together, sounds weave into a melody
Heard across the world
Illuminating the path to tomorrow
As though not to melt the fluttering snowflakes
The ashen sky is gentle
As it wraps up and sings this song
A new type of artificial fairy.
We received info from a certain
source about the Black Fairy Tome.
Pursuing the target!
Cut me a bit of a deal.
Next Time
Fellow Traveler
My little she-dog.