24 years ago, in the year U.E. 481,
the War of Unification began.
All of Eastald was plunged into a tempest of conflict.
In this intense, drawn-out war,
the greatest weapons to be had were...
Fairy Soldiers.
- The Fairy Village -
Lay!
Why are you doing this, Lay Dawn?!
Do it!
Stop, I beg you!
People struggle. They fight.
Even should they lose that which they hold dearest.
All that gathers are the irreversible
consequences of their actions.
Marlya.
Stand up, Marlya.
This rain has to stop eventually.
Final Moments
of the War
All things come to an end...
Message! Official message!
His Majesty has announced our surrender!
Message! Message!
Damn it!
...even should it come too late.
Nine years ago,
with the compliance of the king of Cidal,
Eastald was unified under the emperor of Zesskia,
bringing an end to the war.
While a range of contradictions,
tensions, and antagonism remained,
the great War of Unification had,
at least officially, come to an end.
Stop!
Wolf!
Wolfran!
We Fairy Soldiers no longer had a place to go.
And now...
As I wake up, tired,
I find a world in ruins
I was never like this, I even had dreams, too
No one can stop me, believe in me surpassing
Can we ever break free of this miserable life we're living?
We'll never stop, we'll find a way, always, if we pray
I hear them coming for me now
Trying to wear me down
And all this time, I knew where it was
So I'm fired up and ready, looking for a good fight
So break it down and never give up
This is your only chance to make a stand, so rise up!
It's your life!
Now is the time!
Fight for your life!
Don't ever stop, not until you're done!
Break free of these chains
And give it all you've got!
Episode 01
The Ash-covered Girl
Former Territory
of Kal-o
I'm rather looking forward to this.
Yeah, it seems there's some
real treasure to be had today.
Oh, it sounds like we're getting started.
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen!
We are truly grateful that you could join us today.
We're already on our fifth Squire All-Night Auction,
and it's all made possible by you, our patrons.
Is this...
Hey! You there.
Aren't you one of the Cocolu Family's underlings?
What are you doing back here?
The auction's already underway.
Get back to your post.
Oh, sorry.
You're with... Gui Carlin, right?
The head of security...
It's Free. Surely we've been introduced.
Ah, that's right. Mister Free.
Drop the "Mister". Just "Free" will do.
Surely I told you that as well?
Did you now?
I—
...believe I did.
Maybe I wasn't paying attention.
None of you guys are posted here.
Get back to work.
Yessir, Mister Free.
Er, sorry. Free...?
Well, whatever.
Hurry along to your post now.
Yessir.
Wow, what's this creature here?
Hey!
Up next, we have the centerpiece of the first group!
Lot number 23.
An extremely valuable item not only financially,
but also historically and scientifically as well!
A single page from the Black Fairy Tome!
How cute.
Hey! I said get back to work.
My name's not "Hey".
Huh?
It's Marlya.
I introduced myself to you, too.
Right, sorry.
Actually, I was wondering
why you carry a hunting rifle.
It's what I'm most familiar with.
It's friendly with people...
What is this little thing?
I'm pretty sure that,
unlike us humans, it can see fairies.
Or maybe it can detect them by their scent?
It's going to be sold at auction too, isn't it?
Win the bid and it's yours.
It ain't bloody cheap.
Fairies?
1,500,000 galey! 1,550,000 galey!
Oh! We have two million galey!
This is a top-quality fairy bottle.
Look how clearly you can see the fairy primordials.
Fairy... primordials?
These things.
Aren't they just fairies?
In a general sense, yes.
"Fairy primordial" is the formal
scientific term for them.
The things we refer to as "fairies" are...
In any case, if they get out of the fairy bottle,
we won't be able to see them.
Oh, okay.
Hey, the—
Th-The cage wasn't locked!
Huh?! I bet you let it—
What's happening?
Wh-What?!
H-Hey!
That Black Fairy Tome is—
I'll be taking this.
You lot don't need it.
Who the hell are you?!
That's not something you need to know.
A-A monster?!
Isn't that a fairy?!
Stop it!
A fairy!
No way! A fairy?!
Get back here!
Hold it right there!
Is that her fairy?
I've never seen one like that before.
I knew it...
I finally found you.
Ver!
It's you, isn't it?
Veronica!
Marlya?
Ver!
I've been searching for you for so long!
And now I've finally found you!
Eyes on your opponent!
You two know each other, huh?
But that can wait when there's work to be done!
Not bad, for a mere guard.
Believe it or not, I'm actually head of security.
Damn, this one's no pushover.
As it stands, she has the upper hand.
Think I'll let loose for a change.
Stop it!
That's easy for you to say!
Both of you, stop! Why are you doing this?!
Shut up!
Ver! Wait! Hear me out!
Ver!
Hey, don't run off!
I said stop!
Don't follow me, Free!
You'll just complicate things!
You're not making any sense!
Wait!
Ver!
Veronica from Suna no longer exists.
At all.
Forget about her.
Ver!
Why...
Reckless idiots!
What if they hit an attendee?!
Why?!
This way!
This way, quickly!
Save me!
Shit! Shit, shit!
It's absolute chaos!
A fairy...
What?
Look out!
No!
That's... Suna.
My hometown...
Our hometown...
That forest is no longer...
Ver.
Why?
Do it!
Lay Dawn. You were born in Suna, too...
You'll pay for this, I swear!
So long as I draw breath, you will pay! I swear it!
Ver!
No!
What are you doing here?
Ver!
A relic of the great war—a Fairy Soldier?
I could ask you the same. Where does a young
lady like yourself get her hands on a fairy?
Veronica.
You are an extreme threat.
I won't be holding back.
Howl!
You withstood even that?
Unfortunately for you...
Don't move!
I don't want to hit you.
I'm with Gui Carlin.
I outrank you.
Is that the truth?
Veronica, come with me.
I've been searching for so long.
You joined the mafia just to find me?
Yes. I thought that would be the quickest way.
So come with me.
Where have you been all this time?
I missed you so much.
You and I are the only remaining survivors of Suna.
It's just the two of us.
Shut up.
Ver, what's wrong?
Don't call me "Ver"!
I'm...
I'm not the Veronica you know.
You're still you, right?
Wrong!
I'm...
Stop!
A fairy?!
Marlya, you too?
Is that fairy... mine?
How?
Veronica?
I went to a lot of trouble to infiltrate Gui Carlin.
Now it's all ruined.
Infiltrate?
So you weren't with Gui Carlin after all?
I'm sure you've at least heard of the name
"Dorothea" during your time in the mafia?
The regulatory agency for illegal fairies?
The government's lackeys?
It's because you saw that.
Saw what?
That Veronica woman.
She used a fairy and made off
with the Black Fairy Tome.
Then there's the matter of you...
Me?
You're able to use a fairy.
Your very existence is illegal.
Are you going to arrest me?
Who says that's my only option?
Free Underbar, Dorothea Unit 1.
Will you be arrested, or will you become
a "government lackey", as you put it?
The choice is yours.
I have a name, you know.
Marlya Noel.
I want to talk to Ver. Properly.
Deep in the forest
A quiet song is sung
Carrying fate upon its shoulders
A song of life
Quoth the lying raven
"Only calamity awaits beyond"
The fox asks, in hushed tones,
"Is there such a thing as happiness?"
Vanishing as quickly as it gathers
Drawn together, sounds weave into a melody
Heard across the world
Illuminating the path to tomorrow
As though not to melt the fluttering snowflakes
The ashen sky is gentle
As it wraps up and sings this song
Well done.
Ah, unfortunately this is a fake.
I can tell at a glance.
Is that so.
Marlya...
This place must be ruins or something.
A fairy primordial directly possessing a human.
Small fry like to swarm.
The other one is a Fairy Soldier!
I see you still haven't learned how to shut up.
Next Time
Wolf Collar and Swan Feathers