Rondacia Imperial Palace
Duke Hybranz, your recent deed
was noble and righteous.
You are an exemplary loyal subject.
I am unworthy of your praise.
It is my greatest pleasure that
the prime minister escaped danger,
and Your Imperial Majesty's mind rests at ease.
I narrowly escaped death.
For that, I must thank you once more.
I just did what anyone would do.
I am no hero, unlike Duke Kal-o
of the Seven Knights.
But I, too, was once a soldier.
Ray Dawn.
He certainly was a hero, once...
Emperor of Unified Zesskia
Castal Harol
I shall reward you handsomely.
Is there anything you desire?
Yes, Your Majesty.
I wish for you to bestow upon me a Fairy Weapon.
Pardon?!
A Fairy Weapon, you say?
I wake up, tired
So sick, bored, and fed up
I was never like this, I even had dreams, too
No one can stop me, bully me or suppress me
Can we ever break free of this miserable life we're living?
We'll never stop, we'll find our way, always, if we pray
I hear them coming for me now
Trying to lure me out
And all this time, I knew where it was
So I'm fired up and ready, looking for a good fight
So break it down and never give up
This is your only chance to change the world, so rise up!
It's your life!
Now is the time!
Fight for your life!
So don't cry out to stop! Not until you've won!
Break free of these chains
And give it all you've got!
Episode 09
Rolling Stones and Seven Knights
I heard the news.
Sounds like you guys had
your hands full at the ceremony.
Yes. But it's not like I really...
Their attitude toward those guys
has improved since you came.
I'll say it has.
Well, maybe? I mean, I hope so.
But even though ten years
have passed since the end of the war,
it looks like another one might start soon.
Huh?
Will it be Kal-o, or Hybranz?
Well, I suppose Kal-o is the shady one here.
Kal-o Official Residence
Schwarz Diese is making a move?
Tell me more.
Prime Minister's Official Residence
We'll have Fairy Minister Sett take responsibility
for the blunder at the war anniversary ceremony.
Vice-Minister Bellwood, you'll succeed him.
Yes, sir.
Duke Hybranz has requested
we hand over one of the Fairy Weapons.
Well...
He intends to use it to protect
His Majesty in case of emergency.
That's the pretext, at least.
Duke Kal-o is one of the Seven Knights,
and thus already has a Fairy Weapon.
Duke Hybranz, however, does not.
Hence, there's a lack of balance.
What do you intend to do?
I'll give him one.
Vice-Minister Bellwood,
retrieve a Fairy Weapon from the vault.
We'll have Dorothea transport it.
Understood, Director Auler?
Yes, sir.
More trouble.
Ministry of Fairies
So the Fairy Weapons were held by
seven knights during the War of Unification?
The Seven Knights, yeah.
Painsealer. Fratanil. Verosteal. Aliadra.
They killed many a Fairy Soldier during the war.
Of the seven that exist, four are stored here.
Our Ministry of Fairies maintains
strict control over them.
Ray Dawn has one too, doesn't he?
Yes, Sororias.
Incidentally, the director is one of
the Seven Knights, and the owner of Aliadra.
Oh, I have heard that one of
the Seven Knights was a woman.
So that was Director Nein.
Doesn't Verosteal belong to you?
I'm not one of the Seven Knights.
It was just entrusted to me.
You're handing over Fratanil
to Duke Hybranz, right?
Yes.
Fratanil, which once belonged to Garlan Battle,
chief amongst the Seven Knights.
I wonder how Duke Hybranz intends to use it.
Outskirts of Rondacia
From this angle, Rondacia looks beautiful.
That beautiful jewel is within reach.
I'm in for a spectacular time, aren't I?
Naturally. I've set a wonderful stage for you, Colonel.
Now you've got my hopes up.
Rondacia Station
Fratanil is a national treasure.
Make sure you deliver it safely.
Yes, ma'am!
Man, wish I could've gone to Hapstadt, too.
Wanna switch places?
I'll pass, thanks. This job looks too serious.
Be careful.
We will, Robert.
You're not going? That's a shame.
My able subordinates will get Fratanil to Hapstadt.
Rest assured.
We shed much blood and sweat
to build this time of peace.
I doubt anything will happen.
Rondacia Palace — Heavenly Gate Plaza
It's usually artificial fairies on patrol here.
The credibility of every model,
both new and old, has been put under scrutiny now.
We'd be in serious trouble
if a war were to break out now.
Would you mind not jinxing us?!
Dorothea HQ — Interrogation Room
How did you get involved with Arcame?
Who knows.
Weren't you in contact with Wolfran Row?
Your plan failed. Therefore,
you'll probably avoid the death penalty.
Provided you tell us everything.
I'll probably spend the rest of my life in jail, anyway.
Amnesty could reduce your sentence.
You might even get to turn a new leaf.
Ted.
Hanns said you're like a son to him.
Don't make this any harder on your adoptive father.
Chief...!
Colonel, the sun is setting.
Unless blood flows and seethes, it just stagnates.
Unless a person dies, they just rot.
Sophie, will you die too?
Anytime, if it's by your side.
Don't mind him.
Nein Auler can't leave Rondacia, eh?
I'd comment on how small your force is...
but that would sound thoughtless to you, Colonel.
Join in if you'd like some fun, Wolfran Row.
That's not my job.
I-I'm sorry.
Oh. Yeah...
Don't worry about it.
Shouldn't I, though?
It won't be long now.
What are they doing on the tracks?!
What?!
What do you think you're doing?!
Do you want to die?!
Go, Eizenkopf!
Thank you.
Get some more sleep.
We use every part of a kill. No exceptions.
I'm sorry, Marlya.
It's all right, Victor.
I wonder if it's my fault again...
Since I'm a cursed child, after all.
Marlya! Marlya!
C'mon, wake up!
Are you hurt anywhere?!
No, I'm all right.
Third Unit, guard Fratanil!
We're under attack. Can you fight?
Yes, sir.
There are between ten and fifteen enemies.
It's not a large force.
They're probably after Fratanil.
Is Duke Hybranz...
No, I guess Fratanil's our top priority right now.
We've gotta retaliate.
I'll go.
Okay. We'll cover you.
That guy's... Great, just what we frigging need!
Who is he?
Beevee Liscar, one of the Seven Knights!
He fought against unification until the very end.
Does that mean he has a Fairy Weapon?
Agent of war and mercenary band leader
Beevee Liscar
Dorothea!
See if you can stop me!
That's it. Gaddfacs.
Fairy Weapons are a fairy's natural enemy.
And his Eizenkopf is...
I'll use Fratanil.
There's no other way to fight back.
We've got to draw them away.
You pebbles.
Lily!
So I cast the trap, make a real impact
Ozz?!
No way in hell you gonna walk away alive intact
Oh, ho?
Blast away, blades of steel locked in combat
It's either win or lose, and I'll be the one to get the final laugh
Roll like the pebble you are!
So I act, exact, make shields collapse
No way in hell I'll let you run away, all relaxed
Fratanil, huh? Interesting!
Take, attack, carry it all on my back
But...!
It's always live or die, but coming out on top's just my style
You'll have to do better than that!
Blast off
I guess a pebble can't suddenly become steel.
A fairy?
You don't have what it takes
to fire me up as you are now.
Sophie!
This world is mine!
All you gotta do is worship me instead
So I cast the trap, make a real impact
No way in hell you gonna walk away alive intact
Blast away, blades of steel locked in combat
It's either win or lose, and I'll be the one to get the final laugh
So I act, exact, make shields collapse
No way in hell I'll let you run away, all relaxed
Nothing personal.
Take, attack, carry it all on my back
It's always live or die, but coming out on top's just my style
The mediocre should learn from defeat.
If you can't turn humiliation into strength,
next time will be your last.
You've got a lot of spirit.
I probably would have enjoyed fighting you again.
Ozz...
With those wounds, you'll never fight again.
So the least I could do is...
Deep in the forest
A quiet song is sung
Carrying fate upon its shoulders
A song of life
Said the lying crow
"Only calamity awaits beyond"
The fox asks, in hushed tones,
"Is there such a thing as happiness?"
Vanishing as quickly as it gathers
Drawn together, sounds weave into a melody
Heard across the world
Illuminating the path to tomorrow
As though not to melt the fluttering snowflakes
The ashen sky is gentle
As it wraps up and sings this song
Ozz... Ozz!
Ozz...
Ozz?
Ozz!
I don't want people to die because of me!
I wonder if Marlya will come back.
We're not a family. We are, however,
comrades who watch each other's backs.
Next Time
Cursed Child
I... can't do it.