I wake up, tired
So sick, bored, and fed up
I was never like this, I even had dreams, too
No one can stop me, bully me or suppress me
Can we ever break free of this miserable life we're living?
We'll never stop, we'll find our way, always, if we pray
I hear them coming for me now
Trying to lure me out
And all this time, I knew where it was
So I'm fired up and ready, looking for a good fight
So break it down and never give up
This is your only chance to change the world, so rise up!
It's your life!
Now is the time!
Fight for your life!
So don't cry out to stop! Not until you've won!
Break free of these chains
And give it all you've got!
Episode 08
Pipe Blowing in Stage Wing
Warlock Residence
The gift is these two, as a matter of fact.
They're both with Dorothea.
And what, exactly, am I supposed to do with them?
Whatever you want.
I'm sure you'll find some use for them.
There's the signal!
Let's go!
Sweetie!
Going to shoot me?
Guess you don't care what happens to Gilbert, then?
Drop your weapons!
Looks like you'll finally grant me my request.
I never expected you to work with Dorothea.
Have you no shame?
East End Base — Hangar
I will see you again tomorrow.
The Security Bureau?
Hanns Efmed.
What can I do for you?
Daniel Keys, Security Bureau.
We have a few questions for you regarding
the new models that malfunctioned.
Please come with us.
Chief!
Two days until the anniversary of the war's end
It's like a maze.
Serge and I will go that way.
Ozz, you search this side.
Okay.
Do you understand what it is you're doing?
Of course.
The unit has already stormed the place.
We should wait for them to regroup with us.
No.
He's a cautious man.
He might have something up his sleeve.
I'm hardly the cunning
schemer that you are, Sweetie.
I'd watch my back if I were you.
This woman is a born swindler.
This room is a dead end?
Just where is the Black Four?
Yes, I don't see anything that looks like it.
Gilbert.
Lead the way.
Wh-What are you—
Wouldn't you rather have
the younger girls babysit you?!
Hey!
You're kidding!
Bitter Sweet!
She got us!
It's no use, it won't open!
What happened?
Bitter Sweet went through here!
Are there any other passageways?!
Chief!
What happened?
What's the chief supposedly done?!
Calm down.
Where's Hanns?
The Security Bureau took him away!
Quick, aren't you, Daniel?
Already making your move?
It won't budge.
Must be set up so it won't open
if you shut it from inside.
I'm glad you're not hurt.
Yeah, sure.
No, I mean it.
In here?
This ought to do.
Another passageway?
Let's move.
Yes, sir!
Is this...?
Could this... be the Black Fairy Tome?!
Looks like it.
Sweetie, where'd you disappear to?
Security Bureau
Hanns has yet to confess.
Try to keep it short.
Sure.
Hanns.
Tell me the truth.
They say I tampered with the new models?
What nonsense.
The new model was developed to be a
symbol of unification after the war ended.
This is a serious matter. You understand, don't you?
Yeah. I get it.
You're hiding something, aren't you?
What?
Assistant Vice-Minister Griff,
please take a look at this.
Some kind of device was installed, then removed.
I don't think there's any other answer.
Dorothea HQ
Bitter Sweet got away?
We had planned to arrest her
once we obtained the Black Four...
She left the Black Four behind, though.
So, we both got what we were looking for.
That makes it a draw.
Director!
What's with the outburst?!
Well, because...
We just got word they found signs that
those new models were tampered with!
Unified Zesskia Prime Minister's Official Residence
This is truly regrettable,
but while the culprit was someone on the inside,
the new model still has a frame
that can be made to malfunction, and so...
I have only one question.
Can the new models protect His Imperial
Majesty during the ceremony, or not?
In light of all the available facts, well...
The ceremony is tomorrow.
We cannot postpone it.
I-In that case...?
We will not be using the new models.
So much for the ten-year turning point...
I'd expect no less from the son of Ledrad's late king.
Hybranz Official Residence
I'm actually his illegitimate son...
Noble of Former Ledrad
Christoph Rahn
but only royalty get to know about this.
Oh. Well, well.
If Hanns is the culprit, what's his motive?
Yeah.
Maybe it was for Eddy Lloyd,
his unrewarded colleague?
But a colleague is still not oneself.
I doubt he feels such a strong
sense of obligation toward him.
The new model frame was
developed under the leadership
of the Ministry of Fairies as
a symbol of unification, right?
Even if military mechanics like Hanns Efmed
are qualified to be artificial fairy technicians,
they didn't get to be key figures in the development.
Perhaps he bears a grudge over that or something?
Which would make getting rid
of the new model his only aim.
If so, that's how it went down...
You don't buy it?
I'd like to look into Eddy's personal life again.
Sorry, I know we're busy.
Get the director to agree to it.
We'll handle things here.
Thanks.
One less thing to worry about
after tomorrow, at least.
Just a little further to go.
Hey Serge, wake up!
Wake up!
What?! What?!
Did something happen?
I swear.
Tomorrow, huh?
Rondacia Palace — Armory
East End Base — Hangar
You guys are up.
Rondacia Palace — Heavenly Gate Plaza
Oh, Eddy?
I heard he forfeited his pension,
even though he had a son.
A son?
Yeah.
Eddy's a workaholic kind of guy.
His wife got sick of him and
practically raised the kid by herself.
There was no mention of that in his military record.
He brought him along to work once or twice.
I remember because I played with him.
Eddy Lloyd has a son...
Anniversary of the war's end
I just realized something about Chase.
His name is Robert Chase.
Nobody calls him "Robert."
Do you know what military police are?
I've heard of them, at least.
They're police who oversee internal military affairs.
Chase was originally in Cidal's military police,
and after the war he kept an eye
on soldiers for the Security Bureau.
Then, he joined us.
He's not a bad guy,
but most don't think too highly of the military police,
the Security Bureau, those kinda orgs.
Maybe I'll try calling him "Robert" next time.
I think he'd like that.
What could someone possibly want at this hour?
You're Eddy Lloyd's wife.
Sorry, ex-wife.
That creep...
This isn't about Eddy.
Where is your son, and what does he do?
Ted Livingston.
He was raised by his mother,
so he doesn't share your surname.
Ted, who you called your
right-hand man, is Eddy's son.
So what if he is?
You were covering for him.
The son of Eddy, your old colleague... your friend.
Think about it, Hanns!
If Eddy's son—if Ted is behind this—
do you think his only goal is to force
the new model off the center stage?
No, wait...
Ted might use the old model's override function!
Override function? Old model?
Will I make it in time?!
I played with Eddy's son a
number of times, many years ago.
It took a while for me to realize
the new trainee was that same kid.
And it's not like Eddy ever bothered to tell me.
You held my tiny trembling hand when I was little
Even once Eddy quit and disappeared after the war,
Ted continued to devote himself to his work.
And you tried to show me the world
I've no doubt he was concerned
about his dad, but he never let it show.
No one could ever find it
Laughing out loud until late into the night
Saving me from my nightmares
So I could learn what love is
Zesskia! Zesskia! Zesskia! Zesskia!
Though I have to say "Sorry,
Ted wasn't involved in
the new model's development,
but if he used some illegal interrupt device or something,
he maybe could manage to cause a malfunction.
But I need to leave this place."
The old model Eddy developed
has what's called an override function.
How many tears must be spilled by you and me
But it's for testing purposes, and currently disabled.
What would happen if he activated it?!
What could he do?!
To let our deepest sorrows heal
No one could ever fix it
He could operate them
any way he wants, all at once.
Any number of them within the audible
range of the special override pipe.
Day by day, I realize how you've brought me to life
They'd disregard their operator?!
So I could know where to come back to
That's why it was sealed up.
He'd have to apply some change to the frame itself.
The way you wipe away my tears, my fears
Only Eddy knows how it's done... or so I thought.
The way you just trust me from deep within your heart
Eddy was sheltered by Arcame.
That same Arcame is now up to something.
Makes me stronger than I've been for countless nights before
If Ted got his hands on information
about the old model's override function...
It pains me to admit this,
but I failed to notice Ted's feelings
Don't worry about me anymore
or the fact that he tampered with the new models!
Did you think that I was gonna cry
You have to go and stop him!
Please! He's like a son to me!
Over this endless cycle of pain
I know I've come so far and now I'm all alone
Zesskia! Zesskia! Zesskia! Zesskia!
But your wisdom echoes through me
Again and again
Ray Dawn!
That means Ver might be here as well.
I don't think now is the time.
I know.
I won't let it end so easily.
Chase?!
What's going on?
Their true targets are the old models!
Old models? What's going to happen?
There's no time! Allow me to secure Ted Livingston!
Hanns' assistant?
Arrest Ted!
Yes, ma'am!
Where's Ted?!
He went out there a while ago.
To hell with your "unification", Golbarn Helwise.
Is that what you call eliminating
all who refused to bend the knee?
Ten swift years have passed since His Imperial Majesty
announced the end of the War of Unification!
Once those who served you
and gave everything to end
the war became obstacles,
Today we dedicate the victory
to those who fell in battle,
they were mercilessly cast aside!
those who survived, and all those who today sing—
Just like my old man!
Meet the artificial fairies my
old man made to help you win.
Prime Minister!
Shit!
Ted Livingston!
Get that pipe!
Sorry!
Are you unharmed, Excellency?
Yes, I'm all right.
Did someone try to assassinate the prime minister?
Ray Dawn didn't try to protect the prime minister.
Get in.
Golbarn's dogs!
Content to simply lick your master's hand
and receive his praise, are you?!
Just get in!
Such lowly acts are wasted
on a man of your conviction.
My dad, the man who built
those amazing artificial fairies,
was stripped of his pride and honor,
then hounded by the Security Bureau!
It's no different from being killed by Golbarn!
How can I forgive that?!
You don't have to forgive. But accept it.
The war is over.
Murderers are judged fairly.
Good era, isn't it?
You're saying Golbarn's a man, too?
Yeah. He's just a human being, like you.
That's why you don't kill him.
Deep in the forest
A quiet song is sung
Carrying fate upon its shoulders
A song of life
Said the lying crow
"Only calamity awaits beyond"
The fox asks, in hushed tones,
"Is there such a thing as happiness?"
Vanishing as quickly as it gathers
Drawn together, sounds weave into a melody
Heard across the world
Illuminating the path to tomorrow
As though not to melt the fluttering snowflakes
The ashen sky is gentle
As it wraps up and sings this song
Dorothea HQ
What a day!
Good work today.
Good job today, Robert.
Oh, yeah. You too.
See you tomorrow.
See ya.
And, good work.
Maybe this place has changed
a little since she joined.
Eh, Robert?
Yes, I suppose.
There are from ten to fifteen enemies!
See if you can stop me!
Fairy weapons are a fairy's natural enemies.
You want to die?!
Now, you don't have what it takes to fire me up.
Next Time
Rolling Stones and Seven Knights
The mediocre should learn from defeat.