Rondacia Palace
Heavenly Gate Plaza
It can't be...!
Damn it!
Two malfunctioning units?
Warlock Residence
Gilbert Warlock.
Bitter Sweet.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
How about we discuss this over a drink?
I no longer drink. You know that.
The Black Four that Dice won at the
auction is here with you now, isn't it?
And I previously got my hands on the Black Three,
and presented it to you.
You are capable.
One of the four Gui Carlin mafia bosses
Gilbert Warlock
Show me the Black Four.
I just want a look, that's all.
You're being modest, Sweetie.
Our guest is leaving. See her out.
You think I'll just give up like that?
I wake up, tired
So sick, bored, and fed up
I was never like this, I even had dreams, too
No one can stop me, bully me or suppress me
Can we ever break free of this miserable life we're living?
We'll never stop, we'll find our way, always, if we pray
I hear them coming for me now
Trying to lure me out
And all this time, I knew where it was
So I'm fired up and ready, looking for a good fight
So break it down and never give up
This is your only chance to change the world, so rise up!
It's your life!
Now is the time!
Fight for your life!
So don't cry out to stop! Not until you've won!
Break free of these chains
And give it all you've got!
Episode 07
Stubborn Blacksmith and Biased Rabbit
At this point, our only option is to
take custody of the faulty new models
and perform a thorough examination.
That is the opinion of the Ministry of Fairies.
The minister of fairies,
and the minister of the military...
Artificial fairies,
including the new model, are military assets!
Minister of the Military
Bruno Bohme
...and their respective vice-ministers.
But Military Minister Bohme,
Minister of Fairies
Joachim Sett
our Ministry of Fairies has a duty
to manage all matters regarding fairies.
I am speaking with Minister Sett!
Not with a mere vice-minister!
The vice-minister's statement is correct!
Minister Bohme, are you obstructing
our ministry from performing its duties?!
And we in turn have a duty
to protect the peace of Unified Zesskia!
I thought your shared duty was to find
ways for your ministries to cooperate...
The same is true for us.
How does one get to live in a house this huge?
Rich ancestors,
otherwise you can probably forget about it.
You won the Black Fairy Tome on behalf
of Gilbert Warlock at an auction in Escreque.
Dorothea HQ — Interrogation Room
We've already looked into it. Just 'fess up.
That guy's not going to talk
unless we torture him or something.
Aren't there any interrogation techniques
you learned at the Security Bureau, Chase?
How about we force our way into Warlock's place,
then confiscate the tome?
He's not just some rich guy.
He's also got connections in the unified government.
All we have is Axel's testimony.
And he's with the mafia.
So for now, we just walk up
to the door and ask for him?
If they turn us away, we're done.
And the matter of the new artificial
fairy model is a whole other mess.
Three days until the anniversary of the war's end
Hybranz Official Residence
The military minister is here as well.
Sorry to summon you here.
What can I do for you, Duke Hybranz?
I understand you're on good terms
with the Ministry of Fairies,
but can I get you to back the military this time?
Dorothea is neutral.
If you're neutral,
you can surely understand the harm in tolerating
the Ministry of Fairies' high-handedness.
Director Auler, the ones protecting
Unified Zesskia are our military...
and your Dorothea.
Wh-Why?!
I was thinking you could pay me back for a favor.
A favor?! You shot me, you know!
And you're still alive, no?
You're still here because I spared your life.
I'm with Arcame. What would a Gui Carlin
leopardess want me to do?
You've been talking.
Don't you have an in with Dorothea?
Why are we being dispatched to East End Base?
Apparently, the Ministry of Fairies' tech crew
has decided to enter the base
and examine the faulty new models.
And that's apparently our problem?
Is it political?
It seems the Ministry of Fairies was
telling them to hand over the new models.
So, it's like splitting the difference?
And we have to go monitor it?
We got our hands full as it is.
You're the least busy.
East End Base — Hangar
The new Zern I artificial fairy was first
developed as a symbol of unification.
Look at the state it's in now.
I don't suppose the guys in the Ministry
of Fairies can bear to just wait and see.
And they probably won't agree
to use the old model instead.
The Psyden VII is still in active service,
including the frames.
Those things shed too much blood in the war.
They've already done plenty of work.
Hi.
Things are unsettled here.
Look who's here.
Hanns.
I appreciate this.
I see the military arrived first.
Artificial fairies are now managed
by the Ministry of Fairies,
but ever since the war,
that hasn't sat well with some on this side.
The Zerns in question are over there.
This feels touch-and-go.
Oops.
Unified Zesskia Prime Minister's Official Residence
There, perfect.
Come in.
Your Excellency.
Nein Auler.
How goes the new model case?
The Ministry of Fairies has dispatched technicians,
and they're starting to examine
the units that malfunctioned.
Nobody's reached a conclusion yet?
If I may offer my opinion,
it might be best to exclude the new models
from the commemoration ceremony.
About Gilbert Warlock.
He's a Ledradian, but he was wise to abandon
his gutless king and invest in us.
Director Auler.
Do all you can to put
His Imperial Majesty's mind at ease.
Yes, Excellency.
Excuse me. A former colleague of mine.
Former colleague, huh?
It looks clean enough to me.
It's a new frame.
The operator orientation
has already been canceled?
Yes. Do you wish to synchronize with it?
Let's try it.
To first activate an artificial fairy,
the operator has to do that to sync
with it and set its orientation.
Once orientation is complete,
nobody but the synced operator
can operate it until it's been canceled.
Artificial fairies ain't machines,
but they can go haywire.
Three of them, though?
Do you have a hard time believing it's a coincidence?
It ain't us mechanics who'll make that call.
It's the Ministry of Fairies, right?
The Security Bureau suspects it was an inside job?
Seems like someone must have made it happen.
If anyone could tamper with a new model,
they'd have military connections.
Security Bureau member
Daniel Keys
It hurts to suspect those close to you.
Close to you? The military?
How unlike you, Robert.
That's true.
Doing work I'm not used to wears me out.
We're practically just watching.
I'd rather be moving around...
It's him!
H-Hey!
Was I seeing things?
What got into you?
Oh, nothing.
If Wolfran is wandering around, then Arcame—
Hey, man!
Wh-What?
It's you, Axel?
Oh, yeah. You're more or less in Arcame!
Wh-What gives, man?! That hurts!
I told you before to look into Wolfran Row.
I just spotted him. What's he doing here?!
Hey, I have no idea!
Another thing...
Is Arcame planning to do something
on the anniversary of the war's end?
Do something? Not as far as I know.
At least, not that I've heard.
I'll pay a lot for this info.
I'll do what I can.
What are you doing here?
Looking for you, of course.
Truth is, there's someone
who really wants to see you.
But I'm sorry to say, it's not Wolfran Row.
Someone wants to see you?
Okay, man, keep it civil.
Hi, Free. And you too, young lady.
Sweetie...
It's been ten short years since the war ended.
You two are the only ones left I can call friends.
I didn't start a war and then win it.
I merely happened upon
an opportunity for unification,
went with the tide, and carried it out.
I am not the victor.
The victors are all those
who won the battles, survived,
and now sing the praises of peace.
Let us share this victory with all
at the coming commemoration ceremony.
Surely, peace is what we always sought.
Even if there are trivial issues we should overcome.
To peace.
Don't worry, you're doing a good job.
Tell me if anything else happens.
Bitter Sweet got in contact with you?
Yes, ma'am.
She approached us about working together.
Not that she seems trustworthy.
We'll get to meet with Gilbert Warlock.
If we believe what she says, that is.
If what she says is true...
Warlock is a chief member of Gui Carlin.
In fact, he's one of the four top execs
they call Eyes, Ears, Mouth, and Nose.
Gui Carlin's Ears, eh?
A very wealthy man who's acquainted
even with the prime minister.
We have to try to make some breakthrough.
Wolfran is involved with the illicit manufacture
and trade of artificial fairies, for Arcame.
He's here in Rondacia?
Do you think there's a connection?
Only someone on the inside
can mess with the new models.
If someone on the outside is pulling the strings...
Lovely, don't you think?
Really?
It looks great on you, don't worry.
You're plenty cute yourself, Klara.
S-Somehow, I doubt that.
Wow! You're insanely cute, Klara!
I'm getting goosebumps.
But there's nothing to be shy about.
I'm making it very clear that I'm uncomfortable.
I'm not good with this kind of thing.
I'll bet.
Watch it!
What?
Don't be so tense, ladies.
I'm not.
What do you expect?
I can do whatever it takes,
in exchange for what's most important.
If you obtain the Black Fairy Tome,
you'll hand it over to Dorothea.
But before that, you want to look it over.
Those are your terms, yes?
Yes.
Even though it'll mean betraying Gui Carlin.
Hardly a betrayal.
I was just using them in the first place.
And you're using us, too.
Shall we go, ladies?
As you wish.
Arcame...
Chief mechanic.
You've been around for a while.
Do you remember a man named Eddy Lloyd?
Oh right, Hanns Efmed. I spoke with you
back when I was with the Security Bureau.
It was seven or eight years ago
when Eddy quit and went into hiding.
I don't know anything beyond that.
You were with the Security Bureau?
Yeah, now that you mention it...
I transferred.
I never was able to find Eddy.
Will we really get to see him?
All we can do is wait.
Right now, we're like birds in a cage.
Personal Record for Eddy Lloyd
Eddy Lloyd. The designer of the
old Psyden VII artificial fairy?
The prime minister even personally
awarded him for his devotion to unification.
After the war, he was put in charge of the Unified
Zesskia military's artificial fairy maintenance division.
But this was actually a demotion,
and Eddy didn't seem pleased with it.
He repeatedly requested reassignment,
but was denied,
and seven years ago, he resigned voluntarily.
After that, he fell off the map.
There were rumors that he joined up with Arcame
and got involved with illegal
artificial fairy development.
And ultimately, he was never found...
Correct. I once saw firsthand the dead body
of a man that bore his resemblance.
But it was someone else.
You think he's alive,
and involved with this current case?
I don't know.
However, the Security Bureau
may have kept pursuing Eddy after I left.
All right. Share our information with the bureau,
and continue the investigation.
Yes, ma'am.
At last.
Gilbert Warlock.
Bitter Sweet.
Even if you bring gorgeous young ladies along,
my answer is unchanged.
Really? Aren't they to your liking?
The younger ones in particular.
I'm a little scared...
Listen, Gilbert.
I'm not asking you to give me
the Black Four that Dice won for you.
I just want to see it.
One perusal is all you'd need
to comprehend and memorize it.
You have an unusually good memory,
and you're phenomenal at getting things done.
I value you highly.
I've performed well enough to have earned it.
I gave the Black Three to you personally.
It's only natural that you
work to serve our interests.
True.
However...
What's the harm?
You do still have the Black Four, don't you?
Or has someone stolen it?
There is not a soul in this world
who can take my property.
He admitted to our faces that he has it.
That'll serve as proof.
Pie
&
Mash
Eddy Lloyd, you said?
It seems Arcame is up to something.
Still, I doubt he's alive.
There must still be those in the
military who were close to Eddy.
You mean like...
Hanns Efmed?
Looks like there's nothing abnormal after all, Chief.
Yeah...
I'm not expecting you to show it to me for nothing.
I have a gift for you.
Is that so? You don't appear to be carrying one.
My. Hearing's still going strong,
but perhaps the eyes aren't holding up?
Inconceivable, for the one they call Gui Carlin's Ears.
The gift is these two, as a matter of fact.
They're both with Dorothea.
Deep in the forest
A quiet song is sung
Carrying fate upon its shoulders
A song of life
Said the lying crow
"Only calamity awaits beyond"
The fox asks, in hushed tones,
"Is there such a thing as happiness?"
Vanishing as quickly as it gathers
Drawn together, sounds weave into a melody
Heard across the world
Illuminating the path to tomorrow
As though not to melt the fluttering snowflakes
The ashen sky is gentle
As it wraps up and sings this song
This is Mitt End, Sweetie.
See those ruins in the distance?
Long ago, there was a country there called Tupal.
It was the center of the world.
Then why is it like this?
That's right, Chase is...
Zesskia! Zesskia! Zesskia! Zesskia!
The ceremony is tomorrow.
We can't postpone it.
They'll force the new model off of center stage!
Chase?!
Drop your weapons!
Next Time
Pipe Blowing in Stage Wing
You guys are on.