Director.
Beevee Liscar...
How much blood must he shed
before he's satisfied?
I'm sorry.
I...
I'm responsible for all of this.
No, you're not.
It's my fault.
All mine...
Is it anyone's fault?
These things can't be undone.
Be it those we let die, or the mistakes we make.
That's right.
Of all things, a Fairy Weapon—Fratanil was stolen!
This is Dorothea's first ever massive failure!
But we have to move forward.
Even if we're covered in blood and filth,
we can't just stand still.
Rather, we should consider ourselves lucky
if we were the ones bleeding.
We will perform our duty!
Episode 10
Cursed Child
The Ministry of Fairies will
assume custody of the body.
Why?
We have fairy organs inside our bodies.
Strictly speaking, they're illegal.
We're only pardoned because we're from Dorothea.
Didn't I explain this to you before?
You might have.
Maybe I wasn't really listening,
despite it being so important.
Since I didn't think something
like this would ever happen.
Ozz Mare...
This is all my fault.
Because I'm a cursed child.
Yes?
It's me.
Um, it's Klara.
May I come in?
Door's open.
Please don't be too hard on yourself.
We perform a difficult duty in order to
maintain unification and peace.
That's why we're all determined.
That's not it.
It's nothing like that.
Everyone just ends up dead.
All of them, all because of me.
That's not true...
So the key does lie in fairy-possessed
fairy organs and organ fusion...
That combination?
If only we had The Black Six.
Minister.
Mhm.
I still haven't been officially appointed.
At times like this, we must observe protocol.
As you say, Vice-Minister.
Has the retrieval been completed?
Yes, without delay.
What do you think of The Black Four?
It's quite interesting.
And that's all the more reason to keep it out of
the hands of criminal syndicates like Gui Carlin.
They likely cannot comprehend its value.
Mhm.
No, it isn't easy for us, either.
Tupal, the kingdom that once flourished in Midend...
These are the fruits of its wisdom, after all.
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
PainsealeR
DangeR
Don't Open
Good morning.
Um, are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Well...
We've got to do the Kal-o inspection.
Chase, stay here and assist the director.
We'll perform our duty.
Kal-o...
During the war, my hometown of Suna
was burned to the ground by Ray Dawn.
With no place to go, I fled north.
At first I was with other people who had
evacuated from all over, but I grew afraid.
I'm a cursed child, after all.
I was still little, and some people were kind to me.
But if I was around them,
things were sure to go wrong.
I went into the forest on the outskirts of town.
Maybe I simply wanted to die.
But...
They taught me about life
And they taught me kindness
A hunter named Victor saved me.
But I'm still struggling to be honest
He taught me how to live on my own.
Two Years Later
I wish I could say...
Victor fell ill too, and ultimately...
I wish I could thank you
Each time you looked at me
Tubal, the City of Water.
This is where Ray Dawn, the Duke of Kal-o, is.
But I need to keep it in
Eight years ago, I heard about a girl
who tried to kill him, so I came to this city.
Or else I might end up hurting you
My second hometown,
where I lived until I was sixteen.
No, I can't go that way
And I just don't care what you've got to say
This city is beautiful.
I can't help but fall right back into
a good mood when I visit places like this.
We didn't come to sightsee.
The cold wind pushes me back to where I used to be
Sorry, sir.
Right, right.
It looks like it's time to say goodbye
Kal-o Official Residence
So let me wish you happiness
Thank you for coming, members of Dorothea.
Duke Kal-o.
Ray Dawn...
Since I settled here as the Duke of Kal-o,
I haven't laid a hand on the Fairy Weapon once.
I am still required to examine it.
Our mission this time is to confirm that
the Fairy Weapon and artificial fairies
owned by Duke Kal-o are
within their stipulated parameters.
You seem to harbor some ill will towards me.
Why do you think so?
I'm used to being looked at in that fashion.
There are more than a few who call me a traitor.
Ten years since unification...
This tastes about as good as you'd expect.
Uh, I...
There's somewhere I want to go.
Someone I want to see.
Here?
I guess that's a no, huh?
We are on assignment.
We've got an extra day on the inspection schedule.
If nothing comes up, that's free time.
Can I do it then?
Sure.
May I go with you?
I'm sorry. I'll be fine on my own.
Oh, okay. Well, I just...
Don't worry about it.
This is good, though.
Why? Why am I always the one who survives?
Jingle Residence
Don! Don Jingle!
What's wrong, Diki?
It's Marlya.
Head of the Biaklay mafia group
Jingle
What did you say?!
Oh! Marlya!
It really is you!
Mr. Jingle.
H-Hey!
"Mr. Jingle" sounds so formal!
Just call me Grandpa, like you used to.
No, I couldn't do that...
It's been so long, though!
I'm glad to see you've finally come home.
It has been a long time.
I'm glad to see you in good health.
Aw man! This is where
that Biaklay boss lives, isn't it?
Biaklay, Gui Carlin, and Arcame.
The three big mafia groups.
But while Biaklay might be a mafia,
"We don't break the law" is sort of their motto.
I wonder how she knows him.
No idea.
Would you like to order something extra?
No, I'm good.
I see. I did hear through the grapevine
that you had joined Dorothea.
I'm sorry. A lot's happened,
and I couldn't get in touch.
Did you manage to see Veronica?
Although she told me not to look for her anymore...
Still, you were my bodyguard,
and now you work for Unified Zesskia.
But I've never once protected you.
That's not how I see it.
I was by no means qualified, but you
gave me that bodyguard job anyway.
It was just a favor.
Dorothea HQ
So Wolfran Row was Ted's
frequent point of contact after all.
Arcame isn't usually that direct.
According to Ted, Arcame provided
the new model's interrupt devices,
and even the old model's plans.
To what end?
Arcame was attempting to transport a
large number of illicit artificial fairies somewhere.
It also bothers me that Beevee Liscar
made a move at that time.
You think there might be a connection?
He's a man who gets excited
when he catches a whiff of war.
And in that case...
Could the gang that stole Fratanil
be headed toward Rondacia?
I'd better report in.
If the curtain doesn't rise,
won't that spoil the play?
This is what you get
when you try to stop the colonel.
No matter who you are.
So you did show up in the end.
What do you mean, "in the end"?
I figured you'd be drinking alone, sir.
That was the plan.
So the mafia connections
she had were with Jingle, huh?
They say Biaklay employs thousands,
such as craftsmen and porters.
Their assets and influence
are on par with royalty and nobility.
Is Marlya still in there?
With no signs of leaving.
And for quite a while, at that.
Right.
I wonder if Marlya will come back.
Huh?!
Hey, sir?!
Something big must have happened.
I just wanted to say hello,
since I happened to be in Tubal.
Marlya.
Won't you come back?
You seem to think you bring
misfortune upon those around you,
but nothing happened in
the three years you were by my side.
But, that's...
People sometimes call us the mafia.
But I think of us as an unrelated family.
Don't you need that?
Who the hell're you? It's a little late
to be dropping by somebody's house.
Pardon me.
Why?
I'm sorry for barging in at this hour.
Mhm.
Free Underbar, was it?
What brings you here?
Ah, well... I thought we'd come say hello.
That's the same thing I said.
Hello, eh?
To me, from Dorothea?
Yes, sir. I'm the one who
convinced Marlya to join Dorothea.
You did?
That's why I have a responsibility.
Oh, a responsibility?
Yes.
Which means...
you're determined?!
Whoa...
Determined...
Responsibility without the weight of determination
blows away easily when a storm arrives!
Believe it or not, but I've seen through
a lot of people with these eyes.
And you don't exactly
appear to have nerves of steel.
S-Stop it, Mr. Jingle. Free is...
Marlya. You're like a daughter to me.
No, at my age, a granddaughter.
And not just you.
All those in Biaklay are my siblings,
children, and grandchildren.
What fool would entrust his
own precious family to some coward?
Entrust?
I'm not really...
I have...
...determination.
I may be a coward, but when the need arises,
I have it in me to risk my life for her.
I don't want you to do such a thing.
We're not a family. We are, however,
comrades who watch each other's backs.
I would put my life on the line for
a comrade. No question about it.
I just...
I don't want people to die because of me!
Danger comes with our job, no matter what.
But even if something happens, nobody is to blame.
We risk our lives for each other's sake.
It seems like you're down
That is what makes us comrades.
Lost in the dark, unable to look around
He's right, y'know? I'd go that far as well
if it were for you or Klara.
Crushed by the loneliness
We should do whatever we can
to avoid these situations,
Drowning in fear
but I wouldn't hesitate either.
I...
But please, just know
can't do it.
When it boils down to it, I would always
be the one getting protected.
You'll never be alone
Marlya.
Don't run away!
I'll be right here for you
Didn't you join Dorothea to accomplish your goal?
All you've got to do is decide
Decide if you want to take that step forward
We're all right. So don't run away.
Remember, there's no need to worry
You don't have to run off for our sakes.
All you've gotta do is remind yourself
That it never hurts to smile
If you think you can walk no further
Remember that I'm right by your side
Marlya can use a fairy now,
or something along those lines.
Although how that came to be is unclear.
You can't simply quit Dorothea, even if you try.
There is a way to go about it.
Well, her wishes are what's most important.
That wildcat of a girl made herself
some splendid comrades.
Do you trust them with her?
Diki, what are your thoughts?
He doesn't seem like a cowardly guy.
Yeah. I hope a man like him isn't in any hurry to die.
Deep in the forest
A quiet song is sung
Carrying fate upon its shoulders
A song of life
Said the lying crow
"Only calamity awaits beyond"
The fox asks, in hushed tones,
"Is there such a thing as happiness?"
Vanishing as quickly as it gathers
Drawn together, sounds weave into a melody
Heard across the world
Illuminating the path to tomorrow
As though not to melt the fluttering snowflakes
The ashen sky is gentle
As it wraps up and sings this song
Ray Dawn!
I don't suppose he's come to see us off.
Duke Kal-o, can I help you?
There's something I must urgently
convey to His Excellency, the prime minister.
To the prime minister?
I want your group to deliver a personal letter.
Make sure His Excellency receives it.
Once he does, I expect appropriate measures will be taken.
A-Are they trying to start a war?!
Fights have suddenly broken out in the streets!
It's how mercenaries do things.
Liscar!
If you value your lives, surrender!
The West Gate is on fire!
Now, time to raise the curtain!
Next Time
Uninvited Music Corps