- The Fairy Village -
To cut a long story short, I think I'm cursed.
Fairy Soldier
Research Facility
Ultimately, I should consider myself blessed.
We'll remove the fairy organ from Red Hood here,
and transplant it inside you.
You volunteered, and were chosen based
on your suitability as a Fairy Soldier.
Glory to our kingdom of Ledrad,
and to His Majesty King Olbany.
The person who raised me ended up dying.
And my mother and father
both died the day I was born.
People called me "little disaster".
Everyone who gets involved
with me meets a bad end.
I was cursed.
Dipre, Ledrad
The War of Unification
Fire!
Atone...
for your crimes!
Free!
Jet!
This can't be happening...
Come on, open your eyes...
Jet!
Yeah, I'm blessed all right.
In the worst possible way.
I wake up, tired
So sick, bored, and fed up
I was never like this, I even had dreams, too
No one can stop me, bully me or suppress me
Can we ever break free of this miserable life we're living?
We'll never stop, we'll find our way, always, if we pray
I hear them coming for me now
Trying to lure me out
And all this time, I knew where it was
So I'm fired up and ready, looking for a good fight
So break it down and never give up
This is your only chance to change the world, so rise up!
It's your life!
Now is the time!
Fight for your life!
So don't cry out to stop! Not until you've won!
Break free of these chains
And give it all you've got!
Episode 02
Wolf Collar and Swan Feathers
Dorothea Quarters
Your year-long infiltration
of Gui Carlin ended in failure
due to a woman named
Veronica who wielded a fairy.
You returned with a young lady who
has ties to the aforementioned woman.
Is that an accurate summary, Free Underbar?
As accurate as summaries go, sure.
Marlya Noel.
In your report, you state that
she may be possessed by a fairy?
Nein Auler
Fairy regulatory agency Dorothea
Director & Commander of Unit 1
Free Underbar
Fairy regulatory agency Dorothea
Deputy Commander of Unit 1
I'm told there's no sign she underwent
a fairy organ transplant the way we did.
Director's Office, Dorothea HQ
A fairy primordial possessing a human directly...
Such a thing shouldn't be possible.
But that appears to be the only explanation.
I'm going to keep this matter to myself.
Redo the report.
Is there a problem? How bold of you.
No problems here.
Artificial Fairy Factory
Formerly Territory of Timoon
That's as many as I can bring here.
There aren't many customers
who place orders as big as this one.
If there were, we'd be in another war.
I could do without.
Making it through one was hard enough.
Profit's more my thing...
See you at the rendezvous point, then.
Yeah.
Is it all right if I open the window?
Go ahead.
Was finding Veronica the entire
reason you joined the mafia?
I guess.
For us in Dorothea, that woman's a target.
For regulation?
Stay in this line of work,
and I'm sure you'll meet again.
As enemies?
Veronica from Suna no longer exists.
At all.
How could I ever forget you,
Ver?
So bumpy...
My backside's killing me.
You say something?
No!
The Arcame mafia group deals
extensively in artificial fairies.
Apparently they even manufacture them.
And our mission is to expose
those illegal artificial fairies, right?
According to our intelligence,
a very large transaction is going to take place.
In addition to seizing the goods,
we also want to identify the buyer.
Artificial fairies are used
as substitutes for soldiers, right?
Yeah.
But the war's long over.
What use do they have for such things?
That just means it's anything but over.
Dipre ruins
Formerly Territory of Ledrad
Serge Tova
Fairy regulatory agency Dorothea
Unit 1
Sir! Marlya! Welcome to the party.
Has there been any movement?
Not yet.
Hello, Mr. Tova. And...
Quiet, please. It's distracting.
Klara Kysenaria
Fairy regulatory agency Dorothea
Unit 1
That's right, you gotta be quiet.
You won't like Klara when she's angry, no sir.
I can hear you, you know.
See what I mean? Ooh, scary.
Except you're laughing...
By the way, you can just call me Serge.
And Klara's okay with just Klara.
Looks like they're here.
One person got out.
Can you not see the cargo?
Few more coming in.
Three vehicles?
I'd say about ten or so artificial fairies
could fit in one of those.
In the plaza!
There's another person.
Red?!
This one's a Fairy Soldier!
What?!
We won't be able to get
a good look from this distance.
Are you okay?!
Yes.
He was looking this way.
More specifically, at my fairy.
Think we've been noticed?
We could always rush them and seize the goods.
That's a last resort. Just wait.
Something the matter?
No.
One of them's on the move.
It's the Fairy Soldier!
That one, huh?
Come. We'll shadow his movements.
Are you going? Should I come along?
We might be playing into their hands.
Serge and Klara,
you two continue monitoring the plaza.
Let's go, Marlya!
I see this place hasn't changed one bit.
We seem to be in some sort of ruins.
Have you been here before?
Yes, during the war. It was a long time ago.
Where the hell did they go?
These tracks are fresh.
Tracks?
H-Hey!
The tracks come to an end here.
Huh?
Someone was here!
Are they backtracking?
Doing what now?
Smart animals, such as bears, do it often.
They walk back over their own tracks.
Trying to confuse us, huh? It seems he
looped towards the direction we came from.
Serge!
Take cover!
That's...!
Wolfran Row
Member of the Arcame mafia group
Wolfran!
There's nothing I can do here!
Playing errand boy for the mafia?
How the mighty have fallen!
What happened, Wolfran?!
How's your lovely wife doing?
You had a daughter too, right?
I see you still haven't learned how to shut up.
What?
Marlya!
That fairy...
Don't forget I'm here, sir!
The weak rely on outnumbering their foe.
Damn it!
Is it protecting her?
He's not an enemy. It's all right.
What is this feeling?
Can you stand?
I think so.
Who was that?
A comrade of mine during the great war.
He's always been cunning and cold-hearted,
but I doubt he'll just run for it like that.
Sir!
Go after him!
Klara and I will give you long-range support!
Let's reposition.
You got it.
Are you good to go?
It's my job, right? I'm doing it.
Good.
Looks like the details got leaked.
Dorothea is on their way here.
What should we do? Call off the deal?
We fight back.
They have a sniper. Be careful.
They're meant for sale,
so only three of them are tuned up.
That's more than enough.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Good.
Three of them?
How come?
It took a lot of damage back there.
You can't just summon it again right away.
Oh, okay.
Give me covering fire.
These things aren't people. Don't hesitate to shoot!
I can hit it, but where should I be aiming?
Show yourself, Wolfran!
Range, 620.
Okay!
Boom!
That guy seems really laid-back, but he's incredible!
Get out of the way!
G-Good idea!
What's the matter?
You scumbag!
How ironic.
Here, of all places, facing off against you.
You can't keep up with me.
You survived, huh?
Why?
I used to be a soldier too.
Even if they caught me, I wouldn't talk.
You've got to believe me.
That's what they all say.
Sorry.
You won't get away!
Marlya, you link up with Serge and Klara!
Free!
I can catch up to a slowpoke transport!
Wolfran!
Damn it!
Hey! You!
Who did this to you?
Who do you think did it...
Damn it!
That son of a bitch.
Leave no tracks, huh?
Damn bastard's still as thorough as ever.
He hasn't changed one bit.
So that's how it's gonna be, huh?
Deep in the forest
A quiet song is sung
Carrying fate upon its shoulders
A song of life
Said the lying crow
"Only calamity awaits beyond"
The fox asks, in hushed tones,
"Is there such a thing as happiness?"
Vanishing as quickly as it gathers
Drawn together, sounds weave into a melody
Heard across the world
Illuminating the path to tomorrow
As though not to melt the fluttering snowflakes
The ashen sky is gentle
As it wraps up and sings this song
The place is big enough
to manufacture artificial fairies.
The Black Fairy Tome is a matter of grave concern.
It's ugly. Truly repulsive.
Don't move!
Next Time
Greedy Fox and Lying Crow
You can call me Bitter, young lady.