Ledrad
Military Entrance Ceremony
In U.E. 481, The War of Unification began,
a fierce conflict that would drag on for 14 years.
During that time,
both nations produced Fairy Soldiers.
Over 300 of them, in total.
- A Cave -
Fairy imaginals were hunted down...
...again... and again...
...until they were all but extinct.
We turned fairies into instruments of murder...
...and fought...
...again...
...and again...
...and again.
The number of Fairy Soldiers who survived the war,
as confirmed by Unified Zesskia:
Seventeen.
Final days of the Great War
Ledrad
Like fools, we mindlessly killed each other,
and slaughtered innocents.
Wolfran, is that you?
Wolfran! You're safe!
Thank goodness.
The fighting was fierce around these parts.
You don't mean m-my daughter and wife are...?!
I'm so sorry.
Why...?
Was all of this
my punishment?
Ruins of the Connor Church graveyard
Underground — Illegal Artificial Fairy Factory
Beevee Liscar
Agent of war and mercenary band leader
Beevee Liscar...
Colonel.
Such an eyesore. Repulsive.
The artificial fairy...
Its very existence is the height of folly.
It is the tool of our trade.
Wolfran Row, are you a merchant?
A warrior?
Or merely a pebble?
Colonel, it's time.
I'm none of those.
Artificial Fairy Factory
Formerly Territory of Timoon
There's nothing here!
Nothing here either!
This place is big enough
to manufacture artificial fairies.
They must have cleared out already.
Looks like we came up empty.
Not one to dilly-dally are you, Wolfran?
I wake up, tired
So sick, bored, and fed up
I was never like this, I even had dreams, too
No one can stop me, bully me or suppress me
Can we ever break free of this miserable life we're living?
We'll never stop, we'll find our way, always, if we pray
I hear them coming for me now
Trying to lure me out
And all this time, I knew where it was
So I'm fired up and ready, looking for a good fight
So break it down and never give up
This is your only chance to change the world, so rise up!
It's your life!
Now is the time!
Fight for your life!
So don't cry out to stop! Not until you've won!
Break free of these chains
And give it all you've got!
Episode 03
Greedy Fox and Lying Crow
Rondacia
Axel Laboo
Arcame mafia group member and informant
Axel!
In a hurry, are we?
Hey, that info I shared was legit, wasn't it?
About the transaction and the factory.
Sure was.
I bet right now, Arcame is searching
frantically for whoever spilled the beans.
I-I'll play it cool, don't worry.
You know a guy named Wolfran?
I've heard the name, I guess.
Look into it. You'll be compensated for your time.
I've got Arcame work to do!
That's gotta take priority!
Get going.
Man, talk about a slave-driver.
Unified Zesskia Ministry of Fairies
This time we're acting under the
direction of the Ministry of Fairies?
By order of Director Nein.
It's more of a request than a command,
but Dorothea and the Ministry often work together.
Huh.
Vice-Minister Marco Bellwood
is waiting for you inside.
Thank you.
Come in.
The people from Dorothea are here.
Vice-Minister, you wanted to talk?
Marco Bellwood
Ministry of Fairies
Vice-Minister
Please, have a seat.
Oh! Now there's a rare sight.
A Czeschka maticarna!
Ch-Chess car...?
It's the scientific name of that creature.
What a mouthful.
I think we'll shorten that to "Chima".
By the way, I think you know
why I asked you to come today.
I'm guessing the Black Fairy Tome has been found?
Correct. There was a report
from a certain fairy scholar.
The Black Fairy Tome...
Could it be that there are
fairy tomes of other colors?
Absolutely.
When the term Fairy Tome by itself is used,
it refers to the Certified Text published by Alan Bach.
First to be written was the Original Text,
by Hel S. Bellwood, the first fairy scholar.
Hel S. Bellwood
Fairy Scholar, Author of the Original Text
Jay B. Mercer
Fairy Scholar, Author of the Blue Fairy Tome
Next came Jay B. Mercer's Blue Fairy Tome.
Timothy Connor
Fairy Scholar, Author of the Red Fairy Tome
Timothy Connor's Red Fairy Tome.
Colen Thor's White Fairy Tome.
Colen Thor
Fairy Scholar, Author of the White Fairy Tome
And finally, Crucia Albastora's Black Fairy Tome.
Crucia Albastora
Fairy Scholar, Author of the Black Fairy Tome
It was Alan Bach who compiled
them 200 or so years ago.
Wait, did you say "Bellwood"?
I'm a descendant of Hel S. Bellwood.
Oh wow, I had no idea.
So he wrote the Original Text?
Then there's Blue, Red, White, and Black.
And all of those together make up the Fairy Tome?
Yes. However, the contents of the Black Fairy
Tome are not contained within that Fairy Tome.
It's listed in the table of contents.
But those pages are missing.
Precisely. Based on the table of contents
and the pages that have been gathered,
we know it talks about a phenomenon
called "fairy possession".
But in any case, the Ministry of Fairies is engaged
in the management of fairy-related
knowledge and technology.
For us, the Black Fairy Tome
is a matter of grave concern.
The Black... Fairy Tome...
So, where are we supposed to go?
I want you to visit Cain Distarol,
a fairy scholar in Isharat, the City of Towers.
Naturally, it would be best if you
could keep this matter confidential.
Timoon, huh?
Isharat
Formerly Territory of Timoon
"Sweetie" Bitter Sweet
Gui Carlin mafia group associate member
Businesswoman
Wh-What?!
What are you doing?!
Sweetie. What the hell is she doing here?
You know her?
Is she... your sweetheart?
Wha—?! Hell no!
My.
Free!
Why is the Dorothea guy here, of all people?
And her! It's Bitter Sweet.
She's that Gui Carlin leopardess! Damn it!
What the hell are you doing here?!
I could ask the same of you.
I heard from the organization that
you messed up and went into hiding.
Um, who are you?
I didn't know you were into children, Free.
Like hell I am!
Ch-Children?
L-Listen, this woman here,
she works with the bloody mafia,
but acts like she's not really with them.
Mafia?!
I'm an entrepreneur, thank you very much.
And an adventurer to boot.
You can call me Bitter, young lady.
You gotta be kiddin' me!
This was supposed to be a simple job—
just steal the Black Fairy Tome
from some senile old fairy scholar!
Errand boys have got it rough.
Maybe I should just quit Arcame.
But if I don't do the job, they might snuff me out...
Ain't got no choice, do I?
Whoa, wait!
What's this? No need to rush things.
All you need to do is ask.
Get off me! And let go!
Oh, don't be like that!
What is the meaning of all this ruckus?
Uh, well...
Hello.
Cain, I've brought guests.
Why, if it isn't Bitter Sweet! Long time no see.
Cain Distarol
Fairy Scholar
Sorry to receive you like this.
I don't mind at all, Doctor.
How is your health?
Not too bad, considering my age.
How about yourself?
I haven't seen you two in a while, either.
Yes, it's been some time.
Yes... Uh, hello.
My, look what time it is already.
The men of Timoon have long used this
evening bell as a signal to start drinking.
Damien Carme
Fairy Scholar
Just the men?
Climbin' up this way's just a tad dangerous, eh?
Nice wine. A 499 Rabica.
You can tell?
My family's dealt in wine since my father's time.
So you've known Cain for quite
a long time, then, Damien?
He's known me since I was a baby.
And about us?
The Black Fairy Tome is in
the room where I'm staying.
By the way, Doctor.
I heard you recently got your hands on a rarity.
What keen ears you have.
I'd expect nothing less from Bitter Sweet.
Very well. As a favor, I will show you.
Damien.
Right away.
This one is small, but fairy imaginals
that resemble people are highly valuable.
I see. Because fairy primordials
don't directly possess humans?
That thing's illegal, though.
You could get arrested because of it.
Naturally, I intend to report it
to the proper authorities.
Unified Zesskia isn't so
oppressive that it would obstruct
the research of some no-name fairy scholar.
"No-name"? That's rather modest of you, Doctor.
But what I happened to hear about was—
That's so cute!
What?
A fairy?!
I know this trick!
A thief?!
Thief?
What are you...?
It's safe.
What?!
Stop!
What's with this thing?!
We've been had.
The Black Fairy Tome's been...!
I see him! There!
Good eye.
Hey, you!
I can pull it off when I try!
Bitter Sweet!
Shit!
Pillywiggin! Don't do it!
My, what an adorable fairy!
That useless little...
Don't be going off and doing your own thing!
Sweetie's after the same thing we are.
Some god damn secret this was supposed to be!
Over there!
Axel?!
Get outta my way!
Curse that woman!
Move! Move! Move! Move!
Wh-What?!
God damn it!
Where the hell did they go?
I don't dislike a determined man, but...
Over there!
Damn it all!
The security force, huh?
Marlya, you keep up the pursuit.
Yes, sir!
What's all the commotion?!
Special operations underway.
Free Underbar
Dorothea?!
I've never seen one in person before...
We're pursuing a target. Please assist.
Yes, sir!
Sorry!
You want it that badly, huh?!
Halt!
Look at the uproar the lure produced.
Cain even assisted in setting it up.
It makes me think people are incorrigible.
You won't have to do a thing, Veronica.
I know.
That girl...
She might be fairy-possessed.
Say what?
Marlya. Why is she...?
The Black Fairy Tome. Fairy possession.
Arcame. Gui Carlin. Dorothea.
People really are...
Guess I can pull it off when I try.
Pull what off, now?
I like a determined man,
but not when they don't know when to quit.
You haven't even broken a sweat!
What the hell are you, a monster?!
If you don't value your life...
I-I value it very much!
If you're dead, you've got nothing!
Then I think you know, I want that.
Yes, I know.
But...
Hey there!
You two.
Sure took your sweet time.
Where's the little lady?
Beats me.
You were infiltrating Gui Carlin.
I don't know what you're talking about.
As a man who fought to the end
as a Fairy Soldier for Ledrad,
how does it feel to join Dorothea
and kiss the ass of Unified Zesskia?
Vulgar, aren't you?
Oh, my apologies.
But to shamelessly wear Unified Zesskia's
collar around your neck is a little pathetic.
The war ended a long time ago.
You're not about to tell me
it's just so you can get by?
That it's the only way you can live?
Don't make me laugh.
I don't require your understanding.
Didn't I tell you that I don't like men
who don't know when to quit?
You didn't have to shoot him.
Don't worry, he's still breathing.
S-Sorry about that.
Hey, I've got my job too. With all its risks.
So yeah...!
This is what you're after, right?
You'd shoot me, too?
Walk away and you keep your life.
Don't move!
I don't want to shoot anyone.
But this is my job, so I will.
The young lady is disciplined, I see. I don't like that.
A fairy?!
What?!
Sweetie, what the hell have you done?!
Deep in the forest
A quiet song is sung
Carrying fate upon its shoulders
A song of life
Said the lying crow
"Only calamity awaits beyond"
The fox asks, in hushed tones,
"Is there such a thing as happiness?"
Vanishing as quickly as it gathers
Drawn together, sounds weave into a melody
Heard across the world
Illuminating the path to tomorrow
As though not to melt the fluttering snowflakes
The ashen sky is gentle
As it wraps up and sings this song
You're...
So, what's the job?
If I break the law, I'll leave no evidence behind.
If it's a battle of endurance...!
I have a feeling you'll turn out
to be a lovely piece of work.
You bitch!
Next Time
Impatient Housekeeper and Selfish Artist
Lady...