Kusakabe-san.
It's not like we came to you on a whim.
Please give it some serious
thought before you decide.
Ru
Ha
Ka
Chi
BLOSSOM
into
the
scent
of
rain
until
I
was
breathless
Straight
ahead
chased
the
rainbow
in
the
distance
Will
I
ever
reach
Countless
colours
merge
together
to
become
harmony
suddenly
born
strange
song
with
building
a
bridge
of
echoes
to
far
away
could
make
our
own
rainbow
from
here,
where
we've
come
then
the
colours
in
it
would
be
ours,
ours
only
million
nameless
hues
tion
would
form
its
gradient
rainbow
Let's
not
fear
the
pain
and
push
open
the
door
bathe
in
the
light
of
youth
THE TRIANGLE OF RESONANCE
What do we do?
The competition is only one week away!
Bit late to be saying that, don't you think?
I have to practise more.
Hear me, every living being in this world!
Share your energy with me!
But you have more than you'll ever need.
Ask for musical ability instead.
You're asking for a kicking.
See you later, then.
We'll be awaiting your reply.
Reception Office
Principal's Office
You were still practising?
Yes.
Good work. Be careful on the way home.
We will!
Want me to return the key for you?
Thank you.
We'll be on our way, then.
Let's go, Chika-chan.
Good-bye!
Wait, where are we going?
Follow my lead.
Who knows?
Excuse me!
You're from the Hamamatsu Symphony, right?
Hamamatsu
Y-Yeah.
And you are?
We're huge fans of yours!
Right?
Uh, right!
Thank you.
We've been hoping to see our advisor,
Kusakabe-sensei, conduct such an orchestra.
What brought you here today?
That's exactly why, actually—
I'm afraid we can't talk about it just yet.
Not until it's officially decided.
Anyway, best of luck.
Hamamatsu
What was that all about?
They came here to recruit Kusakabe-sensei.
I saw the envelope he was holding
and the licence plate of the car
and decided to bluff.
Their reaction told the whole story.
They asked Sensei to be their conductor.
But Sensei...
He wouldn't abandon us and leave, right?
I'm not so sure.
If Sensei seriously wants to
go back to the music world,
this should be an opportunity like no other.
But aren't we all aiming to make it to Fumon Hall
in the Category A All-Japans next year?
That's my aim too, but...
Homura-san.
You're not focusing.
Oh, sorry.
Want to call it a day?
No, I'll keep going!
Serizawa-san...
How are we right now?
What do you mean?
How do we look in the eyes of a long-time
musician, like you or Kusakabe-sensei?
Can you handle the truth?
Yeah.
There may have been no
odds-on favourites this year,
but it's still a mystery how you
made it to the Tokai regionals.
Your performances are so unbalanced
that they wear the listener out.
That's not all, though.
Want to hear the rest?
I'll listen until I drop!
Despite all that, Kusakabe-sensei brings
your unbalanced performances together.
And you really know how to make
an impact from the get-go.
You're fearless thanks to
your time in volleyball.
The band lacks both depth and overall skill,
but it stays afloat because Maren, Narushima-san,
Kamijou-kun, and Kaiyuu are doing their best.
Instead of helping the listener relax,
your performances gently wear them out.
And making your audience
feel that way counts for a lot.
So hold your head high.
Okay.
Narushima-san!
Let's do our best!
What's with you?
Apparently Serizawa-san showered us with praise.
All right. Let's begin rehearsing.
Okay!
Okay...
Let's start from the top, then.
The baton broke!
Everything is fleeting.
If it has shape, it will one day break.
It could be a bad omen.
It isn't like you to say such
ominous things, Homura-senpai.
What's gotten into you?
You're usually so thick you wouldn't
notice a black cat crossing your path,
but now you're way too high-strung.
I'm sorry.
Oh, Sensei.
Shall I stick it back together with rice?
Rice?
What a crude method.
Sorry I'm crude.
It's all right. I can use my hands to conduct.
Anyway, let's begin rehearsal.
Come on, Chika-chan. People are going
to find out if you panic like that.
Sorry.
We need to focus on practice right now.
Yeah, you're right.
I want us to perform as well as we possibly can.
Kamijou-kun, Homura-san.
If you don't mind,
could you chip in 100 yen each?
Oink.
President...
Did you run out of pocket money for this month?
I did see you and Haruta
going halfsies on an Umaibo.
That was me graciously sharing with him.
That's not it.
We're gifting a new baton to Kusakabe-sensei.
To Sensei?
We were already thinking about giving him
something as a token of our gratitude.
And we think this'll make a great present.
Kurasawa
Instruments
That baton wouldn't suit Kusakabe-sensei.
But it looks so nice!
Forget about what you want!
Pick something Sensei would want to use!
What would you know about him?!
Pick one already. It's getting late.
I know I don't trust your awful taste!
I'm glad we found something nice.
I'll hand it to him!
No, I will!
As president, I will.
If you're going to fight about it, I will.
Why don't we let Kae- and Sae-senpai do it?
They're the ones who suggested it.
Me!
Kusakabe-sensei!
I mean, I spotted him.
It is him.
I thought he took the bus
to and from school every day.
Sensei!
Homura-san! You'll ruin the surprise!
Oh, right.
Be seeing you, then.
I need to see my family today.
Me too!
See you guys tomorrow!
They're going to see his family together?
Are those two dating?!
Who knows?
You're stealing another march on me?
I knew you'd never go see your
family of your own free will!
H-Hey!
What is this?
It's like we're tailing him.
Awfully perceptive today, aren't we?
Looks like he's changing trains.
He's probably headed to Hamamatsu.
Hamamatsu... Symphony?!
Hamamatsu
What are you planning?
If Sensei's planning to give the
Hamamatsu Symphony his answer,
then I'm going to tell him
how I feel before he does.
I'll say, "Please don't go.
Stay on as our instructor next year too."
Oh.
This isn't a bad offer for him.
Still, I believed that he'd
decide to stay with us in time.
I wanted to believe that he would.
But if I let him leave without
telling him how I feel,
I know I'll regret it forever.
But hey, we don't know for sure
that he's going to accept.
Yeah, but if he was going to refuse,
couldn't he have done it over the phone?
Right...
Coming up: Tanikawa.
He's getting off!
But we're not at Hamamatsu yet.
This is odd.
We bought tickets to Hamamatsu!
Love sure can lead people astray, huh, Chika-chan?
Dude.
I wonder where he's going.
Remember how he arrived late
for the district qualifiers?
Yeah.
On August 1st, the day of the qualifiers,
service on the Tokaido line was interrupted
for a while due to signal failure.
He might have come here that day too.
Maybe that's why he was late.
Then he's headed to the same
place he went to before?
Wasn't he in formal wear then?
He'd taken his jacket off, though.
Maybe he's here today to pick up something
he forgot at a wedding he attended that day?
You remember that whole thing about how Sensei
walked out on the Berliner Symphoniker and disappeared?
Yeah.
That was on an August 1st too.
BLOSSOM
Taking the same bus would be pushing it, surely.
Do you have money on you?
Follow that bus!
As far as you can take us
for 1,000 yen, please.
We'll lose him!
But what about our tickets home?
Youth is a one-way trip.
What.
Tanikawa Cemetery
Haruta...
Are you seriously doing this?
Yeah.
I'll go and tell him how I feel.
Do you have to put it like that every time?
It makes me nervous.
Chika-chan?!
Damn, you're heavy!
Deceased August 1st
We're sorry!
No need to apologise.
But why did you come
all the way here?
We thought you were going to Hamamatsu
to accept the offer to conduct their symphony.
Deceased August 1st
How did you know about that?
Well, Haruta realised that those people
were from Hamamatsu Symphony...
August 1st
The Day of the Qualifiers
The Day Sensei Disappeared
Someone's Death Anniversary?
Isn't that right, Haruta?
Yeah...
Whenever I'm in doubt,
I find myself coming here...
and wondering what they would say.
They?
Sensei.
There's no need to hesitate.
Accept the offer to be conductor.
Remember what you said before?
That getting to Fumon Hall is important,
but our lives after that are much more important.
Shouldn't it be the same for you?
You don't have to worry about us.
We'll take gold this year and
go to Fumon Hall next year!
Right, Chika-chan?
Yeah. You can count on us.
I'm going to stay here for a while longer.
Okay.
Sensei!
Sensei...
To tell you the truth, we both...
have no money to pay for
the train tickets home!
Tanikawa
Why didn't you try to stop him?
I saw the date on the grave he was visiting.
It was August 1st.
The day he was supposed to
conduct the Berliner Symphoniker,
someone dear to him died.
So that's why he couldn't go to the venue?
There's no way to tell what happened.
But right now, he's of two minds
whether to take a step forwards or not.
Will the Tokai regionals be the
last time we perform with him?
Let's put on a great performance, Haruta.
Let's put on a great performance, Chika-chan.
We all chipped in to buy this for you.
Please use it, if you'd like.
Thank you.
I joined the concert band back in the
spring of my first year in high school.
This is the story of the six seasons
that have passed since then.
A story of miraculous chance encounters,
unravelled mysteries,
and the secrets that dwell in people's hearts.
Now for performance number nine.
Representing Shizuoka Prefecture,
it's Shimizu Minami High School
performing their free-choice piece,
"On a Clear Day".
Their conductor is Kusakabe Shinjirou.
Best of luck!
Oink!
Band
Piggybank
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
Fujigasaki High School
Congratulations Concert Band
for Reaching the Category B Tokai Regionals
Hello, Mum?
Listen, we won gold!
Certificate
Bronze
Shimizu Minami
High School
Tokai Concert Band
Bronze is a great result in its own right.
But if those of us with experience
had led from the front...
Maybe I could've played better
if I hadn't quit for a while.
Yeah...
Our concert band used to have
all of five members,
so I thought I'd be content
just making it this far.
But it's the end of the line for us!
I'm disappointed in myself too.
I got nervous on stage.
You all did your best!
Gotou-san,
Narushima-san, Maren,
and Kaiyuu...
We all put on the greatest performance
we could have right now!
Homura?
Where do you think we are?
Not the district or prefectural qualifiers,
but the Tokai regionals!
Isn't it amazing that we're depressed
at taking bronze at such a huge event?
Yeah.
You're right.
I'm counting on you for next year.
The band will be fine with her around.
Good work.
Sensei...
If possible, we wanted to
take gold as a gift for you.
We would never have made it
this far without you.
Thank you so very much.
You all performed well today.
It was the perfect culmination
of all your hard work.
I'm sure some of you aren't
satisfied with how you played.
But if you're willing to see today as part
of the process rather than its conclusion,
then I ask you to work with me
again from tomorrow.
Yes, sir!
All right. Let's get on the bus.
Oh, I need to visit the bathroom.
Chika-chan.
What?
We pour in our blood, sweat, and tears,
believing the sky is the limit for us.
That's a privilege exclusive to youth.
So if we're upset, we're free to cry.
Besides, it's thanks to you that we gathered
so many members and got so far.
It was thanks to your solving all those mysteries.
All I did was unlock the mysteries themselves.
You're the one who unlocked
the hearts of everyone involved.
With your bundles of energy, guts,
shamelessness, and audacity—
Hey! If you're gonna praise me, do it right!
Here.
Jeez...
Quit moping about.
This isn't the end.
Serizawa-san.
You didn't leave with your aunt?
I decided to go home with you.
Why? Did you get into an argument?
I've made up my mind.
About what?
She's saying she'll join the concert band.
You're so thick.
Thank you!
Oh, come on.
We'll be together forever!
Forever's pushing it a bit.
We third-years will be retiring now.
We entrust all our dreams to you.
How nice...
Also, I spoke with Kusakabe-sensei
and decided on the next president.
The next president?
Could be you, Homura-senpai!
Me?!
I hereby appoint...
Maren!
Ma—
I look forward to continuing to work with you!