Back then, I didn't want to be
at school, home, or anywhere else.
I simply sat in a pitch-black place,
holding my knees.
A very good evening to
all those who have tuned in.
I'm your host, Kaiyu.
Tonight, we'll be saving more lost lambs
wandering around our city.
Yes, indeed. It's time for FM Hagoromo's
"The Seven Sages' Life Advice".
Vent your troubles at your aging elders.
That's all this program is about.
Now, our first caller tonight
is actually speaking to us live!
Good evening. Please introduce yourself.
What's in a name?
So you're a no-name, just like FM 77.4.
Please wait your turn, Sukekiyo-san!
How old are you, miss?
Fourteen.
You must be in the third year
of junior high, then?
I don't go to school all that much.
What kind of advice are you looking for tonight?
I want to die.
What a coincidence. I've been thinking
it's about time for me to go as well.
We've lived too long, haven't we?
No need to rush.
The reaper will come for us soon enough.
Don't lump me in with you! I seriously—
Times like these call for booze!
Someone bring Sadakichi-san some cloudy sake!
Cut it out. We're live on air!
We're more sober when drunk.
Once you reach drinking age,
you can drown yourself in alcohol.
And what if I still want to die?
That's what you call a hangover.
What the hell? Are you messing with me?
That's what life is all about.
If you've lost all hope in the world around you,
then why don't you try
seeing it in a different light?
The value of a jewel is determined
by the light shining upon it.
That goes for the world in your eyes, too.
The wedding ring I gave my late wife
had a small but dazzling jewel, too...
Ru
Ha
Ka
Chi
BLOSSOM
into
the
scent
of
rain
until
I
was
breathless
Straight
ahead
chased
the
rainbow
in
the
distance
Will
I
ever
reach
Countless
colours
merge
together
to
become
harmony
suddenly
born
strange
song
with
building
a
bridge
of
echoes
to
far
away
could
make
our
own
rainbow
from
here,
where
we've
come
then
the
colours
in
it
would
be
ours,
ours
only
million
nameless
hues
tion
would
form
its
gradient
rainbow
Let's
not
fear
the
pain
and
push
open
the
door
bathe
in
the
light
of
youth
FREQUENCY: 77.4MHZ
A new school year has begun.
With the addition of Gotou-san and other freshmen,
we now have twenty-three members.
Just as Serizawa-san advised,
we're aiming for gold in Category B.
And today, we have a joint practice
with the famous Fujigasaki High.
Witnessing the part practice and ensemble
rehearsal of a powerhouse would motivate us...
or so we thought.
Your tone is all over the place!
Pay attention to the directions!
I can't believe how much they get
yelled at despite being that good.
Well, yeah, we're nowhere close to
being as good and we're already stuck.
I kept hitting the wrong notes.
Maren and Narushima stuck out like a sore thumb.
Yeah.
Kamijou-kun tried to bridge the gap
between us and the rest, but...
Don't fret, my hard worker.
You've got nothing to be ashamed of.
Oh, right. I'm collecting happiness koalas
from Koala's March in a bottle.
I'll share them with you.
You were surprisingly calm
when it mattered, Homura.
Even when you make a mistake,
you manage to stay calm.
Well, Chika-chan's really
shameless, if nothing else.
Let's figure out what we have to do
and drill it into our very bones.
I'll practise more so that
I don't hold you two back.
I'll work twice as hard! Four times, if need be!
We'll need to practise after school
every weekday and start early every weekend.
Got it.
Okay!
About that...
I'm thinking of placing restrictions
on your practice hours.
Sure, the All-Japans are important,
and so is getting to Fumon Hall,
but your life after that is much more important.
If the second- and third-years don't score
at least the average on their midterms,
I'll cut practice time on Sundays
and after 6PM on weekdays.
Why did Kusakabe-sensei suddenly bring that up?
You three will be fine because
you're in the top 20 of our year, but I...
Are you going to have trouble
hitting the average mark?
A little bit, yeah...
I'll get mad if you don't make the cut, okay?
What?!
Fine. I'll do my best.
I'm gonna take this all the way!
Keep it down!
Studying!
My...
All the way!
All the way...
Well, I can't concentrate when it's too quiet.
Tonight, we'll be saving more lost lambs
wandering around our city.
Looks like it started on time tonight.
It's time for FM Hagoromo's
"The Seven Sages' Life Advice".
Here in the studio, our seven life specialists
are eagerly awaiting their turn.
Picture seven chihuahuas that finally found
someone to play with after a week of boredom.
They can be pretty annoying.
Heh, chihuahuas.
Let's get right to tonight's first client.
He works for a local IT company and
goes by the alias of Corporate Dog.
What is IT?
It stands for "information technology".
Stands for what?
Japanese, son. Do you speak it?
Fine! Just think of it as standing
for Incan Tawantinsuyu!
He threw in the towel.
The civilisation that fell to ruin
because it arrogantly believed
that knowledge was not to
be shared with commoners?
It's like that too.
He threw in the towel,
but they threw it back at him!
Anyway, moving on.
"I work overtime every day,
and even come to work on holidays,
so I've lost touch with my friends
and can't get a girlfriend.
Unable to live a normal human life, I worry about
my future prospects. What should I do?
Top 20 Or Bust
!!
Sadakichi-san, what's a normal human life, anyway?
Average
Marks
In All Subjects
Or Bust!
Average
Marks
In All Subjects
Or Bust!
Average
Marks
In All Subjects
Or Bust!
Average
Marks
In All Subjects
Or Bust!
Being able to get a good night's sleep.
In All Subjects
Or Bust!
That's it, really.
Okay, I'll try to do that too!
Next up, we have a caller speaking to us live!
My, it's been a while since we last had a caller.
Reminds you of the junior high girl who called
and said she wanted to die, doesn't it?
Alias: "Desert Rabbit".
Hello.
You sent in a postcard last time, right?
You're the one who fell in love with
the same person as a clubmate, yes?
If memory serves, the target of your
unrequited love was your club advisor.
That's right.
Wow, there's someone like me out there.
Your don't wanna hurt your rival
cause they're your BFF, right?
But I'd rather fillet them
than have my love stolen away.
Fillet?
Oh, I remember!
You said you were socially
at a disadvantage, correct?
What happened after that?
I'm here to confess tonight.
Actually, due to a scheme of mine,
my rival, who doesn't have the best grades,
was forced to neglect club and study.
I feel kinda bad.
Haruta?!
"Fillet"? You feel "kinda bad"?!
Sorry, Chika-chan.
What was that all about?
I spoke to Kusakabe-sensei alone the other day.
He was worried about our futures.
You know how he makes this
pained expression at times like that?
It made my heart race for some reason.
So I offered a little suggestion...
Your heart raced, did it?
More like you stole yet another march on me!
You owe me an apology.
I was actually studying seriously.
Seriously? Weren't you listening to the radio?
When did you start tuning in to that program?
Right after I joined high school.
Apparently, that local radio station
was originally established by the city.
A private party took over
and now runs it on a reduced scale.
Oh, so that's why it only plays the sound
of waves and whatnot during the day.
It seems that "The Seven Sages'
Life Advice" started two years ago.
The "sages" are seven senior citizens,
and they've never revealed where
the program is broadcast from.
The address they give out
for postcards is a P.O. Box, too.
For some reason, it feels like a hidden village
straight out of Japanese folklore to me.
A hidden village?
Freeze!
Without troubling or hurting anyone,
Kaiyu and the Seven Sages
live quietly in the radio program.
I get the feeling they should be left well alone.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Are you listening to me?
Y-Yeah...
Hey, Homura!
President Hinohara?
You saw it, didn't you?
I know you did, Homura!
Surely it's just one of the
biology club's chickens.
Oh, Kamijou?
Perfect.
Jeez.
You're interrupting our morning practice.
The concert band's budget
for this year has been decided.
This is brutal.
Unbelievable!
Can you blame us? You've achieved nothing.
Ow!
Don't be hasty!
I came to offer you a lifeboat.
I bet it's full of holes.
If you can solve a certain pending issue for me,
I'll add 200,000 yen to your budget.
200,000?!
One of the culture clubs has
declined its funding for this year.
They turned down 200,000 yen?!
Which club was that?
The geological research club.
If you can catch its president and
bring her to the student council office,
I'll negotiate for her to give you those funds.
I smell something fishy!
Speak.
Why'd the geological research
club decline their funding?
Why is its president on the run?
I'll give you the rest of the story after school,
so elect some representatives.
We offer you our lively young girl.
Why do I have to chase after
some helmet-wearing weirdo?
You know her, Senpai?
No way! No chance! Absolutely not!
Be a man and admit it.
But I'm a girl! And I'm busy!
"I'm busy" is the kind of excuse dumbass
old men with too much free time use.
Apologise to fathers all across the country!
Don't you want to buy
instruments for the newcomers?
We're counting on you, Homura-san!
Save the concert band!
All right, all right.
But he's coming with me.
I knew it.
Student Council Office
Her name is Asou Misato. She's in Class 2-5.
The geology club has eight members.
They show crazy unity under Asou, the president.
She's also one of the student council blacklist's top ten.
Another oddball, huh?
Very pretty.
She's narrowed down the club's objectives
to mining precious stones.
Can you even mine precious stones in Japan?
You can find quite a few kinds, actually.
But only in small quantities.
Trespassing on private properties
to mine is a crime, though.
So how are they achieving anything?
By using the geology department
at the prefectural university.
Prefectural University's Geology Club Discovers
Rainbow Garnet From Sculptures Made of Junk
They performed a thorough
survey of the city on foot.
Going by the timing of and channels used
in the distribution of granitic pegmatite,
they identified places likely
to have traces of rainbow garnet
and got the university moving.
Grammatical pragmatic...
Don't strain yourself.
Prefectural University's Geology Club Discovers
Rainbow Garnet From Sculptures Made of Junk
Apparently, they handed the rainbow garnet
they discovered over to the university.
Prefectural University's Geology Club Discovers
Rainbow Garnet From Sculptures Made of Junk
In return, the university agreed to cover
all of the geology club's operating costs.
Prefectural University's Geology Club Discovers
Rainbow Garnet From Sculptures Made of Junk
So that's why they declined the funding.
Well, they're the sort of people who'd rather
not use even a single yen of school money.
Why?
Because they hate school.
What?
They're a bunch of kids who'd never
come to school if it weren't for their club.
The geological research club
is a group of former shut-ins.
I see.
Asou created the GeoClub,
contacted shut-in students,
and successfully got them to come
to school using club activities.
How'd she pull off that miracle?
She barged into their homes
and straight up talked them into it.
The goddess of fate who would change
their lives descended upon them, huh?
I need you, no matter what.
Lend me your strength.
Apparently, a male student named Hiyama
was the only one who didn't agree.
Hiyama?
But why is that goddess on the run?
Asou and gang outdid themselves this year.
They found a mineral more valuable
than rainbow garnet.
Is she some kind of genius?
But after that, Asou sent the uni a blunt email
and hasn't contacted them since.
I found it,
but I'm pretending I didn't.
Over.
Asou Misato
Sub:
Over.
but I'm pretending I didn't.
I found it,
And what were they supposed to mine this year?
Topaz.
Natural blue topaz.
Also known as the jewel of the setting sun.
BLOSSOM
So you're having curry tonight?
I had a feeling it might be that.
Here you go. I'll bring you a spoon right away.
No need, Mrs. Homura.
I've brought my own, eco-friendly chopsticks.
I scoop the rice, but it slips from my grasp.
It's almost like Chika-chan's first love.
Isn't it hard to eat that way?
Did you just come to bum dinner off us?
Nah. I wanted to talk about Asou-san.
Why is she running around like that?
They found the place where the blue topaz rests.
But they don't want anyone to know where.
And why is that?
We'll have to catch her and ask.
Uh, Mrs. Homura,
I could use that spoon right about now.
Should we catch her?
See, I told you it'd be hard to eat!
The GeoClub is a refuge Asou-san built.
And she herself was truant
through most of junior high.
She must have a reason she can't talk about.
It's too late.
President Katagari apparently already
sent her a challenge via Hinohara-san.
Did she respond?
"Bring it. Over."
Bring it.
Over.
Asou!
Where are you?!
Asou Misato-san?
Are you here?
Jewels Alone Tell No Lies
Here it is.
Asou-san, you there?
Geological
Research Club
She's going to run!
Let's barge in!
Why do you have the key?
I borrowed it from the staff room!
DO NOT OPEN
Climb up, Yasu!
You're an imperial soldier fated
to die one step away from his goal!
Asou-san tunes in as well?
FM Hagoromo. Frequency 77.4.
Do you remember what Hinohara-san said about there
being a male student who Asou-san couldn't woo?
I got a little curious, so I looked him up.
His name is Hiyama Kaiyuu.
Kaiyuu?
Kaiyu?!
"I found it, but I'm pretending I didn't."
I thought about what that message meant.
And what does it mean?
If I'm right, then she ended up finding
the hidden village in this city too.
I was really surprised to find you'd become
acquainted with the geological research club.
You know about it?
Asou-san is pretty famous
among the teachers here.
We should end this game of tag as soon
as possible for Asou-san's sake too.
Sorry for calling you out like this.
It's okay.
These two are Kamijou-kun and
Homura-san from the concert band.
I hear you like jewels.
Crystals turn sunlight into
something more beautiful.
Sunlight?
Someone once taught me
that if you have a hard time in
the outside world or lose all hope,
you have to try seeing it in a different light.
Asou-san...
The blue topaz, radio, and Hiyama Kaiyuu
are all connected, aren't they?
While you were protecting
a colony within this school,
there was a boy the same age as you
desperately protecting a colony of his own.
Your pursuit of blue topaz
took you to where he was...
An unregistered retirement home.
Asou-san.
We're listeners who tune
into that radio station too.
You know, "The Seven Sages' Life Advice".
Haruta's asked them for advice several times.
I think his alias was, uh, Desert—
Chika-chan!
Quit running your mouth!
You don't need to carry that burden alone.
Like it matters!
It totally does!
Huh? Oh, right, ahaha...
Don't "ahaha" me!
You have zero tact!
Hey, it's a little more than that!
Not after you round it down, it isn't!
Want me to make a fillet out of you?
I swear I'll never target you
with my schemes again!
Haruta!
I said I'm sorry!
Suiren
Temple
Ward Gate
Fortune Gate
Yes?
I'm Kusakabe Shinjirou from
Shimizu Minami High. I called earlier.
Hiyama Kaiyuu-kun, yes?
Sorry.
And sorry I couldn't join you
even though you came so many times.
Are you guys my classmates?
Nah. We didn't get that opportunity.
Oh, right. I got held back.
This is kinda weird.
Hearing your voice in person.
We three have been listening to you for ages.
Radio host Kaiyu.
I've always wanted to meet you.
The people here all either
fell out with their families
or had nobody to talk to
because they lived alone.
At some point, we started looking
after those people in our annex.
Authorised
Personnel
Only
Past
This
Point
But why'd you start operating a radio station?
Authorised
Personnel
Only
Past
This
Point
Authorised
Personnel
Only
Past
This
Point
Authorised
Personnel
Only
Past
This
Point
Authorised
Personnel
Only
Past
This
Point
Authorised
Personnel
Only
Past
This
Point
Authorised
Personnel
Only
Past
This
Point
Authorised
Personnel
Only
Past
This
Point
Authorised
Personnel
Only
Past
This
Point
Point
b
oq
Authorised
Personnel
Only
Past
This
Point
Authorised
Personnel
Only
Past
This
Point
Authorised
Personnel
Only
Past
This
Point
Authorised
Personnel
Only
Authorised
Personnel
Only
Authorised
Personnel
Only
Someone my dad helped in the past was
on FM Hagoromo's board. He helped us out.
Since we were trying to hide from society,
he probably wanted to provide us
with a connection to it.
You sure think about some complicated things.
You had fun, didn't you?
Yeah, it was fun.
We found something to do together
and had so much fun.
The blue topaz you found, Asou-san.
Was it really here?
Yes, we found it here.
I picked it up and analysed it.
Sorry for trespassing.
Was that when you realised that Sadakichi-san
and the rest of the Seven Sages were here?
If you actually mine this land
and find blue topaz,
it's all yours.
Don't you and your club want it?
Nope.
But in return, tell Sadakichi-san I said thanks.
Tell him that the stupid junior
high girl with a death wish
got mad at their stupid advice
and lost the will to die.
What happened to that stupid junior high girl?
Do I have to spell it out?
The Sages will want to know.
Because they're still worried
about that stupid girl.
Enough with the "stupid".
She's following their advice
and looking for her own light.
P-Please wait!
No can do.
We're pitching a strike.
You mean "going on strike"!
Let's read the postcard already.
No. This ends today.
Our final piece of advice is for you, Kaiyu.
Did you go senile? Give me a break.
The seven of us all agreed on this.
Some friends from school
came over last night, right?
Let's not do this.
Rejoice, boy. Your father finally
found a place that'll take us in.
No need to worry about us anymore.
But...
We've been taking advantage of your kind words.
Go back to school, Kaiyu.
What will I even do there now? It's too late.
I heard you played the taiko
in the fife and percussion band.
Are you talking about drums?
They won't let me join now.
Drums?
I wanted to check if the snare drums
and timpani were still usable.
For a childhood friend.
I want him to come back to school.
Was Serizawa-san talking about him?
Don't you have any fun memories of school?
Well, I did have a laugh at the girl practising
the flute at the parking lot last year.
My recorder skills are probably
a thousand times better.
But it's too late for me to play the drums now.
What the hell?
Slide To Unlock
Slide to read
Asou Misato
New Message Received
I haven't touched them in ages.
"It's too late" is the kind of excuse
only silly old coots like us get to use.
The 200,000 yen is yours if
you train him.
Please.
Over.
Asou Misato
Homura Chika
Sub:    None
The 200,000 yen is yours if
you train him.
Please.
Over.
Asou Misato
A goddess has descended.
Incoming Call
Haruta
Did you tune into the radio?
Of course!
I'm going to barge into Kaiyuu's
place right now and yell at him.
I can't believe he had a laugh
at my flute playing. That jerk!
I'll go with you.
The concert band's honour is riding on this!
This can't wait for tomorrow, can it?
Time for the final episode of our lives!
world
is
still
grey,
but
it's
star
ting
to
chan
words
hang
in
the
air,
pat
ches
of
colour,
hi
ra
drif
ting
thro
ugh
the
world
hide
my
heart
in
doubt
tries
to
figure
out
whe
ther
to
say
'yes'
or
'no'
Some
times
we
lose
each
other
in
our
fanta
sies,
tired
to
walk
clear
of
them,
lody
won't
stop
fuzzy
trian
gle
is
a
circle
of
love,
tur
ning
on
ward
What
ever
for
mula
we
try,
can't
solve
it
an
shin
ease?
An
xious?
mony
might
seem
cont
radic
tory,
will
keep
gui
ding
ards
a
new
future
look
for
the
answer
days
that
are
to
come
Step on it, you useless hacks!
The privacy of your first love
will be violated all the way through.
You're kidding, right?
We're on the forest's side.
FIRST LOVE SOMMELIER
Benjant is a formidable opponent.