My mother left us before I turned ten.
I didn't want to end up like her,
or like my father and grandfather,
who grew overconfident in their abilities.
I wanted to leave home
and pursue a skill that would
mature and refine with age,
or perhaps a career in literature or art.
That's why I decided to walk down
the thorny path of music.
Ru
Ha
Ka
Chi
BLOSSOM
into
the
scent
of
rain
until
I
was
breathless
Straight
ahead
chased
the
rainbow
in
the
distance
Will
I
ever
reach
Countless
colours
merge
together
to
become
harmony
suddenly
born
strange
song
with
building
a
bridge
of
echoes
to
far
away
could
make
our
own
rainbow
from
here,
where
we've
come
then
the
colours
in
it
would
be
ours,
ours
only
million
nameless
hues
tion
would
form
its
gradient
rainbow
Let's
not
fear
the
pain
and
push
open
the
door
bathe
in
the
light
of
youth
Spring break.
Shimizu Minami High School
Freshmen
Uniform Fittings
Materials Introduction
Reception    Office
Venue    Gymnasium
Start  13:00
End  17:00
With freshmen numbers dwindling by the year,
Freshmen
Uniform Fittings
Materials Introduction
Reception    Office
Venue    Gymnasium
Start  13:00
End  17:00
Shimizu Minami High School
Freshmen
Uniform Fittings
Materials Introduction
Reception    Office
Venue    Gymnasium
Start  13:00
End  17:00
Shimizu Minami High School
Freshmen
Uniform Fittings
Materials Introduction
Reception    Office
Venue    Gymnasium
Start  13:00
End  17:00
Freshmen
Uniform Fittings
Materials Introduction
Reception    Office
Venue    Gymnasium
Start  13:00
End  17:00
Shimizu Minami High School
Materials Introduction
Reception    Office
Venue    Gymnasium
Start  13:00
End  17:00
Shimizu Minami High School
Freshmen
Uniform Fittings
Materials Introduction
Reception    Office
Venue    Gymnasium
Shimizu Minami High School
Freshmen
Uniform Fittings
Materials Introduction
Reception    Office
Venue    Gymnasium
Start  13:00
End  17:00
Shimizu Minami High School
Freshmen
Uniform Fittings
Materials Introduction
Reception    Office
Venue    Gymnasium
Start  13:00
End  17:00
Shimizu Minami High School
Freshmen
Uniform Fittings
Materials Introduction
Reception    Office
Venue    Gymnasium
Start  13:00
End  17:00
Shimizu Minami High School
Freshmen
Uniform Fittings
Materials Introduction
Reception    Office
Venue    Gymnasium
Start  13:00
End  17:00
Freshmen
Uniform Fittings
Materials Introduction
Reception    Office
Venue    Gymnasium
End  17:00
Shimizu Minami High School
Freshmen
Uniform Fittings
Materials Introduction
Reception    Office
Venue    Gymnasium
End  17:00
Shimizu Minami High School
Freshmen
Uniform Fittings
Materials Introduction
Reception    Office
Venue    Gymnasium
Start  13:00
End  17:00
Shimizu Minami High School
Freshmen
Uniform Fittings
Materials Introduction
Reception    Office
Venue    Gymnasium
Start  13:00
End  17:00
Freshmen
Uniform Fittings
Materials Introduction
Reception    Office
Venue    Gymnasium
Start  13:00
End  17:00
we minor culture clubs competed fiercely
to recruit them before the school year even began.
The concert band is waiting for you!
Join now, and you'll get to take
the stage at a competition!
A boy!
We want boys!
Hold it right there!
If you want members,
you'll have to recruit them over the drama club's dead—
Outta the way, perv!
We're the drama club.
Please consider joining us.
I'll think about it.
Oh, dear.
Hey!
What do you guys think you're doing?!
SPRINGRAPHY
Haruta!
How'd it go?
Awful.
What in the world did you do?
Weird. Even by myself,
it should've been a piece of cake.
Don't you know how hard we had it last year?
Relax. We'll get loads of girls
joining for you once school begins.
I only like them older.
Hey, I like them older too!
At least ten years older, or I'm not interested!
I guess as childhood friends,
we were fated to have similar tastes.
I'd rather we didn't!
Please, go out with a girl who isn't me!
Girls are great, you know!
What's gotten into you?
What'd you even come here for?
To show you this. Someone from
the newspaper club gave it to me earlier.
Said they took it at around 8AM,
before our practice started.
Look at this.
You can see someone in the music room.
Oh, yeah.
Right? This makes it clear that someone's
sneaking in there before we arrive!
I guess.
Remember the first day of spring break?
Staff Room
When I came to school early
to practise by myself...
Staff Room
Home Economics Kitchen
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Home Economics Kitchen
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Home Economics Kitchen
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Home Economics Kitchen
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Home Economics Kitchen
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Home Economics Kitchen
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Home Economics Kitchen
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Home Economics Kitchen
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Home Economics Kitchen
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Home Economics Kitchen
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Home Economics Kitchen
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Materials Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Materials Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Materials Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Materials Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Materials Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Materials Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Materials Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Materials Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Materials Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Materials Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Materials Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Music Room
Materials Room
Woodworks Room
Art Room
Huh?
Special Classrooms
Please return after use!
B Block
Music Room
Good morning!
Huh?
Nobody's here.
Who's there?
Even after that,
there were several days when the keys
were gone from the staff room in the morning.
I would go to the music room
thinking someone had come before me,
only to find it empty.
Then, finding that weird,
I'd go back to the staff room
and the key would be right there.
So basically, someone was entering and exiting
the music room without ever running into you.
That's right! We have a mysterious
trespasser on our hands!
Surely it's just a student.
But it's spring break!
Normal students would be sleeping in at home!
Why would one ever visit the music room
so early in the morning?
Must've had something more
important to do than sleep in.
What's the matter with you?
Don't you sense anything from this?!
Well, uh, I guess...
Forget it.
I'll go talk to Kusakabe-sensei.
Sorry, Chika-chan.
It's all good. No need to worry.
That student is probably a spring mirage to us.
A spring mirage?
Yeah.
As much as we wish for it to stay forever,
it'll end up as but a fleeting pipe dream.
Thanks to you, I think I can solve
the other spring break mystery.
Maren and Narushima-san?
While the choir uses the music room,
we scatter across the big school campus
and practise by ourselves.
Every now and then, we send out a signal
and break into an impromptu ensemble,
but a certain instrument's been
joining us since yesterday.
What is it?
Just watch.
Found it!
A clarinet?
Wow, who is that?
Looks like it's a student who's taking
makeups during spring break.
Could she be stupid?
President.
Didn't we have an unused clarinet lying around?
What is this, out of the blue?
It needs to be repaired,
so you can't use it right away.
Okay.
Huh?
It really is gone, huh?
They took it without telling anyone?
Repairing these isn't some DIY job, either.
You need technical expertise.
So who could do it?
Serizawa Naoko, maybe?
Wait, Serizawa? The first year?
If so, her playing was a bit weird.
Yes. Her timing was off at
the start of multiple phrases.
That reminds me. I saw her with
Kusakabe-sensei before the closing ceremony.
What?
Time out! Let me in on your conversation!
What do you want to know about Serizawa?
You're familiar with her?
The Serizawas are local celebrities, you know.
Her grandfather was a Diet member,
and her father runs a construction company.
She's a thoroughbred musician
who's looking to go pro.
Go pro?!
Awesome! If someone like that joined—
Forget about it.
She's a hardcore concert band hater.
Talk to her, and you'll get burnt.
Burnt?
When my little sister was in the concert band,
she once went to ask her
to fill in and came back crying.
N-Nobody who loves music
could ever hate concert bands...
Probably... Maybe...
A lot of aspiring pros consider
music a personal battle.
So?
A concert band could have members who
only picked up an instrument in high school,
so they consider practising
with one a waste of time.
Does it burn?
N-Not in the least!
There are also people who can't stand being
lumped in with players far worse than them.
What's the big deal?
We could all level up together.
Want me to put it in RPG terms, then?
Let's say you're a level 1 performer.
Kamijou, Narushima, and Maren would be level 50.
And Serizawa would be level 99.
She's been working several times harder
than you ever since grade school.
I might get burnt to a crisp.
Why would you guys play
with me if you're so good?
I like playing in a concert band
because it lets me play with friends.
There's more to music than just being good.
And nothing beats concert bands
when it comes to fun.
You won't regret it!
I'll do my best!
I'll recruit more members and make sure we can
take part in the Category A local qualifiers!
All right. My HP is restored.
Man, you're easy to please.
Oh yeah, I heard Serizawa-san's grades fell off
a cliff starting from the second midterms.
Before that, she was in the top five of our year.
Is that why she has to take makeups?
That probably has more to do
with her attendance.
She suddenly started having trouble
following conversations,
began to avoid her classmates,
and ended up cut off from the rest.
Due to that, she took most of the third term off.
Haruta, you saw her and
Kusakabe-sensei talking alone, right?
I did.
I saw them going into the career
counselling room multiple times.
Career counselling?
Multiple times?!
Her, of all people?
How did you conveniently end up
witnessing that each time?
I can't relax unless I see Sensei's
face multiple times a day.
You stole another march on me?!
You're her!
Serizawa-san?
BLOSSOM
It really has been repaired.
Where's my thanks?
P...
P?
Please join our band!
Wh-What's with you?!
I love how audacious you are.
You're not a cat in heat!
So why did I bother explaining all that before?
You're Homura-san, of Class 1-2?
Over the past year, the nearly-dead concert band
came back to life with you at its core.
You've got a keen eye.
You even battled the drama club
on stage in the gym.
You saw that?!
But I've known of you since long before that.
Don't you remember what happened last summer?
She came to school by car and nearly
ran you over in front of the main gate.
Hup!
That was you?
Don't be like that, Chika-chan.
You already accepted the expensive
cream bun settlement offered by the driver.
Oh, right.
Um, thanks for repairing it.
I'm not going to join, sorry.
Join?
What's wrong?
Wait. You came all the way,
so let's talk some more.
I'm sorry!
What did she even come here to do?
I think we'd all better watch our step.
Our step?
She probably lost something in
the music room or this prep room.
Think she dropped a contact lens?
No, but it's probably something similar...
and far more serious.
If she wanted to look for it between
the choir and concert band's practices,
the morning was her only option.
But she soon hit a wall looking by herself.
Maybe she snuck out the clarinet and repaired it
so she wouldn't owe us anything
for our help with the search.
Don't tell me...
Our conversation went awry the moment
the choir started practising.
I'll go bring her back!
Chika?!
Her sudden inability to keep up
with conversations, maintain her grades,
get the timing right at the start of phrases,
and the career counselling with
Kusakabe-sensei all points to one thing...
Serizawa-san!
What is it?
Did you lose your hearing?
Sudden sensorineural hearing loss?
I've gone completely deaf in my right ear.
And my left's gotten to the point
where it's hard for me to pick up everyday
conversation unless I'm in a quiet place.
I'm receiving treatment, but...
I played volleyball in junior high.
One of my teammates got hit
in the ear with a really hard spike.
We were competing for
a starting spot at the time,
but she eventually lost out.
After that, she started mishearing things
more frequently, even in daily life.
I saw her crying and—
What does that have to do with me?
Everything!
Could you be any more abrasive?
I don't want your stupid sympathy.
Why would I ever pity a brilliant,
level 99 rich girl?
Oh, I know!
Music Prep Room
Don't move out of line!
It's really small, so be sure not to miss it!
Quit slacking off, Prez. Hold the other side!
That took a while.
Music Prep Room
She came sprinting after me.
I had a hard time dealing with her.
Doesn't seem to be in the music room!
Let's look in the prep room, then.
Hurry up and tell everyone what size and colour it is.
Around the size of a pinky nail. Skin tone.
That small?
And it rolls around. Better not kick it.
That doesn't sound easy to find at all.
Nice idea.
Thanks. We got the paper cups from the infirmary.
These aren't half-bad.
I can even talk to people in noisy places.
Finally found it.
He says they found it.
Don't be in such a rush, now.
Tell her everything I'm about to say.
The concert band members
gave it their all for over an hour.
It was one hell of a workout.
We deserve praise for that, really.
Apparently he wants to run for
student council president this year.
Oh? Then you have my vote.
Your vote?
Chika-chan, are you really
telling her what I said?
I am. Now get on with it.
This was an unfortunate accident.
Accident?
So nobody should be blamed for it.
Infirmary
I never thought you'd be such a pain.
Why didn't you tell us sooner?
If not us, you could've at least
told Kusakabe-sensei.
I couldn't possibly tell him.
Not after all the trouble I caused him
with the career counselling.
I figured it'd be hard for you to
tell them about the hearing aid,
so I called your family and let them know.
Thank you.
What are the others up to?
Tending to the instruments.
We did find a bunch of them
that still seemed usable.
It's all thanks to you, Serizawa-san.
If only you'd repair the rest for free, too.
She can't do everything, you know.
Sorry. I can't handle all of you
talking to me at once.
All done!
There.
Now we can all talk to her.
You're sharing mine, okay?
Be careful not to let the strings loosen.
Mind if I ask you something?
What is it?
What made you pick up clarinet?
My father's introduced me to a lot of aspiring
pro musicians ever since I was young.
But not one of them played the clarinet.
That was probably just bad luck.
As for me, it was anything goes.
All I cared about was becoming a
pro musician and leaving that house.
That's all, really.
Leave that palace you call a home?!
What a waste! You could be a NEET there forever!
President!
Serizawa-san.
How does our band look from your point of view?
You've accomplished nothing worth mentioning,
and you haven't even taken
the shape of a proper band yet.
Tell us something we don't know.
Don't tell me, you're seriously aiming for Fumon Hall?
Yeah.
Then...
Sensei must've found it
hard to break this to you,
but I'll say it for him now.
You need at least thirty members.
Thirty?
In the high-school Category-A All-Japans,
they call you rash if you take part with thirty.
Any lower,
and there'll be a clear gap between you and the
powerhouse bands with the maximum fifty-five members.
Wait.
There is a way to close that gap.
Orchestral reduction, right?
Arranging full symphony music for a smaller band
to surprise pro judges and make an impact.
This school has an instructor capable of that.
An instructor who was once called
Japanese music's wunderkind.
But that won't change the fact
that you'll be at a disadvantage.
Also, you should give up
on this year's nationals.
Instead of suffering a crushing defeat
due to lack of members,
you'd be better off entering Category B
with its thirty-five member limit
and free-choice pieces only.
You won't make it to Fumon Hall that way,
but you can aim for gold
in the Category B regionals,
and gain more valuable experience that way.
So we have to pave the way for
Kamijou and our other juniors, right?
Category B...
You're an amusing one, Kamijou-kun.
I thought Homura-san would be the only one
to have "Join us" written all over her face,
but you're the same.
You're like two peas in a pod.
No way!
You think so too?
Hey...
Could you help us in our efforts?
Consider it a request from me too.
Sensei.
You gave up on becoming a conductor, right?
So why do you still surround yourself with music
by teaching at this remote public school?
Music is all I know,
so I cling to it.
I'm the same.
The door hasn't been completely shut
on my going professional.
I have to cling to the path I have chosen
and keep pushing on until I'm satisfied.
Isn't it the same for you all?
So I'm sorry,
but I can't join you yet.
There's one thing I just don't
understand from this case.
What?
How'd you lose your hearing aid
in the music prep room?
I wanted to check if the snare drums
and timpani were still usable,
so I picked them up to move them,
but then I lost my balance and fell.
Who's there?
That must've been when it fell out.
I didn't realise because I was in such a rush.
Why check the snare drums and timpani?
For a childhood friend.
I want him to come back to school.
He plays the drums?
Forget I said anything.
He must be going through a lot,
and I'm sure he'd hate people meddling.
Sorry for causing such a fuss.
I'll be rooting for you from the outside.
Oh, can I have those?
Thanks!
I don't care if she's a prodigy or whatever.
She's just a troublemaker, if you ask me.
Yet...
She said she couldn't join us "just yet".
Yeah.
A spring mirage, huh?
world
is
still
grey,
but
it's
star
ting
to
chan
words
hang
in
the
air,
pat
ches
of
colour,
hi
ra
drif
ting
thro
ugh
the
world
hide
my
heart
in
doubt
tries
to
figure
out
whe
ther
to
say
'yes'
or
'no'
Some
times
we
lose
each
other
in
our
fanta
sies,
tired
to
walk
clear
of
them,
lody
won't
stop
fuzzy
trian
gle
is
a
circle
of
love,
tur
ning
on
ward
What
ever
for
mula
we
try,
can't
solve
it
an
shin
ease?
An
xious?
mony
might
seem
cont
radic
tory,
will
keep
gui
ding
ards
a
new
future
look
for
the
answer
days
that
are
to
come
I'm here to confess today.
Be a man and admit it.
I'm gonna go all the way!
Our next caller is "Desert Rabbit".
FREQUENCY: 77.4MHZ
What's in a name?