Good morning, Hina.
Come now, be a diligent girl again today.
Well done, Hina!
Wonderfully done, Hina!
You're a genius, Hina.
It'll all be fine now.
No need to worry about anything, Hina.
What about you, Grandpa?!
Me?
I'm a bit tired.
Rest assured, I'll arrange things
so you don't have any problems.
Grandpa...
What's wrong, Hina?
I had a dream about Grandpa.
About your grandpa?
Yes.
There, there.
You really loved him, didn't you?
Yes.
We loved him too.
He was a wonderful person.
Gazing upon this world with you
Makes it so much more beautiful
Living in this moment with you
Makes it so much more soothing
further
Don't go yet! Await me at that distant edge
Await me
Is your job really that different to what I was doing?
I'm really thirsty. Aren't you?
Yeah, there are certainly some things in common.
Huh?
Shall we go get some drinks?
What might you be doing?
I'm getting some behind-the-scenes footage.
Behind-the-scenes?!
I want in!
Now let me tell you about this film!
This is my chance to get some screen time!
Y-Yes, I'll be filming the crew too.
Really? Us too?
Of course!
I guess putting in some earnest
work pays off in the end.
See, even you get to be on film.
Yeah!
I see.
As the lead role, I shall appear at the end of that.
What's the matter?
Nothing. Don't worry about it.
All right then.
I wonder what's going to happen
to all of us when this summer is over.
It would be best if you interview the female lead last.
I don't really believe that the world is going to end.
You are to document the exploits of
the grand actress that stands before you.
But I guess Hina's going to
eventually move out of our house.
I'd really hate for that to catch me off guard.
Episode 8
The Day of to See the Sea
So you said that Hina is the child of relatives of ours,
but how long can she stay with us?
Why do you ask? Something on your mind?
No, just asking.
I was wondering if she'd just disappear one day.
I see.
How should I put this?
Youta and Hina have become close,
so I understand why he's anxious.
Let's tell him everything.
You're right.
Hina isn't really a relative. That was a lie.
She's the granddaughter of a mentor to me
and your mother, to whom we owe a lot.
What about her parents, then?
Her mother passed away.
Her father has remarried and is living
happily with his new wife and children,
but we don't really know where he is now.
Wait,
so Hina was abandoned by her dad?
Yes, and that's why our mentor took care of her.
And where is he now?
We promised him that we'd take care
of Hina if anything were to happen to him.
He said she'd be wearing flashy, mysterious clothes
and to take care of her if we ever came across her.
So when you called me that evening,
I was sure it was her.
Wow, that's quite the story.
So how long can Hina stay with us?
Well...
You should think about that and ask her.
It is time for video games!
Today is the day I shall defeat that boss!
What troubles you?
Your expression is unusually grim.
I found out how you got to stay at our house.
I see.
It is extremely uncouth to pry
into the background of a god.
You have parents, so you're human.
Indeed, I was originally.
However, I am presently a god.
You have yourself witnessed My
godly power on numerous occasions.
Indeed, her mysterious power
has helped a lot on numerous occasions.
And I guess it really seems like
it's beyond what a human can do.
When did you become a god?
334 days ago.
So from that day on,
you started calling yourself a god?
I obtained a power on par with a god.
And what is that power really?
I know not.
I do not fully grasp it Myself.
I heard your father is still alive.
You do not flinch at bringing up
delicate matters, do you?
I was abandoned by My parent.
I owe everything to My grandpa who took Me in.
Let's try to find your father.
He might be able to tell us more about you.
Why seek that?
Your knowledge is sufficient.
What?! It's all question marks!
I know not what you are referring to.
Everything about your past before you came here.
I want to know more about you.
What would be the purpose of
unearthing My past at this point?
Well,
isn't it normal to want to know more
about the people you're close with?
Have you not considered that it would be cruel
toward Me to seek the parent who abandoned Me?
I guess it would be.
I'm sorry for bringing it up.
Well, let's get back to studying.
I am aware you intend to seek him out on your own.
You do realize that with a power such as Mine,
I am already privy to his approximate location.
What? Really?
What do I do with you?
You were so eager to help others
with their family problems.
This time around I want to do something for you!
I see.
Your expression conveys
that there will be no stopping you.
Yeah.
In that case, I shall accompany you.
Really? You sure?
Seeking him out without My power
would be rather laborious.
We shall go together!
Thank you.
It is the ocean!
It has been My desire to see it with My own eyes!
You haven't seen it?!
Only on television and the internet.
Really?
Then let's go see it.
Yes!
By the way, this place is quite far away.
How should we get there?
I already have the solution.
It is not a trip for within a day.
Prepare for one night of lodging.
Ah, okay.
Wait, lodging?!
Mom?
Um,
I'd like to go on a small trip to find Hina's dad.
We probably wouldn't be back until tomorrow.
Is that okay?
Then I guess I'll go make two lunchboxes for you!
Thank you!
I wonder if this is what eloping feels like.
It would definitely not include
lunchboxes from your mother.
True.
However, mentioning eloping makes it sound
as though you have feelings for Me.
O-Oh, I guess it did sound kinda like that.
I may be a god, but I am also a maiden.
You would do well to be cognizant of that.
Yeah.
We're still not done with the movie shoot,
so we'll need to get to that when we're back.
Indeed. It shall soon be completed.
Former Water Treatment Plant
浄水場跡
Delicious!
Former Water Treatment Plant
浄水場跡
Sweet is indeed how an omelette should be.
It's been getting sweeter ever since you came.
Indeed. I did explain to your mother
that she needs to make it sweeter.
Don't just go changing the taste
of other people's mothers' cooking!
You can expect a similar change
in the taste of the curry.
I spoke to her about it yesterday.
Don't do that! It's the taste from my
adolescence that I want to look back on fondly!
Tokai Bus
Also the mapo tofu—
You're kidding me!
Tokai Bus
Former Water Treatment Plant
浄水場跡
This is as far as the bus takes us.
Doesn't look like this road is used much.
And it doesn't look like we'll be able to
catch a cab, so I guess we have to walk.
At this point the sun isn't just hot, it's painful!
My garments also provide
adequate shading from the sun.
I am certain you are impressed.
You actually look like you're boiling.
We are near our destination.
This might sound weird considering how far
we've come, but I'm starting to get nervous.
Aren't you also nervous about meeting your father?
It is nothing for Me to feel timid about.
However, I am certain the mere sight of
the child he abandoned shall give him pause.
That's not funny.
I should prepare myself for this to go horribly wrong.
This is the place.
It's like a mansion!
Even looks like it was built recently.
It is the house he worked hard for.
Okay, here goes.
Hello? Who is it?
Ah... Uh...
My name is Narukami Youta.
I am an acquaintance of
an acquaintance of your husband.
I come to visit today wishing to converse with him,
if that is convenient and would be possible, please!
You are far too flustered.
Hello? You wish to speak to me?
It's him! I'm so nervous!
But I have to man up!
I-I-I have come to ask you about Hina!
Get a grip.
So, you're an acquaintance of Hina's?
Y-Yes!
All right, by all means, come in.
Th-Thank you for having me!
Just stop speaking.
Yay!
You can go play outside.
Really?
Okay!
Later!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Nice to meet you! I'm Narukami Youta!
Nice to meet you. I'm Satou Toshitoku.
This is Hina's father...
He looks like your average father.
I'm here because I wish to
ask some things about Hina.
Hina?
Yes, she was a troublesome child.
Was?
What's this weird feeling?
Here, have some tea.
Thank you very much.
What?!
Only for me?!
Why?!
I'm here with Hina!
Wait, wait, wait!
I've come here with Hina!
She's sitting right there beside me!
No!
This can't be happening!
No! Don't tell me...
other people can't see her!
Oh, the royal milk tea will take a bit longer.
Of course.
They see her!
Why are you yelling?
No, look!
I was taken aback by the outrageous
plot twist I thought was happening!
What are you blabbering about?
And when did you even manage
to ask for that royal milk tea?!
I merely responded to the inquiry
about what I would like for a drink.
Just ask for regular tea!
So, who is your companion?
What do you mean?
It's Hina. Your daughter.
Hina?! How?!
Is it really Hina?!
Indeed,
I am Satou Hina. What of it?
What's going on?
I have become a god.
A god?
What are you talking about?
Wait a moment, I—
No!
Is that her?!
Calm down, Isuzu.
But it's her, isn't it!
This is turning out even worse than I expected!
No! No! I don't want to go back!
Just let me deal with this.
I'll talk to you outside.
Please wait for me at the front door.
O-Okay.
My!
So this is the ocean that occupies
71.1% of the Earth's surface!
It does appear rather large!
And what is your name?
Munin seems eager to play. You can play with him.
So you are called Munin!
Munin, come! Let's race!
Come now. This is not racing!
I'm sorry that I had to ask you to leave
the house after you came all this way.
It's fine.
So, what would you like to know?
Anything you can tell me about Hina.
I can only discuss events that
happened up until she was seven.
Are you okay with that?
Yes.
Hina was born with a congenital
disease called Logos Syndrome.
What is that?
It involves simultaneous brain tissue atrophy
and neurogenic muscle atrophy.
As it progresses, muscles gradually degrade,
and it eventually leads to death.
The Hina I knew could neither stand nor speak.
What? Really?!
You find that hard to believe?
So do I.
Because there exists no treatment
for Logos Syndrome.
But...
Yes.
But if you're saying that this is Hina, I believe you.
I don't know what to feel.
Should I be happy that she recovered?
Or should I blame myself for abandoning
her and forming a new family?
I think I'm supposed to get angry.
Angry at you for bringing her here.
Huh? How so?
You're still a child.
I'm not surprised you don't understand
how painful it is for me to see
Hina healthy after all this time.
I suppose nobody but me, her father,
can know how that feels.
Isn't it possible for her to live with you?
Still so naïve.
You saw my wife's reaction just now.
She knows all too well how hard it was on the family
to watch Hina waste away last time.
Hina's mother felt so guilty for giving
her such a body, that in the end—
Oh no!
But despite all that,
I'm happy I brought Hina here
for you to see her healthy.
I didn't want to see her, healthy or not.
You're her father!
How can you say that?!
You don't understand because you weren't there.
It was a condition so severe a child
like you could never imagine it.
That's selfish!
Very selfish!
Hina is such a nice girl,
and you abandoned her without even knowing her!
Indeed I don't know her.
It was never possible to communicate with her.
But you can now!
Look! She's right there and healthy!
It is truly an incredible thing to see.
However, I did everything I could.
And yet, I could not prevent her
from spiraling towards her death.
I made the decision to let her go,
in order to protect this new life of mine.
Do you understand the weight of that decision?
I don't.
I don't understand what you're saying
or why you can't accept her.
One day you will.
Also,
you may actually meet the same fate as me.
Let me say it again:
there is no treatment for Logos Syndrome.
I'm a physician. I would have heard if there
was such an important breakthrough.
So let me give you some advice from experience.
A miracle shines brightly for a moment,
but then everything slowly
returns to its mundane logic.
That's how the world works.
Hina, did you have fun playing?
Yes. This pup is rather clever and nimble.
It's getting dark.
Let's head back.
I see.
That is unfortunate.
This is where our ways part.
Yeah. Say goodbye.
Yes. I am rather peckish too.
Farewell, Munin. Bye-bye!
Anything you want to say to your father?
No.
I am here merely as your guide.
Okay. Let's go then.
And with one last bow,
I parted ways with Hina's father.
So what was this trip about, anyway?
Did we gain anything?
I feel like everyone would have
been better off not knowing.
Nobody would be hurt.
Everyone's peace of mind
would have been unscathed.
Now I'm just left feeling uneasy.
Behold! This shrimp is still alive!
Just eat your food like an adult.
Behold! Behold!
...you may actually meet the same fate as me.
...everything slowly returns to its mundane logic.
That's how the world works.
I wonder what he meant by that.
What's going to happen to Hina?
She's so lively that she shook
my mundane life to its core.
Itou Tourism
井逗ツーリズム
She can't wither away!
What is troubling you? You have had
a frightful expression all evening.
Nothing's going to happen to you, right?
That was just adults making excuses, right?
Regardless of what words have thrown
your mind into turmoil, the world is soon to end.
That turmoil along with everything else
shall return to nothingness.
Thus, would you not be happier were you
to enjoy yourself before that occurs?
Itou Tourism
井逗ツーリズム
Ah, I have spotted a video game!
What?
We should play!
Really?
You want to play in a place like this?
Also that's a really old one.
Come, I shall instruct you in the Nagoya Attack.
How do you even know about that?
In fact, how do I?
Though the wind is urging me to set off on a journey
I didn't feel like giving it my all right from the start
I don't really have anything I wanted to protect
No matter what clothes I change into, nothing feels right
Even just being alive feels like a chore
All I have is mountains of regret
If this was a game I'd just hit reset
And start all over again
Hello! Goodbye!
We didn't know anything
When we set out on this long adventure
We all start this journey in our youth
With nothing in our bags but hope and some water
Toshitoku...
Yes?
You have another visitor.
Hello? Who is it?
The Day I Became a God
until the end
of the world