Building No. 12 - Haruki's Bond With His Sisters
My, that felt really refreshing.
I already flushed Eiji down the toilet...
Play your cards right and—
Do not
disturb!!
Gaming!
Haruki
What are you doing?!
Didn't you see the sign I put up?!
Haruki, I want to play a game with you.
Huh?
What brought this on?
Don't sweat the details!
Are you playing on your computer?
Yeah. It's an online game.
I see.
Hey, you should let me try
that game you're always playing.
Yayoi's acting weird.
All right, how about we start with—
Hey.
Oh, sorry. I started feeling
sleepy all of a sudden.
Then go back to your room.
No way! I don't wanna get up.
Huh?
I want to sleep here.
Got it. You've got a fever.
I do not! Um...
The faster you deal with a cold, the better.
Just rest.
Haruki!
We caught you.
We've got something good to show you!
Come with us!
Us!
Occupied
We want you to watch until we're done.
Done.
Wait up!
Up!
You two are already in third grade!
Occupied
Have some decency!
D-Don't get the wrong idea!
This is... um...
It's a prank!
Prank!
Yeah, yeah. You got me.
I'm gonna go now, okay?
Stupid Haruki!
Meanie.
Okay, sorry!
I'll stay here until you're done.
Okay, time to hit the s—
Geez, Sis.
I already had to deal
with the younger ones earlier.
Wake up or you'll be found out.
Wh-What the?!
Flip
Yikes! I'm dead if they find her here!
Haruki? We're coming in.
We've all decided to sleep here tonight.
Huh?
Wh-What's going on?
Look at how she's behaving
even when our sisters are nearby.
I'm only in my first year of high school,
so sometimes her actions escape me,
but I guess that's part of who she is.
Will there ever be a day when Yayoi
stops hitting me every chance she gets?
Regardless, she's studying for her
high school entrance exams this year,
so I'll have to keep helping her with that.
As Uzuki's older brother,
I'd really like her to stop with the pranks,
but I can tell she likes me well enough.
I guess I can put up with a few pranks.
Satsuki's the only one who shares
the same interests as me.
There's a D.C Gai event coming up,
so I hope we can go together.
I'm still not sure how
things turned out this way.
But I guess spending the night together
like this isn't bad once in a while.
Hold on. Where am I supposed to sleep?!
My dear sisters!
Feel free to rely on me
without restraint from now on!
What?
Let's avoid watching
anything scary for a while.
Yeah!
Yeah.
Girls, wash your faces
and get ready for school.
Huh?
Hurry! Hurry!
Danchigai!