Fist of Flowing Water Crushing Rock!
Offense and defense in perfect harmony.
The same fighting style, but Bang's form is flawless.
The victor is already clear.
What the hell?
The old SOB... It's not like him
to just whale on an opponent.
C-Crap,
I'm blacking out...
I'm about... to die!
What is that preposterous style?
Where'd you pick it up?
It's as if you've become an animal.
I'm not done!
I can use him and carve out an advantage!
No you don't.
I took care of the monsters.
Bang, all that remains is Garou!
Cleaning Up the Disciples' Mess
We sent in a team to bring Garou back alive,
but we had no idea Demon Cyborg was so strong.
And then there's Silverfang...
I can see no way to pull Garou out.
But if I return empty-handed,
Orochi might devour me this time.
I need Garou to somehow get through this alive...
But it looks hopeless.
If that were you, Brother,
would you still be standing after so many wounds?
If I were 60 years younger, I could hang in there.
So I hope...
Anyway, just a little more.
Now, Bang!
Bang, you damn geezer...
Coming at your former top disciple
when I'm at my weakest.
And worse, the other old fart is Bomb,
master of Fist of Whirling Wind Smashing Steel!
Aren't they ashamed, ganging up on me like this?
Even if I put on a sob act and beg for my life,
Demon Cyborg would never let me go.
My only way out of this is killing all three of them!
There's no way.
Feel the pain Charanko felt,
Garou!
Let's play heroes and monsters!
You're gonna play too, aren't you, Garou?
C'mon, man!
O-Okay.
Dan-da-daan!
Justice Man is here!
Hah!
Justice Man Kick!
Watch out!
Huh?
That must have hurt.
Okay,
then you be the monster.
What?
You be the monster!
Is my life flashing before my eyes?
Everything about this sucks.
What was his name...
You're the monster now, got it?
That's right. Tatty...
The most popular kid in class.
What is it? What happened?
Garou was fighting!
We were playing,
then out of nowhere, Garou got mad.
It was just heroes,
but then Garou went ballistic on Tatty.
What the heck? What's wrong with him?
Poor Tatty!
Why did you get into that fight?
Well, because...
Is it true you became violent
over heroes and monsters?
Tatty is always—
Can't you tell what's real and what's pretend?!
No, that's not it.
I'm always the monster and—
You're the one who lost his temper!
How will you make up for it?!
It's not like I didn't want to be the monster...
Did I hate that Tatty always played the hero?
No, not that either.
It's because playing heroes and monsters
felt so overwhelmingly unjust.
Heroes and monsters is just a game
that recreates kids' TV shows.
Everyone is free to choose what role they play.
Tatty was the most popular kid in class.
But me, I was the loner kid,
always gloomy and friendless.
Everyone knew who the hero was going to be.
I didn't stand a chance.
Justice Man Cross Chop!
Why'd you dodge?
Huh?
Guys, hold Garou for a sec.
Okay!
Huh?
Naturally, there was no scenario
where the monster wins.
I was always the loser.
Justice Man Kick!
Garou the Poop Monster has been crushed!
The popular kid at the center of everything
would always beat up
the little guy that no one liked.
I can't take it anymore!
Tatty, fight me!
Huh?
What're you talking about?
I don't want to be the monster anymore!
If I win,
promise me you'll leave me alone!
Guys, hold Garou for a sec.
That's cheating! Let go of me!
I want to fight Tatty!
The other kids say you got
violent while you were playing.
That's not what happened.
Tatty is just popular,
so everyone is making me into the bad guy.
No, you did something you shouldn't have!
You have to apologize!
Screw justice. And screw evil.
I'm gonna be killed because
that's what everyone else wants!
It's not fair! I can't stand it!
It friggin' pisses me off!
All I want is to make them understand!
I want to strike a blow for the little guy!
"Good" and "evil",
I reject them both!
This is the end, Garou!
Nothing's...
...ended!
What the—?!
Garou...
Bang! Above you!
A monster?!
Genos...!
Bang, he's a monster now!
I will shoot them both down!
Hear me now!
I've got Garou with me!
The others I leave to you,
Spiral Incineration Cannon!
Elder Centipede!
What is this devilry?!
I-Is that a living creature?!
Look! The other heroes!
It took the full brunt of Genos's
attack without a scratch...
This adversary will no doubt be fearsome indeed.
Centipede Monster
Elder Centipede
ii
Threat Level:
Dragon
Tch...
What's the big idea, butting in like that?!
Never mind. Let Elder Centipede handle the rest.
He's a living catastrophe, destroying all in his path.
I admire such indiscriminate destructive power.
As usual, you didn't close out
your opponents, hero hunter.
Once they're down, you have to
keep on them until they're truly done.
Those heroes lying on the ground were still alive.
Well, not to worry.
Nothing can survive Elder Centipede.
You all can piss off!
Those are my prey!
Now, now. Keep still.
Put me down, you shit!
I won't let you do this!
Why are you upset?
It's your own fault for not finishing them.
The elimination of two Class S heroes
makes all this very worthwhile for us.
They're our greatest enemies, after all.
You experienced that for yourself first-hand.
Fights, you see, are all about matchups.
According to our strategist, Gyoro-Gyoro,
the only ones who could resist Elder Centipede are
the powerful psychic with abilities
beyond any other, the Tornado of Terror,
the recluse with a massive arsenal
of military technology, Metal Knight,
the hero called the strongest human, King,
and the top-ranked hero who
nearly killed him already, Blast.
Elder Centipede is working
with the Monster Association
specifically to get vengeance against Blast.
He's quite desperate to lure
the number one hero to the battlefield.
From a matchup perspective, those two Class S heroes
lack the means to escape from their present predicament.
Silverfang boasts peerless technique,
but it's only effective against
opponents of a certain size.
Demon Cyborg's capabilities are truly outstanding,
but his strength cannot exceed
the firepower of his components.
Those three face nothing but certain slaughter.
Here it comes!
Genos!
You're up!
Understood!
Whirling Wind...
Flowing Water...
Roaring Qi Rending Sky Fist!
What an amazing move.
Against a carapace that hard,
it's the perfect counter!
Again! Again! Again!
We should've seen that coming.
Yes, but we only had one shot with that technique.
Thank you, Genos.
It was nothing.
The attack we dealt was devastating.
The shock will travel through its entire body.
May you shatter into a million pieces,
damned demon!
We're done here.
Really?
The damn thing just molted!
That's all we did?
If we can't beat it, what now?
The city's over there.
If it heads that way, it'll be a massacre.
Bang.
Hmm?
I will take the thing on.
I will hold the monster here as long as I can.
You two run for it.
Genos, I can't go along with that.
You mustn't be rash simply
because you know you cannot win.
The future needs the young.
Genos...
Whatever you do, don't be rash.
Is this truly the right path?
I do not accept that!
It's suicide!
Your cannons won't work on it!
Elder Centipede, Gouketsu, even Garou...
They are with the Monster Association.
There is no avoiding this fight!
Dual Blade Rush!
To fight one is to fight them all!
I will smash you apart!
If battling them is being rash...
Genos!
...then I can no longer be...
...worth anything in a fight!
Jet Drive Arrow!
Insignificant flea!
What the—?!
He went into its mouth!
Die!
This is stomach acid!
I will leave you melted into nothing!
You are the one who will melt!
Ultra Spiral Incineration Cannon!
He did it!
It happened again.
I...
could not win.
I could not save them.
Run, Brother!
Pointless.
What's the matter?
You've become awfully quiet, little hero hunter.
This isn't how things were supposed to turn out.
I wanted to defeat them using my own strength,
and by doing so,
become the very symbol of their fear.
Why else even be the hero hunter?
The symbol of their fear? You?!
As you are now, your power does not come close to
Elder Centipede or the leaders of the Monster Association.
As I am now...
But just you wait.
What is it that I lack?
There are still many more like this monster.
Am I to be merely a spectator
against monsters like that?
Bang, we have a problem!
It's driving us toward the city!
Think of the civilian casualties!
Bang.
My brother...
It's time I go all in.
I will offer all the power
that remains to me in this life!
Courage.
Elder Centipede!
Listen up, noxious pest!
I brought Blast, the guy you want!
That's King's voice!
Did he say Blast?!
Hey, look!
It's turning toward the voice!
Blast?
You heard me.
The guy who once beat you so badly,
you ran away dribbling piss everywhere!
Blast, the hero, is here!
If you want a rematch, get over here!
What's the problem? Scared?
You coward!
If you're gonna shit out
your guts for fear, do it at home.
A lowly bug like you needs to go back to your
hidey-hole and suck on your mommy's milk!
It appears King made it in time.
Yes.
He asked for information that he
could use to provoke Elder Centipede.
He's planning to draw it in for a head-to-head clash.
Though it's classified,
I told him about the run-in with Blast.
And his response?
One word:
"Understood."
I also heard the roar of the King Engine.
For the final blow,
lure him here and refrain from
any attack that might affect the city.
That should do it.
Uh, Saitama?
Saitama!
That you, Genos?
I guess he was here.
Yeah.
Good thing we came.
Hmm?
Saitama, it is just me?
You look relaxed or something...
I'm kinda refreshed.
I was stressed from you handing me
my butt at all those games.
So he was still pissed off...
Master Saitama!
I need to ask you something.
Yeah?
What do you think it is that I lack?
I mean, power, right?
Thank you very much!
Aw man!
No!
If you use Saitama as your baseline, you'll...
Don't do it, Genos!
Master's battles show me the true path...
He is a symbol of strength.
He is what I strive to be.
I will get there too.
Wanna head home?
The power lies in my hand
You'll know now, ONE PUNCH!
Through the one-time tranquil town
Thunderous roars begin to fill the air
Watch out! Freak out! Monsters!
DRAGON
WOLF
TIGER
DEMON
Who will stand to take the lead
When we slay the evil ones?
Mayhem, mix-ups, morons!
We know we are
Heroes!
(Ah) Why on earth were you
(Born to be) destined for villainy?
(I know why) If you too wish to know
(If you ask) Then I shall tell!
This night the fist of justice is coming for you
And your fate is a punch straight into hell!
(HERO) That word exists for you, indeed, for you alone
(Go! Go!) Thrust forth your silent fist, raise it to the sky!
(HERO) The solitude is borne by the apostle for
(Go! Go!) A peace not built up from hatred and fear
All to defend the world!
(HERO)
Raise your power!
ONE PUNCH!
Garou?
Did you pass out?
Rest well, then.
For soon, you will meet Lord Orochi.