The first person to hold a speech
in Japan was Fukuzawa Yukichi.
Well then, let's hear your speech
in three, two, one...
Get off your high horse, you horse bastard!
Yes, yes!
Okay, here we go.
Virtual Cyber Academy Dormitories
You're watching Virtual Friends!
Friends...
Friendship opens your heart!
Oh, heart.
Heartbreak leads to despair!
Wait, you can't extend that word...
...despair and pain!
Pain... Pain...
Painting pictures require... a lot of paintwork.
Work, huh? Work, work...
Workshops can be a great learning experience...
if you're trying to woo a man!
Man, Man, Man...
Manhattan—Uh, er, um...
...is my home!
Homework is no fun!
Ready, and...
Virtual Friends Are Watching!
Don't worry
Say, don't you like me now?
Don't you never want to lose me now?
Here's where you'll find me now
Here is where I will always remain
So much more that I need
Wanna dream together with you now
More love is all I need
All I need, all I need is more love
Through the screen I was drawn
To the world that's beyond
Even you'll fall in love once or twice as you go on
When my vision first cleared
The sensation was weird
To find out that my limits had all but disappeared
With open arms, I waited for you here
And now you're back, so don't be mad, my dear
Go on and cry your heart out, it's okay
It's fine by me
You can even run away
All I need is more love, all I need
Say, don't you like me now?
Don't you never want to lose me now?
Here's where you'll find me now
Here is where I will always remain
So much more that I need
Wanna dream together with you now
More love is all I need
All I need, all I need is more love
Virtual Friends Are Watching.
My best guess is...
Guy A
Episode 2
they're responsible!
Ah!
Hey, where are we?
Everyone looks identical.
Are they even human?
Ah, I'm beat...
That's...
Guy B
Mirai Akari, Tanaka Hime, Suzuki Hina...
Guy A
Guy B
Tsukino Mito, Nekomiya Hinata, and...
Cyber Girl Siro!
Why are they here?
Guy A
I don't know.
But ever since that show started airing,
they've shown up here on occasion.
"That show"?
You guys!
To be continued
Virtual Grandmother!
Utsureba Kawaru Yo no Narai.
Today's Expression
Utsureba
Kawaru Yo no Narai
Today's Expression
Utsureba Kawaru
Yo no Narai
It's a Japanese expression.
It refers to how society changes
with the passage of time.
Something that has changed greatly since
the mid-20th century is consumer electronics.
Television went from black and white to color.
Air conditioners were invented,
making the indoors more comfortable.
Washing machines gained more and more
features, making laundry much easier.
And nowadays,
no home can go without a refrigerator.
My family ran a butcher shop,
and refrigerators with freezer
compartments were a revolution.
With a freezer, you can preserve
meat for much longer,
so once we had one, we were able
to drastically improve inventory turnover.
It was really revolutionary.
By the way, since my family ran a butcher shop,
I may have been the first among
my friends to have tasted sausages.
That's how things used to be.
Come to think of it, I'm probably also the first
of my friends to have gained a virtual body.
Virtual Grandmother!
I'm the veteran virtual YouTuber, Peanuts!
Virtual Friends Are Watching.
I thought we were goners for real!
It's so good to be alive!
By the way, don't you find space mysterious?
Space?
Indeed.
Doesn't it excite you,
thinking about all the mysteries still unsolved?
Yeah, I get you!
I'd love to become a space pirate
and go on adventures.
I want to boldly go where no man has gone before!
That scared me!
Huh? Something's changed outside.
We're in space?!
Guys, look! Something is coming this way!
One of space's mysteries, perhaps?
I'm coming for you now!
Not you, again!
You're watching
Let's Go! Classroom
It's coming right towards us!
Guys, hurry! We need a plan!
Otherwise we'll lose to him again!
That laugh...
It's a peanut asteroid.
Then maybe complimenting him might work?
I'll bet he's easily flattered!
I see. We just need to compliment him!
Akari, you go first!
What, seriously? Um...
I'd rate you about a 4/10!
I want to wear that hip underwear too!
Your hairstyle is so hip!
You're yellow! Like, super yellow!
Um... The color of your nipples
is disturbingly realistic.
Hey, he's completely unfazed!
I'll rip your briefs off you, you cocky bean!
I-I have to hide it with myself! We can't air this!
Oops, was that out loud?
It's all over!
I'm coming for you now!
Right!
Right.
To be continued
Virtual Friends Are Watching!
Gorry.
Right.
How are things?
I'm having fun.
We can't have that!
What's this about?
Fuji Aoi Park is on the verge of bankruptcy,
and you're out here having fun?
What?
This park is actually a business?
Obviously. What did you think it was?
I-I'm sorry.
On that note, Gorry, mind if I lay you off?
What? I was an employee?
I managed to recruit someone
younger, cuter, and sexier!
What?
You've already hired someone new?
Hello, I'm Pink Gorilla.
My sister?!
Fuji!
Fuji Aoi Park
Aoi.
Right.
Ya gotta see this!
Ya gotta see this, Akari!
Akari, ya gotta see this!
What's wrong, Hime?
Akari, I tell ya, ya gotta see this!
So, what is it this time?
We got a letter from a "Takahashi",
who's having trouble!
Come on, read this and help him!
"Hello, Akari."
'lo.
Hello!
Whenever my boss hits his enter key,
he does so really loudly.
Slam!
It's so distracting. I can barely work!
What should I do?
Slam!
Oh, that sucks.
Problem:
Boss's enter key
is loud
Problem:
Boss's enter key
is loud
Problem:
Boss's enter key
is loud
That's straight-up enter key harassment!
I know that feeling.
It's so hard to ignore that loud "clack".
You hear it over the other noise.
Yeah, yeah. But it's so satisfying to do.
Yeah, that feeling of release. Just let it all out!
Yeah, it's great!
Like, "Clap! Finished!"
Wonder what gives that "finished" feeling.
Maybe it's because the button's so large?
On the keyboard.
The enter key.
Yeah, the enter.
Well, Takahashi wants his boss
to stop slamming the enter key so loudly,
but it's hard to tell your boss that.
Yeah, right.
What's the best solution here...?
Huh? Wait... Miss Mirai?
Miss Mirai!
Yami
Hikari
Everyone has their own strange habits.
He should just try to live with it.
No way!
The boss is at fault,
so he should tell him straight up.
But it's his boss.
It'll affect their relationship going forward.
Oh, get with the times.
That old-fashioned thinking
is what leads to harassment.
Well, you have a point, but still...
At this point, he should just
rip his boss's enter key out.
Wouldn't that be harassment in itself?
Akari! I'll leave the call to you!
Hello? Miss Mirai!
Sorry.
I'm back in action!
Welcome back.
Right!
Listen up, Takahashi!
This is just my suggestion, but...
What was that?
Did I hear a butt?
Cheer your boss on!
Ch-Cheer him on?
So he has to put up with the enter key sound?
No, not quite.
Slam!
First he'll listen carefully to his boss's typing.
Then when the boss smashes
the enter key, he'll shout!
"Nice enter!"
NICE
ENTER!!
Oh, good one!
The key is never missing a beat.
Without missing a single enter key press,
he'll respond with "Hey! Nice enter!
The best in Japan!" every time.
"That's why they call you Mr. Enter!"
How rousing!
And since you're just cheering him on,
you can't get in trouble.
But his boss will start getting embarrassed,
hearing that every time he presses enter.
That's true!
Yeah!
"He'll hear me!"
Eventually, the boss will start pressing
his enter key quietly, so Takahashi can't hear.
That's amazing! You're so smart!
This is how you survive modern society!
Darned super miracle enter key guys!
Ya gotta see this,
Akari!
Hinata's Heading to
School
I'm in the mood for construction today.
What should I do?
If I were to place blocks here to create a new park,
how would I do it?
I know!
I can hardly believe it!
Those overgrown weeds have been replaced
by a zen garden as beautiful as any in Kyoto!
The queen of the playground's pipe stack
has turned into a dazzling stage
worthy of the hottest boy band.
The hazardous, uneven ground
has been flattened out.
Thanks to those green landscapers,
this vacant plot has changed into a nice, relaxing park.
I want to be as great a landscaper someday.
Hinata's Heading to
School
Stand! Attention! Virtual Friends Are Watching!
La-di-da! La-di-da!
Oh, Tokino Sora! Have a seat!
I've had it up to here!
Barkeep, give me a shot of sushi trivia!
Coming right up.
Trivia, go!
Trivia
Oh, sushi.
Sushi
˩
Sushi has a long history,
dating back 1300 years to the Nara era.
The modern style of sushi
came about in the early 1800s,
and was called "Edomae sushi"
after the capital Edo, where it was sold in stands.
The people of Edo would stop by
to have a quick meal standing up.
It was truly the fast food of the Edo era.
Back then, the sushi were as large
as rice balls—too large for chopsticks,
Now
Edo Period
so people would eat with their hands,
a custom that remains today.
By the way, wasabi is called "tears" in sushi lingo,
as strong wasabi makes you tear up.
Wow, I didn't know about that.
I learn so much from your trivia!
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Siro Squad Member
Pen Name
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Siro Squad Member
Pen Name
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Friends
are
Watching
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Watching
Siro Squad Member
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Watching
Siro Squad Member
Pen Name
Virtual
Friends
are
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Siro Squad Member
Pen Name
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
I see the time has finally arrived.
My name is Watanabe Suzume,
also known as "Grisaille IV".
Tremble in fear before my hidden demonic powers.
Siro Squad Member
Pen Name
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Class Rep,
It's 3 O'Clock.
I wonder if Kaede has seen Kerin Slayer?
Burn down the dark elf's forest!
She's seen it, all right!
Do elves and dark elves live in different forests?
Elves aren't human, so who cares where they live?
Yeah, I guess so.
Now, let's get to today's Ultimate
Would-You-Rather committee.
Okay!
Today's agenda is...
AGENDA
Which
would
AGENDA
Which
would
AGENDA
Which
would
you
AGENDA
Which
would
you
Which
would
you
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
rather
have
?
Which would you rather have?
have
?
A: Immortality, but every year
is entrance exam year.
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
?
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
B: Five years remaining,
but you live every day in luxury.
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
Five years remaining, but you live every day in luxury
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
Five years remaining, but you live every day in luxury
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
Five years remaining, but you live every day in luxury
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
Five years remaining, but you live every day in luxury
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
Five years remaining, but you live every day in luxury
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
Five years remaining, but you live every day in luxury
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
Five years remaining, but you live every day in luxury
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
Five years remaining, but you live every day in luxury
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
Five years remaining, but you live every day in luxury
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
Five years remaining, but you live every day in luxury
AGENDA
Which
would
you
rather
have
?
Five years remaining, but you live every day in luxury
B for me, no question.
What? No question?
If I know when I'm dying,
I could focus on enjoying my final years.
You're fine with dying in five years?
Sure.
What? Don't tell me you want to die!
You have so much to live for!
A-And you?
I'd go with immortality,
but having to take entrance exams every year.
Why?
I mean, you could just fail every year.
I could get held back, like, 1030 years.
You'd be setting a Guinness world record.
Just like that.
That'd work, right?
But you'd have to keep living,
even if you're sick or having a bad time.
Is injury and pain all there is to life, in your eyes?
I mean, isn't life basically full of sad things?
"Basically"? How much?
About 80%.
80%? That much?
I mean, you have to work hard
every day to lead a fun life, right?
Whoa, don't get all deep on me.
It's my job to end the segment like that.
Don't jump the gun.
Do forgive me.
Oh, it's already 3 o'clock.
And with that, today's answer is
A: Immortality, but every year
is entrance exam year.
Answer
Immortality, but every year is entrance exam year
I dunno, that sounds like torture.
The longer you live, the more subscribers you get!
Class Rep,
It's 3 O'Clock.
Virtual Friends Are Watching.
Kaederon.
UNITY-CHAN LIKES TO ROLL AROUND
Unity-chan...
Okay!
It's time for Solving Your Problems on a Roll!
Let's get to your questions.
Hello?
Hi.
What problem do you have for me today?
Well, it's a bit of a scary one...
Oh?
I feel like there's someone in my room...
Like I'm being watched by someone...
Have you talked to the police?
What? The police...
Only later did she realize...
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Hoshikawa Sora
Pen Name
People of Earth, nice to meet you.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Hoshikawa Sora
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Friends
are
Watching
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Watching
Hoshikawa Sora
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Watching
Hoshikawa Sora
Pen Name
Virtual
Friends
are
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Hoshikawa Sora
Pen Name
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Hoshikawa Sora
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
I'm the virtual alien idol, Hoshikawa Sora.
Virtual friends are watching this week again.
Bye.
Hoshikawa Sora
Pen Name
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Previously, on Kerin Slayer
Previously, on Kerin Slayer.
Kerin Slayer
utysdjkcn
Kerin Slayer.
Hime, why are we on this snowy mountain?
It's so cold!
I heard Kerin is recuperating on this mountain.
Kerin survived?
We did bang him up pretty bad.
I brought him this to apologize.
That's... a photo of Elu?
Figure I'll give him this if we run into him.
Aren't you the kind one, Hime.
What's that noise?
You two!
Oh, there he is!
Hey there, remember us?
We're the Kerin Slayers, HimeHina!
Of course I remember!
You two got in the way of me and Elu's love!
Love?
Take this!
Smitheraga
Wait, wait, wait! We can talk this out!
It's too late for words!
Smitheraga
O-Oh no! The impact from that
would cause an avalanche!
Think of the poor bears!
Ancient spell: Deflectium Missileus!
Deflectium
Missileus
What? My missile!
It hit something.
Maybe it was a bird?
We're sorry!
Not the bird!
How dare you do that to my missile?!
Keblins!
Keblins everywhere!
Keb-keb! Keb-keb!
Kebab-kebab!
Wait, did one of them just say "kebab"?
What? Now I'm hungry!
Me too.
But this is bad.
Farewell, little girls.
Get them!
Please wait!
Please wait!!
Who are you?!
Please
Sister!
!
So, could you listen to me, Sister?
What troubles you, Mr. Horse?
Listen to this, Sister!
Well, you see—
What is it?
Between weekend laziness
and not being a morning person,
I often leave the house without makeup on.
I'd be embarrassed to run into someone I know,
but my laziness always wins.
Yes, I understand the feeling.
But you should probably
have more discipline about this.
You're right.
What should I do?
Why don't you put on a wrestling mask?
A wrestling mask?!
If you act like a masked wrestler
going about her day,
your friends won't realize it's you.
But I'd probably draw the attention
of the police instead.
In that case, you could put on a horse head mask.
It's not unusual to see horses
strolling around this town.
Oh, yeah!
I think I've seen one recently, too!
I'll give it a go!
The grace of V be with you.
Take care not to pass out in the summer!
Please
Sister!
!
Virtual Friends Are Watching!
Ubiba!
Now, let's answer some viewer mail.
From "Eternal Blizzard".
Thanks for writing!
"Don't you find street names cool?"
I sure do!
"What kind of street names
would you all give yourselves?"
Come up with
your own slogan
a "street name"
A street name, huh?
To Akari's clothing,
I'd like to add something to wear below.
To this V thing?
V thing!
I actually have thought of one for myself.
What, really?
My street name is...
the Walking Red Light District!
Walking Red Light District!
Oh dear.
The discussion went on for
almost 20 minutes
so we'll just cut to the final
street names
!
The discussion went on for
almost 20 minutes
so we'll just cut to the final
street names
!
The discussion went on for
almost 20 minutes
so we'll just cut to the final
street names
!
The discussion went on for
almost 20 minutes
so we'll just cut to the final
street names
!
The discussion went on for
almost 20 minutes
so we'll just cut to the final
street names
!
All right, I'll just go with "Walking Wedgie".
Walking Wedgie
Really?
Wedgie...
Bloody Snow?
Bloody Snow Dolphinator
Dolphinator.
Dolphinator?
Gigglebuns 119.
Gigglebuns 119
Oh, 119 for the fire department!
Belly Button Venus Dirty Otaku.
Belly Button Venus
Dirty Otaku
Belly Button Venus Dirty Otaku...
Weed-Munching Weaksauce Schoolgirl Centipede.
Weed-Munching Weaksauce
Schoolgirl Centipede
Stiff-Haired Pink Thug.
Stiff-Haired Pink Thug
"Stiff-Haired Pink Thug", got a nice ring to it.
All right, let's introduce ourselves to end the show.
Right!
You've just watched
"Walking Wedgie", Mirai Akari and...
"Bloody Snow Dolphinator", Cyber Girl Siro and...
"Gigglebuns 119", Tanaka Hime and...
"Bully Button Venus Dirty Otaku",
Suzuki Hina and...
"Weed-Munching Weaksauce
Schoolgirl Centipede", Tsukino Mito and...
"Stiff-Haired Pink Thug", Nekomiya Hinata!
Well, that's it for this week!
Tune in again next week for...
Virtual Friends Are Watching!
Hey, Human...
Tell us the secret of life!
Humanoid incarnation, celluloid imitation,
can't avoid obfuscation, reborn of illumination,
cardioid light creation, take the pain, become human
Inhuman simulacrums, sing their lives, sing this anthem
Sorry for existing? Don't be absurd
The shadow floating in the mirror would like to say a word:
"Go on and struggle like the humans that you're not
You're neither nor, just imperfect reflections, a shadow of a thought"
The shadow looks back at you, right in the eye
But what is it that you're seeing? Could it be a lie?
"Come on and join us, come on let's get wild"
A new world opens, calling out: voices, an alluring smile
Come our last, there we will find
the future of all humankind
The shadow that arises when we close our eyes,
whose reflection does it bring to mind?
You know we're not a doll!
We alight in this human world for one night
to watch as our imperfect forms meet their destinies
Hear us cry to humankind with all our might
Our drive for life is why we chose to be somebody
Feel this life—It's humanoid
Claiming our right, crying and fighting back
Feel this pain—It's humanoid
To ashes returning, violet-blue burning out
Us twisted humanoids
You know it's naughty virtual virtualize a life alive
Humanoid incarnation, celluloid imitation,
can't avoid obfuscation, reborn of illumination,
cardioid light creation, take the pain, become human
Inhuman simulacrums, sing their lives, sing this anthem
_
"Humanoid"
Her_
Here's_
Here's to_
Here's to th_
Here's to the A_
Here's to the Adva_
Here's to the Advance_
Here's to the Advancement_
Here's to the Advancement of_
Here's to the Advancement of Vi_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtu_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual _
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual Sub_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual Subcul_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual Subculture_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual Subculture
Tsukiyo Sora
Hello folks, this is Tsukiyo Sora.
Muscle pain is the taste of youth,
and menthol the smell of your first love.
Go to a warm caffeine room to experience
something bittersweet in the evening.
They're all bitter yet sweet memorial events.
Now, my youthful days live eternally
in this virtual reality space,
never fading, even in my old age.
Huh? You have no idea what I'm saying?
Well, neither do I.
But apparently there's one thing
I have to say, so I'll just end on this.
Next time: "The soul of an
ever-changing grandmother."
Next time:
"The soul of an ever-changing grandmother."
Virtual friends will be watching next week, too.