Did you know cucumbers have fewer
calories than any other vegetable?
Yes, yes, yes, yes! What about carrots?
I'm talking about cucumbers here,
you horse bastard!
Yes, yes!
466... 467... Feel the burn!
Let's all strike a bodybuilder pose today!
Here we go! One, two...
Virtual Friends Are Watching!
I want more, I want more, such a wonderful surprise
Hey who says, hey who says, I've had enough?
All I see is like a dream that goes on and on and on
Pittery pattery and away!
Ready, and!
Come on and clap, and play this melody
But how come? But how come?
Who needs a reason why?
To all the ha-ha-ha-ha-happy folks at home,
I blow one, I blow two naughty smooches to you
Hey, we can keep on keep on going, don't stop!
Dizzy tizzy waiting for my smashing debut
Splishing splashing showering with love raindrops
AI love AI love AI love
I want more, I want more, such a wonderful surprise
Hey who says, hey who says, I've had enough?
All I see is like a dream that goes on and on and on
And to you, and to you, how are you?
Here we go!
Ready, and!
AI AI AI
M-More more more
A-AI AI AI
Virtual Friends Are Watching!
I'm sorry about last week...
Just don't make any more weird devices, okay?
Have either of you seen the president?
Uh, Kaede?
We detected life out in space earlier,
so she went to check it out.
Ow...
President, what's wrong?
I found something I'm not sure was dead or alive,
and it bit me.
President, you're hurt?
We must see to it at once!
It's a very light wound, so I'm probably fi—
Kaede?
President!
What?!
Hey!
P-President!
Kaede, no!
Not my neck!
The president is eating Pinky!
Harutrash...
Ryo! Retreat!
Something's wrong with the president and Pinky!
Ryo...
Haru, help me!
President, stay away!
Please, I said no...
Dammit!
Is this some kind of pandemic?!
At this rate, the Game Club will be annihilated!
Harutrash...!
Chomp
Game
Club
Zombie
Now we're all happy and zombified.
I thought we'd go all mindless, but guess not.
Yeah, really.
If anything, aren't we unstoppable
now that we're immortal?
You're right.
Looking good for the camera, guys!
That's what I call a Cut of the Dead!
There goes the president
hopping on the latest bandwagon...
I wanna do the Thriller together!
Pinky, nice idea...
All right! Time to dance our way past enemy lines!
The quest for galactic conquest continues...
The Game Club's quest for
galactic conquest is far from over!
Virtual Grandmother!
Sunpo Nankou.
Today's Expression
Sunpo Nankou
It's a Japanese expression.
It refers to not being able to move an inch.
Being unable to move is an extreme way to put it,
but moving from place to place
was much harder back in the day.
That is, back when our road infrastructure
was just getting underway.
There was constant roadwork,
which meant gaping holes all over the place.
In terms of walking, what surprised
me the most when I came to Tokyo in 1964,
was women in high heels.
Granted, the roads were in better
shape than in the countryside.
In Niigata, where I'm from,
construction still hadn't started,
so there were no smooth roads at all.
Coming from such a place to Tokyo,
I couldn't believe anyone
could walk in high heels at all.
However, as Virtual Grandmother,
I can move freely, no matter how old I get.
Yes, indeed. Just watch!
Oh, I can move vertically too, no problem.
Three, two, one, blast off!!
Fly, Sachiko!
Virtual Friends Are Watching!
I thought we were goners for sure!
It's wonderful to be alive!
Oh yeah, did you guys see
the animal special on TV yesterday?
Yeah, I did!
The chimpanzees were so cute!
The cats from the cat special were cute too!
I liked the penguins!
I know! How about we all go to the zoo together?
Good idea!
I want to go!
Oh no!
What's happening?
That scared me!
What was that tremor?
Hold on.
Isn't it eerily quiet?
There's not a sound coming from outside!
You're right!
I can't hear the wind, or anything else!
C-Could this be...
P-People,
could this be...
The bottom of the sea?!
Why are we at the bottom of the sea?!
But, hey, if you think about it, we still have air.
And the lights are still on,
so do we really need to panic?
Maybe we'll go back if we just wait!
You're watching
Let's Go! Classroom
You're right! Let's just wait here
until the classroom is back to normal.
You know, I had no idea the deep sea was like this.
You'd never get to dive this deep,
so this is kinda fun!
Oh!
It's a penguin!
What? A penguin? Where?!
You're right! It's so cute!
It may be cute, but...
You're watching
Let's Go! Classroom
Deep sea penguins sure are large.
Huh? Wait, it's huge! Too huge!
Look, it's opening its mouth!
I'm coming for you now!
Not you again!
Come on, Hina, you like penguins!
Do something about this!
Oh god, oh god, oh god!
What?! The penguins I like aren't this huge!
It's gonna eat us!
To be continued
Thank you for calling.
You have reached Virtual Friends Are Watching.
This'll do it.
When Gorry goes for the banana,
I'll pull the string and trap him.
I can't wait!
Yo, yo, Gorilla's coming into view!
The forest's sage is coming through!
Raise your hands, you too!
Reachin' the next level here at the zoo!
Huh?
Right.
Hell, you can even shrink?
Fuji!
Fuji Aoi Park
Aoi.
Right.
Ya gotta see this!
Ya gotta see this, Akari!
Akari, ya gotta see this!
What's wrong, Hime?
We got a letter from a "Yumerin",
who's having trouble!
Oh?
Here, give this a read!
Let's see...
Hello, Akari.
Hello.
Hello!
I'm currently thinking about quitting my job.
Oh, really?
My boss treats me awfully and there's
so much overtime that every day is a struggle.
But I feel like quitting would be
admitting defeat! What should I do?
Wow, that's serious!
To        or not to
quit
What's a good solution?
Good question. I wonder...
Huh? Hey, Miss Mirai?
Miss Mirai!
Yami
Hikari
I think she should quit.
Her own well-being takes priority over anything.
But just quitting is a bit boring.
She should take revenge.
Revenge?
Put an incriminating photo in his drawer.
Wait, this sounds familiar.
Or have Chono slap him.
Oh, that's from that TV show!
I'll leave the rest for Akari to decide.
Bye.
Do the right thing, Akari!
Hello? Hello?
Miss Mirai!
S-Sorry, I was lost in my own world.
Good morning.
Listen up, Yumerin!
This is just my suggestion, but...
What was that?
Did I hear a butt?
Change jobs to a company that runs a hookup app!
Change jobs?!
Then search for a girl who your boss would like!
Match
Found!
What?!
Then, hire a private investigator!
Wh-Why? Why?
Set the boss up with the girl,
and have the PI tail them.
Have the PI take photos of them going out,
House of Secrets
and send the scandalous photos
to your boss's family!
What? That's terrifying!
That way you can take revenge on your boss,
while also getting a new job.
Akari, you're a genius!
You know it.
Amazing!
But, you know, if they get married after hooking up,
won't that just make the boss a lucky
old man who scored a young chick?
That's true.
But if that happens, we'll call in Chono.
Okay, got it!
Let me go and catch us a Chono, then!
Um, wait, Tanaka.
You're getting a little ahead of yourself!
Ya gotta see this,
Akari!
Hinata's Heading to
School
This vacant lot is actually pretty big.
Here we are...
This is bad.
On closer inspection,
this place is surrounded by buildings.
What if the building behind me,
the houses on either side,
and just across the road were full of enemies?
I mustn't run away. I mustn't run away.
I mustn't run away!
This isn't enough to bring me down!
Ah, now I feel like playing video games.
I know!
I'll skip school today and head home.
Hinata!
Ah! Akari! What are you doing there?
You can't just skip school!
This pipe is my turf!
What?!
I have to ink it!
Come on, let's head to school already.
Wait!
Hinata's Heading to
School
Yay! Virtual Friends Are Watching!
La-di-da! La-di-da!
Oh, Aoi! Have a seat!
I've had it up to here.
Barkeep, give me a shot of candy trivia.
Coming right up.
Trivia, go!
Trivia
Oh, candy.
Candy
˩
There's one candy you probably know of
that was invented in Germany
to prevent tooth disorders.
It was 1920, a time when few foods
in Germany required intensive chewing,
so many children suffered from tooth disorders.
So in order to strengthen children's
jaw muscles and prevent disorders,
they developed a firm candy, which they called...
gummies.
The name comes from the German "gummi",
which means rubber.
By the way, giving someone gummies on White Day
means "I hate you," so take care.
Wow, really?
I learn so much from your trivia.
BREAKING
THE SUDDEN APPEARANCE OF A CITY
THE MASSES ROAMING THE STREETS
TITANS
TRANSFORMATION
THE SECRETS OF THE OPENING WILL BE REVEALED!
COMING SOON!!
Class Rep,
It's 3 O'Clock.
I've got a bad feeling today.
Something tells me I shouldn't open this door.
Ow, my ears! Mugi, calm down!
Watch those decibels!
It's just, I was so scared and all alone,
then you suddenly opened the door...
I scared you? I'm sorry.
But this is the Ultimate Would-You-Rather
Committee. Are you ready?
Yes!
Today's agenda is...
Which would you rather eat for the rest of your life?
AGENDA
What
would
AGENDA
What
would
AGENDA
What
would
AGENDA
What
would
you
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rather
eat
for the
of your
rest
life
of your
rest
life
?
rest
of your
life
?
rest
of your
life
?
rest
of your
life
?
rest
life
?
A: Meat.
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
B: Weeds.
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
Weeds
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
Weeds
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
Weeds
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
Weeds
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
Weeds
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
Weeds
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
eat
for the
rest
of your
life
?
Meat
Weeds
Option B is referring to you, isn't it?
Well, I did eat some as a
curious elementary schooler,
but I've grown out of that.
So, which would you prefer?
I think I'd have to go with meat.
I dream of living a long life,
and did you know?
What?
Setouchi Jakucho eats 800 grams of meat every day
and has lived to be 95!
Yes, I guess she's living proof.
Yes, really!
But Mugi, you've never eaten weeds, right?
Huh? Well, no, I haven't.
It's important to try new things, you know.
Or are shut-ins just as conservative as they say?
No, that's not true!
It's already 3 o'clock!
It was a tough choice for me, too,
but the answer's clearly B!
Answer
Weeds
But weeds don't taste good!
What?
Do you want to eat meat?
I do!
You know, it's obvious those were crocodile tears.
But it gets everyone to feel sorry for me!
This girl...
Well, everyone, try eating the weeds
growing around your house!
It'll really spice up your life!
Class Rep,
It's 3 O'Clock.
Virtual Friends Are Watching.
UNITY-CHAN LIKES TO ROLL AROUND
Unity-chan!
Hey guys!
Ootori Kohaku here!
Today I'll show you how cool I am!
This is a huge port warehouse I got from Dad!
It's my personal playground!
There's a bunch of stuff here that I've collected!
Like this, or this.
And this, and I like this one!
Also this... one... here!
Isn't it awesome?
But why?
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Pen Name:
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
are
Pen Name:
Ruruno Rulu
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Friends
Watching
are
Everybody's
Friends
are
Watching
Ruruno Rulu
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Watching
Friends
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Ruruno Rulu
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Everybody's
Ruruno Rulu
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Watching
Pen Name:
Ruruno Rulu
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
are
Watching
Everybody's
are
Watching
Pen Name:
Ruruno Rulu
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Friends
are
Watching
Pen Name:
Ruruno Rulu
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Pen Name:
Ruruno Rulu
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Pen Name:
Ruruno Rulu
Saotome Miko
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Suzuki Miyano
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Pen Name:
Nadasaki Toru
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Pen Name:
Sanbi
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Pen Name:
Kishitsurone
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Pen Name:
Turtleneck Maniac
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Shinonome Kizuna
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Pen Name:
Vortex
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Pen Name:
Maron
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Previously, on Kerin Slayer:
Previously, on Kerin Slayer
Elu!
Right!
Kerin Slayer
utysdjkcn
Kerin Slayer.
Why?!
It's a gorilla! He's so cute!
Right?
Did Elu turn into a gorilla?
Don't be stupid.
There's... There's no way
my Elu could turn this furry!
Helu-elu-o!
I'm Elu, the lone and enlightened
beauty from the land of elves.
Right!
Stop that!
Stop
that!
Keblins, take this gorilla away!
Keb-keb-keb!
What are you doing?
I only just got out!
Wait!
Let the gorilla have his say!
Let's hear it, you gorilla.
You know, bananas are often
thought to grow on trees,
An herb
but those are actually herbs.
Also, did you know they're technically berries?
Berries... berries... berries...
berries... berries...
Take him away!
Right!
Dammit!
What a monkey wrench in the works!
My plan to free Elu,
make her fall for me, destroy the world,
and create our own Garden of Eden is ruined!
Wait!
So you really were plotting evil!
You little ponpoko-pon!
You're the ponpoko-pon here!
Go, keblins!
Keb-keb!
Hao!
Hao-hao!
They keep coming!
Ah! Hina, look out!
Keb!
N-No, stop!
Don't touch my belly button!
Time to finish you off!
I'll blow you both away!
Oh no!
Super-Ultra Ultimate:
Smitheraga!
Hime, this is bad!
SMITHERAGA
It's the final level of Smithereens, Smitheraga!
Sounds like something out
of a certain fantasy franchise!
What do we do?!
I didn't think it would come down to this...
Extreme protection spell:
Gorillaga!
Gorillaga
ga
la
Gorillaga
ga
ril
la
Gorillaga
ril
ga
Gorillaga
Go
ril
ga
Gorillaga
Go
la
ga
Gorillaga
Go
la
ga
Gorillaga
ril
la
Gorillaga
Go
ril
Gorillaga
Go
ril
Gorillaga
Go
SMITHERAGA
Ri-ight!
Right!
No way!
Why must you get in my way, you gorilla?!
You'll regret this!
Phew, that was close.
Yeah.
Oh, Hina!
Let's go get banana shakes!
Oh, I like that idea.
Bananas are herbs, you know!
Right! Bananas! Right!
That's cute.
Kerin Slayer
utysdjkcn
To be continued
Please
Sister!
!
Please listen this time, Sister.
What troubles you, Mr. Horse?
Forgive me Sister, for I have s—
Listen to this, Sister!
What is it?
I lent a book to a friend,
but I still haven't gotten it back.
It's too awkward to just say,
"Give it back." What should I do?
How about asking your friend to give it back
because someone else wants to borrow it?
I actually already tried that,
but my friend waved it off with a vague apology.
Then, why not write a letter?
What? Would someone that flippant
bother with reading my letter?
No,
not to your friend, but to their parents.
The parents?!
Have their parents ask your friend.
I'm sure this will make them
give up and return the book.
Okay!
I'm off to buy a writing set!
The grace of V be with you.
I was the one who borrowed it, Sister!
Please
Sister!
!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Virtual Friends Are Watching, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Now, let's answer some viewer mail.
From "Tom is a Pen".
Thank you for writing!
Okay!
"Lately I can't stop playing video games.
Tell us about your favorite games!
Without using the letter 'e'!"
Why?
Topic
Talk about your
favorite games
No letter "E"
Topic
Talk about your
favorite games
No letter "E"
And... Start!
Today's Topic:
Fav. Games (No 'E')
Gong!
An activity... I fancy.
Games!
Game
Tanaka!
Oh wait, I gotta keep count!
No, wait!
Oh, you said "keep"!
Keep
We're not even trying here!
I'm fond of visual books.
Ah, visual books!
A visual book I'm playing now is cool.
On that topic, do you usually binge—
Uh, I didn't say anything...
Ah, bang!
Do you usually bang?
Binge
Bang...
No, wait!
Akari, stop!
It's not that kind of game!
You said "game", Mito! You said "game"!
Game
This is a mess!
Well, that's it for this week!
Tune in again next week for...
Virtual Friends Are Watching!
Back to camera
because she lost
Hey, Human...
Tell us the secret of life!
Humanoid incarnation, celluloid imitation,
can't avoid obfuscation, reborn of illumination,
cardioid light creation, take the pain, become human
Inhuman simulacrums, sing their lives, sing this anthem
Sorry for existing? Don't be absurd
The shadow floating in the mirror would like to say a word:
"Go on and struggle like the humans that you're not
You're neither nor, just imperfect reflections, a shadow of a thought"
The shadow looks back at you, right in the eye
But what is it that you're seeing? Could it be a lie?
"Come on and join us, come on let's get wild"
A new world opens, calling out: voices, an alluring smile
Come our last, there we will find
the future of all humankind
The shadow that arises when we close our eyes,
whose reflection does it bring to mind?
You know we're not a doll!
We alight in this human world for one night
to watch as our imperfect forms meet their destinies
Hear us cry to humankind with all our might
Our drive for life is why we chose to be somebody
Feel this life—It's humanoid
Claiming our right, crying and fighting back
Feel this pain—It's humanoid
To ashes returning, violet-blue burning out
Us twisted humanoids
You know it's naughty virtual virtualize a life alive
Humanoid incarnation, celluloid imitation,
can't avoid obfuscation, reborn of illumination,
cardioid light creation, take the pain, become human
Inhuman simulacrums, sing their lives, sing this anthem
_
"Humanoid"
Her_
Here's_
Here's to_
Here's to th_
Here's to the A_
Here's to the Adva_
Here's to the Advance_
Here's to the Advancement_
Here's to the Advancement of_
Here's to the Advancement of Vi_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtu_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual _
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual Sub_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual Subcul_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual Subculture_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual Subculture
Roboco
Hellobot!
I'm the super high-spec robot VTuber, Roboco!
I'm sure anyone with glasses
knows they tend to fog up.
Like when going inside on a cold day,
when you're wearing a face mask,
or when drinking hot coffee.
Oh?
I guess it'd be a complete mess
if you drank coffee with a mask on!
Did someone just call me a toaster?
Next time: "Life's Easier When
You Stop and Eat the Weeds!"
Next time:
"Life's Easier When You Stop and Eat the Weeds!"
Virtual friends will be watching next week, too!