Everyone thinks and everyone lives
Good morning to you, cock-a-doodle-doo!
Luluco
You just have to accept that everything is simply weird
All of your dreams can come true
Alpha-Omega
Nova
Both the big-brained and the bird-brained
Are saying "nice to meet you," cock-a-doodle-doo!
Midori
Suddenly you pretend to be a lantern
And throw important information at me
I'm going now, so get ready, future!
SPACE PATROL LULUCO
I'm Luluco.
A job,
my first love,
and Ogikubo...
I've got it all!
Now I can go back to normal life on Earth!
Wow, this is the greatest feeling ever!
Nova!
Yeah, it's the greatest.
My, oh, my...
Thank you.
N-Nova?
Yo, what? The heck is goin' on?
What?!
The Space Patrol Galaxy Commander-in-Chief
was actually a Blackholeian?
What? He's from the app?
No, from what it's based on.
You could say it's the root
of all evil in this universe!
I appreciate the compliment.
You are quite right.
I am a Blackholeian who has
taken over the Space Patrol's HQ.
Whaddya think yer doing?!
You betrayed us, Nova?
That's right.
Hey, B-hole!
It's Blackholeian.
Quit abbreviating everything,
you stupid middle schooler.
What did ya do to Luluco?
What are ya even after?
Allow me to give you a brief yet in-depth lesson, you stupid still-in-education schoolgirl.
Blackholeian Lecture
Space Shoplifting Seminar 1
~What Should We Steal Now~
Lesson 1 of 13
We Blackholeians kept shoplifting
everything of value in this universe
and became black holes.
How evil!
As if Ogikubo has any value!
Shut up and look at page two
of the handout, stupid.
Once it reaches a certain technological level,
all intelligent life in this universe
will create a cultural hotspot like Ogikubo
and have it shoplifted by me...
You stupid middle schooler! Falling asleep
as soon as things get even slightly complicated!
A stupid middle schooler who grows
10cm in a year might not understand,
but the most valuable thing in this universe...
is Ogikubo.
You have my thanks, stupid middle schooler
who eats nothing but sweet bread,
for fostering such a wonderful Aflutter Jewel.
Aflutter Jewel?
Please turn to page three of the handout.
The least valuable thing in the universe;
a thing born in Ogikubo, the most valuable...
That is the Aflutter Jewel.
Wait, ya old B-hole.
Don't ya only lift things of value?
I'll tell you this, stupid middle schooler
who tears the hems of her own tracksuit.
We Blackholeians have shoplifted
all kinds of things that hold value.
But because we shoplifted
too many valuable things,
we instead ended up wondering if worthless
garbage was actually more valuable.
"Huh? We made light of this stuff until now,
but maybe it's actually amazing!"
After taking several laps around the universe,
we truly came to believe that.
And we realized that a reckless,
ignorant middle schooler's foolish first love
was the most worthless,
trashy garbage in the universe.
That is what creates this Aflutter Jewel.
It's marvelous how completely
unattractive and uninteresting it looks.
Its utter uselessness
actually makes me want it!
So that thing is Luluco's shitty first love?
Nova...
Nova!
Fostered by a genuinely normal girl,
it's not at all lopsided or unbalanced...
It's a thoughtless and especially flat first love.
Nova?
Ah, how wonderful is the colorless
and transparent emotion of a fool!
It's not special at all!
It's totally hollow!
Zero truly is the most valuable,
and the void is what fuels black holes.
Enslaving Nova and sending him
to Ogikubo was the right call.
A job well done, Nothingling Alpha-Omega Nova!
Nova's a Nothingling?!
What's that now?
Nothinglings are hollow, shallow beings
hailing from a planet that has nothing.
For real?
No wonder our conversations felt so empty.
The first love of a stupid middle schooler
is a boy who is nothing but his looks.
This is the pinnacle of worthlessness!
The Nothing!
H-How cruel...
That's so cruel.
You tricked me?
It was all a lie?
I never once lied to you.
Nova, I loved you...
I loved you so much!
I'll never forgive you!
I don't mind either way.
Alpha-Omega Nova, it seems you were
the beginning and the end for her.
Look, your words just now finished her off.
She's dead.
Luluco?
First you shoplift it,
and now you destroy it yourself?
Why'd ya even steal it, then?
He makes no sense.
True evil is often terrifyingly incomprehensible.
Luluco...
Did she actually die?
We should probably stuff
something up her nostrils.
I hear Earthlings discharge
something when they die.
"Something"?
Something, Midori.
Quit sayin' creepy things, ya little shit.
Guess I'll stuff some tissues in there.
So, what're we gonna do about this?
She died for justice while acting
as part of the Space Patrol.
She died in the line of duty!
We'll have to hold a funeral, then.
Man, I died.
I came to the end of the universe,
got betrayed by Nova,
had the flutter of my heart in love shoplifted,
and died a pathetic death.
It's all over.
Never to be continued.
Going from one planet to the next
Going from one place to another
I'm broadcasting my feelings of love to you, beep, beep
So please receive them!
They float gently
In this endless universe
I've locked on to that heart of yours
So you will never be able to run away
I want you to hold my hand
To make my head spin like a merry-go-round
To make my heart skip a beat
The world will be dyed in the colors of my love