We've come a really long way by believing in ourselves
Even the most impossible dreams can come true
Luluco
Humanity and their lives depend only on them!
We learned that only waiting doesn't lead to anything
Alpha-Omega
Nova
Now it's time to see the greatest outcomes with our own eyes
Midori
There's nothing better than experiencing it ourselves
So let's go! Keep trying our best!
You are the future!
SPACE PATROL LULUCO
I'm Luluco.
I was living in Ogikubo,
the most abnormal town on Earth,
until it was shoplifted
by my space pirate mother.
When my Space Patrol father's brain met her,
they had a heated spat, things went
horribly wrong, and the warp gate distorted,
which made space you-know-what
and teleported us somewhere!
We have to find Ogikubo
and my father's body somehow!
Wake up, Luluco.
Luluco...
Nova!
Ba-dump!
Your face is super close to mine!
A-Are you gonna go all the way and...
Space ethics have gone to the dogs!
That's why a pirate like Lalaco
could sneak into Ogikubo so easily,
and why space auctions have
become a sea of lawlessness!
It's because order in this
universe is in disarray!
The idea of self-policing and upholding
the law has been lost to this generation!
Justice...
Yes!
I say what we lack is love
that transcends generations!
Looks like it was impossible for
his brain to stay active on its own.
What even happened, anyway?
Where's Dad's body? Where's Mom?
Where's Ogikubo?
And where are we?
What's that planet?
Your father's body is with
your space pirate mother.
And it looks like she was sent flying
somewhere by the warp gate's distortion.
It seems the distorted warp gate
did a number on us and Ogikubo, too.
We must find Ogikubo as soon as possible!
But indeed, what is that planet?
I think I've been there once before...
Probably this?
Thread-Ball Planet: KLK-X.
That's it!
Apparently it's the closest
Ogikubo from our location.
What?!
Closest? There are multiple Ogikubos?
Thread-Ball Planet KLK-X
That's Ogikubo, you say?
Ogilog
by Goose
It's authentic Ogikubo!
Fresh new Ogikubo collection!
Most efficient Ogikubo!
Safe and secure Ogikubo!
But if space Ogikubo user review site
Ogilog says so, it must be true.
"The junction of destiny,
Thread-Ball Planet KLK-X.
The universe's biggest tourism hub,
everybody visits it at least once."
What's more, it says they got
some fresh Ogikubo recently.
Seriously? We gotta go now.
Ogikubo? Here? You're kidding me, right?
A 3.5-star review means
it's basically the real thing.
Let's go!
Uh, when are we going back to Earth—
Oh, right. Ogikubo vanished
from the face of Earth!
Luluco, we have to look for
our home so we can go back.
They really are selling Ogikubo.
This is pretty well-made.
Nah, it's probably a knock-off.
Could Ogikubo really be here?
Wow, this is scarily accurate!
It's almost like the real deal!
Look, it's Hand-Kneaded Ramen No. 18!
An OGKB Must-Visit
Hand-Kneaded Ramen No. 18
Harujuya
And there's Harujuya and O-naga Chinese Soba!
O-naga Chinese Soba
Harujuya
They even have a Tabibito no Eda!
O-naga Chinese Soba
Tabibito no Eda
Ogikubo Ramen Street really was here!
But is it me, or is it kinda different
from the Ogikubo I know?
Hey, Nova.
O-naga Chinese Soba
Huh? Guys?
Oh, there you are, Nova!
O-naga Chinese Soba
Tabibito no Eda
It's me you want.
Huh? Wh-What are you saying out of the blue?!
You and I are bound by the thread of fate.
Uh, where's this coming—
What?! Is this really the thread of fate?!
You, I, and everybody else...
We're all connected.
I'm a Kill-**-Killian.
To each of you, I have taken the
appearance of your heart's desire.
Your powerful desires
will feed us space life fibers
and provide us energy.
And let me tell you two useful
pieces of information.
What? He looks like the person we desire most?
First: We've made this planet, which has good
Space Feng Shui vibes, into a tourism hub,
So the person we love?
Who is Nova seeing, then?
I can't tell!
and feed on 1 in every 100 people
so that we don't get caught.
Does he like me?
Or someone else?!
Oh, shut up and go away! Nobody cares!
This way, we don't have to go
out of our way to seek living—
Space Crime Detected
Oh, this is a space crime?
Uh, you're under arrest for
some kind of space fraud!
SOME KIND
OF
SPACE FRAUD
CAUGHT
RED
HANDED
Awaken: Judgment Gun Mo-Mo-Mo—
Huh? I can't complete the Gun Morphing?!
Aren't these threads? Why can't they be cut?
Second: Nobody can ever free
themselves from these life fibers.
Because unless you use a scissor-like
thing made of super-hard life fibers
to cut them from both sides at once,
they'll keep regenerating!
Ju... stice!
Hot!
What do you think you're doing?!
Oh crap!
My hands are made of threads, too!
HANDS
MADE
OF
THREADS
Oh, I get it. Life fibers are threads,
so they're highly flammable.
H-Huh? So it actually was a knock-off?
Guys, this planet is a hotbed of space crime!
What?! Men, Judgment Gun Morphing!
Roger!
Awaken: Judgment Gun Morphing!
You're under arrest for some kind of
space crush gib energy pl0x huehue scam!
SPACE CRUSH
GIB ENERGY PLOX
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
SPACE CRUSH
HUE HUE
SCAM
If I'm going to be burned
by you snot-nosed brats,
I'd rather burn myself!
Thread!
THREAD
"STRIPPED"
OF THE
WILL
TO FIGHT!
"Stripped" of the will to fight!
Oh, no! It's a planetary wildfire!
Run away at once!
Run! Run!
Guts!
Damn, this is hot!
Our feelings for Ogikubo ended
up creating that town, huh?
It's hot!
It can still get even hotter!
It can still burn hotter! Ah, so hot!
Yeah. So it wasn't the real Ogikubo.
So hot!
But eating the desires of people?
That's kinda scary.
Maybe he was
lonely due to spending all that
time in space all by himself.
Hotter... Hotter...
It keeps burning hotter!
And maybe the hunger in his heart
Hotter and hotter...
I'm not dead yet!
could only be satisfied by love.
Everyone, can you hear me?
Don't forget me, please!
I don't really get it yet.
But this will continue, right?
Yeah. It is to be continued.
I'm searching the entire galaxy for you
Going from one planet to the next
I'm broadcasting my feelings of love to you, beep, beep
So please receive them!
They float gently
In this endless universe
I've locked on to that heart of yours
So you will never be able to run away
I want you to hold my hand
To make my head spin like a merry-go-round
To make my heart skip a beat
The world will be dyed in the colors of my love