Cocona...
You're always hard on yourself
Claiming that you're just a tool
And that's why
I've got you in my arms
Even if the world suddenly became unrecognizable
I'm confident I can be anything if I'm with you
mas
shi
ro
na
Let's search
Till we find some snow white dreams
bou
ke
n
ga
Our adventures
Will color in all of those lines
ma
ji
wa
ru
Blending
Slipping
Changing into
A future, calling out
Don't you dare miss it
We're always together no matter how far apart
I won't let go of this heart that draws me to you
Those are some long limbs.
Did she run away from somewhere?
She's awake.
Hey, do you understand us?
Think we can sell this?
Cocona?
That's...
Elder!
Wait!
Sorry.
They're all scared because they've
never seen anyone like you before.
You won't try to scare them?
No.
It's empty.
More!
Everyone gets a meager share
of our underground water.
People who grow our crops, cook our food,
or wash our clothing get more as needed, however.
Thank you for saving me.
It's somewhat poisonous, so don't ingest too much.
Where are you from, Papika?
Somewhere far away.
I'm looking for Cocona and the others.
Cocona?
I got separated from them.
I've been searching a long time for her,
but I can't find her scent at all.
I saw a shooting star a few days ago.
I made a wish, and then it split into two.
Maybe that was you guys, and...
Which way did Cocona go?
Er...
I only have potatoes,
but if you'd like...
Potatoes?!
Tch. If it isn't the desert's sphincter.
Give us all yer water an' yer grub!
Quick-like, you slugs!
Now that's livin'!
O-Our water!
Please, have mercy.
We barely have enough to get by...
Quiet, old one!
Drop dead!
One less mouth to suckle on his mother's teat.
You sow!
Who's this brass-balled bitch?!
Papika.
G-Girl...
Papika? Where's yer pack then?!
What a nonsense name!
I think it's cute. Sounds kinda like "puppy".
Ain't that right, Puppy-chan?
Shake!
Let's try again... Shake!
Sit.
Schlanger! She's cooked!
Don't piss yer dacks!
Lady Cocona!
She's all yers, Lady Cocona!
Cocona?
No! That mask...
Cocona...
No, you're not.
You...
I hate you!
Milady!
Papika!
We must go after her.
Who are you?
Why'd you attack the village?
Those are Cocona's clothes!
Where is Cocona?!
That's the Illusory Divine Fist!
You know it, Elder?
Watch closely.
We are about to witness what you could call
Milady!
the secret foundation of our very world—
the Dance of Miracles.
Give back Cocona!
This scent...
Don't lose, Papika!
Fight, Puppy!
Fight!
Is it you, Cocona?
Found you.
Papika!
R-Real flower-like, ain't she?
Move it!
Whoa!
Papika! Papika!
What have I...
Cocona?
Found you...
Papika!
What, done already?
What a letdown.
I knew it.
Who's that?!
Another flower!
Me
It's you...
I'm glad you remember me.
Is this...
Pure Illusion?
Bu-chan, where's Papika?
Papika! Papika!
Where did she run off to now?
When I find her, she's really going to get it.
Me
women
Bu-chan!
Sorry, it seems my foot slipped.
I don't—
think so.
Are you looking for a friend?
I'll help you meet her.
Why did you do it?
I was bored.
I wanted you two to play with me.
That's it? That's why you
brainwashed me and hurt Papika?
You're the one who hurt her, Cocona.
You can probably still feel her blood
on your knuckles, right?
How did it feel?
Did hurting Papika make you feel better?
Huh?
All that mask does
is amplify the feelings you already have.
Cocona, deep down,
you must have wanted to hurt Papika.
All I did was give you a push.
Hey, sow!
Let our lady go!
Filthy worms.
Run for it!
Shh!
How cute.
How pitiful.
The mask's power only possessed
you because you're empty.
Oh, Papika-san!
Puppy...
You're so lacking in identity that you
couldn't stay in control of yourself.
There's nothing there.
It probably felt good playing the villain, didn't it?
You truly are a natural.
You have ambition, don't you?
You want to be somebody, don't you?
If you come with me, I'll make you somebody.
No.
Oh?
Too bad.
I'll just take your fragment, then.
Cocona!
漢
Heroic
Cocona.
Papika? How?
I ate a potato.
Potato?
It was warm and sweet, so I got all shiny!
Shiny?
Say "ahh."
Ahh.
Make sure to swallow!
Cocona, after you?
Yeah.
Transform!
TRANSFORM
My passionate feelings will repel all things!
Pure Barrier!
Cut and slice and shear all things foul!
Pure Blade!
Evil flower of Pure Illusion...
We shall pluck you!
That's the Lively Tater for you.
They're very lively now.
Now this is a real fight!
It'll take more than that!
It's two against one, after all!
Papika Hundred Raging Waves!
Cocona Flash Rending Slash!
It hurts...
but it's so much fun!
I think it's about time I got serious.
What is that?
It's huge!
I'm scared!
It showed its true form.
She's gone.
Yeah.
Behind you! Behind you!
My!
Ow...
Now's our chance!
Yeah.
Papika!
Yeah!
Here we go!
Full power!
We did it.
All right!
What in the world was that?
Sorry for hitting you, Papika.
It's okay. I punched and kicked you, too.
And I said I hated you...
But I love you.
Uh-huh.
It's true! I love, love, love you!
Gee, thanks.
Listen to me! I love, love, love, love, love, love—
Shut up.
Wow...
U-Uh, thank you—
You're too naïve.
You can't traverse Pure Illusion like that.
Yayaka?!
Why?
Hey, don't take that!
It's only fair, isn't it?
We're the ones who finished it off.
No!
How did you transform?
Tell us.
Cocona!
Let's go. We got the amorphous.
Roger.
Your hole looked like it was pretty high up.
Good luck getting back.
Bye-bye.
Hold it, Yayaka!
Papika!
What was that?
The girl just now?
Yes.
So that's Papikana...
One half of the Direct Drive.
Asclepius. Asclepius.
Only a few amorphous remain.
All for our glorious world.
Ow!
Ouch...
Salt!
Yayaka was... This weird bunch was...
Stabilize the impedance.
We'll talk after that.
Hey, Salt!
They're coming directly at us now.
Look at them!
Trying to show us they can walk around so freely!
Even if we try to collect fragments...
We'd just be sitting ducks.
Dr. Salt.
There is a way.
ko
sso
ri
so
cchi
One day I thought I would sneak a peek at you,
so
cchi
mo
ko
cchi
But there you were, looking back at me
I went and fell deep inside your eyes
Lost, I thought, "Now, where could I have gone?"
When I hold your hands, enclosed in mine,
Oh so soft, like a lamb freshly sheared
And I knew, I just knew, without a reason why
That you felt the same way as me
I saw it there as you tried to wipe them off,
drip
ping
tears
Someone just like me, dripping tears
Always chasing the clock the wrong way, here we are
trip
ping
Tripping
flip
flap
Flip! Flap! Flip! Flap!
When I open it
flip
flap
Flip! Flap! Flip! Flap!
This little locked-up box
It's filled up to the brim
With distant voices
Look, they spread, they fill us up, so
flip
flap
Flip! Flap! Flip! Flap!
Even the stars around us
flip
flap
Flip! Flap! Flip! Flap!
They go and dance around
Follow me to a twinkle on high,
mi
chii
Like a guide to the ends of this world
And now with you, together we...
flip
flap
Flip! Flap!
Isn't Yayaka your friend?
We go way back.
You got payback?
I've known her for years...
How should I put it?
What time is it?!
I'm home.
The cram school called.
What happened?
Cocona.
I'm glad you're okay.
From now on, call and let me know
when you're going to be late, okay?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Next time on Flip Flappers:
"Pure Eagle...
P-Pure Equalit...
Pure Qual...
Pure Equalization
Next Episode
Pure Something!