Narukami Youta, I need to talk to you.
All right.
You are not a lab assistant dispatched
from a research institute, are you?
I'm not.
But—
I'd like you to leave immediately.
But...
You should be grateful I'm not calling the police.
Would I be able to see Hina again?
There's plans for us to move
to an overseas facility.
Huh?
It will be a much better-equipped facility.
So you probably won't be able to see her again.
I beg you! Please let me stay with her
for the rest of the day!
Narukami!
I beg you!
At least for half the day!
Very well.
Thank you very much!
Hey, Hina.
Because of some things that happened,
I need to leave at the end of the day.
Today is the last day we can play together.
Maybe she only opened up her heart to the game.
Zeus Attacks!
You won't be sad if I'm not here, huh?
Thought so.
All right, Hina,
what number is this?
This will be my last study session.
Hina?
I hope you'll answer me
at least once to say you're okay.
a God Chose
Episode 12
Hina?
I'd do anything to take you back home,
if that was what you wanted.
So just give me a nod of agreement.
Hina, would you like to get
out of here and live with me?
We spent last summer together.
We were surrounded by family and lots of friends.
Do you remember that?
I guess you don't.
Those were such fun days.
Maybe she would prefer to stay here.
Sora.
Yes, that's Sora!
You're right! Did you remember?
And who's this?
Daichi
Sora's name means "sky",
his name is the opposite. What's below your feet?
Daichi
Earth.
Almost! How do you make a name of it?
Daichi.
Yes!
And who's this?
It's something to do with time.
Time is "toki", so...
Tokiko.
Yes!
Okay, then, um...
Who's this?
What's in the sky during the day?
The big burning star!
Don't give up!
Ah, sorry for shouting.
Hina?
Hina...
It's time.
No!
Just a bit more!
Give me just a bit more time!
Please escort him out.
Hina!
No!
No! I have to—
Don't struggle.
I can't go back like this!
I'm going to take Hina home.
I'm going to...
I didn't want to do this.
I'm sorry, everyone.
I couldn't bring Hina back.
Hina,
I guess this is your home now.
bye! Take care.
Youta is saying goodbye.
Wave bye-bye back at him.
Let's go.
Farewell, Hina.
Not.
What?
Not enough!
What's not enough?
Youha!
Not enough Youha!
Wait, is that why?!
She was doing that because I was already there.
That was why!
Need one!
Hina, stop!
Hina!
No!
Youha.
What in the world...
Hina woves Youha!
I love you too.
Hina...
The way you felt during our summer
together is still within you!
You still have feelings for me too!
And I couldn't see that.
I didn't realize how you felt!
Hina!
Youha. Youha!
Hina loves Youha!
I love you too, Hina!
Love Youha!
Me too!
It's fine.
Ms. Shiba?
She herself chose where she would be happy.
Let's go home, Hina.
I'm back!
And our princess has returned with me!
Hina!
Welcome back!
Welcome back, Youta.
You know Hina is now...
You don't need to say it.
I can tell by the look on your face.
You really can get stuff done!
Respect!
Thanks.
I'm grateful to have such a warm family.
And also for having such great friends.
Welcome back.
Welcome back, Hina.
You cut your hair.
I hate to say it, but it looks good on you.
What happened to her usual clothes?
Oh, she doesn't quite look like
herself without them, does she?
We can't really shoot the rest
of the film without them.
Yes, they're crucial.
Indeed.
No way! Ms. Tengan agreed with me!
What?! Are you implying I'm a contrarian?!
You're really cheeky for a nobody!
They all want to continue from where we left off,
despite how much Hina has changed.
I can use my connections
to have it tailored in no time.
The power of a celebrity!
That would be great!
We have plenty of images of how it looked.
Would you like that, Hina?
Wanna play a bit again?
Yeah! Let's play!
Look, Hina!
Try to get it through that loop.
You can throw from below.
Just toss as high as you can.
Oh, that's right.
This was the first thing she
showed interest in when we met.
The light of the sun was so dazzlingly bright
Could it be
that all the things we did since we met
I had to close my eyes for a moment
were all part of the normal life
that Hina wanted to experience?
As I did, I drifted off to sleep
Playing basketball.
Eating ramen.
Up high beyond the stars
Living as part of a family.
She did whatever she wanted,
even starring in a movie.
Fireworks sprang forth and blossomed
I see now!
That summer was filled with
all the things Hina wanted to do!
But now that's just a distant memory
I was an idiot to try and forget that summer!
We can't turn back time
What's the matter, Youta?!
Through all the joy, through all the tears
Nothing. I'm fine.
I want to live my life right by your side
Come on, throw the ball, Hina.
So please smile
It's fine if you cry at times too
It's okay.
You can keep trying.
Let’s find a way to travel back to that summer
Let's go at it until it goes in.
Before the gods, we'll make a miracle happen
Oh yeah!
Great shot!
All right!
That was great, Hina!
All right! Now that you've
got the hang of it, go again!
The light of the sun was so dazzlingly bright
Be still for a bit, okay?
Let's see if this fits.
I had to close my eyes for a moment
Here we go.
As I did, you were right there beside me
And now put this on too.
Okay.
And we're done!
Her hair's a bit shorter,
but she looks the same as before.
Now we can go ahead with the film, right?
Okay, let's start with a scene
where you walk in the temple.
Ready...
Action!
Hina, just come over here.
Remember?
Hina, you are the main character of this story.
And I play the boy who travels with you.
We were the stars of the movie.
And now we want to continue filming it.
For starters just hold your head
up high and walk straight to me.
You can do it!
You can do it, Hina!
Whenever you're ready. We can wait.
I believe in you!
You don't need to rush. Just come here.
That's great!
Keep going, Hina!
Don't rush!
Cut!
That was great!
I can't compete with such a masterful performance.
Indeed.
Good job, Hina!
Everything that's happened so far
feels like something out of a movie.
A normal boy meets a girl who says she's a god.
They resolve various situations throughout
a summer break and fall in love.
They face a huge crisis, but overcome it,
and are back together again.
Hina, we both chose to be here
with one another, right?
I'm not just imagining that?
All right! I've made up my mind!
I'll apply for university again.
I want to try to become a great
researcher like your grandfather.
I'm going to study your disease thoroughly.
I want to do something to help you!
I'm going to unravel the mystery
that no one else could before.
Even if it's beyond human understanding,
I'm going to find a way.
So we're going to be together for a long, long time.
How about it?
Hina loves Youha.
All right!
I suddenly have confidence!
Let's do it!
My life never had any clear purpose before.
But now I have a dream to strive for,
and I feel really motivated.
I've never felt something like this before.
You guided me to the life I want to live.
Perhaps you really were my god.
Cut!
That's a wrap!
Thank you so much, everyone!
You did really well, Hina!
Once it's finished, I want to do a screening!
But there's a lot left to do before that.
You're in charge of music, right, Izanami?
Yes, of course.
Lighting boy here has served his purpose.
Nice working with you.
I want to stay until the end though!
Jeez.
Winter passed by, and a chilly March came around.
High School
Mikuriya
Prefectual
Graduation
Ceremony
High School
Mikuriya
Prefectual
Graduation
Ceremony
What?! You're waiting until next year?!
Come on, now, calm down.
You got into Hachiman though!
Are you giving up on that?!
Well, my motive for going there
was impure to begin with,
and I found something I really want to do.
That's such a waste!
I'll go in your place! Let's switch names!
I'll get plastic surgery done if I have to!
No way.
So,
we're about to start the movie screening.
I've been waiting for this!
Hina, our movie is done!
It's the star role you wanted to have!
You managed to act until the end!
We're about to see the results.
All right, let's begin.
The world is on the brink of disaster
People came to know the inexplicable calamity as
The world is on the brink of disaster.
The world is on the brink of disaster
People came to know the inexplicable calamity as
The Sundering of the World.
The Sundering of the World
You still have not found
the cause of the world's ruin?!
All mages are presently occupied with saving lives.
Your Majesty, this is the brain of the world.
It's called SYSTEM.
The issue is that its energy has been depleted.
Thus its circuits are shutting down one by one.
And that is the cause of the calamities?
Indeed.
We should engage all spirits
of the realm in this search.
Very well.
Why do so many spirits flock to her?
What's wrong, Anne?
What happened to your shoes?
Rommy.
To be honest, I must travel to the royal capital.
That was what the elder called me for.
But why?
I do not know.
They merely said that I alone can save this world.
But it's so sudden! When are you coming back?
Boy,
I know it is cruel, but it shall be forever.
Forever?! You mean until she dies?!
But why?! Why Anne?!
She's clumsy and bad at singing,
and doesn't really have any talents of speak of!
Alas, she has plenty of talent for saving the world.
I can't believe this!
We set off at dawn.
I'll grab Anne when they're distracted.
And we'll go far away, the two of us.
We don't have to be the ones to save the world.
The ritual is about to begin.
The ritual where Anne will be sacrificed.
The ritual to save the world in exchange for her life.
And she's making her way to the altar.
I don't need her to have talents.
I love her all the same!
So I'm going to thwart this ritual!
What is he doing here?!
Anne!
Get him out of here!
Stop!
Anne!
Oh no! The ritual! The circuits!
The mechanism maintaining the world!
It's going to be all right now.
Let's go.
The world is crumbling!
What did you think?
Marvelous! A masterpiece!
I was completely immersed!
Great performance, Hina.
Indeed, I couldn't have pulled that off.
And we have such a masterful director.
Oh, shucks.
It sure is something we'll all
be able to look back on fondly.
I don't possess any pleasant memories.
Having such things must bring humans happiness.
Yes, it will be a really pleasant memory.
Right, Hina?
She's asleep.
All right, I'm starting the camera.
Indeed.
What's this?
Behind-the-scenes.
Hina told me to put it at the end.
So, how does it feel to become a god?
Let your fingertips reach out
Ah, yes.
Everything was so novel.
To feel the beautiful shape of this world
Each day bright and full of joy.
These memories are like gems
overflowing from a treasure chest.
No matter where your gaze drifts to
Even if the world ends in ruin,
these memories shall remain.
Your eyes are always filled with the hope of life
They are My eternal treasure!
The clouds we yearned to reach were so far away
I see.
So that's how she felt.
But still we eagerly chased them
I'm so happy to hear it.
The fond memories I hold from that summer
I can't imagine the future that awaits us.
Maybe it'll be a cruel world
with no miracles and no salvation.
I'll race to your side to share them from my heart
But still,
I'll pour my heart into living alongside Hina.
Don't hide yourself away
When you're worn out from playing, come on over
It's sad to be all alone
That's how it is for even the gods
Let the tip of your nose catch the scent
Of the fragrance human kindness radiates
So many things have happened to you
But please don't give up on life
The dreams we yearned for were so far away
But still we reached them