Whenever you're in trouble,
you can count on Mobami!
Hey, #1.
Do you like anime?
I love it! Especially Mobami!
That show is the greatest!
That's perfect, then.
The company that makes that anime
is understaffed and having all kinds of problems.
Go help advance them!
For real?!
Awesome! On my way!
I lovehate you, lovehate you, baby, yeah!
Hacka Doll
The Animation
You won't find anything ordinary around here!
Just make a splash and I'll be yours!
Don't be shy and don't run away!
Bang! Bang! Just leave it to us!
C'mon, just be true to your feelings
and let yourself be taken with the flow!
This freedom is finally letting me see
that there are so many choices in front of me
Which one do I pick? Won't you help me choose?
Let's keep touching today, baby!
How do you want to feel?
I can be in the minority or the majority
They're both just as fun to me!
Let's keep touching today, baby!
So won't you softly touch me, baby?
I want to be with you for as long as I can!
I lovehate you, lovehate you, baby, yeah!
In the anime production studio...
The men spending nights
sleeping at their desks
are about to meet a Hacka Doll.
Episode 7: KUROBAKO
Excuse me...
Are you that Hacka Doll they say
can help advance anything?
Y-Yes, I am!
I am a Personal Entertainment AI
that syncs up to you! A Hacka Doll!
Oh, you can skip that stuff.
Okay.
Please take good care.
Mobami
I'm going to have you help with
Mobami's seventh episode, "KUROBAKO."
Please take good care.
Mobami
What? Awesome!
You can count on me! I'll do anything!
Am I a key animator? An animation director?
You're doing the same task as me:
production assistant.
Huh? What's that?
Mobami
We have the crappy task of coordinating departments,
such as key animation, tweening, filming, and editing.
Mobami
Really? I love anime, though,
so I'll give it my all!
Is that so?
Don't try to escape.
Um, I'm calling about
the keyframes for Mobami...
30 Days Until Airing
Oh, you can't do it this month?
Then what about next month?
You can't predict your schedule?
You can't stand the director anyway?
This is crap... Utter crap...
O-Okay... Goodbye.
I'll use you for a character design.
All fifty turned me down, one after another.
Stop crying and keep working.
Ack!
20 Days Until Airing
Y-Yes?
We're going to collect the keyframes.
Go. Hop to it.
O-Okay...
Excuse me! I've come for the keyframes.
Hello!
Seems like they're inside.
Um...
Here it is!
Give them a
second touch-up, please.
Speed Lines
Huh?
What does this mean?
You have to start over
again from the layout.
14 Days Until Airing
You've gotta be kidding me!
Huh? I didn't realize #4 was here too.
There's no way we can have
this all done in two days.
B-But Hagiyama has put together 100 cuts.
The art and filming departments say they can't wait any longer.
You think I care?
Making things meet the deadline is your job.
The post-process doesn't concern you.
I'm going to work down to the last second.
Sheesh, what a useless production assistant.
I can't take it anymore!
Okay, take over where she left off.
Huh?!
7 Days Until Airing
Y-Yes?
Time for the after-recording.
Awesome! I get to meet voice actors!
Oh, maybe I'll get some autographs.
I didn't get to meet the voice actors.
It doesn't even feel like we're
working on the same project.
They live in a completely different world.
Let's go collect more keyframes.
I-I'm so bummed!
6 Days Until Airing
#1?
Y-Yes? Is the tweening done?
I brought this for you.
Have you been sleeping okay?
Ah... Y-Yeah.
Oh, sorry! Wait just a minute.
I'm back.
Huh? #1, did you go take a shower?
I guess... I just washed my hair in the bathroom.
I haven't bathed in a week.
#1...
It was nothing like I imagined.
Everyone is so strained, and irrational...
I wanna go home!
Oh, dear. But you can't.
You need to stick it out until the end.
If you run away, all the fans looking forward
to the anime will be disappointed.
But...
Come on, we'll help you.
Right?
We'll help.
Let's work hard together.
O-Okay!
Let's all work hard together!
Keyframes:
540 cuts
Number of Drawings:
12,800
Number of Runaways:
1 (Hacka Doll #4)
Revenue:
In the red.
Hacka Doll #3
Healthy
Hacka Doll #2... Healthy
Hacka Doll #1... Healthy
Day of Airing
Whenever you're in trouble,
you can count on—
Mobami
Well... I guess that'll do.
Good work, Director.
Once we take this disc to
the station in Osaka, we're done...
But we won't make it in time.
Ugh... We totally dropped
the ball on this one.
Hey...
A recap episode, eh?
And the third one this cour.
A miracle didn't happen.
You're wrong!
A miracle will happen.
I'll make it happen!
#1?
We Hacka Dolls can do it!
The three of us will go together to Osaka!
Advancing this company is our mission!
We made the delivery!
You girls...
Good work.
Th-Thanks!
I look forward to working
with you on episode 8!
Now I know that anime
is best enjoyed at home!
This animation is a work of fiction, and has no relation whatsoever to companies, people, place names or organizations, such as "Creators in Pack".
I want you to know how I feel every time I want to see you
There's nothing for me to be shy about!
I need to be more honest!
I need you to know how I feel every time I want to see you
I need to take the first step
and accept these feelings of mine
I've gotta work on that!