I lovehate you, lovehate you, baby, yeah!
Hacka Doll
The Animation
You won't find anything ordinary around here!
Just make a splash and I'll be yours!
Don't be shy and don't run away!
Bang! Bang! Just leave it to us!
C'mon, just be true to your feelings
and let yourself be taken with the flow!
This freedom is finally letting me see
that there are so many choices in front of me
Which one do I pick? Won't you help me choose?
Let's keep touching today, baby!
How do you want to feel?
I can be in the minority or the majority
They're both just as fun to me!
Let's keep touching today, baby!
So won't you softly touch me, baby?
I want to be with you for as long as I can!
I lovehate you, lovehate you, baby, yeah!
Episode 2: Please Let Us Be Idols!
IWS Idol Agency
What...
is this?
A triple booking? Wait...
A four-times booking?!
The correct phrase is "quadruple booking."
Guess I screwed up...
However! Being able to fix messes
like these is what makes a great producer!
What's three or four events?
I can fill this schedule...
I couldn't!
Damn it!
I just can't fill this last slot!
If only there were an agency that
could introduce me to an available idol!
What you need is...
The Personal Entertainment AI
that syncs to you: Hacka Doll!
H-Hacka Doll?!
The AI that can advance
any part of a person's life?!
Now that we're here, you can rest at ease!
We'll fill that open event slot for you!
Huh? You weren't going to
introduce me to an idol?
We don't need to do that!
Look!
Look at what we can do!
Isn't that CG?
Shush!
We're going to be idols?
We'll get to wear cute costumes, sing, dance,
and make everyone go crazy for us...
It's every girl's dream!
I think you just really want to do this.
I appreciate the offer, but...
Please!
I promise we'll advance your company,
so please let us be idols!
But I don't want to trouble the sponsor—
Please let us be idols!
But this is a very important event—
Let us be idols!
There are a few days left until the event.
If you'd just give us a chance
and let us prove ourselves...
Yeah, but—
Let us!
Fine!
We'll get you started with some training.
Okay! We're totally ready for this!
IWS Idol Agency
And so, our days of training began.
Running...
Hopping...
Practicing handshakes...
Photo shoots...
This... might just work.
Hacka
Dolls
At last, the big day is here!
What a huge audience...
I'm so nervous...
Today's event is very special.
It's special?
Yes. The winner of today's event gets to
release a debut CD with a major record label.
A-A debut CD?
Only if you win, of course.
Oh, right! No problem!
It's almost time. Get ready!
Hacka
Dolls
Bathroom!
Now I'm really nervous...
Did you hear?
There's a last-minute replacement today.
Oh, you mean the group that claims
they can "advance" people?
They're making a mockery of idols.
They're probably nothing special.
Yeah, I don't really get them.
They're most likely going to suck.
But we worked really hard for this!
I know we can do it!
Maybe the audience won't like us that much though...
I really want to be an idol,
but if the audience doesn't enjoy the show,
then I won't be able to advance the producer's career...
I wonder if anyone will even watch us...
Girls...
Producer...
All idols struggle with that insecurity.
And it's the miracle of overcoming that insecurity
to stand on stage that the audience has come to see.
I'm already excited to see what kind
of miracles you girls will perform.
Remember how badly
you wanted to be an idol?
And you want to advance
my career too, right?
Then don't worry!
I'm sure there'll be people watching you!
Now, go make miracles!
Okay!
We're still in the girls' bathroom...
Who's next?
Hacka Dolls?
A last-minute filler?
Oh, I know them.
The ones who can "advance" anything.
Oh, them?
So they can be idols, too?
Awesome!
Nice to meet you all!
We are...
Hacka Dolls!
We trained a whole lot
to become idols today,
so please listen to our song,
"Cabbage Testing"!
Cabbage Testing
Lyrics: Ikuo Geso
Composition: Daisuke Horita
Cabbage Testing
Lyrics: Ikuo Geso
Composition: Daisuke Horita
Cabbage Testing
Lyrics: Ikuo Geso
Composition: Daisuke Horita
Oh, cabbage! How round you are
Let me tell you a story that started one deep-blue night
A cabbage will never change, always and forever round
It's still a cabbage when it's a soppy, wet soup
Ever since we can remember,
we've been at the cabbage top
Like a green thumb for companies,
we're the secret ingredient!
These vibrations...
Will we ever see a day
The building itself is resonating!
when we can be ordinary cabbages?
To be but cabbages
That is our wish!
Did I mess up?
Not at all!
#1, you were great!
Your soul reached me!
You were awesome!
Thank you so much!
I want you to know how I feel every time I want to see you
There's nothing for me to be shy about!
I need to be more honest!
I need you to know how I feel every time I want to see you
I need to take the first step
and accept these feelings of mine
I've gotta work on that!