Anime Specials
Episode Seven
A Cooking Lesson in
the Ohta Household
OHTA
So, how come you want me to teach you
how to bake sweets all of a sudden?
Rino made a lot of cookies recently,
and she shared some with me.
Oh, Tanaka's sister?
Nissei
Sunflower
Refined Flour
tempura, sweets, okonomiyaki, udon
Yeah, and they were really good!
So that got me thinking that I wanted to try making some too.
But I'm not really that good
when it comes to cooking,
so I thought that, since you
are good, you could teach me!
And if they turn out well, I'll give them to Rino!
I see.
We'll have to try our best, then.
Yeah!
First, we should precisely
measure out the ingredients.
It's very easy to make a mistake if you do it by eye.
I see.
Big Bro, you're in the way.
The dust will get in the air,
so can you move somewhere else?
I'm sorry for being in the way.
What kind of person is Tanaka's sister?
Seems like she's the total
opposite of her listless brother.
That's right, she's very reliable.
She's the manager of our club,
and she's always thinking about how
she can make things easier for us players.
Really?
So having a brother to take care of
has made her really capable.
Now we should add the egg yolk.
Okay!
Big Bro, you're in the way.
At least sleep in your room.
I'm sorry for being in the way...
Honestly, where would he be without me?
I actually baked some cookies!
That's good.
Yeah!
Thank you, Brother.
No problem.
Let's make some more sometime.
I don't think they're as good
as the ones you baked, but...
Thank you, Saya.
They're really good.
She doesn't seem like she's the sister of that annoying Ohta's at all.
So honest and cute!
They're good.
Really?
That's good.
Wait, these are the ones my brother baked.
A-Are you okay, Rino?!
Y-Yeah.
I can't believe I called something he made good!
But...