Anime Specials
Episode Two
Is being small a good thing?
Cold
Satoen
Is this what you wanted, Miyano?
Thank you very much, Ohta-kun!
Good for you, Miyano-san.
Yes, Master!
Strawberry Milk
EITO
Milk Beverage
There's really nothing better than strawberry milk!
Still, I can't believe they changed the position.
I can't reach the button anymore.
It's not easy being small.
Sounds tough.
It really is.
I run into a lot of problems because I'm small!
I'm jealous of you, Ohta-kun! You're so tall.
Being tall isn't good either.
It can be pretty inconvenient sometimes.
I hit my head a lot, for example.
When you're small, there aren't any cool,
mature-looking clothes and shoes,
and even if you try wearing them,
they don't suit you!
When you're big,
there aren't many clothes to choose from.
But, but!
When I want to buy a ticket for a bus,
they ask me if I want a children's one!
When I want to buy a student ticket in a cinema,
they ask me if I'm really in high school,
even when I show them my student ID.
Now now, you two, no need to get so heated.
My stomach is too small
to eat all of the things I like!
When I wait in line in a confectionery,
people give me weird looks.
I can't reach the luggage rack on a train!
When I go to a cinema, I'm worried people
behind me can't see because of me!
In toilets, hangers are usually
so high I can't reach them!
When I'm walking,
sometimes I get candies from grandmas
I don't know telling me I'm cute!
When I get close to a girl
to save her from shady people,
they run away the second
they see me and she thanks me.
I'm close to the ground,
so I notice dropped things a lot!
I can reach high places, so it's convenient!
I'm jealous of tall people.
Being small isn't bad either.
In the end, everyone just wants
what they don't have.
I'm so glad I'm ordinary.