Anime Specials
Episode Three
The Recipe For
Ohta-kun's Happiness
Ah, this establishment's chocolate cakes
are as excellent as I expected.
They've perfectly balanced
the sweetness and strength.
This exquisite cross-section,
revealing multiple layers of sponge and cream...
It's virtually a work of art.
Sorry, Tanaka.
I don't have time today,
so I'm going ahead without you.
You got something planned?
This place is selling limited edition sweets today.
They're so good that there's always a queue.
If I don't go now, they might sell out.
Actually, they might have sold out already.
I see.
Good luck.
Thanks.
See you tomorrow.
Shall I carry those for you?
Where might you be headed, ma'am?
Thank you, young man.
Is something the matter?
Thank you.
Is this yours?
Make sure you play safely.
You're big, mister!
Play with us!
Let's play!
Did I make it in time?
There's quite a queue.
I wonder if I'll still be able to buy something.
I'm terribly sorry, miss.
Unfortunately, we'll be sold out
after the gentleman in front of you.
Seems I made it, barely.
What? But I want cake!
There's nothing we can do about it.
Let's come here another time, okay?
No! I want cake!
Next time we'll come earlier.
So, you let them buy the cake?
Yeah. I can always wait for another chance.
Here. For you.
I bought it, but couldn't eat the whole thing.
Are you sure?
I'll gladly accept, then.
Tanaka-kun, Ohta-kun!
Good morning.
Morning, Shiraishi-san.
Morning, Shiraishi.
You know, I tried making new macarons yesterday.
I'd love to get a second and third opinion.
Sure, thanks.
Oh, Master, Ohta-kun!
I baked some cookies yesterday,
and I wanted to share them with everyone.
Myaano herself made those cookies.
You'd better be grateful!
Don't you want to give them
what you brought today, Ecchan?
I-It's not like I particularly wanted
to give it to them or anything!
It's the newest edition of these sweets.
You can have it if you want.
Oh, thanks.
Ohta.
Lucky you, huh?
Yeah.