Anime Specials
Episode Five
The Destined Confrontation
with Echizen
Today at last, I want you to fight me for real!
Show me everything you've got!
Seriously...
Do I really have to?
Quit your grumbling!
Well, then.
Ready...
Go!
Great, I won!
Hey, I told you to fight me for real!
Ready?
Here it comes, Tanaka!
Oh, that was a pretty nice shot.
How many times I gotta tell you?!
But there's no way I could've caught that...
Jeez. Fine, I'll fight you in something you're good at.
So you're not going to give up fighting?
I couldn't live with myself if I missed
my chance to fight you for real!
Seriously? Fine, then...
I'm good at afternoon nap contests.
What kind of contest is that?
Oh, but you know, Tanaka's ability to sleep
could definitely be called a talent.
You're totally missing the point here!
Oh, what are you guys doing here?
Myaano!
Tanaka and Echizen were just about
to fight in afternoon napping.
What? That sounds amazing!
I wanna partcicipate too!
M-Myaano?
Come on, Ecchan, join us. It feels great.
O-Okay, let's do this, Tanaka!
Hey, you dozed off way too fast!
Ecchan, shh.
O-Okay...
Isn't it pretty?
It sure is.