Here's my next request.
At 3 PM, go do some shopping in the
supermarket near Nanasaka Middle School.
It's almost 3 PM.
CHOCOLATE
SWEETS
Was Souma Sumire trying to make us meet her?
I don't know.
I already said no!
I got a good score on my last test,
and you said you'd buy it then!
The test was last month!
CHOCOLATE
SWEETS
Bargain
Corner
Broccoli
Carrots
Scallion
Tomatoes
Peppers
Eggplant
Bargain
Corner
Meat
Side Dishes
CHOCOLATE
The second incident should happen around now.
I
used
to
say
there
was
a
novel
I
loved
That
I
kept
on
a
shelf
and
never
opened
up
"See,
this
is
how
you
stay
true
to
yourself"
Showing
off,
proud
of
just
being
me
People
around
me
Try
to
sound
mature
and
take
some
wise
words
They
use
them
as
if
those
words
belonged
to
them
Showing
off
the
fake
wisdom
they
had
stolen
So
I
laughed
at
them
But
actually
my
sense
of
self
that
I
kept
on
a
shelf
Was
no
different
from
what
I'd
been
laughing
at
And
the
truth
is
that
I
already
knew
But
no
more
lies,
it's
time
For
my
heart's
reset
I'll
myself
So
I
told
myself
somewhere
deep
down
in
my
heart
Even
if
they
might
talk
behind
my
back
Why
should
I
care
when
I
don't
turn
around?
You
can
choose
To
follow
the
path
someone's
already
walked
But
wouldn't
you
rather
leave
footprints
yourself?
You
believed
your
own
dreams
and
chose
a
path
So
it's
the
right
one,
just
trust
in
your
heart
It'll
all
be
fine
Hitsuuchi
Options
Hey, Kei, it's been a while.
It certainly has.
I was actually just thinking
that I should contact you.
I'll help you.
But I want something in exchange.
What is it?
A picture of Souma Sumire.
Did Minami ask you for it?
You sure figure things out quickly.
I thought it'd be easiest to ask you for it.
Should you really be telling me about this?
It's not something I have to research in secret.
I'm sure she's in the yearbook.
That'll do. Take a picture with
your phone and send it to me.
Can do that much.
So? What do you want to know?
About the traffic accident
that happened this morning.
Ah, it's indeed the kind of
case you'd get involved in.
A case? Not an accident?
That's apparently what the Bureau's concluded.
It's one of the serial ability rampage cases.
Another one was everyone in a supermarket
suddenly bursting out laughing.
How big of an issue is this case for the Bureau?
No idea.
But something feels wrong.
On the surface, it's not that big of a case.
And yet, it seems to me they're panicking.
If I had to be honest...
I'd say the Bureau fears the possibility
that all abilities could go berserk.
Two abilities went out of control.
The Witch disappeared from
Sakurada two months ago.
She didn't foresee the problem
just two months in the future.
What's worse,
something similar might happen again.
There are tens of thousands
of ability users in Sakurada.
That means there's a risk of all
of their abilities going berserk.
How will the Bureau deal with such a problem?
It was around forty years ago.
The one year between the first abilities
appearing and the Bureau being established.
Back when only three people in
the world were aware of abilities...
Urachi
Piano School
If we execute this plan,
you'll meet a terrible fate without doubt.
We three discussed many possibilities together.
And I confirmed the futures behind all of our ideas.
The fate this plan will lead to is the
lesser evil of all possible outcomes.
There might be something you haven't checked.
I'm sure there has to be a way to make
the whole world forget about abilities.
We couldn't find a way to get rid of all abilities,
but we could create a world
where no one knows about them.
With the help of my ability.
The ability to erase one specific piece
of information from the whole world.
To make one memory disappear
from the heads of all people.
Actually, even at this very moment,
I'm making all people outside
of this room unaware of abilities.
However, when the time comes for you to leave
this world, everyone will remember about them.
The world will be overwhelmed by them,
and the chaos will be unimaginable.
That's the future I've seen. I assure you,
it's a future that we cannot allow to happen.
Which is why we need to protect your ability.
Forever...
To achieve that, we have to let
other ability users be born.
We'll have to expand the border
to cover at least all of Sakurada,
and keep those outside of it unaware of abilities.
Your wife happens to have the perfect ability.
The ability to never lose a specific thing...
If she specifies this cup to never
be lost in regard to this room,
no one will be able to take this cup outside of it.
If she specifies the warmth
to never be lost in regard to this tea,
it'll never go cold.
She's using her ability in regard to this room,
to make sure we don't lose
our memories about abilities.
If you leave this room,
you'll forget all about abilities.
We need to expand this border
to cover all of Sakurada.
I'll keep watching the future with my ability
to predict any accidents related to abilities.
Twenty years, was it?
Yes.
In twenty years, one of Sakurada's residents
will get an ability that can stop your time.
But it's twenty years
assuming that ability users
will be born in this town, right?
If we moved to another town,
it's possible the ability user
we need would be born sooner.
And what good will speeding things up do?
You'll be able to live like a normal person.
You'll forget about all abilities and live in peace.
It'll take ten years for me to lose my name.
I'll be able to stay human
for at least another ten years.
I'm chronically ill.
I'm not supposed to live more
than just two more years.
In the future I saw,
if more abilities are born in Sakurada,
you'll be able to live for another twenty years.
That seems very unfair.
You're supposed to be able to live normally,
and yet in just ten years,
you'll have to throw away even your own name.
I'm sure the reason you got this ability
was to let your beloved forget about your death.
Who knows.
But in truth, you don't want to be forgotten.
That's why your ability
will lose its effect once you die.
What an ironic contradiction.
If Sakurada becomes the town of
ability users and you keep on living,
the two of you will eventually have a child, a boy.
I think we should try our best for his sake as well.
Then, a year passed,
and the Bureau had built its foundations.
The border was forcefully expanded.
Its new size was keeping
the whole of Sakurada in check.
Erasing this border and getting rid of all
memories of abilities all around the world
is definitely the Bureau's trump card.
Hitsuuchi
Message
A message from Hitsuuchi...
It's the info on the people
from the ability rampage cases.
Inbox
Subject:
Delete
Forward
Reply to all
Reply
Subject:
Reply to all
Reply
Subject:
Reply to all
Reply
Hello? Asai here.
I know.
You sent me the picture of Souma Sumire.
Was it okay?
It reminded me of something.
Tell me, what's going on?
What do you mean?
Connected
End call
Just who is Souma Sumire?
She's a girl who passed away
two years ago in an accident.
I know that.
But I also know it's not all.
Why's that?
I've met her once.
So that's what it was!
When was it that you met her?
Two years ago. June, if I remember correctly.
She suddenly appeared at my place.
So my hunch was right.
When he met Souma years ago,
she must have had him manipulate memories.
Wasn't that when you were still a vampire?
That's right.
Before the Bureau noticed me,
that girl was the only one
who knew about me absorbing
information from people.
In exchange for keeping the secret,
she asked me to steal some
information from a certain person.
Who did you steal it from?
I don't know his name. It was some boy.
It's definitely Tomoki.
Souma first made him deliver her messages to me,
and made Hitsuuchi steal those memories from him.
I remembered everything looking at the picture.
She mentioned the location of the car crash,
and the supermarket from the second case.
So everything Souma Sumire
said in her messages to me
was actually from two years ago.
Is there anything else you remember?
Only one more thing.
And that is?
I think she was talking about a shower.
A shower?
Kei,
can you answer me?
Connected
End call
How could she be involved in the current events?
I don't know anything.
I can't bring myself to imagine you
being friends with a perfectly normal girl.
That's mean.
Well, she was a strange girl.
Very smart, full of confidence,
but somehow lonely.
And...
I'm sorry.
I don't really want to talk about her.
Connected
End call
No, I'm sorry for asking. See you.
Ending call...
Souma... You...
Was such a stupid reason really worth
dying for?
Well, Kei.
It's time for the next request.
Can I ask something?
What is it?
Would you prepare an
Ashiharabashi High uniform for me?
If possible, also textbooks and a gym uniform.
Once our plan succeeds, all information
about abilities will disappear from Sakurada.
Our memories will be rewritten,
and I'm sure I'll become a normal student.
We've already arranged for that.
It's one of the reasons Tsushima
Shintarou is cooperating with us.
I see. Thank you.
We're here. It's time to say goodbye.
What is it?
Just wondered if you'd get upset.
That's a lie.
You knew the result.
I guess. Let me correct myself:
I was trying to make you upset.
And what was the point?
Let's drop the act and talk honestly here.
What do you want to talk about?
Let's see... What do you think about the Bureau?
The same as people not involved see it.
Calm, cool, collected, and with no compassion at all.
So it's the same when you're inside it.
Unfortunately.
There's really strong, deep-rooted faith towards
the three founders, especially the unnamed system.
They think there's no way she could ever be wrong,
which is why the Bureau is always so calm.
But today it was all destroyed.
The Witch didn't predict the current events.
That's right.
The very foundation of the Bureau was shaken.
Did he do something?
Most likely.
There's no point trying to figure out that guy.
He's almost like a monster.
I see.
Well, I think I've mostly figured it out.
Figured what out?
What he did.
You're also like a monster.
It's not very polite to call a girl a monster.
So? Were you watching my future just now?
No, I can't see the future anymore.
Why?
He ordered Oka Eri to use her ability on me.
I've forgotten how to use my clairvoyance.
When?
Just a moment ago.
I guess it means my ability served its purpose.
Do you think what he's doing is right?
There's no way it could be right.
I wouldn't have thought he'd actually
cause an accident on purpose.
Then why are you obeying him?
I can't imagine abilities being for the best.
But I don't know how to erase them from this town.
So I have no choice but to help him.
Why do you think abilities are harmful?
I wonder.
Maybe it's because I'm in the Bureau.
You're surely not a monster.
That much should be obvious.
I'm an ordinary government worker.
I'm glad we were able to talk.
Thanks.
Goodbye, Souma Sumire.
Don't call me by that name.
I'm the Witch.
October 24th
Tuesday
Kei, here's my third instruction for you.
In the morning of October 24th,
you should deliver a book you like to Haruki Misora.
Put a nice cover on it.
I'm sure she'll like that.
Kei.
Good morning, Kei.
Morning.
I saw you from the window.
Did you need anything?
I had something to give you.
I put it into the mailbox, so take a look later.
I could have invited you inside.
I didn't want to impose this early in the morning.
Kei, are you tired?
Yeah.
It's a bit painful.
You should rest then.
There's just a few more things that I have to do.
No.
No?
What you have to do is rest.
It's fine.
I'm good at pushing myself.
It's the first time I ever heard
the word "painful" from you.
Even two years ago, when Souma Sumire died,
you never said such a thing.
What happened?
Nothing really.
I've simply been thinking about something.
And what is this something?
It's basically about Souma.
Did you figure something out?
Yeah, I think I've worked out most of it.
It's just like you said yesterday.
No matter the reason,
there's no way dying was the right thing to do.
Souma Sumire died for your sake, didn't she?
You really should rest.
You should lie down and stop thinking about things.
Thanks.
I'm fine, though.
What are you going to do now?
I'll aim for the happiest ending.
I can't do anything to help you, then.
And since I can't help you, I'll be waiting for you.
Thanks. I'll do my best.
The world inside Katagiri Honoka's dream...
Tyltyl? Mytyl?
They're locked.
It's that Bureau employee's ability.
Tyltyl?
No, I'm not Tyltyl.
I'm an ordinary bird.
Ordinary birds don't talk.
I'm a bird that talks, then.
I don't have any god-like powers.
Was it Tyltyl or Mytyl that created you?
Tyltyl.
I was born right before his time was stopped.
What happened?
First, Mytyl's time was stopped.
The Bureau people came soon after that.
I see...
They locked Katagiri Honoka in reality,
and then entered the dream world.
Tyltyl can't oppose the Bureau.
He can't do anything when
they use Mytyl as a shield.
What did they do?
They asked Tyltyl if he knows a future-seer.
And Tyltyl told them about Sumire,
just like they asked him to.
Why didn't Tyltyl create himself?
He was planning to.
But you know, Index asked him a few questions.
"Is there anyone in this world other
than you two who has god-like powers?"
"Are you trying to create one right now?"
And he had no choice but to answer them honestly.
Yeah.
"I was trying to clone myself, but decided not to."
I don't know what's happening in reality,
but please, help Mytyl.
Answer my questions, then.
When did the Bureau people appear here?
Around three weeks ago.
Did they leave the dream world immediately?
No, they went to meet with Sumire from this world.
They talked with her, and then stopped her time.
Do you know what they talked about?
No, I don't.
I was just watching them from high above.
I see.
By the Bureau people,
you meant Index, Kagaya, and...
the man who always smiles?
Yeah.
The last one is called Urachi Masamune.
Urachi?
Something wrong?
It's nothing.
Anyway, once you're back in reality,
I want you to contact Sumire.
I'm sure she'll do something.
Okay, I'll try to do that.
But I don't know how to contact Souma myself...
The rain woke me up...
Urachi?
That name was in volume 407 of the Script...
During the first year of Sakurada,
two of the first three ability users
were Urachi Seijurou and Urachi Haruko.
The Urachis...
Next Episode
Is the restriction of abilities progressing?
I'm scared of abilities.
I can't make a decision yet.
Mr. Tsushima! Why?
I... I want to stay selfish.
What will Urachi Masamune do next?
I want to like this town.
On such a cold dark sky of grey
Rises the sun, which breathes life into it
A scenery so plain and so mundane
And yet it seems to break my heart, it's so dear to me
As the time never stops passing by
You get lost while searching for
Pure like the rays of a morning star
What we all yearn for the most
In what colors bliss is dyed
Struggling against all your past mistakes
At last from the answer you found kindness fills your heart
More beautiful than anything you know
And you find it behind a dark veil of sadness
If I closed my eyes and stopped my thoughts
If it were so simple to just
Lock your own heart
How lovely life would be
But I believe you have the key
To let my soul be free