Oh, the sunset was so beautiful
that I took that one on a whim.
The contrast between the sunlight
and shadows is splendid, isn't it?
Souma Sumire...
It's the same place where we first met.
There was also the MacGuffin...
Why did she have it?
Hey...
Hey, you!
Are you crying?
Why would you think that?
I figured it'd make you answer me.
Unfortunately, I'm not really
in the mood to talk to anyone.
How come?
I dunno. Why do you think?
Because the sunset is really beautiful?
Yeah, that's exactly right.
Now, you've lost your reason
for not wanting to talk to anyone.
That's true.
What do you want?
Why do you think there are
tetrapods in a place like this?
Were you waiting this whole time
just to ask me about that?
Well, doesn't it make you wonder?
Isn't it because there's a river
with a beautiful sunset here?
Is that a reason?
Well, I kinda like the sunset here.
I like it, too.
It's sort of like a scene out of a story.
I think it's wonderful when a boy and girl
make a promise to each other in such a place.
That doesn't sound half bad.
Why don't we promise something?
The sun's already set.
Let's meet again, Asai.
Is that our promise?
It will be, if you agree to it.
August
.10th
Thurs
day
.9
.10
th
Wednes
Thurs
day
.8
.9
Tues
Wednes
.7
.8
Mon
Tues
Second Time
It's August 7th. The time is 11:49:32.
Looks like we've reset.
What happened?
All sorts of things.
If I were to sum it up, there's about three things.
I used my reset ability for those things?
Do you remember Oka Eri?
She's one year below us.
She used to be Fujikawa Eri.
Her parents got divorced two years ago,
so her last name changed.
She didn't possess any ability at that time.
I remember.
She was the girl who was afraid of her violent dad.
I hate Fujikawa Eri.
She's weak and worthless.
I absolutely hate Fujikawa Eri.
My dad was strict.
He'd get mad at me no matter what I did.
The flow of time makes a continuous sound (so close your eyes and feel it)
My mom always sided with me,
but all she could do was cry.
It's a melody that invites the coming future (which begins today)
But then one day, he saved me.
What's your mother's maiden name?
What kind of world is waiting for me? (Who is calling me?)
It's Oka.
I'll call you Oka Eri, then.
Huh?
It's a very nice name, isn't it? "Oka Eri"...
I tried asking myself for an answer (in my heart)
It's not really dainty, it sort of seems like a joke,
Here, in the middle of ideals and reality (I'm searching for them)
and it won't make you feel troubled at all.
It's a strong, brazen name.
It's good that it doesn't suit you at all right now.
The hands of the clock are being constantly moved (as I turn them back)
Take up the name Oka Eri.
You should ditch your father
and the Fujikawa name.
I'll do anything to erase all sadness (over and over again)
Your father leaked some information.
It's information that should never be leaked, you know.
Even if it means going back down the passage of dark stairs (to recreate the past)
For example, you should try telling him that you'll send this to the Bureau.
Isn't that a bad thing to do?
There's something I want to protect no matter what (I'll protect you)
Bad? Of course it is!
I'm telling you to threaten your father.
I'll say that out loud (and try resetting again)
You must decide for yourself on what to do.
Believing that fate will bring us together again
I'm gonna be a strong,
wicked person like you, Asai Kei.
I'll become Oka Eri.
Looks like I'm going the right way.
Tsushima Shintarou
The person you're investigating is Oka Eri,
the third-year from Nanasaka Middle School, right?
Yes.
She's probably affiliated with the Bureau.
Lately, a Bureau staff member has started
utilizing the abilities of a person called Oka Eri.
Does that mean Oka Eri sealed Mr. Sasano's
ability under the Bureau's orders?
I still don't know.
I've sorta got a bad feeling about this.
Did you find out anything about her ability?
Not yet. We ran into a bit of trouble.
Is someone hiding it?
There's a high possibility.
Well, I'll probably learn something
once I find out a little more.
Also, I think you already know,
but I'll say it just in case:
August 8th
Tuesday
Second Time
Be careful out there.
Are you going to see Oka Eri?
Yeah.
I feel like I need to speak with
her first before anything else.
I reasked Murase the favor,
so she's looking for her for me.
Will that improve the situation?
I'm not sure.
It'd be nice if it's the sort of problem
I can resolve with just an apology.
I have just one question.
Kei, if I were to ever lose my ability to reset,
will that change anything about our relationship?
I don't know.
If you're unsure, I swear I won't ever lose my ability.
It's been about 24 hours.
Save.
That outfit... That's probably Oka Eri.
Huh?
Murase Youka?
You want one?
No, I don't.
What? But I split it in half already.
How do you know my name?
Because I'm doing an investigation on Asai.
And I more or less know what
happened between you and him.
But I wonder why Murase Youka is here.
I was looking for you.
So they did a reset, huh?
How do you...
It's simple.
There's no reason for his associate
to look for me right now.
Which means that the cause
could only lie in the future.
Why are you doing his dirty work?
It's not like that.
He's not the kind of guy you'd
team up with or befriend, right?
Why would you care?
That's not good, not good at all.
Asai Kei isn't like that.
He has to be a more egocentric, selfish villain.
What are you trying to say?
As he is now, he's become far too weak.
Seeing him like that pisses me off.
At the very least, Asai is stronger than you.
You're adorable!
I like how you glare at people when you're angry.
What the hell does that mean?
Nothing.
It's just... Well, I should probably
prove Asai's weakness soon.
Hello.
How many years has it been?
A little over 28 years.
Today is August 8th.
I see. It's almost time, then.
Our promise will be fulfilled soon.
May I see your future?
Please go right ahead.
Are there any problems?
No. There are no major ones.
But...
But?
The Bureau noticed that you're
able to go into photographs.
How?
I don't know.
I'm sure something happened
that made him more wary of you.
Around three o'clock today,
a girl will come by to collect all of your photos.
That's not good.
It's okay.
Even if you lose your photos, our plans won't change.
It'd be best not to put up a fight.
As things are right now,
it will end up going just as planned.
Huh?
Do you want to see the real me again no matter what?
Of course I do!
Even if it means making someone else unhappy?
Even if it's bad for us to reunite?
For me, good and evil hold no meaning
in a world without you.
All right.
Send the photos I'll specify
now before they're collected.
Send them? To whom?
To Asai Kei.
Help me!
Murase?
Please, help me! Come right away!
Got it. Where are you?
I'm at a store in front of the station.
Where are you?!
I'm at the café where we first met.
I'll head over right away.
I'll head to you too!
Something came up. Pay the bill with this.
I'm going, too.
I'm sorry, but I'm going alone.
Nice to meet you, Haruki.
Hey, now! Aren't you being rude?
There's no point in hiding there.
You sure are confident!
But I also pride myself in never
holding back when needed!
Man, the basket on my bike
got dented 'cause I fell down.
I kinda liked this bike, you know.
But not as much as these contacts.
These are custom-made.
There's something faintly written here.
Can you see it? Look, right here.
Take a good look.
Murase!
Asai!
What happened?
No one followed you here, right?
As much as I glanced around, it seemed like no one did.
Be more specific!
There isn't anything scary around?
Anything scary? Like what?
Like a monkey!
A monkey followed you?!
It followed me,
or I guess I should say it stared at me.
Anyway, there is no monkey.
Really?
Really.
Please take a look behind you.
There isn't one, huh?
Yes. There isn't a monkey in sight.
Just a little while ago, I met Oka Eri.
And?
And... I don't really know.
In any case, I was so scared
that I felt I just had to call you.
But my memories are all scattered.
What about the monkey?
The monkey looked at me.
Its head was split open above its brows.
It was bleeding, and I could see its brains...
I was so scared.
Did you get all of that?
I did.
Did you really get it?
Typically, you'd say something
impossible happened, right?
Then we can assume that it's someone's ability.
Are you saying it's Oka Eri's ability?
I'm guessing Oka Eri's ability is the type
that can tamper with one's mind.
But there are some things I just don't understand.
Haruki Misora
Talking
Hello?
Hey there!
I took Haruki Misora's reset ability.
I completely took it away!
Oka Eri, please keep Haruki out of this.
Hell no. There's no point if I don't do this.
I want to prove your weakness.
Prove my weakness?
If you want her reset ability back,
then hand over the MacGuffin.
Okay.
Well, let's see here...
Nighttime would probably be best.
Let's meet up tonight at nine o'clock.
Where at?
I haven't decided yet. I'll get back to you later.
I'm returning this.
Are you hurt anywhere?
It's nothing at all.
I'm not hurting anywhere anymore.
I'm sorry, Kei.
No, it's my fault.
Please give me orders to reset.
I'm begging you.
Please do what you believe
is the most appropriate thing to do.
Hold on for just a moment.
Haruki, reset.
Reset.
It looks like I really can't do it.
Let's try something else.
Right hand. Oka Eri's ability.
Haruki, reset.
Reset.
I'm sorry. I really can't use my ability, after all.
I see.
I beg of you, Kei. Please restore my reset ability.
Yeah. That's what I was planning to do.
I swear I'll get it back.
But what are you going to do?
First, I'll meet with Mr. Tsushima,
and I'll ask him for details on Oka Eri's ability.
Also, I've got a favor to ask, Murase.
You sure are shameless.
I am pretty selfish.
You become friends with girls
before you realize, Kei.
It'd be good for you to make
some more friends, too.
Do you mean male friends?
It doesn't matter what gender,
but it'd be more fun to see you talking to girls.
Who do you recommend in that regard?
Nonoh, maybe?
I'll do what I can.
Hey, Oka Eri.
Don't call me Oka Eri! We're not that chummy.
Were you able to dispose of the photos?
I will now.
Why are we burning the photos after all this time?
Because things that shouldn't be recreated
with his ability are in those photographs.
Even though I sealed Sasano's ability?
He had lied about it.
Lied?
We discovered that Sasano's ability
is used when he takes photos.
As long as he has photos that he took with his ability,
he can go into them even with his ability sealed.
How stupid! To think the Bureau
would get an ability wrong!
Even despite claiming to have someone
who knows the future, too.
That's true. She is exceptional.
But I guess no one told you yet.
She's going to die soon.
For real?
Yeah. If you want her ability,
it'd be best for you to act quickly.
Sorry I'm late.
No, I should apologize.
I'm sorry for making you come out here.
Things seem to be getting rather complicated, huh?
Yes, in their own way.
What do you think Oka Eri's ability is?
I think she has an ability
that's similar to brainwashing.
Maybe one that manipulates memory.
Why do you think that?
Before the reset, she didn't use her ability on me.
I'm guessing it might be an ability
that's difficult to use on me.
You're correct.
Here's information on Oka Eri's ability.
Thank you very much.
Her ability appears to be one
that adds and subtracts memories.
The adding effect works by planting a fake memory.
If she plants a vague mental image, the person will
create a memory based on that image on their own.
That's how Murase was shown a monkey.
She can even specify actions to some extent.
For example, she can manipulate
your memories to the point
you think it isn't just a looming danger,
but you actually feel the need to run away.
The effect Haruki is under is probably the other one.
You mean, the ability that subtracts memories?
The ability that makes you forget something.
Haruki has forgotten how to use her ability.
That's true. Right now,
I can't remember how I used to reset.
What should I do to remember?
There are three weaknesses to Oka Eri's ability.
Firstly, she needs to lock eyes with you for
at least five seconds in order for it to work.
Secondly, even though her ability
can do a lot, it's very easy to overcome.
If you're able to pinpoint it from the outside,
the correct memory will come to you.
So I'll be able to remember
how to use my reset ability?
It's theoretically possible,
but it's impossible in reality.
You were the only person in the world who
knew how to use the reset ability, Haruki.
No one around you can tell you the correct answer.
You can expect the ability-sealing
to be a permanent effect.
And what's the third weakness?
Oka Eri's ability only has one type
of effect on each person.
If she uses her ability on someone
she's already used it on,
the previous effect disappears.
Will it work out?
I'm not sure yet, but it's still better than
my previous assumptions about her ability.
Hey there.
I've decided on the stage for tonight.
The lighthouse visible from our middle school library.
Remember?
Yeah. Of course.
NO TRESSPASSING
Hey there. Long time.
It's been a long time, huh?
You were a hero to me, you know.
You're the one who saved me.
I believe that you were right.
I always have, even now.
I believe that when you first appeared in my life,
you were more right than anyone else.
But I think I was wrong.
I admired my hero, so I'm trying to become one.
But the main hero is denying that.
That's a cruel betrayal.
No matter how villainous you are, that's no good.
It's a bit too savage.
Sorry.
But I can't accept who I was two years ago.
I shouldn't have denied Fujikawa Eri.
Even with the name Fujikawa Eri, there should've
been a way for you to become happy.
I never wanted that. I'm glad I became Oka Eri.
Even so, you shouldn't have picked a method
that made you carry all the responsibility alone.
You're wrong.
Taking responsibility is what strength is.
Avoiding it is a sign of weakness!
I'm strong. It's okay if it's all my fault.
I'm going to get stronger.
I'm going to become a brazen villain!
I'm fine with living in a way that only
a strong person would understand.
Those were your words, weren't they?!
Don't you dare deny any of it!
You won't accept Fujikawa Eri, no matter what?
Don't call me by that name ever again.
Okay. That's fine.
Oh? I thought you were going to deny,
acting all hypocritical.
Now, I'm going to take the MacGuffin
away from you in a magnificent way.
I'll give it to you.
Are you messing with me? It's a fake, isn't it?!
It's the real deal.
There, you've got the MacGuffin.
That means you've accomplished
what you set out to do.
Wrong. I'm going to beat you!
I want you to understand that you're
worthless and not even worth my time!
But that's already impossible.
That's not true.
I'll easily take the MacGuffin from you!
Yeah, you can easily take this away.
You're so unfair.
I think so, too.
I see.
Let's change the rules a bit
so that you'll actually get serious.
I can see everything in plain sight from here.
I know that Haruki Misora is trailing behind you.
This is the new rule.
I'm going to plant a memory into
Haruki Misora that she'll absolutely hate.
You're going to prevent that from happening.
That's pointless.
Your memory manipulation is easy to overcome.
If she's able to pinpoint it,
she'll realize that it's wrong.
Just by noticing that it's wrong,
the memory itself will continue to remain.
If you still don't mind,
you can watch right here from the sidelines.
Bye-bye.
Where am I?
Could this be a world within the picture?
Mr. Sasano's ability...
NO TRESPASSING
Who's there?
Hey there!
I've got Asai Kei.
You're next.
Next Episode
A story of a witch who rode on a broom, flying through
the sky to knock on the window of her beloved's room.
But that's no good.
I don't believe that Kei would ever lose to you.
This is a future I didn't see.
I think I was summoned by you.
In that case, I'll take all of your memories!
I don't want to reset.
We're always simply standing in a rain of eternal sadness
That is why I need that warmth of yours
Life is but a dream we never wake up from
We repeat it over and over, praying for salvation
I kept waiting endlessly for your signal
To make sure you wouldn't disappear all by yourself
Ah, it doesn't matter where I am or what I'm doing
My heart can't go against your will
So I'd follow you even to the ends of the world
I fell in love with you at the dawn of our new world
But we kept pushing the hand of the clock backwards
And lost not only time, but our smiles as well
You're the one who brought it back
And taught me that even lies can be meaningful