Do you want that red crystal so badly?!
That worthless piece of trash?
Are you sure about this?
Let's go, Felia.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Sogo.
You must be hungry, right?
Don't want it.
Why not? Your mom told me you love curry.
I said I don't want it!
I don't want this!
I want Mom's curry!
A warm light shines upon the ground
With it, that seed can sprout from the earth
There's a magic that can overcome
cold rain, heavy winds, and anything else
So why does it push our backs?
You know we've all had days where we almost gave up
But then a strange power surges from within us,
and we forge ahead like a boy chasing the sun
At the end of the long winter,
spring's warm breath embraces us with the good news
I've been searching for you,
having waited the entire time for this day
Never be afraid of the trust held in your heart
It'll surely come to ease the loneliness one day
So even if you do return to the stars,
let's plant more seeds
Feelings That Must Be Conveyed
Do Mon's always had a cold side to him.
Are you still mad about that, Sogo?
You shouldn't fight with your father, Sogo!
You've got it wrong.
Do Mon's not my father.
Really?
He was a friend of my late mother's.
With nowhere for me to go,
he took it upon himself to care for me.
But he had no clue how to raise a child.
Nor how to cook or do laundry.
And the curry he made was nasty.
Compared to my mom's curry,
it could barely be called food.
Still...
So, what's the plan now?
Head back to Indigo?
Or go after Sogo?
You guys should head back.
Don't worry about me.
Whether he manages to protect Felia or not,
Sogo isn't coming back.
After what happened with Do Mon,
he won't be returning to the café.
So while he can either find a happy end or meet
a tragic one, they'll both be with Felia regardless.
Pretty hot and humid today, huh?
You can say that again.
I can't wait till the end of my shift.
Not Authorized
Sorry, I'll need you to step out of the car.
His ID's been deauthorized, huh?
Well, it's gotten me plenty far already.
Forgive me. Right now, I can't afford
to be picky about my methods.
Damn, I'm getting old...
That's a lot of soldiers.
Did they know we'd come here?
We can't get through?
Do Mon was right.
I'm not giving up.
I'll get Felia to the Altar, no matter what.
Sogo, here.
Is that...
It's Do Mon's, isn't it?
You need to return it to him.
But I...
Don't be like that, Sogo.
Promise me that once you get back,
you'll make up with Do Mon.
Felia...
Watch out!
I have a visual on the target.
It's the Bipedal Armor from before.
Lima has also been spotted,
along with a boy.
It's just those two?
All units, set up a perimeter!
Do not let them escape this time.
If we fail a second time, heads will roll!
You okay?
Yeah.
Stay right where you are!
Damn it.
Moura!
Artillery!
Take aim!
Fire!
Moura...
Otto!
Get ready. We're leaving.
Great. We're going back
to the mansion, right?
No. We're going after Sogo.
But he left us behind!
Why care about that massive jerk?
Because he is a massive jerk.
Can't leave without
punching his lights out first.
Isn't that right?
Yeah!
My apologies,
but the secretary isn't presently here.
That so?
Could you tell him that I'll be waiting
at Cochineal Memorial Cemetery?
Certainly.
So long as we keep them surrounded,
victory will fall into our laps soon enough.
Fire!
Moura!
Don't give it a moment's rest!
Cut off all escape routes!
Moura, the commander's unit is over there!
What?
That unit!
Gus! You were supposed
to be deployed elsewhere!
Show yourself, Do Mon!
You think you can leave me
and retire all by yourself?
My war is only just beginning!
How time flies, Ena.
Sogo, your son, is now fourteen years old.
Zone will be here soon, too.
I called him out here.
He's become the secretary now.
Pretty much the
Administrative Bureau's top dog.
He did what he said he'd do.
Some guy, huh?
I have a request for him today.
Oh, it's a request the secretary
could grant with just a click of his fingers.
I'm going to ask him to stop
attacking Sogo and the others.
You have my thanks
for getting my blood boiling again.
But today you're not on my agenda.
I know you're out there, kid.
Where's the kid?!
I'm the one he's after.
I'll keep him occupied.
In the meantime, you head to the Altar!
Sogo!
There you are.
Get over here!
Maybe you should focus on
watching your back!
What, you think this is unfair?
Al, launch it.
Okay.
You know what they say...
All's fair in love and war.
Winning is all that matters!
Moura!
Weren't you the one who taught me that,
Do Mon?!
Found Lima!
Felia!
I'll release Lima for you, no hassle.
But only if you bring Do Mon here.
Isn't he adorable?
It's a picture from his
school entrance ceremony.
This one's from the first time
we made curry together.
It was so delicious.
I haven't tasted curry that good since.
How do you know Do Mon?
Do Mon's my mentor.
The two of us slaughtered
countless people together...
Enough to fill an entire town.
You're lying!
Don't believe me?
Call Do Mon here.
I know he infiltrated the Bureau.
The Bureau?
I had a fight with Sogo for the first time.
But you know...
All these years, I never had it in me
to raise my hand against him.
What do I do?
I wonder if he despises me now.
I'd hate that!
I don't want Sogo to despise me!
I mean, I love him so very much!
Do Mon used to be like a razor-sharp knife,
but you turned him into
a dull piece of scrap metal.
You're wrong.
I know him far better
than you could ever hope to!
Do Mon didn't grow weaker.
He grew kinder!
Story of Lucifer
Son of a bitch!
Ready to shine baby
Story of Lucifer
Ready for the new world
Ready to shine baby
Story of Lucifer
Do Mon?
Ready for the new world
Roman!
Every time I looked into your eyes
I am Roman Valov,
heir to the Valov family!
And I'm Otto Moto, his butler!
I felt like I could see a world
This guy again?!
Roman!
We will not allow you to do as you please!
And just as if I was taking a deep breath
Take this!
I knew I would be reborn anew
That body of yours will soon bear fruit
She's gone! My little mademoiselle!
One day it will ripen, pure as it is now
And in its innocence, without losing its dream
Mademoiselle!
It will fall from the tree
Where are you? Where did you go?
Don't panic!
I want to know, I want to find out
Mademoiselle!
It fills me with pain, it fills me with sadness
You idiot!
I can't stop it, I can't run away
I just love you
Felia?
Felia!
Let all of my feelings soar on magnificent wings
Fly over all the worlds I never experienced
Kaon?
Sogo!
I've got Felia covered!
Tell me who I really am
And with your hands, welcome me to the free world
Found you!
Story of Lucifer
Do Mon always thought of me first.
Ready to shine baby
Story of Lucifer
Ready for the new world
He cared more about me than anyone else!
I close my eyes in this storm
And when I embrace your kind hands
Moura!
Answer me, Moura!
Destiny starts to shine ever so faintly
Moura...
We need your help, Moura!
We exchange the shortest of goodbyes
And connect
Just as stars shine upon one other
Our hearts
Love resonates with others
I don't want to lose, I grow, I accelerate
Have it your way.
That will be your coffin!
I believe in you
Sogo? What did you do?
I gaze into your beautiful eyes
Moura! You're alive!
And this incomplete heart of mine beats so fast
Let the light turn into life and connect us
To the deepest depths of the universe
So fast...
Where did it get all this speed and power?!
Story of Lucifer
Sogo was so cool.
Ready to shine baby
Story of Lucifer
Ready for the new world
Ready to shine baby
Said he's protecting a girl, like a real man.
Story of Lucifer
Ready for the new world
Beyond the beginning and the end
I can't lose to you.
You are born without a thought of the world
I refuse to lose to you!
Gus!
Let all of my feelings soar on magnificent wings
Fly over all the worlds I've never experienced
Tell me who I really am
If I lose, ten years of Do Mon's
life will have been in vain!
And with your hands, welcome me to the free world
To the deepest depths of the universe
They grow up so fast...
Goddamned brat!
I'm not...
Story of Lucifer
I'm not about to lose to the likes of you!
Ready to shine baby
Don't you dare insult Do Mon!
Story of Lucifer
Ready for the new world
He's my...
Gus!
Do Mon, I...
managed to keep her safe.
Kaon...
Thank you.
But why?
We couldn't just look the other way.
We're friends.
Besides, I have something to say to him.
Sogo's grown into a fine young man...
He'll be all right now.
Took you long enough, Zone.
Coming across a familiar scent from that day
I-Impossible...
Sogo, here.
I start to recall my memories of it
Thanks.
Sure.
What's that?
It's such a bittersweet memory
Recipes for curry.
Do Mon kept trying to recreate my mom's curry,
no matter how many times he failed.
You're always smiling at me
In these distant memories of mine
Well, did he pull it off?
Not at all.
But it became Do Mon's curry,
the best in the world.
These feelings I would never have been able to tell you
If I remained with you
Now are pouring out from me
Ena...
When I truly began to realize
Ena!
That you weren't here anymore
These tears started falling
I missed you so much!
and nothing could stop them
I knew you couldn't have died back then...
Why...
I need him to stay alone for a while longer.
Sogo...
At the end of the journey
lies the door to new beginnings.
And waiting beyond is...
Next time, on Comet Lucifer:
The Altar of Abyss.
The Altar of Abyss
Grab a ticket and join us on this adventure!