Look at me, I'm an apprentice shrine maiden now!
Yay!
I'll have books! I'll finally have books to read!
Myne shall soon join the temple as an apprentice,
and she is overjoyed at the
thought of reading books there.
Meanwhile...
Eckhart.
Justus.
Procure information regarding a commoner girl
named Myne, who is afflicted with the Devouring.
She will be joining the temple
as an apprentice blue shrine maiden.
A commoner girl with the Devouring
is becoming a blue shrine maiden?
She runs a workshop where she makes
something called plant-based paper,
and in order to be able to read books,
she did not hesitate to offer one gold
in exchange for being made a shrine maiden.
In any case, she is an odd child.
An odd child?
Precisely, so any information
you can provide is appreciated.
Find out anything you can.
Yes sir!
I have a wish, just one simple wish
Ascendance of a Bookworm
LOREM IPSUM DOLOR SIT AMET CONSECTETUR ADIPISCING ELIT FUSCE EFFICITUR LECTUS ID NISI RHONCUS PHARETRA NULLA QUAM VELIT TEMPUS QUIS ACCUMSAN EFFICITUR TEMPUS EU ANTE DONEC ULTRICES MOLESTIE MAXIMUS DONEC NON LOREM VITAE ANTE PRETIUM VESTIBULUM IN IN MAGNA MAURIS PHARETRA PLACERAT URNA AC FEUGIAT TORTOR AUCTOR EGET MAECENAS SIT AMET EROS FELIS ETIAM SAPIEN PURUS MALESUADA FERMENTUM VIVERRA VEL PORTA SIT AMET LECTUS CLASS APTENT TACITI SOCIOSQU AD LITORA TORQUENT PER CONUBIA NOSTRA PER INCEPTOS HIMENAEOS MAURIS VEHICULA DAPIBUS INTERDUM FUSCE SIT AMET NISI VENENATIS PLACERAT LIGULA ID CONDIMENTUM ODIO DUIS URNA JUSTO IMPERDIET UT COMMODO ID ULTRICES IN ELIT SED EGESTAS FACILISIS EX IN HENDRERIT IPSUM EGESTAS IMPERDIET
I hold it dearly in my heart and hope
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
It'll come true someday soon
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to
I don't have anything, nothing at all
But if I could have this one wish granted
It would fill the void inside my heart
I can feel the warm breeze blowing
And see shooting stars filling the sky
They make me feel as if
I can do anything, y'know?
In this wonderful world
Nothing is set in stone
The as-yet untold future
Shines brighter than the sun
I want to take hold of my future
With my own two hands
And write pages filled with hope
Into the book of my life
Side Story: Chapter 1
Justus' Flawless Plan for Infiltrating
the Lower City
My name is Justus.
On Master Ferdinand's command,
we, as his close aides, are infiltrating the lower city.
It's the beginning of summer.
So this is the lower city...
I'm shocked you can deal with this, Justus.
Are you not bothered by the smell?
I don't really have a choice in the matter.
Our first priority should be locating
a store that sells commoner's clothes.
What's that?
It seems we weren't careful
enough with our choice of clothing.
What are nobles doing here?
Thank you.
Oh, actually...
Have you heard of the Myne Workshop?
It produces plant-based paper.
Myne Workshop?
I'm sorry. I haven't heard of it.
I see.
These clothes smell awful too!
They'll require washing magic
to even be considered wearable.
Stop complaining.
Let's get on with the investigation.
You saw the reaction at
the secondhand clothes shop.
People here are suspicious of unfamiliar faces.
The commoners are cautious,
and have a very tight-knit community.
I'm getting a headache from the stench.
This mission is way worse than gathering materials.
I won't be able to make
any progress if you're with me.
I walked my incapacitated partner to an inn,
and headed to the Gilberta
Company to investigate further.
Mark, please walk Myne home.
That won't be necessary.
I'm meeting up with my mom at the
central plaza today to do some shopping,
and we'll go home together afterwards.
Is this the place?
I heard it's the main trading
partner of the Myne Workshop,
but it seems to be some kind of clothing shop.
Why would they trade with a workshop
that makes "plant-based paper"?
Oh, those are some intriguing hair accessories.
I'm terribly sorry,
but do you need anything at our shop?
Ah, no, it's just that I spotted
some interesting hair accessories...
I don't really need anything.
And so you came back here
without asking any questions?
Yeah. They're so cautious that I won't be able
to investigate further without arousing suspicion.
Which is why...
According to the report,
Myne's residence is close to the south gate.
I will locate it and gather information in the area.
You never fail to impress.
Even under close inspection,
you look like a simple farmer now.
I'm sorry for being so useless.
I'll be goin' now.
Try 'n' get used to it a lil' bit by the end of th' day.
I had studied my surroundings and
crafted an innocuous disguise; a farmer.
Oh, so sorry!
Ya okay?
Yeah...
Actually, what kind of business
does a farmer have here?
There's no market around here.
I'm not anyone suspicious!
I've somethin' to do 'ere, ya see.
Ya know a girl called Myne?
Myne?!
Yeah. She really helped me out, ya see.
I'm lookin' for 'er to thank 'er for it.
I don't know her, no...
I hear she makes plant-based
paper in th' Myne Workshop...
I'm telling you I don't know her!
Outsiders shouldn't wander around too much.
Don't come crying to me
if people mistake you for a thief!
Now go back to where you came from!
I won't let you off the hook if I see you here again!
I guess that's that.
I'll just ask around here instead.
We gathered so much today!
Those children are around the same age as Myne...
Perfect.
Hey, ya there!
But you know...
D'ya know a girl called Myne?
Myne?!
I-I have nothing to do with her, I swear!
Are you still scared of her?
Scared?
Yeah, she chewed him out
for breaking something of hers...
Right?
She was really nice to me, though.
Are you sure that was Myne and not Tuuli?
Yeah. Myne would never be kind to others.
Tuuli?
Myne's sister.
Hey, Tuuli!
What is it?
Gramps here says he's looking for Myne.
For Myne?
Yeah, I want to thank 'er for helpin' me out.
An' give 'er some of these vegetables I grew.
Are you sure it was Myne?
I'm pretty sure that was 'er name...
Was she with someone?
Huh? No, I think she was alone...
Then it couldn't have been her.
Myne can't walk around on her own.
She can't?
Yeah. She's quite frail, so she has to be
escorted by someone whenever she goes out.
I see. I can't believe I got the wrong person...
D'you know about th'
Myne Workshop, maybe, then?
Not really, no...
I don't!
I-It's fine if ya don't, I guess.
Sorry for holdin' ya up.
Please take this as an apology!
See ya around!
It seems I'm not having much luck this time...
She's so weak that she needs
someone escorting her, huh?
I didn't think there would be such
a lack of information in her neighborhood.
What are you planning to do?
I'll infiltrate the Merchant's Guild
at night and search for clues.
We'll make no progress otherwise.
Additionally, Myne's father
is a guard at the south gate.
Let's tail him.
Thank the gods for night duty!
I see, so you'll be a father too now!
How did you decide on the names for your children?
Names?
Yeah. I talk about it with Corinna every night,
but we can't decide on anything.
Come on, the child isn't due until winter.
You're getting ahead of yourself.
Are you okay now?
It's worse in here than outside.
Can't we move onto the next plan?
Okay. Let's go.
The next day, we went to places that trade
with the Gilberta Company to ask questions.
Myne?
That little girl, right?
She writes up supply orders by herself with no issue.
She's really something!
Yes, I know her.
She could put most adults to shame
with how she handles business.
No issues with payment either.
Everyone calls her an odd child,
but to me it seems more like she's simply exceptional.
In any case, she seems to handle her work well,
so there shouldn't be any problems
making her an apprentice blue shrine maiden.
We'll report the details upon our return.
That is all.
Since we're already here,
shall we take a look at the market?
We're done with our task.
Let's hurry back—
Just for a bit.
Sir, where did you get this book?
A noble pawned it off.
A noble?
Could I see it?
Of course! Look at it as much as you want!
The only person who ever took interest in that book,
not counting you, was a weird child.
A weird child?
Yeah! She suddenly dropped to the ground...
I understand that I cannot buy it,
but at least let me touch it!
I want to at least enjoy the sweet fragrance of ink.
Please, I beg you.
I see.
Could I buy it for this much?
She showed interest in books and
wanted to enjoy the fragrance of ink.
She's indeed quite odd.
Now I actually want to see
for myself what kind of girl she is.
Next Chapter
A Visit to Lady Corinna's House
Lord Ferdinand, the situation is blah-blah blah-blah.
I see.
Come to think of it,
the first time I saw her, she was savoring
the fragrance of ink in the sacred book.
In front of you as well, Lord Ferdinand?!
She's truly an intriguing child!
What kind of child is she?
She sets my heart aflutter!
I want to meet her! Talk to her!
You're both weird, so you might get along well.
That aside, let's see.
What kind of person is she?
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
While Justus was gathering information about Myne,
Myne received a summons from Corinna.
A summons?!
What have you done, Myne?
Side Story: Chapter 2
A Visit to Lady Corinna's House
Mrs. Corinna said she wants to see
my baptism dress and hair ornament.
Can I show them to her?
I don't think Lady Corinna
would be interested in seeing that.
I see...
I'll decline the summons then.
You can't decline!
What should I do then?
Uh...
Gods!
I can't give you an answer so suddenly.
Mom seems unusually troubled.
Yeah.
Myne, are you going to take the dress
and hair ornament to her house to show her?
Yeah, I think that's what I'll have to do.
Can I come with you?
I'll ask.
I love you, Myne!
Wait a moment. I haven't said we're going yet.
But we wouldn't decline, would we?
We can't, right?
What are you gonna do?
But...
What ever shall we do?
I wonder how I should greet her.
"It's nice to meet you.
Thank you for your invitation."
How's that?
What about me, Myne?
You should just smile and say
"I've been looking forward to it," Tuuli.
It's nice to meet you. Thank you for your invitation.
I've been looking forward to it!
Yeah, good!
It's nice to meet you. Thank you for your invitation.
I've been looking forward to it!
Mrs. Corinna! Hello!
Welcome, Myne.
It's nice to see you, Myne's mother, Myne's sister.
I'm Corinna.
Good afternoon, Mrs. Corinna!
Please come on in.
Thank you! It was very kind of you to invite us.
They're way too nervous.
Thank you for having us.
It is nice to meet you, Lady Corinna.
I am Myne's mother, Effa.
Thank you so much for your invitation.
Lady Corinna, I'm Tuuli.
I've been looking forward to this.
I'm so glad I got to meet you.
I've been looking forward to it as well.
Please wait here a moment.
I'll have some tea prepared.
I really wanted to see Myne's dress.
Thank you for taking the time to come visit me.
It's so sweet!
It's beautiful!
I adjusted Tuuli's old dress.
I'm surprised to see such adjustments.
It is easier than sewing something from scratch.
We took the parts that were too big
or too long and pinned them up,
and added a few ruffles here and there.
I mean, Mom did!
Can I ask you a few questions?
Of course, I will do my best to answer them.
This is the hair ornament.
I've never seen anything like this before.
I made the big white flower.
I see! You did a really good job, Tuuli.
Thank you!
I'd like to order some of these
to be made at my workshop,
is that fine?
Of course!
It depends on the offer.
M-M-Myne!
Hair ornaments are an important
source of income during winter.
I can't agree to this just like that.
If you really want to make them,
I'd like you to buy the right to do that.
Otherwise it'll be a problem for us.
Myne...
I'm sorry, Lady Corinna.
Please stay quiet, Mom.
This is important.
Myne...
It's fine.
Please talk to Benno about this, Myne.
I will.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Corinna's brother, Benno.
It's nice to meet you, Lord Benno.
I'm Myne's mother, Effa.
Thank you for taking good care of my daughter.
I'm Tuuli, Mr. Benno, sir.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
What do you need, Corinna?
Actually...
Mrs. Corinna wants to buy exclusive
rights to sell the hair ornaments.
How much will you buy it for, Mr. Benno?
You're joking.
I'm negotiating.
How's that?!
I can't sell it for such a small amount.
It might be better to sell it to Frieda in that case.
Hey! Isn't Lutz supposed to be selling
whatever is made in the Myne Workshop?!
Whatever is made in the Myne Workshop, yes.
Instructions are not included in that agreement.
You little! What kind of logic is that?!
Threatening me won't achieve anything.
That just doesn't work on me, Mr. Benno.
Myne's amazing.
Tuuli, Effa, this might take a while, so come with me.
Myne really is amazing.
Being able to talk business with my brother!
I've never seen Myne like that.
She gets feverish easily,
and can't help with much at home,
so I'd never imagined she could
argue like that with adults...
That's a side of her I've never seen.
Let's just leave the business talk to those two,
and have a talk about needlework ourselves.
Sure!
So pretty...
How do you make such wonderful clothes?
Could you show me, Lady Corinna?
The technique is indeed important,
but it's also very important
to see a lot of things for yourself.
Look at this, for example.
The shape of the flowers in this embroidery
is something based on flowers I picked in the forest.
If you make a habit of carefully
observing your surroundings,
it will come in handy when designing things.
I see...
I want to become an apprentice seamstress
so that I can one day make beautiful clothes
like the ones you make, Lady Corinna!
I see. Good luck, Tuuli!
Thank you!
And you used to be such an innocent child!
That's also one of the results
of your teachings, Mr. Benno.
The deal is made.
Seems like they're done.
Mom! Could you show Mrs. Corinna
how to make the hair ornament?
I will.
I'm tired.
Good job.
How much did you settle on in the end?
I'll base my prices for the hair ornaments on that.
I'm impressed you got that much out of my brother!
Your workshop has the exclusive right to sell
the hair ornaments for the next year, Mrs. Corinna.
How much was it, Myne?
Is it so much you can't tell me?
It was a reasonable price,
so I could tell you, but I'd rather not.
Tell me, Myne!
One large gold and seven small golds.
Wait a second.
Did you say "gold"?!
It sounds like a lot of money,
but it's a reasonable price for the transfer of rights!
I'm not Mr. Benno,
I don't go around overcharging people!
You did well, Myne.
Thank you!
It seems you'll be able to celebrate
your child's birth in peace!
And just like that, our visit to Mrs. Corinna's
house concluded without incident.
tell me, oh my angel
oh my lovely, let me dream again
I gently brush my hair
And put a hairpin through it
In the sea of green
A flower ornament blooms
It is a gift from my angel
It touches my forehead
Oh so gently
And it reminds me
Of the warm light that gathered
To bring my angel into this world
This fever is making me delirious
Ah, these times are so dear to me
There must have been something more
Some greater force that led me to you
Our fates tangle and unravel as we become family
I have been always living
Inside a book
But then my heart melted
And now I have experienced
The real world
Back to the main story
High Priest, I want to see
side stories of more people!
I'm hoping for that as well.
We just have to pray to the gods.
Pray?
I don't know what gods merchants pray to,
but O Goddess of Time, Dregarnuhr,
let your threads weave together once more!
Praise be to the gods.
Praise be to the gods!