Maybe I couldn't act
because a fear of taking risks caused me to hesitate.
But I'm done living like that.
These are all the daemons I can lend you.
And only I can control this one.
What are you going to do?
Save Kagari.
I'll do all that I can.
Got it.
Where's Kagari?
Okay, I see her.
I wonder what she feels as she gazes at the city.
Just what are "fond memories"?
I'm going to see for myself,
as I follow Kagari, my lodestar.
Following the path of pain
kutsuu no michi wo tadori
Was too much to continue moving forward
ashi wo tometa darou
My time was frozen
kooritsuita toki mo
Keeping my distant memories out of reach
ima wa tooi kioku wo kasunde
If there are no sacrifices
nanimo gisei ni
Is that the definition of strength I can try to achieve?
sore wa tsuyoku nareru no ka to
But I lack even the courage to let go of your hand
nigitta mama no te mo mada hodoku yuuki ga motenakute
I'll become a hero
eiyuu ni naru
I've learned that
narenai kara
For me that's impossible
sono koto ni kidzuiteta
If nothing else, I'll wish for the strength I need to protect you
semete kimi wo mamoritai sou negau
I'll forge my body into a blade
kono karada wo tsurugi ni kaete
And take the path full of obstacles
are wo deta michi wo yuku
I moved forward by defeating even my own weak self
yowakatta jibun sae kiritaoshi susunda
I wonder if I'll ever reach
itsuka todoku no darou ka
The future you wish for
kimi ga nozomu mirai ni
I'll protect you until the very end, when we welcome that day
sono hi wo mukaeru made wa boku ga mamorinuku yo
Episode 23
"Those Who Follow the Lodestar of Kagari"
That should do.
Feels like I'm playing an RPG
after not touching one in ages.
Scout-type monsters are being hunted down?
If we know where, send in an investigation team.
Sir.
You go, too.
The stage will be set soon.
You haven't found anything?
I'll put more men on it.
There must be something there.
Something...
Tear them to shreds.
Don't leave any in one piece.
The missing search party was found dead.
Was it the Key?
Send every last team we have there!
Sorry, Kagari.
I need you to be my bait right now.
How much longer?
There they are!
Okay, get 'em!
Take out a summoner, and their daemons disappear.
My work here is done for tonight.
All that's left is to go through another nightmare.
Even so, I have no choice but to keep moving forward.
"Martel showing signs of preparing
a large-scale operation."
This legit?
Yeah.
Gather everyone up later.
This 'ere is Oonishi. He was on Team Mikuni.
Remember him?
Yeah, vaguely.
Yo, long time no see.
You're Tennouji, right?
I hear you went through a lot overseas.
Yeah.
Awesome!
You actually seem pretty strong now.
So he's the one with the eyes that can see Kagari.
Pleased to be working with you all.
Who are those people?
Oh, that's the choir.
The stars of the Harvest Festa ceremony.
Team Imamiya commencing investigation.
Each squad is to report in
with their current location.
What's the matter?
Oh, I think I saw something over there just now.
What?
There! Gaia fanatics!
It's the hunters!
You head back and report this
to command! Request backup, too!
Okay.
Scout-type daemons are no match.
Guardian's already won this fight.
B36.
Moving to B37.
B37?!
Wait, that's where...
Confirmed visual on the Key!
Damn that Oonishi!
He can detect Kagari from that far away?
What could I even do there?
I'd be up against several superhumans!
Don't rewrite
Rewrite
Okay, now I can catch up!
Isn't that the daemon that killed Mikuni?
Is that you, Tennouji?
I'll call for medics immediately.
Forget me. Go after Oonishi.
He found it.
We gotta kill it.
Go.
I'll deal with this myself.
Oonishi.
Tennouji?
Glad you're here.
I'm fighting a summoner.
They're strong.
Everyone else got taken out.
A summoner?
They're defending the Key.
Their numbers?
Three daemons.
I took out one,
but the other two... They're...
T-Ten... nou...
Did you set your daemons on them?
Y-Yeah.
I knew you'd pull this crap eventually.
But I...
You are under no duty or obligation
to take part in this war!
Where's Kagari?
I destroyed Guardian's eyes.
Gaia's summoners shouldn't
be able to act for a while, either.
Is this a side effect of the rewrite?
Kagari?
Kagari!
You okay?!
Damn!
K-K...
Kagari!
Kotarou...
I'm sorry for using you as bait.
So you failed to locate the Key?
Yes.
What happened to your hand?
I hurt myself.
What's going on?
Don't look down on us, Guardian dogs!
Good grief.
Talk about pushy.
Now...
Would you kindly come along with us?
Allow me to warn you in advance.
Should it be freed from my shackles,
Martel will go out of control.
You just unleashed that monster into the wild.
Y-You're...
I expected them to have obtained the Key by now.
We must get more men on the search.
The conflict only got worse by the day.
No time...
Kagari?
Won't make... in time...
Ever since that day,
Kagari had lost her way with words.
Hurry.
Must hurry.
I know.
But it's dangerous out there right now.
Everyone's looking for you.
Sad...
Very sad...
Hey, how about we watch some TV?
A planet 18 light years away
has been determined to possess water
and an atmosphere, just like Earth.
Planet?
NASA's research team is currently...
Planet...
Water.
They're called Earth-like planets.
And they're pretty close.
Like, only around 20 to 30 light years from here.
Go.
Uh, not happening.
Close.
I meant in science fiction terms.
Not like we have rockets that can go there.
Purchase.
Buy.
You wish!
On the internet.
They don't sell rockets.
Well, people might be able to go someday.
Take a cruise on an ark or something.
Wh-What is it?
Keep going.
But relocating to another planet
is a huge undertaking.
It'd take a few thousand years, at least.
Hurry.
Like I said, it's impossible as of now.
But I'm trying to bring you fond memories instead.
It's the eve of the Harvest Festa tomorrow.
Both forces are clashing,
and the forest has become a war zone.
And the Key hasn't been found yet.
Your wounds healed up?
I can't retire over that.
Wouldn't be much of a superhuman.
How about you?
That hand of yours still not healing?
Nope.
By the way...
When'd you give birth?
They're not mine!
These girls are Nakatsu Shizuru-chan
and Konohana Lucia-chan,
superhumans like us.
I want to be a teacher here someday.
What, at Kaza High?
Guardian is planning a project that'd
send superhumans to study there.
And I'd be there to back them up.
So are those two...
Yeah, two of the candidates.
Stylish eyepatch you got there, missy.
And this one's a healthy eater.
Can I grab a bite?
Nope.
Jumping the gun a little, don't you think?
It's no more than a few years away.
Back when I attended that school,
I had a lot of fun.
I want these girls to experience that same joy.
I see.
You have my full support.
So the three of us losers
have all found our own paths to walk, huh?
Once again, I'm glad to be
teammates with you guys.
You know you're supposed to place
your hands on mine, right?
Take a hint! It's to show our camaraderie!
Oh, is that it?
All righty, then.
Show...
...our camaraderie.
Yeah.
Suzaki was right on the money.
Kashima Sakura set her plans in motion immediately.
Suzuki Bondo's role is over.
The time has come to go back
to being Tennouji Kotarou.
I've received the proposal.
I don't see any problems.
Great job.
Thank you.
This will be your final order.
Let's begin.
I always knew this day would come,
but I still cried a little just now.
Thanks for everything.
I'm sorry I sacrificed so many years of your life.
I won't waste the chance you gave me for a fresh start.
I'll make sure to see how the world changes with my own eyes.
I'm closing the chat.
Goodbye, Yasmin.
Farewell, my beloved family.
I hope you'll find a good planet.
The truth that Gaia and Guardian
have both kept hidden
will soon come to light.
Once they learn the whole story, people will change.
No, they'll be forced to change.
With the planet slowly but surely dying,
the only resource it has left is life itself.
And the time has come to dip into it.
Kagari, we begin tomorrow.
Let's go witness that moment together.
Will the "fond memories"
involving the whole planet
really be that beautiful?
Let's go see.
Let's watch it all from atop that hill.
No way.
This many summoners?
Kashima Sakura must have ordered it.
That withered old bag.
What do we do?
Initiate an emergency deployment!
Nishikujou, request additional
manpower from HQ.
Y-Yes, sir!
Kagari?
Where could she have gone?
It has to be either the power spot
where she was born, or that hill.
Finally found you.
Kotori.
You're acting kind of scary.
I feel like you'd disappear if I left you alone.
Hey, why are you helping Kagari?
That's a good question.
Can't you choose not to help her?
Then this planet will fall to ruin.
What can we do, then?
The only chance we have
is to create fond memories.
We must show off humanity's potential
to the planet. In other words...
I don't care about that!
That's...
That's not what I'm talking about!
You promised...
Promise?
You never showed me around the Harvest Festa!
You remember something from that long ago?
Guess we're all birds of a feather...
You, me, and Kagari.
Kagari?
That's right.
Kagari's all alone, too.
It's not that I don't sympathize with you,
but I'm sorry.
I'm going to choose Kagari.
Why?
Why would you do that?!
I've been planning to do this for ages.
Why are you always so...
You see, Kotori,
I always saw you as a nuisance.
You were an absolute pain.
But I feel great now.
You always disgusted me,
so this serves you right.
I...
I hate you!
Just die!
See you, Kotori.
Our eyes have reported spotting
something that resembles the Key.
Okay. Order them to move out.
I'm stealing your move, Luis.
Rewrite
Don't
Reach!
Distance to target: 500...
400...
The helicopter crashed?
What the hell was that?
A spear?
Was it a superhuman?
Don't tell me it was that rat.
Kagari.
The hiking trip is canceled.
Let's get out of here.
You're...
Good, Kagari.
Stay in control of yourself.
The planet will cease...
We don't know that yet.
The world is about to change.
The conflict between Gaia
and Guardian will end very soon, too.
Humanity will die...
Don't give up until you see what happens.
The song's growing more powerful...
What?
This thing suddenly showed up!
What is that?
It looks dangerous!
Perish, humanity.
What's going on?
Looks like this is it...
Damn it!
This pressure...
There's a formidable foe around here!
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Intercept
Run
Rewrite and intercept
Rewrite, then run
Sorry, Kagari.
Give me some time.
Knew it.
Block with arm...
Make the daemons attack
Sweep off feet
Try for a counter
Block with arm...
Make the daemons attack
Sweep off feet
Try for a counter
Block with arm...
Make the daemons attack
Sweep off feet
Try for a counter
Block with arm...
Make the daemons attack
Sweep off feet
Try for a counter
Block with arm...
Make the daemons attack
Sweep off feet
Try for a counter
Block with arm...
Make the daemons attack
Sweep off feet
Try for a counter
Block with arm...
Make the daemons attack
Sweep off feet
Try for a counter
Block with arm...
Make the daemons attack
Sweep off feet
Try for a counter
Block with arm...
Make the daemons attack
Sweep off feet
Try for a counter
Block with arm...
Make the daemons attack
Sweep off feet
Try for a counter
Block with arm...
Make the daemons attack
Sweep off feet
Try for a counter
Block with arm...
Make the daemons attack
Sweep off feet
Try for a counter
Block with arm...
Make the daemons attack
Sweep off feet
Try for a counter
Block with arm...
Make the daemons attack
Sweep off feet
Try for a counter
Block with arm...
Alter my blood to an oil-like state!
Head-on
From a jump
From right
From left
Head-on
From a jump
From right
From left
Head-on
From a jump
From right
From left
Head-on
From a jump
From right
From left
Head-on
From a jump
From right
From left
Head-on
From a jump
From right
From left
Head-on
From a jump
From right
From left
Head-on
From a jump
From right
From left
Head-on
From a jump
From right
From left
Head-on
From a jump
From right
From left
Head-on
From a jump
From right
From left
Head-on
From a jump
From right
From left
Head-on
From a jump
From right
From left
His hand
His weapon
His head
His torso
His feet
His hand
His weapon
His head
His torso
His feet
His hand
His weapon
His head
His torso
His feet
His hand
His weapon
His head
His torso
His feet
His hand
His weapon
His head
His torso
His feet
His hand
His weapon
His head
His torso
His feet
His hand
His weapon
His head
His torso
His feet
His hand
His weapon
His head
His torso
His feet
His hand
His weapon
His head
His torso
His feet
His hand
His weapon
His head
His torso
His feet
His hand
His weapon
His head
His torso
His feet
His hand
His weapon
His head
His torso
His feet
His hand
His weapon
His head
His torso
His feet
His hand
Use left hand to surprise him
Hit hard with right hand
Headbutt
Use both hands
Use a kick
Use left hand to surprise him
Hit hard with right hand
Headbutt
Use both hands
Use a kick
Use left hand to surprise him
Hit hard with right hand
Headbutt
Use both hands
Use a kick
Use left hand to surprise him
Hit hard with right hand
Headbutt
Use both hands
Use a kick
Use left hand to surprise him
Hit hard with right hand
Headbutt
Use both hands
Use a kick
Use left hand to surprise him
Hit hard with right hand
Headbutt
Use both hands
Use a kick
Use left hand to surprise him
Hit hard with right hand
Headbutt
Use both hands
Use a kick
Use left hand to surprise him
Hit hard with right hand
Headbutt
Use both hands
Use a kick
Use left hand to surprise him
Hit hard with right hand
Headbutt
Use both hands
Use a kick
Use left hand to surprise him
Hit hard with right hand
Headbutt
Use both hands
Use a kick
Use left hand to surprise him
Hit hard with right hand
Headbutt
Use both hands
Use a kick
Use left hand to surprise him
Hit hard with right hand
Headbutt
Use both hands
Use a kick
Use left hand to surprise him
Hit hard with right hand
Headbutt
Use both hands
Use a kick
Go for annihilation
Hit
Hold down
Go for annihilation
Hit
Hold down
Go for annihilation
Hit
Hold down
Go for annihilation
Hit
Hold down
Go for annihilation
Hit
Hold down
Go for annihilation
Hit
Hold down
Go for annihilation
Hit
Hold down
Go for annihilation
Hit
Hold down
Go for annihilation
Hit
Hold down
Go for annihilation
Hit
Hold down
Go for annihilation
Hit
Hold down
Go for annihilation
Hit
Hold down
Go for annihilation
Hit
Hold down
Go for annihilation
Is this where it ends?
Give up
Don't give up
Let's call it a day, then.
I'm sorry, Esaka-san.
I've done something awful.
What are you saying?
Any old weakling can remain pure.
But only the strong can win.
You are strong.
Hold your head high.
I've been betraying you this whole time
and protecting what you call the Key.
What will you do with the Key?
Show her my last piece of work.
If that stops her from wiping us out,
we'll have a future filled with promise.
Is that so?
Very well, then.
I won't let all your work go to waste.
That is my plan.
Good.
Now go.
People don't die so easily.
I won't ever forget all the things you taught me.
Thank you very much!
Hurry up and go.
The world you live in
nemuru koto no nai
Is one that never sleeps
anata ga tatsu sekai wa
And it's still so pure
mada muku na mama de
If I can leave something
moshi kono daichi ni
In the ground here
nanika wo nokoseru no nara
Let it at least be some kind of a trace
semete omokage wo
I can't even do a simple thing like gaze at the sky
sora wo miageru sonna kantan na koto mo
So I close my eyes
yurusarezu hitomi tojiru
I was only ever looking
tada hitotsu dake
For one thing
mitsukete hoshii no
Sunken in memories
kioku ni shizumu
Feelings of love
itoshisa wo
At the ends of time
ikusen no hate
I hope you stay safe
tadoritsuku anata ga
Until we meet again
sukuwareru you ni
It's fine as long as my song reaches you
kono utagoe todoku kagiri