Wow! This is awesome!
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
It's the tournament! The real deal!
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
It'd kinda be a problem if it weren't.
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
Yeah! Of course!
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
All–Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
My final high school tournament!
I'm so glad we got to participate!
I'm moved to tears!
Captain! I'm going to do my best!
That's the way, Kurashina! Show some spirit!
Why are they so hyper?
Meow...
Would it hurt to not have
this start in the morning?
We'll have to ask really nicely for
your match to be in the afternoon.
Yeah...
There are stalls, too!
Awesome!
Misaki-senpai, Mashiro Udon's
also setting up a stall here.
Meow?!
Yippee! Udon for lunch!
Our Famous
Flyer Stock
Right...
I'm sorry, flying fishies.
But you were delicious!
Mashiro!
Minori?
I'm gonna be commentating on
the matches today. Let's have a good time.
Commentating?
This tournament is actually
getting broadcast on TV.
For real?!
But if I appear on TV,
I'll end up becoming everyone's idol!
No way in hell I'm letting that happen!
You're my idol, and mine alone!
Censor her face!
Wh-What the hell?!
So where's it being broadcast?
On Shito Channel.
Four-Island-Archipelago-Exclusive Cable Channel
Shito
Channel
Oh...
Just our local cable TV, huh?
Come on, let's go check the draw already.
Four Rhythm Across the Blue
The birds and the wind
Pat my hair as if inviting me into the sky
And steal my attention upwards
As the sunlight burns my cheeks
I could look into the sky
If only I could fly like them
Open your ears and listen to the starting whistle
It shakes the wings of my heart as it resounds through the blue skies
Let's soar past these boring, monotonous days
The miracle we've been looking for is just ahead
With it, we can reach the future we've dreamed of
It lies just beyond our fingertips
Episode Five
Yeah.
Keep Calm and Carry On.
Episode Five
Yeah.
Keep Calm and Carry On.
What a pleasure to see you all again.
Satouin-san!
Oh, thanks for all your help during camp.
It's certainly been some time.
Huh? Since when were you two friends?
We formed a first-year alliance.
Is your team in good shape, Hinata-kun?
Good question.
We're inexperienced, and many of us
are making our official debuts today.
But underestimate us, and you'll regret it.
I'm looking forward to it.
Everyone, come take a look!
Satouin
Reiko
Arisaka
Mashiro
Kunahama High
1st Year
Takafuji
Academy
2nd Year
I'm up against Satouin-san?!
What rotten luck!
Inui Saki
Aoyagi
Shiori
Kairyou Academy
2nd Year
Kunahama High
3rd Year
I'm taking on Inui Saki,
a second-year from Kairyou Academy.
I've never heard of her before.
Ichinose
Rika
Takafuji
Academy
1st Year
I've got Ichinose-chan, huh?
Kurashina
Asuka
Okoze
Arika
Kunahama High
Shitou Suisan
1st Year
2nd Year
And Asuka's opponent is
a first-year from Shitou Suisan.
Another powerhouse team,
just like Takafuji.
They must be good then. I can't wait!
Carefree as ever, I see.
Wait, Okoze Arika from Shitou Suisan?
Now if it ain't Mashiro!
So you really did pick up FC.
Figures.
Someone you know, Mashiro-chan?
We've known each other since we were kids.
Oh hey, it's Li'l Tuna.
Don't call me that!
If she's the same age as Mashirocchi,
that means she won a starting spot
at Shitou Suisan despite being a first-year.
When I heard Mashiro picked up FC,
I knew I had to play against her.
So I tried my hardest.
We're in different blocks, you know.
That means we can only
face each other in the finals.
Well then, you'd better make it there.
I'll make sure I do as well.
Whoa, awfully confident there, Li'l Tuna.
Seriously, stop calling me that!
Just stop! Don't you dare call me that again!
Dear me, Arika. Once again, you forget to address
your elders with the necessary respect.
Lady Mayu?!
As my pupil, your failings are my own.
How disappointing...
Forgive me, milady!
I beg of you! Please don't discipline me!
That simply won't do.
You meanie...
Oh, my...
Rest assured.
I love you far too much to put you through that.
Milady...
Apparently it's a tradition
at Shitou Suisan for students to exchange vows
with their seniors and learn from them.
"Exchange vows"?
Let's transfer!
Not a chance in hell!
The opening ceremony will begin soon.
All participants, please assemble at the event HQ.
I'm terribly sorry for interrupting you all.
Until we next meet.
See ya, Mashiro.
It's that nice girl from back then.
So she plays FC.
U-Um, thank you very much for the—
Saki.
To all our Shito Channel viewers
at home, the wait is finally over!
I'm Hosaka Minori, first-year at Kunahama High,
and I'll be your commentator today!
Takafuji Academy
The All-Japan Flying Circus Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers are taking off!
I finally get to wear a flying suit in a match!
I can't wait!
Settle down, Asuka-senpai.
You're way too hypurr.
You look great in your suit too, Mashiro-chan!
I wanna put plate armor over this.
Uh, what.
It's almost time!
Do your best out there, team.
I'd like to make it to the second round
and face Shindou-san again.
You really are aiming
for the quarterfinals, huh?
I'm gonna rule over the skies!
Isn't that...
Business as usual with Asuka, I see.
That's the way, Kurashina!
It's all about spirit!
Yeah!
We will now hold the first match
of round one in the A Block.
Good luck out there, Mashiro-chan.
Keep it together.
I really do have the worst luck.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, I don't stand a snowball's
chance in hell against Satouin-san.
Look, you've improved a lot
since the training camp.
Have some confidence in yourself.
How do you want to go about this match?
Forget winning or losing for now.
Playing the way you want to comes first.
I...
I want to take her on as a speeder, fair and square!
All right then.
But you have to start your
low yoyo later than usual.
Why is that?
Satouin-san's an all-rounder type.
More often than not, all-rounders will adapt
their strategy based on their opponent.
But she doesn't know that you've
changed to a speeder yet, does she?
Probably not.
If we keep her under the
assumption that you're a fighter,
she's unlikely to take a shortcut.
That'll let us turn this into an all-out race.
I see. Understood.
Assuming you win the first line
sprint by a narrow margin,
you'll have the edge in speed
going into the second line.
That should allow you
to take the third buoy, too.
Got it!
It's finally time!
Second-year at the powerhouse Takafuji Academy
and self-proclaimed "Purple Rose,"
Satouin Reiko, takes on
first-year at Kunahama High
and poster girl of Mashiro Udon,
Arisaka Mashiro, in a match
that's just about to start!
Get ready...
Set!
Both players are off and away!
But what's this?
Arisaka seems to have made a delayed start!
It's all right. Calm down.
Start your low yoyo!
R-Right!
Satou-kun, your opponent's using a low yoyo.
Call me "Satouin", Captain.
Wait, what? A low yoyo?
Isn't she a fighter?
Point to Arisaka!
All right!
Now this is a surprise!
Arisaka, a first-year in her debut match,
has just scored the first point!
Wow!
Go get 'em, Mashiro!
Don't tell me she's a speeder?!
And a fast one at that!
Satou-kun, you won't beat her in a head-on race.
Take a shortcut to the third line.
Captain, "Satouin", if you please.
Point to Arisaka!
Arisaka is up, 2-0!
All right!
Awesome!
That's enough of your little game.
What do I do?
Oh, right.
Remember my practice with Rika!
All right. Nice decision.
She's hardly the same player she was at camp.
She's got a strong grasp of the basics.
However!
Speeders who stick only to
the basics are nothing new to me!
Mashirocchi's hanging in there by
using her petite frame to her advantage!
Point to Satouin!
I hope you're prepared for my counterattack!
I'll leave the rest to you, Satou-kun.
As I've been saying, call me Satouin!
Game, set!
Satouin is the victor!
Good game.
That was a good game.
Man, I lost after all.
But you were dazzling up there,
like a flying fishy!
Well played, Mashiro.
Yeah.
Thank you!
Four Rhythm Across the Blue
The second match of
round one in the B Block:
Kunahama High's Tobisawa Misaki versus
Takafuji Academy's Ichinose Rika.
Ichinose may have scored the first point,
but the match has been
completely one-sided since!
Point to Tobisawa!
Misaki-chan's so good!
I guess she's the kind of person
to step it up when it matters!
She's like a cat after a mouse.
A dog after a bone...
Or Madoka when she yells at me.
Hey, I don't yell at you that much.
Rika...
You mustn't fall back any farther.
O-Okay!
She's fast!
Go, Rika!
Whose side are you on?
Both!
Point to Tobisawa!
Ichinose's desperately struggling
to break free of this dogfight,
but Tobisawa's completely blocking her path!
I won't lose!
Oh, I see.
What are you talking about?
She's deliberately trying to bait you into touching
her so she can use the recoil to make a getaway.
What am I supposed to do?
Keep circling her.
Don't make the first move yourself.
Ignore the bait.
Roger that!
In situations like these,
the first one to make a move is at a disadvantage.
So they're planning to stall
until the final whistle?
I never knew there were strategies like these.
This is all very educational.
Game, set!
Tobisawa is the victor!
Tobisawa just eliminated a member
of the mighty Takafuji Academy!
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Ichinose
Rika
Tobisawa
Misaki
Good game!
Well played, Misaki!
That was amazing!
You're awesome, Misaki-chan!
That will do nicely, I suppose.
Tobisawa-san!
Hm?
Good game!
You totally outplayed me.
Thank you for the game.
Thanks to you, too.
Let's play again sometime.
I'll be sure to win next time!
I focused so hard on locating her
openings that I'm exhausted meow.
Well, winning isn't easy.
Yeah...
Tobisawa's all about that confidence, huh?
A tennis player who won the French Open
at the tender age of eighteen once said,
"Things won't always go
the way you want them to,
so confidence becomes essential."
All right!
I'm gonna go play with all the
confidence in the world, then!
Just try to make sure it isn't baseless.
What was that?!
The tenth match of round one will begin shortly.
Participants, please get ready.
You're facing Inui Saki from Kairyou,
but there's zero data on her.
There's no knowing how she'll play.
Don't worry about it!
If I go fast, faster, fastest,
and leave her eating my dust, I'll win!
Speed is king, baby!
It's all about spirit, spirit, and more spirit!
Well, whatever works.
Um...
My name is Irina, second of Inui Saki.
I'm Hinata.
Nice to meet you.
It is her first match in Japan.
Please don't be too tough.
So she used to play abroad, then?
Yes, in England, actually.
Well, let's both do our best.
England?
The birthplace of Flying Circus...
I've never seen Grav-Shoes like those before.
Captain... Your opponent, Inui,
is short and has a light frame.
It's possible she's an evasive fighter-type.
Pick up your pace on the first line
so you don't get caught in a dogfight.
I know!
Get ready...
Set!
Captain! She's a speeder, too!
She's quick.
So it's an all-out race?
Point to Inui!
The score is 3-0!
Can this deficit be overturned?!
Hinata, I'm having the time of my life right now!
Before my very eyes is someone faster than me.
Then what choice do I have...
but to overtake them with sheer spirit?!
Game, set!
Inui is the victor!
Bro, you were so fast out there!
I was moved to tears, Captain!
The way you stuck to
your beliefs was wonderful!
You have a talented speeder there.
Oh, that was no big deal.
Uh, it was most definitely a big deal.
Oh, right.
I've been meaning to ask
about those Grav-Shoes.
These are Avalon Grav-Shoes.
My father started the brand.
Avalon...
See you later!
C-C-Coach, it's finally time for my debut match.
Yeah. Keep calm and carry on.
It's all good!
Right now, I'm totally a flying fishy at heart!
Uh...
Your opponent is a speeder.
To start with, play by the book
and see what she does.
Got it! I'll see what she does, and then some!
I'm definitely not gonna lose!
Okay!
L-Let's h-have a f-fun game!
Now, it's time for another
B Block first-round match:
Kunahama High's flying fish-lover,
Kurashina Asuka, versus
Shitou Suisan's promising fine tuna, Okoze Arika!
Get ready...
Set!
Arika, do a low yoyo!
Sure!
What's this? Okoze's using a
low yoyo to pick up some speed!
Asuka, take a shortcut to the second line!
O-Okay!
Point to Okoze!
Here she comes!
Ambushing her at the second line.
Here I go!
What's with those wide scissors?!
But because her movements are so big,
they should be easier to predict.
Take another shortcut!
R-Right!
That was no good at all.
But I can't believe there's
a passing maneuver like that!
That's what makes official matches so enjoyable.
This is fun!
Huh?
Not knowing what's coming is exciting!
I'll take her down next time!
Point to Okoze!
Shake them up more, Arika.
Yes, milady!
Wait for the big move...
Here it is!
Whoa, look at her go.
She's matching Arika move for move!
Right! Left!
What? How is she keeping up with me?!
Right... or not?!
A tailspin?!
Impossible!
While in a tailspin...
...she pulled off an air kick turn?
Wow. Talk about a free-spirited brand of FC.
Asuka.
That's the way. Keep up the dogfighting.
Gotcha!
Game, set!
Kurashina is the victor!
Way to go, Asuka!
You were incredible, Asuka-senpai!
You were like a flying fish up there!
She's asleep?!
Wh-Why'd you suddenly fall asleep?!
Watch out! Grab hold of her!
She's surprisingly heavy!
Aw, jeez. I'll carry her to the rest area!
I'm sorry, but I was really looking forward to today.
And then I started to get nervous,
so I couldn't sleep a wink.
So that's why you were more hyper than usual.
What are we gonna do with you?
Right, almost forgot.
Congrats on your first victory.
Thank you very much!
You'd better get some sleep tonight.
We've got the second round tomorrow.
And she's already out like a light.
To Be Continued
A single lonely cloud
Floats in the sky I gaze up at
My friends' laughter and voices are growing distant
Just like how I was today
I hide away
My small sighs between the waves
I could do it so well today
But now I can't even catch up to them
You used to be so unreliable but now you've gotten so much stronger
The color of the sky changes too
The wind knows all too well
What regret and sadness feels like
Let's take to the skies again
This is where everything begins
It won't be the same as yesterday
Look, the view from here just keeps expanding
I'll fly over to those cheeks of yours
That I can see nodding in the distance
Spread out these hands you've clasped together
And let's fly together
Preview
Let's zipzap, Shindou-san.
...but I'll give it my all!
Thanks, Asuka.
Episode Six
Is That All You've Got?
Is that all you've got?