Club Activity:
Team
Class:
Reason for Withdrawal:
Full Name:
Tobisawa Misaki
For personal reasons.
Flying Circus
Notice of Withdrawal
Wha—
N-No way...
W-Wait, what?
Y-Y-You're kidding, right?
K-Kagami-sensei said she found this on her desk.
Why, Misaki-chan...
Four Rhythm Across the Blue
The birds and the wind
Pat my hair as if inviting me into the sky
And steal my attention upwards
As the sunlight burns my cheeks
I could look into the sky
If only I could fly like them
Open your ears and listen to the starting whistle
It shakes the wings of my heart as it resounds through the blue skies
Let's soar past these boring, monotonous days
The miracle we've been looking for is just ahead
With it, we can reach the future we've dreamed of
It lies just beyond our fingertips
Episode Eight
I... Can No Longer Fly.
Misaki-chan!
Misaki-senpai!
How are you at school already?!
Oh, you must've wound up sleep-deprived
after waking up too early!
So that's why you turned in that notice!
Wait, what does sleep deprivation
have to do with quitting the team?!
You're not supposed to point
that out yourself, Mashirocchi.
Ugh, keep it down.
It's too early in the meowning.
You're not serious, right?
D-D—
Derp pucker.
Come again?
Your turn. R.
Huh? R-R...
R-R-R...
Uh, this is no time to be playing word chain.
I never expected Asuka to be the voice of reason.
Talk to us, Misaki.
What are you thinking?
Come on! Can't you read?!
Notice of Withdrawal
Club Activity:
Flying Circus
Team
Reason for Withdrawal:
Cut Here
Notice of Withdrawal
Club Activity:
Flying Circus
Tobisawa Misaki
For personal reasons.
Team
Class:
Full Name:
Reason for Withdrawal:
Cut Here
Notice of Withdrawal
Club Activity:
Flying Circus
Tobisawa Misaki
For personal reasons.
Team
Class:
Full Name:
Reason for Withdrawal:
Notice of Withdrawal
Club Activity:
Flying Circus
Tobisawa Misaki
For personal reasons.
Team
Cut Here
Class:
Full Name:
Reason for Withdrawal:
Well, I got bored with it, y'know?
Not to mention the morning purractice.
We're being serious here, Misaki.
Don't worry your pretty little heads about me.
How could we not worry?!
Class is starting. Get going.
This isn't over!
Misaki-chan's not coming back, huh?
Got ourselves a fugitive, eh?
Misaki-senpai!
Look at this udon I've got for you!
Gonna be like that, huh?!
Um, Tobisawa Misaki-san of Class 2-C,
please report to the student
counseling room at once.
What the...?
Did Misaki do something bad?
Maybe she quit the team so she
wouldn't get us caught up in the mess?
What are you two doing here?
Didn't you hear Misaki-chan get summoned?
We got worried and rushed here.
Sorry, that was a trap I set.
Seriously?
I can't believe you two fell for it and she didn't.
So she hasn't shown up?
Misaki-chan!
Why would you tip off the target?
Misaki!
S-Silly me!
Misaki-senpai!
Mashirocchi!
A-Are you all right?
Mission failed.
Misaki-chan...
We still have after-school!
We'll execute phase two of
"Operation: Capture Misaki-senpai"!
The first part of the plan is as follows:
As soon as the bell rings,
Firstly, as soon
as the bell rings,
Asuka-senpai and
Madoka-senpai are
to secure the front
and rear exits
of the classroom!
Guard!
Back
Front
Step 1
Mashiro's
Great Misaki-senpai
capture plan!
Phase Two!
Asuka-senpai and Madoka-senpai secure
the front and rear exits of the classroom.
Let's stop here for today.
Uh, could you let me through?
O-Oh, sorry about that.
She got away!
Misaki-chan!
Misaki!
Tobisawa!
Captain?!
Er, I mean, ex-captain?!
Did my retirement upset you that much?!
Bro, I'm dead sure that wasn't the reason why!
Wh-What? She wasn't following me out the door?
The roof?
Cleared fur takeoff!
Oh, come on!
Kunahama Institute High School
Send
Enter your message
Mashiro
I'm so sorry!
I'm too useless (>_<;)
Waiting at the
school gates atm
Sorry! (><;) Look up!
Madoka
Up?
Kunahama Institute High School
Misaki-senpai!
It's against the rules to take off from
anywhere other than the terminals!
Why am I running away?
Misaki-chan!
Asuka?!
Gimme a break!
Misaki-chan!
Please wait!
Why are you quitting?
Did something happen?
I want to keep flying with you!
I...
can no longer fly.
Like, I stopped finding it fun, y'know?
You should stick with it, though.
You're good enough to go toe-to-toe with
Shindou-san despite having only just started.
And you're gonna take part
in the fall tournament, right?
Better get back to practice, then.
She can no longer fly?
Yes.
She said she stopped finding it fun.
If that's the case, let's turn this team
into something she'd enjoy.
How so?
Make it the FC Udon team!
What kind of team would that even be?
A team that eats udon indoors on rainy days.
How about the FC Nukazuke Pickles team, then?
Or the Sleeping-In FC team?
The Game FC team, maybe!
That's just something you'd enjoy.
Leave her alone.
Quit putting so much pressure on her.
Okay...
Well, Misaki can be pretty hard to reason with.
Besides, she might come back
all by herself eventually.
Right.
Y'know, I was worried you'd quit with her.
I want to keep getting better.
Same here.
The former captain's counting on us
to win the fall tournament, too.
Yeah. Time to grind in some practice.
A famous baseball player once said that
it's the baby steps that lead to big results!
Wow, you're a cutting-edge captain! Got it!
You're making her sound like a razor.
Are you talking about my razor-sharp wit?
Let's do our best!
"Stopped finding it fun," huh?
Do people really fall out of love
with something that fast?
And here I was glad the team
was finally getting back on its feet.
But there's no need to
force yourself to keep going.
Whether you pack it up or not is entirely up to you.
That said...
You can understand how
Tobisawa feels, right, Masaya?
Tobisawa
I'm rather curious what yer makin' for me.
You'll find out soon enough.
Huh? We're out.
Wonder if there's still enough time.
Shopping?
Y-Yeah...
My folks are out tonight, so I came to buy dinner.
Hey...
Why won't you say anything to me?
I guess it doesn't matter that I'm gone, huh?
There are more talented people left on the team.
Don't say that.
Sorry, I...
Oh, I know.
L-Let's eat.
This is great!
The curry's made with flyer stock!
Oh...
I made the fukujinzuke
and rakkyo pickles myself, too.
Eat to your heart's content, okay?
I will, thanks.
Thanks for dinner.
See you tomorrow, then—
Misaki.
What?
You asked me earlier why
I wouldn't say anything to you.
Let's just say that I get how you feel.
Because I ran away from FC, too.
Four Rhythm Across the Blue
I started playing Flying Circus in grade school.
For the longest time, I was unbeatable,
even winning the All-Japans.
At first, I was just happy that I could
soar the skies, and had a lot of fun flying.
The Prodigy
Hinata Masaya
But when I was selected to represent Japan
in the World Cup, I became... scared.
I think people instinctively feel fear
once they dedicate themselves to a craft.
We fear failure. We fear losing.
We fear encountering someone better than us.
The moment I started having those feelings,
the fun I once gained from flying was lost.
And around that time, a boy who called himself
a beginner challenged me to a match.
And would you believe it? I lost.
I felt like I'd hit a ceiling—
that it was the end of the line—
and decided to quit FC right then and there.
To be honest, I was probably
just looking for any excuse to quit.
I wanted to distance myself from FC, and fast.
But here's the thing you realize after quitting.
Running away is far from easy.
Misaki wasn't her usual self today either.
It was like her mind was somewhere else,
even while eating udon for lunch.
I've never seen her be that
apathetic toward udon before.
Don't you start on me too, Asuka-senpai...
What did she mean, flying wasn't fun anymore?
I just don't get it.
What's that sound?
Wh-What's a helicopter doing at our school?!
Avalon...?
What's a helicopter doing here?
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
What's going on? Some sort of incident?
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Kunahama Academy
2nd Year C Class
Class Log
Filming for a movie?
What's happening, Sensei?!
My sincerest apologies for the unexpected visit.
I simply wanted to suggest
a practice match against Saki.
A match?
A match against Inui-san!
Do you accept?
Not happening, sorry. It's too sudden.
I'd love to!
Kurashina?
That final was incredible!
You are...
Kurashina Asuka!
Oh, Shindou's opponent in the third round?
Perfect.
Ask for the match, Saki.
Please.
Kurashina.
Y-Yes?
If you start having a hard time,
let Masaya know immediately.
This is a practice match.
Do not push yourself.
O-Okay.
Asuka.
From the second line onwards,
go after her and force a dogfight.
Make sure you stay on the offensive.
Got it!
I'm really excited I get to play you.
Sorry, that wasn't appropriate for pre-match talk.
All righty!
The All-Japan Summer Tournament champion, Inui,
and the third-round-loser
but up-and-comer Kurashina!
This practice match is about to get underway!
Who asked for commentary?
Saki, shall we show them our beautiful FC?
Okay, Irina.
Get ready...
Set!
It's 1-0.
Inui has opened the scoring.
Saki, Birdcage.
Okay, Irina.
What's this? Inui's still as a statue high up above!
As I expected.
She plans on turning this into a repeat
of the match against Shindou-san!
Kurashina'll have to attack from below,
which will put her at a disadvantage.
On the other hand, if she goes after the next buoy,
Inui will beat her to it.
But at this rate...
Kurashina took a shortcut to the second line,
so she can't go after the next buoy unless
she either crosses or makes contact with Inui!
Coach.
Use a high yoyo to get directly below Inui!
Directly below?
I'll tell you as soon as she makes a move.
Use an air kick turn to accelerate in the opposite direction.
That should get you flying close to Inui.
Understood!
Here I go!
There she goes!
Make contact, anywhere!
Got it!
Here I go!
Once more!
Coach, she keeps fending off my attacks!
What in the world...
No matter where she attacks from,
Inui keeps repelling her in the same way.
What's going on?
Inui's sending Kurashina flying downwards
at the same angle each time.
That's just a coincidence, right?
Of course not.
It's all planned with flawless precision.
Asuka...
Create some breathing room!
You'll just wear yourself out like this!
O-Okay!
You cannot flee.
Inui-san...
Inui's got Kurashina's back sitting right in front of her,
so why isn't she moving in for the kill?
How do you like our perfect and beautiful FC?
We took what you left unfinished and perfected it.
Pull some feints, Asuka!
Vary your flight both
vertically and horizontally!
I-I can't!
No matter where I run, she's right above me.
I don't see any way out!
Forcing their opponent to dance
in the palm of their hand,
making them fly around
pointlessly to exhaust them...
"Birdcage." What a fitting name.
One minute left!
Saki, stay alert and perfect until the final whistle.
Okay, Irina.
If there's no way out,
we'll have to make one ourselves.
Asuka, use an air kick turn and fly right into Inui!
At this proximity,
it should be enough to throw her off!
Asuka!
Asuka?
I was so completely hopeless.
I even got you soaking wet, Misaki-chan.
I'm sorry.
Take a quick shower and get changed.
And then let's go grab some udon!
Oh, good idea.
B-Back to school we go, then.
Yeah!
R—
Right...
Yeah...
I...
To Be Continued
A single lonely cloud
Floats in the sky I gaze up at
My friends' laughter and voices are growing distant
Just like how I was today
I hide away
My small sighs between the waves
I could do it so well today
But now I can't even catch up to them
You used to be so unreliable but now you've gotten so much stronger
The color of the sky changes too
The wind knows all too well
What regret and sadness feels like
Let's take to the skies again
This is where everything begins
It won't be the same as yesterday
Look, the view from here just keeps expanding
I'll fly over to those cheeks of yours
That I can see nodding in the distance
Spread out these hands you've clasped together
And let's fly together
Preview
I think she's saying, "Yes, yes."
That's not what I mean.
Let's just eat.
The answer is up in the sky!
Episode Nine
The Answer Is Up in the Sky!