Hello? This is Kagami, from Kunahama High.
Yes. We've got more members now,
so if we could be so rude as to ask Takafuji,
the powerhouse school, for a duel...
If you would be so kind,
we'd love to hold a joint
training camp with you.
Takafuji Academy FC Team Training Area
Listen closely, everyone.
Maintaining the correct posture is key to field flying.
Focus on the task at hand, and get to work.
Yes'm!
You're flailing your arms, Kurashina-san.
Right!
I have to keep my arms steady.
Now your legs are flailing.
Legs steady!
Picture yourself floating in a pool. Relax your body.
Wow, she's gotten a lot better
at flying since her first day.
Misaki-senpai really is amazing.
Stabilize your upper body!
Next up, Ichinose Rika.
Got it.
H-Hey...
Second field-flying group setting off!
Four Rhythm Across the Blue
The birds and the wind
Pat my hair as if inviting me into the sky
And steal my attention upwards
As the sunlight burns my cheeks
I could look into the sky
If only I could fly like them
Open your ears and listen to the starting whistle
It shakes the wings of my heart as it resounds through the blue skies
Let's soar past these boring, monotonous days
The miracle we've been looking for is just ahead
With it, we can reach the future we've dreamed of
It lies just beyond our fingertips
Episode Three
I Just Got
a Little Fired Up.
Episode Three
I Just Got
a Little Fired Up.
What? Masaya saw you changing twice?
What a creep! He deserves a public execution!
Anyway, this training camp's got me thinking.
Is practice at Takafuji always this intense?
I can't keep up at all.
I'm so hopeless.
But that's what makes them a powerhouse.
Makes me glad I go to Kunahama.
And you're a regular starter here?
You're incredible, Ichinose-san.
Oh, no. I have a long way to go.
Speaking of Takafuji, your captain...
Shindou-san, was it?
Haven't seen him around.
He should be returning from the
students' invitational training camp soon.
Invitational? He must be good, then?
"Good"? He's the reigning national champion.
Really?
That's news to me!
Apparently he's even had scouts from
Europe's pro leagues come to watch him.
A pro in the making, huh?
No wonder they make you
work your tails off in practice.
And Satouin-san was like a drill sergeant, too.
Eh?
Do pardon my tardiness.
Speak of the devil.
I, Satouin Reiko,
have arrived to wash the backs
of you fine ladies from Kunahama.
Not again!
She had her way with you yesterday,
and she's still not done?
Let us begin,
Tobisawa-san.
Me?!
No way...
My condolences.
Wh-Where are you going?!
Hey, wait!
Are you sufficiently prepared?
Please sit still!
Stop it!
Hang in there, Senpai!
I'll watch your valiant efforts to the end!
N-No, don't!
T-Time out! Pawse!
Running simulations of the practice matches?
That's right. Why do you ask?
I'm the captain of the
Takafuji Academy FC Team,
Shindou Kazunari.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Hinata Masaya, from Kunahama High.
Nice to meet you too.
I wasn't planning to go to
the invitational training camp,
but they insisted I drop by.
How's practice?
Is it helping the Kunahama players at all?
Yeah. Thanks to you, we've improved a lot.
But...
But?
To be honest, Takafuji's way out of our league.
I don't see this camp benefiting you in any way.
So why did you agree?
Well, for one, because it was
Kagami-sensei's request.
And also partly because I idolized
a certain player in the past.
I picked up FC because
I wanted to be like him,
but he disappeared from the spotlight.
Beating him in a match was my dream.
That's why I agreed to this training camp.
Hinata-kun,
could I ask you to play against me?
I don't play FC anymore,
so I can't face you. Sorry.
You say you quit, but then why come back?
Was it the girl who supposedly used an
air kick turn to score against our vice captain?
Well...
I guess I'll see for myself tomorrow.
Eat to your hearts' content, my dears.
Eating well is the first step
to developing physical strength.
Here you go!
Hey, Bro, that's your fifth bowl!
Thanks for the food.
Done already, Arisaka-san?
I don't have much of an appetite.
And you sure have a lot of meat
on your plate, Ichinose-san.
Well, I do love my meat.
You're stuffing your face,
too, Kurashina-senpai!
I need to build up my strength!
Man, if only I'd brought my nukazuke pickles.
How could I furget?
That's Misaki-senpai for you.
Marches to the beat of her own drum.
Your attention please, everyone.
Tomorrow's the last day of camp.
We'll be holding practice matches
between Takafuji teams,
and between Takafuji and
Kunahama representatives.
Matches at last!
I can't wait!
Let's do our best.
But I'm still such a newbie.
I expect everyone to do their absolute best!
Yes'm!
You're eating too much, Bro.
I'm not even close to done!
Ta-da!
I feasted my eyes on it in the locker room earlier,
but you really do look awesome, Misaki-senpai!
You're so sexy, I want to jump—
That looks great on you, Tobisawa-san.
It's my junior high suit.
I brought it along in case we had matches.
It's better than a swimsuit,
but this is still pretty revealing.
Quit ogling her with such
lecherous eyes, Hinata-senpai.
More importantly, look at this.
Kunahama
Takafuji
Match 1:
Kurashina Asuka
Ichinose Rika
Arisaka Mashiro
Satouin Reiko
Tobisawa Misaki
Shindou Kazunari
Match 2:
Match 3:
It's the draws for the matches.
Lemme see!
Arisaka Mashiro
The Takafuji reps are all starters!
Not to mention Shindou-san's playing, too!
We're gonna get steamrolled!
Huh? I don't see the captain's name on here.
Forgive me!
Not even my iron abs
could subdue this stomachache!
...he said.
Wait, why am I up against Shindou-san?
They asked for Kunahama's current best player.
Hey.
Shindou-san.
Let's have some good games today.
Oh, so this is the guy.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
So you're not the one facing me, huh?
I heard you played well
against our vice captain.
N-Not at all. I only scored one point.
Considering you'd never played FC before,
scoring even a single point against
her is an amazing feat by itself.
Your second's instructions
must have been on point.
Let's have a good game.
Later.
Uh, I'm the one you're up against, you know.
Yeah, yeah.
Let's go.
Let's have a good game.
I-I'll do my best!
You're up against a speeder.
Take a shortcut and head her off.
Okay!
Just keep your eyes fixed on your opponent.
I'll tell you what to do.
Got it!
Get ready...
Set!
Take a shortcut, Kurashina-san!
R-Right!
Point to Ichinose!
That's one point down!
What was that Ichinose-san just did?
That's called a low yoyo.
By descending, you take advantage
of Earth's gravity to accelerate,
and then use that acceleration to gain altitude.
It's a move that increases flight speed.
I'll ambush her.
Kurashina-san, follow her.
Sure!
Attacking!
Oh, no, you're not.
Whoa! She's fast!
You don't have time to be impressed!
R-Right!
Wow, this is so exciting!
Don't chase after her!
Take a shortcut to the third line!
Okay!
The second point...
...is mine!
Point to Ichinose! 2-0!
Hey, she's using a low yoyo again!
Which means she'll come back up, right?
Exactly. But we're gonna stop her before she does.
Fly 45 degrees downwards!
Okay!
That's the way.
Catch me if you can!
Oh, you can't!
Smart move.
What was?
She halted her descent and rose immediately.
She sacrificed the speed she was building up.
She's playing that way because
she knows her opponent's a beginner.
She's good, that Ichinose-san.
Kurashina-san. Forget about that and move on.
I think I'm starting to get it.
What do you mean?
Call it...
intuition.
Point to Ichinose.
She's coming right at her this time!
I'll go after her!
And that zigzag move just now?
Scissors.
You move left and right to confuse your opponent.
But while she did get confused,
she's still barely keeping up.
Yeah.
Kurashina-san's movements have clearly
gotten better since the start of the match.
She's the type that thrives on competition, huh?
Is your tummy okay, Bro?!
Don't worry about it!
4-0!
Keep your eyes on Ichinose-san
and predict her movement.
Understood.
I'll go after her.
Wait...
It's a high yoyo.
Another point is mine!
She's going to touch her back!
An air kick turn?!
I did it!
Point to Kurashina!
All right!
The match is over!
In the end, I could only score one point again.
I'm totally hopeless.
Nah.
You've gotten a lot better,
and not just at the basics.
I couldn't believe my eyes.
Wouldn't you agree, Misaki?
Yeah. You're improving like crazy.
Wait!
W-Wait, I-I'm up next.
Shall we go, Arisaka-san?
I'll work you over nice and good.
No!
Four Rhythm Across the Blue
The match is over!
Satouin Reiko of Takafuji Academy wins 20-0.
You're too harsh, Sarge.
Excuse me?
Well, uh, good game.
Please make sure you put up
a better fight next time.
'Kay...
Too bad, Hinata-kun.
Looks like you're going to lose all three.
Captain.
Shindou—
Hey, I haven't exactly
lost the last match yet.
Perhaps.
Well, I hope it's a good
learning experience.
Them's fighting words, buddy.
Don't lose your cool, Misaki.
Don't worry, I'm good.
I just got a little fired up.
The next matchup:
Shindou Kazunari of Takafuji Academy
versus Tobisawa Misaki of Kunahama High.
Let's have a good game.
Yes, let's.
Shindou-san's an all-rounder.
You're a fighter, so you have a
disadvantage when it comes to speed.
Yeah. I'll start by taking a shortcut.
Good idea.
Get ready...
Set!
Step on it, Misaki!
What's wrong?
Shindou-san's insanely fast!
H-He's so quick!
Point to Shindou!
1-0!
A low yoyo!
Cut him off below!
I know!
This is but a mere glimpse
of the captain's explosiveness.
Even Grav-Shoes calibrated for a speeder
can't account for his extraordinary speed.
No wonder he's the reigning champ.
So?
What next?
Just hurry up and take
a shortcut to the third line!
Roger!
Point to Shindou!
That makes it 2-0.
He's only getting started.
Hang in there, Misaki-senpai!
I'll get him this time!
Say, what do you make of this?
Shindou-san stopped?
If he'd shaken her off,
he could've taken the fourth buoy with ease.
He's kinda uncanny.
He's toying with me, isn't he?
Don't fall for his provocation, Misaki.
Did I ever say...
how much I hate people like him?
Calm down!
Don't take the bait!
I could use my speed
to keep racking up points,
but that would hardly be
any form of practice for you, no?
Cut to the chase.
I'll throw you a bone and
take you on in a little dogfight.
"Throw me a bone," you say?
Throw you a bone, yes.
Misaki.
Stay calm but take the bait.
Huh? You told me not to earlier.
I'm telling you to let your
body rage with a cool head.
Uh, I'm not sure I follow.
But the bottom line is I can
zipzap with him in a dogfight, right?
That's right.
Done with your little conference?
Yeah.
This what you mean by
a raging body and cool head?
Something like that.
Now fly around and zipzap
to your heart's content.
Roger that!
You've got some rather amusing
offensive maneuvers.
Gee, thanks!
That's one point, for starters!
And this makes it...
two!
Point to Shindou!
He scored twice!
Go wild, Misaki!
I don't care what you do!
Swing your arms, legs, and body around!
Easy for mew to say!
How will you attack me this time?
It's like he knows exactly
what she wants to do.
He's the reigning national champion.
He knows all there is to know
about FC theory and its basic moves.
Still, his reflexes are crazy.
I don't really get it,
but I do know they're both really good!
Not coming at me?
I wanna wipe that ugly smile off your face!
Then why don't you take this more seriously?
You're a fighter, and yet you're letting
an all-rounder toy with you.
Isn't that just embarrassing?
Misaki, focus on defense!
Don't wanna. I'm gonna attack.
No!
Don't wanna!
Oh, come on.
Misaki-senpai, an udon buffet!
All you can eat!
H-How about that?
Listen to me, and I'll feed you plenty!
Fine, I'll listen to you.
All right!
Yay!
Listen up, Misaki.
Ignore any openings you see to attack.
Shindou-san's just luring you in.
Just stick close to him,
and keep dodging his attacks.
What's your plan, Hinata?
In a dogfight, Shindou-san
doesn't make the first move.
He's looking to land counters?
Yes.
I think that's our best shot.
You should attack me, Shindou-san.
What, too scared?
Am I, now?!
She dodged it!
Stick close!
I know!
You're awfully persistent.
That I am!
Amazing. She's not faltering
in the least against Shindou.
She's sticking to him like glue!
Not half-bad, I must say.
Tobisawa-san's awesome!
Won't take no for an answer, eh?
No, I won't!
You're mine!
Damn, I attacked!
No udon?!
Yes, udon!
She did it!
Way to go, Misaki-senpai!
N-No way...
She scored against the captain?!
The match is over!
Shindou wins 4-1!
Takafuji Academy
Fukutome Branch School
Thank you so much!
Thank you, too.
That was more productive than I expected.
Do you really think so?
H-Hey...
Of course.
Sorry about my provocative style of play today.
I'd like to see more of your skills.
Let's save that for the summer
tournament, shall we?
Hinata-kun.
Yes?
I'm looking forward to seeing
all of you get better.
Hey, you'll get hurt flying asleep!
Jeez.
Oh, right, Hinata-kun.
Ichinose-san said she wasn't mad
about the changing thing anymore.
Oh, that's a relief.
Misaki-senpai.
The training camp is over now,
so why don't we go grab some udon?
Oh, yeah! All-you-can-eat udon buffet!
But first...
Masaya!
Can we practice a bit now?
Right now?
Just a little bit.
Great!
Okay, Mashiro, Kurashina-san. Let's do this!
Seriously?
Hurry up!
All right! Let me join in!
You're not invited, Captain.
Why not?!
To Be Continued
A single lonely cloud
Floats in the sky I gaze up at
My friends' laughter and voices are growing distant
Just like how I was today
I hide away
My small sighs between the waves
I could do it so well today
But now I can't even catch up to them
You used to be so unreliable but now you've gotten so much stronger
The color of the sky changes too
The wind knows all too well
What regret and sadness feels like
Let's take to the skies again
This is where everything begins
It won't be the same as yesterday
Look, the view from here just keeps expanding
I'll fly over to those cheeks of yours
That I can see nodding in the distance
Spread out these hands you've clasped together
And let's fly together
Preview
Hurray! Hurray! Mashiron!
Hold it right there!
Meat makes me happy!
Episode Four
Meat Makes Me Happy!