A single lonely cloud
Floats in the sky I gaze up at
My friends' laughter and voices are growing distant
Just like how I was today
I hide away
My small sighs between the waves
I could do it so well today
But now I can't even catch up to them
You used to be so unreliable but now you've gotten so much stronger
The color of the sky changes too
The wind knows all too well
What regret and sadness feels like
Let's take to the skies again
This is where everything begins
It won't be the same as yesterday
Look, the view from here just keeps expanding
I'll fly over to those cheeks of yours
That I can see nodding in the distance
Spread out these hands you've clasped together
And let's fly together