That is one adorable cat.
Nice... to meet you.
Nice... to meet you, too.
It's beautiful.
Indeed.
I'm reminded of Sark's night sky.
The sky there was really pretty, too.
That was right after we met.
Soon.
Kagami Aoi's perfect and beautiful
FC will be within our grasp soon.
Her Angelic Halo...
Captivated by the beauty of its dazzling light,
we've pursued it ever since.
Forever striving to approach it...
To surpass it.
Saki!
This view reminds me of all our struggles.
Our ceaseless efforts will soon bear fruit, Saki.
Yes,
Irina.
Four Rhythm Across the Blue
The birds and the wind
Pat my hair as if inviting me into the sky
And steal my attention upwards
As the sunlight burns my cheeks
I could look into the sky
If only I could fly like them
Open your ears and listen to the starting whistle
It shakes the wings of my heart as it resounds through the blue skies
Let's soar past these boring, monotonous days
The miracle we've been looking for is just ahead
With it, we can reach the future we've dreamed of
It lies just beyond our fingertips
Episode Ten
Is That for FC, Too?
All right, another lap.
Okay!
You want us to keep running?!
Trail running is the ideal way
to develop the stamina,
lower-body strength,
and jumping ability required for FC.
Not to mention coping with
unpaved and uneven ground
will help you learn to recover
your posture during dogfights.
Inui-san's always in control
of her opponent's position,
so we'll need to put in this level
of effort to drag her into a dogfight.
I ran out of stamina during
the summer tournament,
so I need to work on my conditioning.
Okay, I'll set the pace for the next lap.
Follow me, girls!
Okay, Ex-Captain!
I'm gonna win this time, too!
Wait for me!
What're you even doing here, Bro?
What purpose does this training serve?
Swimming exerts your entire
body's muscles equally,
so it's the perfect way to
refine membrane control.
Training underwater also improves lung capacity.
Think of it as a more strenuous dogfight of sorts.
Stunning, Asuka-senpai!
Get ready...
Set!
Okay, I'm up next—
Go home already. You've got college
entrance exams to study for.
Quit forcing me to face reality!
Noses to the grindstone, I see.
How nostalgic.
Back when you'd just picked up FC,
flying put a smile on your face much like theirs.
Their expressions reminded me of that.
All right, that's a wrap.
After you get home,
be sure to do your stretches before bed.
Good work!
I don't think I've ever put so much effort
into something my whole life.
Should I get some running in before bed, too?
Get a hold of yourself, Asuka-senpai!
There isn't much time left
before the fall tournament,
so we'll have to focus on FC
throughout the breaks.
Practice starts at 6 AM sharp, tomorrow.
Roger that, Coach!
Think you can do that without dying, Misaki?
6 AM? Seriously?
No problems there!
As usual, I'll be your personal alarm clock,
so sleep as soundly as you like!
Forget it! I'll wake up by myself!
Whoa, someone's motivated!
Way to go, Misaki-chan!
Birdcage isn't the only thing
Inui has going for her.
If we're to stand a chance,
we'll need a trick or two up our sleeve.
Apart from the current practice regimen,
is there anything else
I can do to help the team?
Anything else at all?
Tobisawa
Safe...
Suck on that...
alarm clock!
It's a miracle!
I went to wake Misaki-senpai up, but...
Good morning.
Guess that goes to show how much
I'm itching to play FC right now.
Asuka?
Oh, good morning!
Morning.
You came early?
Yes. I've been here since before dawn.
D-Dawn?
Too early!
I'm just so thrilled I can fly again.
Sorry.
Well, it's nothing to apologize for.
Masaya!
Start the practice already!
O-Okay!
Don't you think they'd be able to give
Inui-san a run for her money right now?
Yeah.
They've shown solid improvement
in their stamina and fundamentals,
all of which are crucial in a match.
Dealing with Inui's perfectly
choreographed movements, however,
will require more flexible
offensive and defensive skills.
Unfortunately, we don't have the
manpower to train those efficiently.
Oh...
Well, we're not exactly a large team like Takafuji.
Whatcha doing, Mashiro?
I'm calibrating my Grav-shoes for fighter use
so I can dogfight with you later.
All right!
Done and dusted!
Cleared fur takeoff!
Mashirocchi!
Mashiro?!
Spread your arms and legs wide and relax!
O-Okay...
That nearly gave me a heart attack!
You forgot to switch on the balancer
after calibrating it, didn't you?
I guess so...
You pulled off some amazing
moves just now, Mashiro-chan.
Uh, it wasn't on purpose, you know.
I wanna try spinning at full speed, too!
A-Are you serious?!
Hey, Asuka!
Are you sure about this?
Yep!
Be careful.
I will.
Fly!
A-Amazing!
Wait, why are you fighting it?
Well, uh, how do I put this...
Remember, Asuka-senpai!
High-speed spinning!
Here I go!
Spread your limbs as far wide as you can!
Wow, I can't even fly straight.
Balancers reduce your Grav-shoes' sensitivity,
which makes it easier to fly,
so if you turn them off,
the Grav-shoes will be responsive
to finer membrane control,
but you'll lose all stability and
even the capacity to fly straight.
So it's kinda like taking
a spacewalk without an MMU?
S-Something like that, yeah.
Anyway, let's get back to practice.
Okay!
Indeed, I expected no less from Europe's finest.
They certainly make for great sparring partners.
Saki,
unlock your balancer.
To the first phase?
No, you've already perfected
its use at 50 percent unlocked.
Let's proceed to the next phase.
Okay.
Second phase...
100 percent unlocked.
Four Rhythm Across the Blue
Wow, I can't believe you woke up
early two days in a row!
It's a miracle!
I hope hell doesn't freeze over
and cause something terrible!
Lay off.
Today, let's start with practice matches—
This voice...
Don't tell me...
S-Satouin-san?
Why a fishing boat?
See? Something terrible happened!
Don't blame me.
How do you do, ladies and gentlemen?
Good morning.
M-Morning.
Thank you for coming all this way, Satouin-san.
What? You called for them?
Yes.
I texted them, asking if they wanted in.
Asuka?
Now then, Kurashina Asuka-san.
You're challenging me
to the rematch we agreed on
during our first meeting, I take it?
Very well!
You wish to duel me, knowing full well
that the fall tournament approaches?
I must commend such mettle.
I've brought Ichinose-san
to serve as our witness,
so let us have a fair and honorable contest!
Th-That wasn't what I meant!
I was just asking if you wanted
to join us for practice.
What?
I-I see how it is.
So we utilize this opportunity to
observe how the other is doing,
and reserve the rematch for the tournament?
Pleased to be working with you again.
I'm glad we can practice together once more.
Let's have fun, Mashiro.
Thank you.
The more sparring partners we have,
the better prepared we'll be to take on Inui.
Naturally, I too have every intention
of defeating Inui Saki.
Captain Shindou's honor shall be avenged
by none other than myself, Satouin Reiko!
Sh-She's awfully fired up.
Switch.
Next up, Asuka.
Got it!
We're on standby.
Okay!
Listen up, Asuka.
You have to slip through those three's
attacks and touch the second buoy.
The time limit is two minutes.
Got it!
Okay, Satouin-san,
Ichinose-san, and Mashiro-chan...
Let's do our best.
Set!
Mashiro, going for the kill!
There!
Got you!
You're wide open!
Inconceivable!
She dodged it?
It's practically impossible
to see attacks from above.
That's pretty scary, if you ask me.
Inui's FC is all about maintaining
that position of dominance.
I did it!
Asuka-chan's amazing.
Tell me about it.
Asuka really is amazing.
But I have my sights set higher.
I need to visit the pharmacy.
What's wrong?
I kind of sprained my wrist.
Huh? Where's the new captain?
Madoka went back home to check whether
Shion-senpai is studying as he should be.
She sure has it rough.
Let's wrap up early today
so you can all get some rest.
Okay.
See you tomorrow, then.
You're going home already?
What about udon?
I'll pass today. Sorry.
I'm totally up for some udon with meat.
Can I come over?
Yeah! Yeah!
Oh, it's a little kitty.
U-U—
Um...
Wh-What are you doing here?
I came to see her.
I'm not allowed to keep her at the dorm.
Is that so?
That's an adorable kitty cat.
Mind if I pet her?
No.
Come here.
She hates me.
She's a shy one.
Don't let it bother you.
I guess.
Oh, right!
Thank you for playing me the other day.
I'm really sorry I wasn't able to
put up much of a fight, though.
But I'm practicing really hard right now so I can
have an exciting match with you next time.
So look forward to the fall tournament—
That's out of the question.
Our FC is nothing like yours.
Irina and I will always be the victors.
Inui-san...
Is that for FC, too?
Of course.
At times, it is necessary to have a clear mind.
Satouin-san told me that you're
training yourself here now.
Can I help you?
I want you to teach me FC.
Why me?
Shito Bus
Iron Mall
Destination: ferry port
You said before that you enjoy
being in a state of fear.
I want to know how fun fear can be.
Well, then.
Where to begin?
Where'd you go yesterday, Misaki-senpai?
I sent you ten whole messages filled with love!
Sorry. I had some stuff going on.
How's your wrist, Asuka?
It's all right now.
Heal up in a jiffy, youngsters do.
You sound like the friendly neighborhood
housewife, New Captain.
Seriously, enough with the "new" alread—
Good morning.
Allow me to join you.
I asked him.
Let's have a good time.
Strategy meeting to decide on a tactical game plan vs. Inui Saki
Menacing
High Yoyo
Beating Inui Saki.
We've practiced as hard as we could,
focusing on just that one goal.
Satouin-san, Ichinose-san, and even Shindou-san
are giving Asuka and the rest a helping hand.
So I...
Is that the answer you found?
Yes.
I want to do everything I can to help them, too!
I see.
Very well.
I'm off.
Masaya...
This is nothing!
Shindou-san's imitating Inui-san's movements.
He mastered them after just one look?
That's the King of Kings for you.
Feral combat instincts...
You're starting to display an asset
Kurashina-kun doesn't have.
Why, thank you very much!
Misaki...
You're getting too worked up and
losing track of your surroundings.
Coach?
Hinata-kun?
Those Grav-shoes...
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Look at the sky
Keep looking at the sky
The answer is right there
Asuka!
Y-Yes?
Take me on in a dogfight.
Throw a kitchen sink at me for all I care.
Just score a point against me!
Got it!
Fly!
Things are getting kinda crazy.
That move...
Sonic Boost, not unlike Inui-kun's sudden elevation.
An explosive acceleration move that uses
slight movements to trim the membrane.
Hinata-kun had already mastered
it back in grade school.
Welcome home, Masaya.
You're too predictable!
Mix things up to confuse your opponent!
O-Okay!
If your opponent's heading you off,
use a Sonic Boost to shake them off!
Amazing.
I've got your back—
I-Incredible!
What was that move?
Blaster Roll.
Together with Sonic Boost from earlier,
they were originally Kagami-sensei's special moves.
Kagami-sensei's?
I aspired to be just like her.
And I wanted to use the same moves she did,
so I begged her to teach me.
Though if anything could be called
hell on earth, that was it.
Shall I remind you...
of that hell once more?
All of you, come at me together.
I'll teach you my ace in the hole.
Our FC is beautiful.
Just as Kagami Aoi's play style was.
We'll bring the world to
its knees and make it admit
our perfect FC is superior
to that circus imitation.
To Be Continued
A single lonely cloud
Floats in the sky I gaze up at
My friends' laughter and voices are growing distant
Just like how I was today
I hide away
My small sighs between the waves
I could do it so well today
But now I can't even catch up to them
You used to be so unreliable but now you've gotten so much stronger
The color of the sky changes too
The wind knows all too well
What regret and sadness feels like
Let's take to the skies again
This is where everything begins
It won't be the same as yesterday
Look, the view from here just keeps expanding
I'll fly over to those cheeks of yours
That I can see nodding in the distance
Spread out these hands you've clasped together
And let's fly together
Preview
What is this feeling?
How's that? Did it fire you up some?
You're so cool, Misaki-chan!
Episode Eleven
I Refuse to Lose!
...I refuse to lose!