History is outdated,
and I'll rewrite it by my own hand!
Now, time to raise the curtain!
I-Impossible...
How can this be?
W-We must fight back!
Military Minister, we have to
halt the enemy's incursion!
R-Right!
Drive out the rebels!
No, kill them all!
Yes, sir!
Curse you, Liscar!
Prime Minister's Official Residence
Are you trying to mimic me, Schwarz Diese?
Your Excellency, where are you going?
I'll deal with this myself!
That's how I've always done things!
The Heavenly Gate's been breached!
Sir?
Beevee Liscar...
Let's go stop him!
I wake up, tired
So sick, bored, and fed up
I was never like this, I even had dreams, too
No one can stop me, bully me or suppress me
Can we ever break free of this miserable life we're living?
We'll never stop, we'll find our way, always, if we pray
I hear them coming for me now
Trying to lure me out
And all this time, I knew where it was
So I'm fired up and ready, looking for a good fight
So break it down and never give up
This is your only chance to change the world, so rise up!
It's your life!
Now is the time!
Fight for your life!
So don't cry out to stop! Not until you've won!
Break free of these chains
And give it all you've got!
Episode 12
Powerless Soldier
You guys are worse than pebbles!
Get lost, dirt!
Why stand on the battlefield if you lack resolve?
That's just stupidity.
Why's it like this?
There's no way the enemy
is a large force, right?
It's no exaggeration to think of "genuine"
Fairy Soldiers as mighty warriors.
You experienced the War of Unification.
Aren't you "genuine" too?
Yeah, that's right.
Since the director's gone, I'll stop Liscar!
Friendlies, I knew it!
You're with Dorothea, right?
Military Minister Bohme?!
Come under my command! We can get
around in front of them if we go up!
Free...
You don't have to do everything
this guy tells you to.
All right.
In U.E. 481, Prime Minister Golbarn
Helwise was the king of Cidal.
He launched an invasion of neighboring Timoon,
by the emperor's imperial command.
At the time, who ever foresaw that
Cidal would later achieve unification?
I was still a child.
Yes, it was 24 years ago.
I was in the Ainedern military when it happened.
I thought the move was the decision of a madman.
I figured the imperial command had been falsified.
However...
Garlan Battle, the Knight of Cidal,
took Emperor Castal Harol away
from the imperial capital Mazria,
which at the time was under the
Kingdom of Ledrad's control.
That incident changed things.
Yes.
The order maintained by Ledrad's
manipulation of the emperor,
with my native Ainedern acting as accomplice.
Order?
Conflict was non-stop,
but the supremacy of Ledrad and
Ainedern almost never wavered.
Golbarn overturned that framework
by obtaining the playing piece that is the emperor.
Once unification happened, I was convinced
he would become emperor himself...
But he remained a loyal subject.
That's not it. He feared the stigma
of being a usurper.
Go, Eizenkopf!
S-Stand your ground! For His Imperial Maj—
It stinks.
Peace makes people rot.
What a stench!
Reinforcements!
Fall back for now!
I didn't know such a passageway existed.
It's been said that not one person knows
every little detail about the palace.
They're a floor below us.
Just like I predicted.
This way we can get ahead of them.
Military Minister!
You have a message?
Yes, sir! Reinforcements from the West Gate!
They're currently stopping the enemy's advance!
Oh! Who's commanding them?
Well, it's...
Don't take me lightly.
Rondacia is my turf. I won't let
rebels trample it any further!
Keep the heat on them!
Don't stop firing!
The idiots are wasting their damn ammo.
It's like old times.
During the War of Unification,
this kind of fighting happened every day.
Are you enjoying it?
Of course.
Here goes.
Wow!
No, don't retreat an inch!
We'll stop them here!
Are you guys... dirt?!
Or are you pebbles?
There's too much blood on my hands
Fight! Show me what you're worth!
Take him down!
Despite what anyone says
Where do you die?
We've spent so many years
That's for you to choose.
Killing each other to grasp victory
Follow the colonel!
Contradicting between justice and evil...
Such is the world we live in
So, lets move on!
Put an end to these sleepless nights
Why do people fight, anyway?
Put an end to this waste of human life
I can't think of any reason
to take a fight this far.
Look deep inside—Is this your war?
Endlessly repeating these nightmares and realities
Rethink—What are we waiting for?
Fighting is always scary.
We need to fight against this world
Raise your first, break through this world!
Hold your spirit tight
Escape from this Hertzsprung gap
Looks like they haven't started yet,
so you stand by.
It's like grasping sand slipping through your fingers
See you later, Marlya.
Some things are limited, you can't always hold on to them
So we must keep faith
Focus on one direction
Trust your partner to keep you alive in this world
Contradicting between justice and evil...
But I don't want to run away.
Know thy enemy
Not until I make that guy, Liscar, pay!
So don't hold your breath in!
Release your endless possibilities
Tomorrow? You never know!
Look deep inside—Is this your war?
Keep your eyes open
Remember why you're standing here
Rethink—What are we waiting for?
Now!
Military Minister!
R-Right.
We need to fight against this world
Charge!
Shut down this deep, dark history
Tomorrow we'll wave our flag
Escape from this Hertzsprung gap
Oh?
They were lying in wait.
I think I'll wave goodbye to my weaker self
Return fire!
Ozz.
And try to become stronger every day
I won't ask you to help out.
Just keep watching!
Even if it's a needless, worthless wish, hey
This is what I've been waiting for.
I'll move forward to a new day
Not bad.
Oh, really?
Oh?
Yeah, that's the way!
You think you're superior?
Let me cut you down to size!
He's on par with the colonel!
If we don't stop him, the fighting won't end!
Colonel! From the rear, too!
Beevee Liscar!
This isn't an age of war anymore!
Nobody asked for this!
Doesn't matter what age it is!
I never change!
Forward.
Free.
When you grow afraid and lose sight of your path,
that's the time you go forward.
Too true, Jet!
Follow the colonel and go around outside!
I've been inside, eyes closed
Not bein' myself, and I won't deny
That we're born and will die alone
But through the tears we've shed
It's clear 'n' simple, I bet
We're made to live for other's sakes
No one can live all by 'emselves
That's why we have each other
Yes, just like that!
You're better than I expected!
You remind me of Jet Grave,
the guy who used to wield Verosteal!
I won't be afraid!
I won't look behind or walk off this road
You talk too much!
'Cuz you 'n' I, we ain't alone
I will be okay!
Gravitation won't do me any harm
'Cuz I've got you
I'll always have your back
And you'll always have mine
We're never, ever alone
But you're not there yet!
Yeah, I don't need you to tell me!
Never be afraid!
Never look back to the past you've walked through
That path still led you here to me
My goal was never to beat you one-on-one!
You will be okay!
Even when you're feeling powerless
Ozz, we'll get revenge for you!
'Cuz I've got you
I'll always have your back
And you'll always have mine
Thanks for waiting!
Colonel!
We're never, ever alone
We of Dorothea will perform our duty!
It won't be long now.
Still, I'm surprised you gained an ally in
Christoph Rahn, a surviving Ledrad royal.
It's thanks to him I got the palace plans.
Not that he's my only collaborator.
There are many who support the
reform you'll bring to the world.
That's right. Once this is done
and I have the emperor,
the latent opposing forces
pretending to obey Golbarn
should defect en masse from Unified Zesskia.
Now is a good time.
My blood is seething!
This is what a fight should be like!
You treat it like it's a game!
Shit!
That should be enough!
Colonel! Don't you tell me
this is our last battlefield!
Make the call, Colonel!
It's time!
What? What's going on?!
The enemy is withdrawing!
You won't get away!
Who goes there?!
I've come to protect His Imperial Majesty!
Someone lead me to his side!
D-Duke Hybranz!
I'm no longer a duke,
but I am indeed Schwarz Diese!
You're a traitor! Guards!
I must see His Majesty!
Lead me there, quickly!
Move it!
Marlya! Don't be hasty!
Why?
Why are you here?
For Your Majesty's sake, of course.
Where's Wolfran?
He was with us until a little while ago.
He performed his role, and left.
It's you...
Ray Dawn.
You...!
I see. Wolfram must have been working for you!
You don't need to know that.
Knowing would do you no good.
What?!
Throne Taker...
Your fairy's power!
Diese, you don't understand the times.
What's happening?
That's... Beevee Liscar?
P-Protect the prime minister!
At this rate...
Fall back! Retreat!
If you... have that much power...
why do you... kiss up to Golbarn?
I never liked you.
Shallow, and overly frank...
It irritates me.
Schwarz Diese, the traitor.
Know that even death does not fully atone
for the great crime of betraying His Majesty.
Look at this mess.
They really would try to start a war.
It's not over yet!
Wait, Marlya!
Let go! I have to chase him!
Just wait!
Is it for revenge?
We drove back the enemy
that entered the palace.
We performed our duty.
But is that...
Is that good enough for you?!
Yes.
We won, didn't we?
That's right. We fought...
and we won!
Deep in the forest
A quiet song is sung
Carrying fate upon its shoulders
A song of life
Said the lying crow
"Only calamity awaits beyond"
The fox asks, in hushed tones,
"Is there such a thing as happiness?"
Vanishing as quickly as it gathers
Drawn together, sounds weave into a melody
Heard across the world
Illuminating the path to tomorrow
As though not to melt the fluttering snowflakes
The ashen sky is gentle
As it wraps up and sings this song
And suddenly, the war was over.
For what purpose do you fight?
What do you protect?
You can't get back what's been lost!
Even if you get revenge, the past won't change.