What?!
Sweetie, what the hell have you done?!
Hey! Look at what we have in here
You’re just a prisoner of the tears
And all the noise the city fears
Oh, I wasn’t a fan at first, oh no-no-no neither
But I just couldn’t find any place mo-more greater
The crowds, the cars, the howling horns
Damn, so any damage we inflict
is reflected back at us?
The winds that carry wounds and mourns
Oh let me hear you scream and shout, "I lo-lo-love despair"
I’ll challenge you even if it is unfair
Good boy, Skriker.
Are you ready now?
I already knew she was trouble,
but to think she even has a weird fairy to boot!
I will show you how it’s done
Just biting, dust winding and breaking
and shakin’ the ground
Awaking, handholding and feeling
Heart pulsing in rhythm
You make me feel alive and certain, my style is
My, is that a trendy dance or something?
Damn it...
It's rather adorable. May I see it again?
just cuttin’ loose pain,
Care to dance with me, Sweetie?
survivin’ grief, I don’t care anymore
Ow.
Is it caused by this?
It's no use...
Is that a yes or a no?
If you're not in the mood, I'll be taking it.
Just biting, dust winding and breaking
I won't let you have the Black Fairy Tome!
and shakin’ the ground
Awaking, handholding and feeling
Heart pulsing in rhythm
You make me feel alive and certain, my style is
Meddlesome little girl, aren't you?
just cuttin’ loose pain,
Don't be stupid!
survivin’ grief, I don’t care anymore
If it's a battle of endurance...!
Protected by a little girl—you look so cool, Free.
Shut up!
You'll regret this.
We must secure... the Black Fairy Tome.
Yeah... that's right.
Don't push yourself too hard.
It's part of the job...
You did well.
I wake up, tired
So sick, bored, and fed up
I was never like this, I even had dreams, too
No one can stop me, bully me or suppress me
Can we ever break free of this miserable life we're living?
We'll never stop, we'll find our way, always, if we pray
I hear them coming for me now
Trying to lure me out
And all this time, I knew where it was
So I'm fired up and ready, looking for a good fight
So break it down and never give up
This is your only chance to change the world, so rise up!
It's your life!
Now is the time!
Fight for your life!
So don't cry out to stop! Not until you've won!
Break free of these chains
And give it all you've got!
Episode 04
Impatient Housekeeper and Selfish Artist
Do it!
Ray Dawn, why are you doing this?!
Find them!
They must have run this way!
Set fire to the forest, too!
I'll draw the soldiers away. Use that time to escape.
If you do that, you'll be...
It's okay. I'm fast, remember?
They won't catch me.
But...
Ver?
Ver!
It's okay.
Absolutely nothing bad is going to happen.
- Two Years Prior -
Fairies...
You're Marlya, aren't you?
If you know that, then why...?
Why what?
I mean, I'm...
It's okay.
Absolutely nothing bad is going to happen.
Ver...
This isn't Sweetie's. Axel's, perhaps?
Did someone carry him out of here?
How goes the search?
I managed to find some clues.
At least there's a silver lining.
We did manage to recover the Black Fairy Tome.
She is still asleep.
Thank you for letting her use one of your rooms.
I don't mind. Having Dorothea
in my debt could prove useful.
Would it be all right for us
to stay here until she wakes up?
Certainly, by all means.
Does that bring this inspection
to an end, Nein Auler?
Yes, Duke Hybranz.
Just Schwarz Diese is fine. We're no strangers.
Schwarz Diese
Duke of Hybranz
I was your subordinate.
The war may be over,
but I am still in no such position.
There shouldn't be anything
I wouldn't want your people to see.
Not a single thing.
The government will receive my report.
If I break the law, I'll leave no evidence behind.
If I don't break it, there'll be no evidence.
Don't you find this all a bit pointless?
We simply carry out our duty.
I see you still haven't changed, either.
We will take our leave, then.
Sure. I look forward to working with you again.
Heya! How you doin'?
Can I take your order?
Okay, I'll have fresh water.
Water, you said?
Fresh water.
Very well.
I'm not about to drink something that's flavored.
You haven't changed a bit, Patricia.
Please, just Patty.
I'm glad you were in Isharat.
Here I was thinking I would have to send for you.
I take it Jonathan is here too, then?
Perhaps. So, what's the job?
The usual. I need you to do some cleaning.
Why do I feel lethargic?
Free...
You awake?
Yes.
How long was I out?
About a whole day.
That long?
I'm actually glad it wasn't any worse.
Don't push yourself too hard.
You're repeating yourself.
Oof.
You're okay to get up?
Yes. Um,
where's the Black Fairy Tome?
Right here.
This victory's all yours.
But if it's a fake, it will have all been for nothing.
It isn't the real thing?
There's no telling until it's fully
appraised at the Ministry of Fairies.
Of the fairy tomes,
the black one is by far the most valuable.
It's not uncommon for fakes to be bought and sold.
At mafia auctions?
Yeah.
They're always the showpiece
wherever they're featured.
And they hired us as guards, remember?
Seems there's been trouble at a number
of auctions these past few years.
I'd heard about that too.
There hadn't been any
break-ins at Gui Carlin auctions,
and we didn't have any detailed info...
But Veronica.
Was she the auction thief?
I had no proof, but I figured maybe she was.
There were some connections.
To the mafia, huh?
Then Ver came after the
Black Fairy Tome, and made off with it.
Who knows, maybe Veronica
is where this came from.
If that's the case,
Cain and Damien might know about her.
How did we get our hands on
the Black Fairy Tome, you ask?
That is... not something we can tell you.
Why not?
Is this a Dorothea inquiry?
Oh, not at all.
You reported to the Ministry of Fairies
that you had the Black Fairy Tome,
and we just came to collect it.
If it's simply a chat rather than an inquiry,
there are things we can divulge, and things we can't.
Private fairy scholars such as ourselves
are permitted to exist, just barely,
because we share the results
of our research with Unified Zesskia.
Weren't you offered jobs at
the Ministry after the Unification?
I'm far too much of a nobody for them to notice.
Though Cain, of course,
received multiple invitations.
The nine years since the war ended...
I was already an old man at the time.
Veronica...
Veronica Thorn.
Do you know a woman by that name?
I can't say it rings a bell.
How about you, Damien?
No, I'm not familiar. Who is she?
I see.
Thank you.
You haven't fully recovered.
Stop stuffing your face.
We have plenty of time to catch the train.
I'm not stuffing my face.
And I can't get better if I don't eat.
Hey, this isn't bad.
Those two.
Cain Distarol and Damien Carme?
Yes.
I know I should be grateful to them, but they're liars.
Liars? You got any proof?
No, but...!
Can't blame them for keeping
their source of information secret.
Being a private fairy scholar ain't easy,
in more ways than one.
Then they should just join the
Ministry of Fairies, or whatever.
They don't want to.
There's some things you
can't do once that collar's on.
Heave-ho!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Welcome.
I'll have fresh water.
Water, you said?
Fresh water.
Very well.
For me, love and despair, back to back.
Taken to their extremes.
Sir?
Oh, just bring him something
that can be prepared quickly.
Yes, right away.
Hi.
Huh?
Bye-bye.
What about her fresh water?
What is it?!
Dimwits.
Hey, stop!
Hey, what's wrong?!
It was stolen!
Can you keep up?
Yes, sir.
All right.
Must be the ruins of an old church.
Down here?
Beneath Isharat is a labyrinth
of old water and sewer passageways.
I think there are crypts down there, too.
Crypts?
Someone's living here.
Looks like it.
Someone's there.
No...
Get inside.
In here?!
Don't exactly have much choice!
Howl!
I can't see anything!
Neither can they! Stay put!
Are they leading me in? What for?
Why lure me in?
If they were Arcame, or Gui Carlin...
All they need to do is to get away
if it's the Black Fairy Tome they're after.
Are they targeting me?!
Red Hood!
Patricia Pearl
Gui Carlin mafia group member
It's her!
I think I'm cursed.
Sorry.
I've been a little disaster
ever since I was born.
It was pitch dark before... right?
Where might you be going?
I envied Ver.
She was always surrounded by people.
Laughing, radiant.
She had friends, and parents
who were actually related to her.
Patty said to catch you.
It seems she means to use you
if Free Underbar proves too formidable.
You'd never tell from looking at her,
but she's cautious about such things.
Behind me?!
My, well done.
Do resist some more.
Jonathan Passpierre
Gui Carlin mafia group member
I can feel it—you'll make a lovely work of art.
Lady...
What the hell?!
I'm Jonathan, an artist!
Oh, but please don't call me Jon.
I'd much rather you call me Jonathan, or Jona.
All I ever do is run.
Pain is a blessing.
The more I inflict,
the closer I get.
This guy really doesn't make any sense at all!
I still can't summon my fairy?!
When I say "art,"
I refer to the act of understanding a person!
I want to be someone who understands you.
Ver!
It's okay...
It's okay.
Absolutely nothing bad is going to happen.
Deep in the forest
A quiet song is sung
Carrying fate upon its shoulders
A song of life
Said the lying crow
"Only calamity awaits beyond"
The fox asks, in hushed tones,
"Is there such a thing as happiness?"
Vanishing as quickly as it gathers
Drawn together, sounds weave into a melody
Heard across the world
Illuminating the path to tomorrow
As though not to melt the fluttering snowflakes
The ashen sky is gentle
As it wraps up and sings this song
Ver!
Because I'm still empty.
Am I a little disaster?
I am not a king.
It's all your fault!
Next Time
Black Moon and Lost Child's Song
Ray Dawn!