Imperial Embassy
Ambassador to the unified government,
please get up.
Wh-What's going on?!
Get him out of bed.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Ambassador, you shall be
leaving our country at once.
"Our country"?
Starting today, Hybranz is a sovereign state
and no longer part of Unified Zesskia.
Wh-What do you...?!
Dorothea HQ
Director!
You heard?
Yes, ma'am. We've heard that there's signs
of a revolt in the Duchy of Hybranz.
Could it be true?
That was a silly question.
So you've betrayed us after all, Schwarz Diese.
I wake up, tired
So sick, bored, and fed up
I was never like this, I even had dreams, too
No one can stop me, bully me or suppress me
Can we ever break free of this miserable life we're living?
We'll never stop, we'll find our way, always, if we pray
I hear them coming for me now
Trying to lure me out
And all this time, I knew where it was
So I'm fired up and ready, looking for a good fight
So break it down and never give up
This is your only chance to change the world, so rise up!
It's your life!
Now is the time!
Fight for your life!
So don't cry out to stop! Not until you've won!
Break free of these chains
And give it all you've got!
Episode 11
Uninvited Music Corps
Damn you, Diese!
Why pretend to protect me if you
were just going to rebel either way?!
To get me to lower my guard?
Arcame was the one pulling the strings
from behind the scenes with that incident.
If Duke Hybranz has connections with Arcame...
I'm well aware! Everything's gone
according to his plans.
He acts like a military man, but his
true face is that of a cunning schemer!
He is also a rebel by nature.
But Diese wasn't the only one
making careful preparations.
Military Minister Bohme.
Your Excellency! I-In a few days,
a suppressive force can—
Have them set out within one to two days,
and not a single day later.
Yes, sir.
By order of Your Excellency,
a plan to suppress the Duchy of Hybranz
has already been formulated.
It's just...
The plan calls for the primary use of artificial fairies.
Oh, that's right.
The malfunction of the new models was due to
an interruption device installed by Ted Livingston.
And the override in the old models
is disabled in ordinary frames.
The new models are still few in number,
and all their frames have been inspected.
We can operate them with no problem.
But the old models are still being checked...
If the old models were to be
overridden on the front lines,
it would cost us the battle.
The only ones we can use are the new models.
They really outwitted us.
Director Auler.
Your Excellency.
You are to join the suppressive force
as additional insurance.
I permit you to retrieve the Fairy Weapon, Aliadra.
Yes, sir.
I will have Aliadra taken out
of the vault immediately.
Times have changed.
We need naught but the masses
and a monarch to unite them.
Why can't the fools see that?
Rondacia Station
East End Base
The main street in front of Rondacia Station
Rondacia Palace
A rebellion, by Duke Hybranz?
Didn't we only just reward him?
It would appear that he wasn't loyal after all.
Unlike yourself, huh?
Very well. In the name of the king, I hereby strip the
title of Duke of Hybranz from the traitor Schwarz Diese.
Defeat him, Golbarn.
As you wish.
Ministry of Fairies
Go ahead.
Over some worthless ambition...
"You don't have to run off."
I've never been told that before.
Maybe I have just been running
from one place to the next.
But it's not like I wanted to run.
I couldn't stay where I was.
Running was always my only choice.
See that?
Weird, isn't it?
Oh, yeah...
He dozes off like that quite a bit. It's gross.
Do you really have to go that far?
Man, that's gross.
You just said it yourself.
I mean, wasn't that creepy?
He's suspicious all around.
You're a little too tough on him, though.
Am I really?
Lousette Station
Huh?! A revolt?!
By Schwarz Diese?
What's the situation?
We don't know the details yet.
But an imperial command to
subdue it has already been issued.
What the hell?
Rondacia Station
The second we get back,
we're plunged into war. Say it isn't so.
Let's hurry! We've got to see the director!
Yes, sir!
Understood!
Dorothea HQ
I'm afraid you've missed her.
Although, the director departed yesterday
as part of the suppressive force's vanguard.
Seriously?
Chase, as well as Lily's Third Unit, went with her.
Huh?! So the only remaining staff left here are...
Aside from support personnel
such as myself, just you guys.
Actually, we were entrusted with
a personal letter by Duke Kal-o.
What do we do?
If the director's gone,
we'll have to deliver it ourselves.
To the prime minister.
Wait, who'll do it?!
Well...
Me, huh?
I wonder if we should have gone with Free.
It's the prime minister he's dealing with.
Since he's the director's deputy, he'll probably
be the only one who gets to see him, anyway.
Oh.
You're right.
Are you worried?
I wouldn't put it that way.
Well, he might not look it, but he's
the kinda guy who always gets the job done.
I think?
He isn't irresponsible.
Unlike a certain someone.
Oh? And who would that be?
Can't you tell?
No, no, I don't have a clue.
Nobody is to blame,
but for each other's sake...
Prime Minister's Official Residence
I'm sorry to make such an unreasonable
request, Fairy Minister Bellwood.
I don't mind.
On the contrary, if it's an urgent matter,
I'm glad you turned to me.
Unlike the director, I can't get
through to see him right away.
Yes, the prime minister is
terribly busy at the moment.
So, what's the pressing matter?
This is the deputy commander of
Dorothea's First Unit, Free Underbar.
Your Excellency.
On our way back from an inspection,
we took custody of a personal letter from Duke Kal-o.
A personal letter?
Move aside.
What did Duke Kal-o write?
Ray Dawn... It seems Duke Kal-o
foresaw Diese's rebellion.
He must have obtained some
highly reliable information somehow.
He warned you about it, then?
It seems to have arrived too late.
That's not all.
Fights have suddenly broken out in the streets!
The enemy is weaker than expected.
Doesn't that worry you?
It does make me wonder,
but what about the director?!
That's no concern.
She's one of the Seven Knights.
The Witch of Ainedern.
If you value your lives, surrender!
Why aren't they putting up more of a fight?
Hey, you there!
You say that's not all?
Duke Kal-o writes that the troop build-up in the
Duchy of Hybranz is nothing more than a diversion.
What would he gain by attracting the
Unified Forces to his own territory?
It's difficult to take at face value,
but according to this letter—
I-I beg your pardon, Your Excellency!
We just received word!
Th-The palace! The palace is under attack,
with His Imperial Majesty inside!
East End Base
Move it! Move it!
Rondacia Palace — West Gate
Dorothea HQ
Free!
The palace is under attack!
The palace is... what?!
We're moving out!
Yes, sir!
Understood!
Why are there non-Unified Forces
artificial fairies in the capital?!
Rout them!
In the end, they're nothing but rabble.
Right, we'll make our way into
the palace from the East Gate!
I, Bruno Bohme, will take direct command
and protect His Imperial Majesty!
The palace has three gates.
The East Gate is near East End Base,
and the Heavenly Gate...
...is rarely opened, bar special ceremonies.
Even then, it remains heavily guarded.
Which means...
The target is the West Gate?
Most likely.
Fi—
Who are those guys?!
It pains me to think of those
we left behind in my territory.
Arcame will take part in
this uprising until the end.
Expect to be rewarded handsomely.
Unlike Unified Zesskia,
I don't plan to monopolize fairies.
Free and open use of fairies?
And that will stimulate development
and reform, opening up a new world.
Now that's what I call ambition.
Kal-o Official Residence
Draggin' all what I've got
I walk towards my target, slowly, eyes locked
I'm having fun
Rondacia Palace — West Gate
This is what makes me feel alive
The West Gate is on fire!
Tryna survive
Hey, wassup? How y'all doin'?
And there's gunfire!
I'mma Master of Evil, stingin' till you notice
Nice of them to wage war in the capital!
Then again, I know it's all pretty obvious
When in pain, I know you'll know I'm glorious
This can't be...
Don't be afraid to come defy me
What's with this half-assed attack?
Won't be delayed, it's a piece of pie
No gimmick, I'm notorious
Enemies!
This is how it goes down, my audience
You're making everything so obvious
I am the greatest one
Figured guns wouldn't work.
So don't you try to run
I'll show you how it's done
With thunderous cheer, here I come
Jet!
If anything were to happen to me,
you should be the one to use this, Free.
Don't worry, it's okay
But hurry, don't be late
'Cuz today's a special day for us
Huh?
Not that it'll ever come to that.
Just take your leap of faith
Don't be 'fraid and embrace
Let me hear your voice
Let me hear you scream 'n' shout!
Kick ass, sir!
Wait, that weapon...
Yeah.
The Fairy Weapon, Verosteal!
So you received permission to take it out?
Arcame's artificial fairies?
Let's go!
Yes, sir!
One truth is that I'm a lonely gun
Are those what set the gate on fire?
Shock many, fought many, I'm the one
This isn't how the regular army fights!
More bitter than the devil, hotter than a blaze
Winner of the game and beginning of the end
It's how mercenaries do things.
You're right, I'm a skillful trickster
Got a lotta power, I'mma dynamite fixer
It's gotta be Beevee Liscar.
Showin' you all what's critical
Liscar...
I promise y'all, you gonna need a miracle
That's why I'll say it again 'n' again
I am the greatest one
So come try 'n cut me down
Spread out!
I'll show you it can't be done
The fearless year is now
Colonel?
If you want to hit me with a slug, here's the spot!
Stick your muzzle right here! Pull the trigger!
You grains of sand aren't even
fit to be curtain raisers.
The enemies at the East Gate are being driven back,
and our forces at the West Gate are holding fast!
Thank you. Dismissed.
Shall we send our strength at the Heavenly
and West Gates over to the East Gate,
and wipe out the enemy in one fell swoop?
No.
We'll continue to bolster our defense,
while we have a separate unit strike from behind.
Moat
West Wall
West Gate
Truly an excellent plan!
They may have set me up as Minister of
the Military, but I was originally a soldier.
Your staying in the capital instead of going
to Hybranz was divine providence.
Yes, I certainly have been graced by Lady Luck.
Reporting!
A-A new enemy approaches,
from near the Heavenly Gate!
Don't panic!
The Heavenly Gate wouldn't even yield
to an onslaught by tens of thousands!
Y-Yes, sir!
But this new enemy appears to be one
of the Seven Knights, Beevee Liscar!
Liscar?!
Let's follow.
This isn't the work from those guys earlier, is it?
Doesn't this seem rather strange?
They started moving away in
the middle of the West Gate attack!
It means the West Gate attack was a decoy!
Then what's their real target?
Liscar...
He's taunting us.
What're you doing?! Shoot!
Fill him with holes, now!
Yes, sir!
F-Fire!
The height of weakness.
This does nothing for me.
You guys don't even have the right to fight.
You fool. This castle withstood
the War of Unification.
Nobody can breach the Heavenly Gate.
That's what history has shown.
Colonel...
History is outdated,
and I'll rewrite it by my own hand!
Liscar!
Now, time to raise the curtain!
Deep in the forest
A quiet song is sung
Carrying fate upon its shoulders
A song of life
Said the lying crow
"Only calamity awaits beyond"
The fox asks, in hushed tones,
"Is there such a thing as happiness?"
Vanishing as quickly as it gathers
Drawn together, sounds weave into a melody
Heard across the world
Illuminating the path to tomorrow
As though not to melt the fluttering snowflakes
The ashen sky is gentle
As it wraps up and sings this song
Fight! Show me what you're worth!
You don't understand the times.
You treat it like it's a game!
Now is a good time.
We of Dorothea will perform our duty!
Next Time
Powerless Soldier