Rondacia Palace
Unified Zesskia
Nine years ago,
the War of Unification came to an end.
The king of Cidal, Golbarn Helwise,
surrendered his crown to the emperor,
and became the prime minister.
Prime Minister of Unified Zesskia
Golbarn Helwise
The following year,
Golbarn was officially inaugurated.
Five men who played key roles in
the war were specially granted territory:
the so-called Five Dukes.
However, this system of
Five Dukes would be short-lived.
The Duke of Widonia, Patrick Starry—
Duke of Widonia
Patrick Starry
apprehended as the ringleader of a plot
to assassinate the prime minister.
Prior to his trial,
he drank poison, taking his own life.
The Duke of Nova, Ewan Breeze—
Duke of Nova
Ewan Breeze
being suspected of rebellion enraged
him to the point of actually starting one.
This hero of the war—
one of the renowned Seven Knights—
died fighting.
The Duke of Littroke, Umar Jujuman—
Duke of Littroke
Umar Jujuman
while he was a sworn friend
of Prime Minister Golbarn during the war,
he rose in revolt for no reason beyond paranoia.
He failed, and was summarily executed.
They say there can be no peace without sacrifice.
Right.
After finally unifying, it was a big mistake
to set up the Five Dukes at all.
And the war heroes were us soldiers
and commanders on the front lines.
Heroes my ass, asshole.
Shut up, you old bastard!
You're an old fart too!
What was that, you prick?!
What's your problem?!
But you're both young.
Oh yeah?
You know it!
Lively, too.
Only seven days until the
tenth anniversary of the war's end.
The war seems like a distant memory now.
Even so, it was just last year
that Duke Littroke was executed.
Two of them are still left.
The Duke of Hybranz, Schwarz Diese,
and the Duke of Kal-o, Ray Dawn.
Hybranz Official Residence
You're looking well.
Duke of Kal-o
Ray Dawn
As are you.
I wake up, tired
So sick, bored, and fed up
I was never like this, I even had dreams, too
No one can stop me, bully me or suppress me
Can we ever break free of this miserable life we're living?
We'll never stop, we'll find our way, always, if we pray
I hear them coming for me now
Trying to lure me out
And all this time, I knew where it was
So I'm fired up and ready, looking for a good fight
So break it down and never give up
This is your only chance to change the world, so rise up!
It's your life!
Now is the time!
Fight for your life!
So don't cry out to stop! Not until you've won!
Break free of these chains
And give it all you've got!
Episode 06
Fellow Traveler
All right, in you go.
Hey, wait a minute!
Look, I was just earnin' some money on the side!
It is quite illegal to mislead others into
believing you possess a fairy primordial.
Dammit!
Ow!
Looks old, but well-made.
Even if it's just an empty casing,
it's illegal if it's genuine.
Excuse me, we'd like to talk to you.
D-Dorothea?!
Uh, you've got the wrong idea. That's...
Those are new ones.
I see them a lot, those...
The Zern I models?
A new type of artificial fairy.
They're quite different from the previous ones.
They're making their grand debut
as security for the war anniversary ceremony,
but they'll surely still need some preliminary testing.
Like a rehearsal?
What?
No!
Shit, it's not accepting commands!
Marlya!
Right!
Why can't I control it?!
Seriously?!
This way!
Hey! Activate the others!
Are you all right?
Thank you!
Were you able to determine
the cause of the malfunction?
Ah, you're from Dorothea.
Hello.
You're from the Ministry of Fairies, um...
Griff Mercer.
He may not look it,
but he's the assistant vice-minister.
Oh, what an honor.
Oh, not at all. I only just received
word and came rushing over.
Ministry of Fairies
Assistant Vice-minister and fairy technician
Griff Mercer
Just an errand boy, nothing more.
I hear you two were there when it happened?
Yes. Are you with the military?
Just a civilian mechanic in military employ.
I'm Hanns. This is Ted.
Unified Zesskia Army
Artificial Fairy Technician - Head of Maintenance
Hanns Efmed
Unified Zesskia Army
Artificial Fairy Technician
Ted Livingston
You could say he's my right-hand man.
Hanns is head of the maintenance division,
and a master artificial fairy technician.
Flattery will get you nowhere, you know!
So, how did it go?
A cursory inspection revealed
nothing out of the ordinary.
I don't think my superiors will simply
accept that there's nothing wrong.
This new model is nearly ready for practical use,
and it was developed to replace the Psyden VII,
which has been in use since the War of Unification.
What a headache.
Yeah, I'll say.
By the way...
We've received info from a certain
source about the Black Fairy Tome.
The Assistant Vice-minister of
the Ministry of Fairies, Griff Mercer,
mentioned it earlier at East End Base.
Why now, of all times?
The Black Fairy Tome you obtained
previously was apparently a fake,
but this time it might be the genuine article.
And we're going to retrieve it?
I already know whom I'm sending.
Wow.
I've never been to this city either.
I hope we don't get lost.
You'd get lost after having seen the map?
Buz the informant, I presume?
Informant
"Buz" Sebastian
I believe you've been paid in advance.
Go ahead and tell us what you know, please.
That advance payment ain't even close to enough.
Sweeten the deal for me.
My little Dorothea bitches.
Boss!
I-It was a joke! Just a joke!
Right? Right?!
Now the story, if you would.
O-Of course.
At the time, did you notice anything unusual
about the new-model artificial fairy?
I have no clue.
I see.
It must be a defect,
or else it was tampered with somehow.
I doubt anyone on the outside could
tamper with a military artificial fairy.
Daniel.
A former colleague of yours, Chase?
Yeah.
I think he's still with the Security Bureau.
Give me a minute?
Sure.
Something's nagging at me.
What, though?
I'm at your command!
At your disposal, even!
Um...
In that case, prepare a vehicle for our use.
Consider it done, boss!
On my way!
"B-Boss"?
In a recent auction held in this city,
the Black Fairy Tome was put up for sale.
They referred to it as "The Black Four"... or something.
Most of the attendees were outbidding
each other with shockingly high bids.
The winning bidder was an agent
who's quite well-known in such circles.
He's a man called Dice.
Oh, that guy.
Yes.
Agent
Dice
We're following him.
Understood.
The train's about to leave!
We might just make it.
Dorothea. We're pursuing a target.
Oh, yes, ma'am.
Please go ahead.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Pick up the pace!
I can't stand obtuse men.
We're boarding!
Please cooperate with our investigation.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Departing for Rondacia!
Ma'am, wait!
You want my ticket? Here!
No, that's not what I was saying.
You already missed it.
Bitter Sweet.
So, Dorothea wasn't the only one to get their hands
on the information on The Black Four. Gui Carlin did too.
He's not here.
I could have sworn he got on this train.
Any luck?
Let's take another look.
Yes.
He really isn't here, after all.
Maybe he's on the freight car instead.
You can't enter or exit that
while the train is in motion.
Isn't the next stop at some station called Sharbit?
When we reach the station, let's have them open it,
and we'll check the interior.
Come to think of it, this is the first mission
where it's just been the two of us.
Klara...
How did you join Dorothea?
I volunteered.
I lost all my family in the war.
That's far enough!
Huh?!
I was saved by Director Nein.
Sounds rough.
That's how the war was.
I never knew my mother or father.
I suppose that makes me one of the lucky ones.
After all, they may be gone,
but their memories live on.
Are you getting off at the next station?
Thanks for that.
Sharbit Station!
We'd better get off!
If you would, please.
He's not here.
That's impossible!
That briefcase!
Stop that man!
Huh?
Klara!
Stop right there!
Where is he?
Freeze.
Put your hands up.
Dorothea HQ
How about you say something, already?
Any luck?
He's a tough one.
I doubt even a broken arm
or two would make him talk.
He didn't have anything that
looked like the Black Fairy Tome.
But supposedly he's the one
who won it at the auction.
If he's an agent, he must have won
the auction on someone's behalf.
I guess the question then becomes who that is.
Ah!
Welcome back, Klara!
How'd the mission go?!
Were you lonely without me?
Quite the opposite.
There you go again!
Any progress on the cause
of the artificial fairy malfunction?
They still haven't found anything wrong.
And Dice isn't talking.
Pretty much.
Axel! You...!
H-Hey, wait!
Ow...
Oh, that's right, you got shot.
I nearly kicked the bucket, too.
That woman's somethin' else.
Ow!
I'm surprised you made it.
I can finally manage to get around,
so I wanted to tell you something.
Huh?
I wasn't out to get in your way that time.
Just so happened, y'know? No hard feelings.
I don't care. I've got a full plate right now.
The anniversary of the war's end is coming up soon.
Some kinda trouble?
Anything I can help with, you just let me know, yeah?
Well, you do know an awful lot
of people and hear plenty of things.
Ah.
Dice.
You know him?
He's famous in certain circles.
He's got the skills and he's tight-lipped.
Who does he represent?
Rarely does a professional
agent only have one client.
But if you believe the rumors,
Dice often works for...
Gilbert Warlock.
Deep in the forest
A quiet song is sung
Carrying fate upon its shoulders
A song of life
Said the lying crow
"Only calamity awaits beyond"
The fox asks, in hushed tones,
"Is there such a thing as happiness?"
Vanishing as quickly as it gathers
Drawn together, sounds weave into a melody
Heard across the world
Illuminating the path to tomorrow
As though not to melt the fluttering snowflakes
The ashen sky is gentle
As it wraps up and sings this song
Now if you'll excuse me, I must be on my way.
Come now, Military Minister.
Don't be that way. Stay and enjoy yourself.
I'm afraid I can't.
Is there some problem?
Keep this between us.
There's actually been a malfunction
with the new artificial fairy model.
Oh!
Well, well...
Look at the state this Zern I is in.
It hurts to distrust those close to you.
Don't worry.
These, as a matter of fact.
Next Time
Stubborn Blacksmith and Biased Rabbit
Ears within Gui Carlin, eh?