The colors I saw the other day
are all gone again.
Many nights I felt like I'd lost my sense of self, my heart and soul
Many nights I felt like there was no love left for me anymore
I wanted to see the world clearly as the sun rose
But I've come to doubt even my own hopes
It was so bright, so dazzling, blinding me from the world around me
I couldn't even tell what colors your feelings were
As the seasons change, and people change with them
We all run through life to not miss this chance
It might be so far, so distant from here
Yet our feelings become one in this wish
We're running to find what our lives can become
Like the clouds parting to reveal a rainbow in the sky
Do you have any idea what might've
been the reason you saw colors, Hitomi?
No...
I see.
I wonder why you can't see them anymore...
I'll do some fortune telling for you!
We can't really see many stars tonight...
All right, let's do some astrology!
Stellamare. Let the stars spread
across the canvas of sky.
What's your zodiac sign again?
Leo.
Leo, got it.
O Stars, reveal to me what awaits Leo tomorrow!
Interesting...
"Accept your life the way it is now.
If you do, a colorful future awaits."
That's what it said!
Sounds very generic...
No, I'm sure it'll happen!
Why?
'Cause summer break starts tomorrow!
That doesn't make sense.
Huh? What's wrong?
Apparently her mock exams didn't go well.
Just look at this!
And it's summer already. I'm so screwed!
Don't you mean it's only summer?
Aren't you aiming for a national university?
The tuition's cheap, so yeah.
That's the reason?
It's important!
Hitomi, Kohaku!
Isn't there some kinda spell
that'd make me smarter?!
There's one for a clear mind,
but I'm not so sure about getting smarter...
That'll do!
I wanna be able to think clearly!
And forget the results of my mock exams if possible!
What if it wipes all your
English vocabulary clear as well?
Chigusa...
Wanna see what happens when you
mess with someone who's studying?!
Time out! Time out!
For the love of god!
I swear, Chigusa!
Hey, what about the meeting?!
I'll be back as soon as I land
at least one good smack!
Man, those two...
Chigusa probably did something stupid again.
I'm surprised how active
they can be even in this heat.
They'll come crawling back exhausted in no time.
Art Classroom
G-Good morning.
Oh, um, morning.
Let me explain again for the
benefit of our new members.
Our club goes camping every
year over the summer break.
Wow, camping?
It's one of the traditions of the Photography Club.
Yep. What better way to bond
than by sitting around a fire?
We go to the same place every year,
so we get 50% off, too!
That's great!
I know, right?
And we usually let the next
club president organize the trip.
Not just because we third-years
will soon be busy with summer courses,
but also because it's an excellent learning
opportunity for the upcoming president.
Can I count on you, Asagi?
M-Me?
Ooh, so our next president is Asabunny!
In favor! In favor!
Right, Hitomi?
Yeah.
Is it already decided?
You've been in the club the longest
out of the second-years here.
You'll be fine! I have faith in you!
Tell me if you need help with anything.
I'd be happy to help if possible.
Thank you, Hitomi!
And Hitomi's gonna be the vice president!
I was planning to take a lot of photos
that day for an anthology,
so I'll be counting on you, Prez and Vice Prez!
Here.
It's all set up for you.
Thank you very much.
I'll return it soon.
The Magic,
Photography and Art Club
Today
Read
Kohaku has added Hitomi to the group
Tsukishiro Hitomi here.
Thanks for having me.
Asagi
I'm glad that you joined, Hitomi!
Chigusa
omg Hitomi's here!
Welcome!
The Magic,
Photography and Art Club
omg Hitomi's here!
Welcome!
welcome hitomi — — — !!!
Welcome, Hitomi!
Well, now that everyone's in this
chat, let's talk about camp.
wow, Prez so serious
STFU chigusa !!!
Kurumi
Shou
Chigusa
Kurumi
Shou
welcome hitomi — — — !!!
Welcome, Hitomi!
Well, now that everyone's in this
chat, let's talk about camp.
wow, Prez so serious
STFU chigusa !!!
Shou
Chigusa
Kurumi
Shou
Well, now that everyone's in this
chat, let's talk about camp.
wow, Prez so serious
STFU chigusa !!!
Chigusa
Kurumi
Shou
wow, Prez so serious
STFU chigusa !!!
Kurumi
Shou
STFU chigusa !!!
Kurumi
Shou
STFU chigusa !!!
These are from last year. Maybe
they'll give you some ideas?
Whoa! What a view!
Is that a blue sky? Or a sunset?
Sunset.
It's a really beautiful red.
How strange.
Until just recently,
it was normal for me to not see colors,
and I never even wondered what color the sky was.
But now I really want to know.
Why not ask the others about it?
I wouldn't even know how to explain it at this point.
I've been keeping it secret for so long...
I should've told them sooner.
Getting depressed won't change anything.
What's important is what you do next!
The Magic,
Photography and Art Club
Shou
Asagi
Read
These are from last year. Maybe
they'll give you some ideas?
oh wow, everyone's so young !!!
It hasn't been that long, lol.
I'll be taking care of all the preparations. I'll
try to do my best, so please bear with me!
Shou
Asagi
Read
These are from last year. Maybe
they'll give you some ideas?
oh wow, everyone's so young !!!
It hasn't been that long, lol.
I'll be taking care of all the preparations. I'll
try to do my best, so please bear with me!
Shou
Asagi
Read
These are from last year. Maybe
they'll give you some ideas?
oh wow, everyone's so young !!!
It hasn't been that long, lol.
I'll be taking care of all the preparations. I'll
try to do my best, so please bear with me!
Shou
Asagi
Read
Hitomi
These are from last year. Maybe
they'll give you some ideas?
oh wow, everyone's so young !!!
It hasn't been that long, lol.
I'll be taking care of all the preparations. I'll
try to do my best, so please bear with me!
I'll try doing my best as well.
Once again, thank you for having me.
Madam!
I'd greatly appreciate if madam
didn't make us deliver a single coffee
all the way out here, thank you.
Thanks!
Here.
Why don't you study at home?
Too many distractions.
So you say, but perhaps
you just want to see me more?
Yeah, yeah, we saw each other in the morning anyway.
Now shoo, before I catch your stupidity.
Will you be fine getting home?
It gets really dark around here after sunset.
My dad will pick me up.
Now to focus on studying...
I guess I'll be heading back.
Good luck with your exams.
Thanks!
Oh, there she is.
Kurumi!
Sis!
I'm here to pick you up.
Um, gimme a sec!
Sure thing.
Entrance
What about your work?
You're earlier than usual today.
I was finally able to take a day off.
So I decided to do some research.
The Sweets Art
You really shouldn't be thinking
about work on your day off.
The Sweets Art
Well, Dad is paying so much for my
studies to let me become a pâtissiere
that I have to be this determined.
He used to complain so much!
You got into a national university,
and then suddenly brought up
wanting to study abroad...
You were working in secret to save money
so you could go to a baking school.
Shianbashi
I had to try all kinds of things to convince him.
Those were the days.
You were always busy back then.
I mean, that hasn't changed.
But I'm having so much fun.
I'm doing what I like, and I'm making
people happy at the same time...
It really gets me motivated.
Why are you taking a picture?
You had a really nice expression there.
崇福寺
Soufukuji
Entrance
崇福寺
Soufukuji
Entrance
崇福寺
Soufukuji
You should do something you like, too.
崇福寺
Soufukuji
Even if Dad is against it, I'll help you convince him.
Heavy! And hot!
Is this some kind of training?!
Stop complaining. We do this every year.
I'd prefer to go glamping, honestly.
Like seriously.
That doesn't count as camping.
Permission
Fyurie
SeeU
Prices
Areki
Camping Site
Sarrink
Adults
QQwerty
Students
duplex
Children
Fyurie
SeeU
Prices
Areki
Camping Site
Permission
Fyurie
SeeU
Prices
Areki
Camping Site
Sarrink
Adults
QQwerty
Students
duplex
Children
Permission
Fyurie
SeeU
Prices
Areki
Camping Site
Sarrink
Adults
QQwerty
Students
duplex
Children
Permission
Fyurie
SeeU
Prices
Areki
Camping Site
Adults
QQwerty
Students
duplex
Children
Fyurie
SeeU
Prices
Areki
Camping Site
Adults
Students
duplex
Fyurie
SeeU
Prices
Areki
Camping Site
Adults
Students
duplex
I've finished our registration.
It's number 10, on the right in the back.
Our future president sure is full of energy!
I'm melting!
Let's go.
We just put those down!
It's heavy, so I'll carry it.
No, I'll carry it.
It's fine, I've got it.
Go, Current Prez! We can always count on you!
You can carry your own things, Kohaku.
Kurumi?
Hey, don't leave me behind!
Th-The Magic, Photography
and Art Club will now bejin—
She bit her tongue.
It's fine, Asagi!
The Magic, Photography and Art Club
will now begin its one-day camp.
Thank you for coming, everyone!
Thank you.
Yay!
And done!
We finished that in no time.
There's more of us here than last year.
I've really worked up an appetite!
Barbecue time!
Isn't this normally a chance
to show off your feminine side?
Why am I helping out?
You're the most skilled one here, to be honest.
Well, I do help out in the
kitchen at work sometimes...
But now I'm kind of disappointed...
Don't be silly.
By the way, you have an older sister, don't you?
Have I never mentioned her?
Nope, never heard anything.
What does she do?
She's a pâtissiere.
Works at a place called Multicolore.
Wait, for real?
I know that place! All the girls in my class love it!
Look! This is the hottest thing right now!
[Like] 13048 Likes
Oh, my sister came up with that one.
That's awesome!
She really is!
She's always been able to do anything,
and even when she was our age she
was already thinking about her future.
She managed to achieve her dreams, too...
Such a role model.
You sound very proud of her.
It's nice to have an older sister, isn't it?
Could you ask her to model for me?
Not a chance!
She's busy.
Well in that case, I guess you'll have to do.
Now that I take a closer look,
the resemblance is kinda there, maybe...
We're not alike at all.
Unlike her, I'm empty.
Episode 7
The Burden of Venus
When do we start the photo
shoot on the way back?
On the Venus Bridge at 9 pm.
Why a bridge?
You know how there's a lot of fancy
ships leaving the Nagasaki Port?
I wanna take a picture of one from an unusual angle.
Wow! I thought you only took
pictures of girls, Chigusa!
A girl, gazing upon the ship her lover is aboard...
I'm planning a picture like that.
Wouldn't the pathos exuded by the nape
of her neck filled be super moving?
I'm sure it'd be a killer photo!
Now, girls, any volunteers to model for me?
I'll pass. Try someone else.
I'm sorry.
I'm also sorry.
Seriously?
In that case... Kurumi!
I already said no, remember?
Come on, it'll be fun!
My photos are always crazy good!
You're annoying. Drop it, seriously.
Check out this meat! Calling dibs on this one!
Hey, I was carefully watching over that one!
Well I'm taking this one, then!
Hey, that was mine!
Fanks for retting me hab it!
Wow, it melz in your mowf!
Jeez, you girls...
Is everything all right, Kurumi?
Hm, what do you mean?
You seemed a little down,
so I was wondering if you're
stressing over your exams.
Uh... Well, yeah.
Sorry for being a bit of a mood killer back there.
No, no, it's fine!
Has anyone told you what
Yamabuki and Aoi want to do?
Huh?
Yamabuki loves taking pictures, so he's going
to an arts college with a photography course.
Aoi was actually aiming for
a national university like me,
but he's suddenly become so motivated
and I feel like he's getting more
and more serious about drawing.
I wonder if something happened.
They both have the same expression as my sister.
Your sister?
Yeah. She's my role model.
How's your drawing?
It's not finished yet,
so I don't really want to show anyone.
Oh, don't be like that.
What about you?
You have to submit some photos
to apply to your college, right?
Not yet.
I'm sure I still have time to get even better.
Right.
So you decided where you're going yet?
I guess.
If I go to a national university,
I can somewhat afford it myself.
I'm thinking about going into art,
since there's people who want to see me draw.
I see.
Shall we bet on who finishes
a nice picture first, then?
Why would we?
She's always honest about what
she wants to do, and gives it her all.
She seems like a strong person.
Just like Kohaku!
I see what you mean!
They both forge ahead, chasing the
things they like, chasing their dreams.
I'm really envious.
It's nice to be serious about something!
I don't really have anything I'm passionate about.
What about photos?
Don't you like taking them?
I do!
But I don't know everything like Yamabuki,
and I'm not as good at taking them as Chigusa.
I like them, but only really as a hobby.
There's nothing I want to do, honestly.
That's probably why I struggle
with studying as well.
Don't you dare tell the others about this, okay?
Especially Chigusa.
He'd totally use this against me!
That's true.
I can totally hear you.
Undasonus. Let this scenery
be frozen in this sand born of stars.
You also have to go to meetings
and report your club activities.
The annoying part is writing applications
for extracurricular activities like this one.
Got it.
Relax. I'm sure you'll be fine.
Memories of our Camp
Okay, this will do.
What's that?
I used a spell to preserve memories.
Someday, we'll use this stardust
to remember this day clearly.
It's the most basic of basic chronomancies!
Here, I'll give this one to you.
All right! Time to make enough for everyone!
A spell...
Maybe if I knew more spells,
I'd be of more help to Kurumi...
What are you doing here, Tsukishiro?
I'd like you to see this.
I finally finished a drawing I could show you.
I want you to see it!
Thank you.
Colors!
So many colors!
It's all thanks to you.
Your magic worked.
Thanks.
It was nothing special.
I'd like to see your next drawing too.
Sure.
I'll be heading back now.
U-Um!
You drew this to show me colors, didn't you?
Thank you very much.
Kurumi!
I didn't expect to find you here.
What's up?
Let me do some astrology.
Huh?
Which zodiac sign are you?
I'm a Libra...
We can see it on the southern sky.
Stellamare. O Stars who illuminate the sky,
reveal to me what awaits Libra tomorrow!
"Accept your life the way it is now.
If you do, a colorful future awaits."
You just made that up.
I guess there's no fooling you.
Gosh, I can't believe I'm making my friends worry!
I need to pull myself together!
K-Kurumi?
Okay, I'm fine now!
The stars are so pretty.
Makes me want to take some photos.
Say, Kurumi.
Have you ever seen a photo of yourself?
Huh?
Ta-dah!
That's from the other day...
Yep! A special edition of my favorite Kurumi!
Look. You're making so many great expressions.
What?
You're not empty at all. If that was the case,
you wouldn't be making expressions like these.
Damn it...
How is it already there?!
Did you get the time wrong?
No, I checked it!
There should still be plenty
of time until the departure...
We won't make it...
No, we just need to run!
Huh? With all these bags?
Just leave 'em here!
What?!
Let's go, Hitomi!
O-Okay!
Seriously?!
Kurumi!
Ah, jeez!
Not everyone "likes" something in the same way.
Maybe you'll find something you like even more.
There's no need to make a decision
now and stick to it for life.
It's fine to take your time! You'll be okay!
Just kidding!
As if I cared about your future,
my dear little Kurumi!
You eavesdropping jerk!
But I'll take photos too!
Better than yours, I bet!
'Cause right now the thing I love most is photos!
Good luck with that!
What? You're so annoying!
Wait! The ship's leaving!
Hitomi! Stop it with magic!
I-I can't!
It's too fast!
It left already! What do we do now?
It's because I was trying not to leave you behind!
You're the one who wanted to take photos of it!
Where's all that determination gone?!
Nice, I snagged an upset Kurumi.
This'll do!
Talk about lively.
Shouldn't you stop them, Prez?
You hear that, Future President?
Is this part of my duties?
Hitomi?
I'm sorry. I'm so tired...
You got that right!
I won't forgive you!
Wait, what do I do about the anthology now?
Just think of something else.
Isn't the scenery from here beautiful enough?
You're right.
It really is nice.
Um!
How does this scenery look to you all?
I...
There's something I want to tell everyone.
Once I've climbed up the hill overlooking the twilit town
The scenery was like something out of a dream
And you were trying to capture it
Magic brushed against my ears
Whispering into my heart
Feeling frozen in time
Left behind by this vivid world of colors
But the future comes like the rain
Chasing, blurring my path forward
I nearly drown in its puddles of monotony
I wish tomorrow never changes
So I embrace the life I have today
Hoping to close the distance between us
I've been wishing for just one thing all this time.
Is this magic?
I want her to keep smiling.
It's hard.
I felt like those feelings were forced.
It's not like we can help it.
I want to remember. About everyone too.
Episode 8
A Piece Falling Out
Time, rewind!