Hang in there, Grea.
All of my tests are producing abnormal readings.
They won't tell us what the problem is.
Do we have any other ways to diagnose her?
I've never seen any medical
treatment records for dragons.
Hold her tail down, Hanna!
Got it.
Princess?
Manaria Friends
Grea?
The Anguished Dragon Princess
I've tried a number of healing spells,
but none of them have any effect.
We've also tested some herbs and medicine,
but they didn't help either.
Grea, can you hear me?
Grea?
We inspected her entire body,
but she didn't have any visible wounds.
It might be something
that only dragons suffer from.
Lou?
Geez, you're always falling over.
You really should be more careful.
Oh, this might be useful.
I brought shum booksh that looked usheful!
A medical journal for goblins?
And this one is a book
about the biology of reptilians.
Where did you find this book, dear?
This is a forbidden text
that students aren't allowed to read!
When I said Grea was in trouble,
the person at the counter let me borrow it!
Forbidden text?
Who exactly was it at the counter?
Either way, how would they have gotten this book?
Princess?
Take care of Grea, please!
Anne?
What happened, Anne?
Princess?
Where did Anne go?
She probably went to the Forbidden Ancient Library.
Forbidden?
Her fever is really high.
Let me have a look...
Hanna, please prepare an antipyretic.
Okay.
Princess?
It's okay. It'll be all right.
What's going on?
We're back in the library?!
That certainly was an
unexpected shortcut, Your Highness.
Go find these!
Understood!
Not here either!
What did the tablet say?
There were parts of it I couldn't decipher,
but we still need...
Where are we supposed to get dragon scales?!
Grea!
Are you okay now, Grea?
Are you all right?
Grea!
Can you hear me? Grea?
G-Grea?
Grea?
Huh? Anne?
Um... Uhh...
Good morning.
Morning...
Good morning, Grea!
What?
Good morning!
What's wrong, Anne?
Stupid Grea, I was so worried about you!
Wait, where are we?
I'm so glad you're okay!
Geez!
A-Anne? Could you let me get dressed?
You were molting?
Yes, it sometimes happens when I grow.
Your hair did get longer.
Oh? Did your chest grow too?
No! Maybe...
You would've been fine
if we'd just left you alone, huh.
Sorry for causing you so much trouble.
Don't worry about it.
I didn't really end up doing anything anyway.
If I'd known you were just molting, I would've just hung around while you were all hot and bothered.
Was I that much of a mess?
You were!
It was quite a sight.
Anne, what's that you've got there?
I-It's nothing!
Is that my skin?
Umm... I was thinking of keeping
it as a memento of our growth.
I guess...
You dummy.
I really did get fatter!
What am I going to do?
Grea, can you pass the salt over here?
My rear?!
No... The salt.
Oh, sorry.
Thanks.
You're not eating much today.
You think?
But you have to eat properly...
You only just...
shed your skin...
so you need to make sure...
Yeah...
...you get all of your nutrients!
Well, whatever.
Psych!
I knew it.
No doubt about it.
Grea...
Your tail is looking grand!
It's wonderful!
Huh?
Grea?
- Episode 3 -
The Princess' Day Off
Manaria Friends, Episode 3:
The Princess' Day Off.
Illustrator: Nijihara