Excuse me.
Y-Yes?
Are you returning these?
Thank you.
Anne!
Thanks for keeping me company
through library duty.
Manaria Friends
Hide and Seek
Let's see here...
"It's important to gather information before
making the first move on your target."
"There are times when being somewhat forceful can work to your advantage."
Forceful, huh?
What exactly are you reading?
"How to Seduce the Opposite Sex."
It even comes with a love potion!
Look!
Oh, I wonder if it will work
on someone of the same sex.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Will that cute little tail of yours
grow back if it gets cut off, I wonder?
N-No! I'm not a lizard...
Oh, okay.
Anne...
Huh?
Looks like everyone's gone.
Grea!
Let's play hide and seek!
Huh?
Eleven!
Twelve!
Thirteen!
Fourteen!
Fifteen!
Sixteen!
Seventeen!
Eighteen!
Nineteen!
Twenty!
Twenty-one!
Twenty-two!
Twenty-three!
Twenty-four!
Twenty-five!
Twenty-six!
Twenty-seven!
Twenty-eight!
Twenty-nine!
Thirty!
Seventy-four!
Eighty-one!
Ninety-three!
Ninety-eight, ninety-nine, one hundred!
Ready or not, here I come!
Here I come!
Why that Grea, gleefully skipping off to hide.
After going "you're it then, Anne" all cool-like!
I'll find you in no time!
Grea would probably hide in a dimly-lit place.
A place like here!
Or not.
I know where you are! You better believe I do!
Mustn't forget she has a tail and wings, too.
Psych!
Slowly sneaking up on your target
is the true thrill of this game!
So that leaves...
a hiding place way out in the open?
I know just the place!
She's really making this fun for me.
Grea?
I know you're in here somewhere!
Grea!
Not bad, Grea.
Time to get serious!
I can't wait to have my way
with you once I find you!
Grea?
Where are you?
Come on! Grea?
Grea?
Grea!
Can you hear me, Grea?
Grea...
If you don't come out right now,
I'm leaving without you!
I mean it!
I'll go for real!
Grea!
Anne?
What's wrong?
Are you all right?
Um...
Grea...
I found you.
Yeah...
Shall we call it a day?
Okay.
I wonder if it's still raining.
Yeah.
Do you have an umbrella?
Nope.
I guess you'll get wet.
Yeah.
This is nice, isn't it?
Thank you...
It even comes with a love potion!
What do I do?
Should I drink this tea Anne made?
Can I say no?
What's wrong?
I used some special tea leaves today.
Wh-What do you mean by "special"?
You'll see when you drink it.
It doesn't smell weird.
Aren't you going to drink it, Grea?
Y-Yes, of course. It has such a nice fragrance.
Maybe I'm just overthinking things.
I think I'll have some too.
Have you finished the book
you borrowed from the library?
Not yet.
What did you borrow again?
Let's see...
A book that will help me
get to know you a lot better, Grea.
What's wrong?
Your tea's going to get cold.
No!
What's wrong, Grea?!
- Episode 8 -
Backstage
Manaria Friends, Episode 8:
Backstage.
Illustrator: Coffee Kizoku