Anime Specials
Episode Six
Saionji-san and
the Baffling Customers
When I became a university student,
I picked up a part-time job in this popular,
nation-wide hamburger restaurant chain.
I've already gotten kind of used to it,
and it's pretty fun.
I know it's a little weird to say this myself,
but maybe I'm good at jobs that deal with customers.
I guess I should consider this
when I'm looking for a real job.
That said...
There's two particular customers
that I just can't wrap my head around.
W-Welcome!
They're here again!
Um...
Yes?
I'll have the new dessert.
The sweet potato rice flour
dumpling shake, correct?
No.
On second thought, I'll have the other one.
O-One soy milk gelato parfait, got it.
No.
Actually...
Why do you have such a scary
face when you're hesitating?!
Set A, please.
Huh?
C-Certainly. Which toy would you like?
This one.
Those two have started coming here often.
Ohta, you can have the rest.
You sure you're done?
You even ordered a set...
If I eat any more, I won't have room for dinner.
Rino will get angry at me again.
If you insist.
Extortion?!
What the heck is going on here?!
And that's when I noticed.
That there's a rule that
determines when they come here.
They'll be here soon.
They're here!
Welcome!
Um...
The new dessert,
chocolate green tea shake, correct?
Huh?
And may I suggest Lucky Set C
for the other customer?
How?
One of them just really likes sweets, and the other one
doesn't eat much, but orders sets because he wants toys!
You guessed what we wanted to order.
Are you psychic?