Noodle
Corner
Lunch
Curry
Corner
I got you today's special,
same as mine. You okay with that?
Yeah.
Thanks for choosing for me.
Bon appétit.
Tanaka...
Is there something in the meal you don't like?
No, it's fine.
I can basically eat anything.
There aren't many foods I don't like, surprisingly.
Good for you.
Young people nowadays are very picky,
so it's impressive that you can eat anything.
Ohta,
deboning the fish is a pain, so you can have it.
Most people would consider that "being picky."
I see...
Then I guess there are lots of foods
I don't like because they require effort.
What foods require effort, for example?
Small things, like beans and corn,
that are hard to pick up with chopsticks.
Also, fruits you have to peel yourself.
If it has seeds in it, that's even worse.
I see...
Wouldn't that mean today's lunch menu
is completely out of the question?
I didn't know, but still,
I apologize for picking that meal, Tanaka.
Why don't you let me debone
the fish for you, at least?
You don't have to do that, Ohta.
Then again, if most of his dislikes
are concentrated in this meal,
it's a chance to overcome his food aversions.
Do your best
I need to just watch,
and resist the urge to help him.
Do your best
There. I took it out.
But is this really all the meat fish have on them?
You had to debone it for me after all...
Sorry.
It's okay.
If I hadn't, then you, the fish,
and I would all be unhappy.
Thanks for the meal.
That was good.
He was able to squeeze out
the grapes without peeling them,
and he ate the beans and corn with a spoon.
It's been a while since I've felt this full.
Good, good. I'm glad to hear it.
Tanaka?!
Hey, Tanaka! Are you okay?!
Did I make him eat something he's allergic to?
O-Ohta...
Tanaka!
I'm so full
that I'm deathly tired...
I always get tired easily,
but this is on a whole new level...
I've never experienced...
such intense...
drowsiness...
Tanaka!
Hey, Tanaka!
I've learned something.
Tanaka runs on power-saving mode to begin with,
so if he consumes the same amount
of food as an average high school boy,
his battery will overcharge.
Come on, rest here for a bit.
I'm fine.
I think the food is starting to digest.
That's good.
By the way, what happened to that thing?
What thing?
The letter of challenge in your shoe locker.
What are you talking about?
You found it this morning.
The thing that said "Letter of Challenge"
in such forceful handwriting?
Letter
of Challenge
I didn't see anything.
I see. He's pretending it never happened.
Found you, you little punk!
You Tanaka from 1-F?
I'm Echizen from 1-E!
Fight me, Tanaka!
Don't fall asleep!
Tanaka...
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
After school I sit next to a window
And the spring breeze entices me to sleep
So I shut an eye against the dazzling world
While the sun makes the scenery dance upon my eyelids
I whistle vaguely at the blue sky
And I get more of a spring in my step
I remove my earphones in a bustling corner of the city
And look into the distance, where I hear a voice
Let's bask in the glowing sun
Ever so gently
Starting another day as usual
Napping in the sunshine
In this cozy place with you
With all these feelings booming in my heart
Episode 3
Girl of Contrast,
Echizen-san
Don't ignore me, Tanaka!
I wrote on the letter to meet me behind the gym!
Why the hell didn't you show up?!
Oh, so you're the one who
wrote that letter of challenge?
O-Ohta! Why are you with Tanaka?
Because we're classmates.
What?
You two know each other?
Yeah, guess you could say that...
We used to hang out in the same gang.
This is Ecchan, my next-door neighbor.
We've known each other since kindergarten.
I told you to stop calling me that, Ohta!
That reminds me, Mom said,
"Ecchan used to love the sweet donuts I make.
It's a real shame she doesn't come visit anymore."
Keep your heartwarming mom stories to yourself!
At any rate, she doesn't seem to be a bad person.
I shouldn't get sidetracked.
I came here for you, Tanaka!
Fight me!
Why do you want to fight me?
For certain reasons, I need to find out
what kind of person you are.
Hm, I see...
Well, it wouldn't be much of a fight,
so I'd advise against it.
Wh-What?!
I'm confident that I'll lose
horribly in any type of fight.
I lack motivation.
What the heck? You should put more effort in...
No can do.
I just ate, and I'm tired...
Uh... Then how about cards, or a board game?
I guess I could manage that...
Listlessness that even diminishes
his opponent's will to fight...
That's Tanaka for you.
We'll settle things with this!
I'll be black.
Guess I'm white then.
Pass.
You sure pass a lot...
For all that time you spent thinking,
you sure were a pushover.
Game Complete
Echizen
Tanaka
Yeah...
But I'm satisfied.
Satisfied? Even though you lost?
White
Invasion successful.
I won, but what is this undeniable feeling of defeat?!
Amazing, Tanaka!
But how did you do it?
This bastard looks like a lazy bum,
but he might actually be pretty capable...
Echizen, you haven't had lunch yet?
Here, you can have this bread I bought for dessert.
Thanks.
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
Bunny
Bread
with lots of
chocolate cream!
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
Bunny's face
is filled
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
Chocolate Cream
with lots of
chocolate cream!
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
Bread
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
Bunny
is filled
chocolate cream!
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
chocolate cream!
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
chocolate cream!
New this month
with lots of
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
Chocolate Cream
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
Bread
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
Bunny
New this month
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
Bunny
Bread
with lots of
Chocolate Cream
Bread
with lots of
chocolate cream!
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
Bread
is filled
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
is filled
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
Bread
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
New this month
Bunny
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
chocolate cream!
Chocolate Cream
with lots of
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
New this month
Bunny's face
Bunny
Bread
New this month
Bunny
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
chocolate cream!
New this month
Chocolate Cream
Bread
Bunny's face
is filled
with lots of
You fuckin' with me, Ohta?!
Ain't a chance in hell I'm eating this!
S-Sorry, Echizen.
Did I put a damper on your fight?
You want me to take a bite
out of this cute little bunny's face?
You're a monster!
Oh yeah, I forgot you're the type
that can't eat chick-shaped manju
or dove cookies because they're too cute.
My bad.
O-Our next match is cards!
You're pretty good at shuffling. Not bad.
Yeah.
I can do this, too.
Sorry, I got a little carried away.
It's pretty windy on the rooftop.
That's dangerous. Maybe you should shorten it.
Shut your trap! This skirt is my identity!
I can't just shorten it!
Tanaka's right, Echizen.
I heard those maxi skirts
are prone to getting caught in escalators.
Don't compare my skirt to that trendy crap!
No matter how many times we
count them, we're still missing one...
God damn...
When we play a board game,
you deviate from the goal.
When we play cards,
you lose them before we even start.
My best friend said she respects you,
so I thought you might actually have a spine...
But you're just a god damn weakling, Tanaka!
I actually tried to believe
that you were a remarkable guy
who was just pretending to be listless!
How'd you come up with that annoying fantasy?
You know what my friend said?
She said she wants to be like you!
What are you gonna do if your
influence turns her into a coward?!
I have no clue what you're talking about...
Echizen, that's enough...
No clue?! How are you gonna
take responsibility for this, Tanaka?!
Ecchan!
Oh, you're here too, Master!
Swoooon
Myaano!
You're as cute as ever, Myaano!
Put me down, Ecchan!
I'm not a kid!
Those two are actually friends?
It is true that Miyano respects you...
Sheesh, Ecchan...
Sorry, sorry.
You were looking for Echizen, Miyano?
Yes!
I was following Ecchan's scent,
and it brought me to the rooftop!
I'm so proud of you, Myaano.
You knew by her scent?
Echizen-san, you don't need
to worry about Miyano-san.
She has no talent for being lazy.
Plus, I excommunicated her.
Th-That's not true!
If I do my best, I can be lazy, too!
That's true...
Unlike Tanaka, Myaano is a hard worker.
Come to think of it, there's no way
Tanaka could influence her.
Sorry for worrying about something so silly.
That is a relief, but...
I'm kinda pissed at how you
made Miyano sound like a fool,
saying she has no talent and
was excommunicated and whatnot!
I didn't mean...
Fight me, Tanaka!
Ecchan!
Calm down, Echizen!
You're contradicting yourself.
What were you guys doing here in the first place?
Tanaka and I were just having a little match.
But he was so weak, it wasn't even a challenge.
Yep, yep.
I'm glad you understand now.
That can't be!
Tanaka-kun is amazing!
You probably just don't realize
Tanaka-kun's true power, Ecchan!
I see...
So he wasn't really trying?
Mocking me, were you?
I want a rematch, Tanaka!
I don't think this will stop until
Miyano stops respecting you.
I knew I never should've
accepted her as an apprentice...
Skirt Swap
T-Too breezy...
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Playing Shiritori
with Character Names
Ohta.
Tanaka-kun...
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Oops.
What's wrong, Tanaka?
Letter
of Challenge
I got another one.
Well, Echizen isn't the type to
give up until she sees things through.
She'll probably keep at it until she's satisfied.
I'm just being myself...
Anyway, it's a bit surprising that
Miyano-san and Echizen-san are friends.
Echizen's always loved cute things.
Really?
I don't know about Miyano, though.
They seem pretty close...
You're so cruel! Why?!
Stupid Ecchan!
I've had it!
W-Wait, Myaano!
There's a good reason for this...
Ask me what happened, punk.
Don't stroll by like it ain't your business.
But my "annoying" sensors are going off...
So, what happened?
A few days ago,
Myaano gave me a homemade cookie...
Here! I made it just for you, Ecchan!
Thanks, Myaano!
I-It's so cute!
Aww, it's just too cute...
It's so cute, I can't eat it!
To Ecchan
It's a bunny cookie!
Heat it up in the microwave
and eat it ASAP, okay?
Ecchan!
No! I can't eat this!
I couldn't eat it because it was so cute,
and before I knew it,
white fluff like a real bunny's started growing...
Oh, you mean mold?
Don't say it so bluntly!
I see...
So Miyano-san found out and got angry.
Yeah, she was so angry,
she wouldn't listen to my reason.
But you see my point too, right?!
A cute cookie made by the cute Myaano...
If I eat it, it'll cease to exist in this world!
What a waste!
You're so dramatic...
To Ecchan
It's a bunny cookie!
Heat it up in the microwave
and eat it ASAP, okay?
Just take a picture with your cell phone.
To Ecchan
It's a bunny cookie!
Heat it up in the microwave
and eat it ASAP, okay?
To Ecchan
It's a bunny cookie.
Heat it up in the microwave
and eat it ASAP, okay?
We live in an age where we can
easily store memories as data.
You can even set it
as your wallpaper...
I don't have a cell phone.
I've never heard of a delinquent
girl carrying a smartphone.
Just because you can easily store memories
doesn't mean I'm jealous...
I see...
Why doesn't she just give up on that hang-up?
In any case, I think the only thing
you can do is apologize.
But she won't even hear me out...
Year 1 Class F
What's wrong, Miyano?
You look like you're in a bad mood.
I had a fight with Ecchan! I'm angry!
A fight, huh?
You two are so close. What happened?
Ecchan didn't eat the cookie I made
for her and now it's gone to waste!
What?!
She wasted a homemade cookie?!
You have every right to be angry, Miyano!
People who disrespect sweets are our enemy!
Right?! It's absolutely unforgivable!
Miyano-san, you got a sec?
What is it, Master?
Myaano, hear me out...
Hmph.
I'm gonna be your apprentice too, Tanaka...
That's a no.
Then cough up some ideas for me, Tanaka!
I'm a pacifist...
I know you've got some ideas
in that little punk head of yours!
If she won't listen to you directly,
why not try writing her a letter?
A letter!
All right!
Maybe I was too cranky earlier.
E-Ecchan...
To Miyano
I have something to say.
Come see me on the
rooftop after school.
Echizen
Forgiveness
Letter
~ With a Dash of Letter
of Challenge Flavor ~
If that's the way you feel,
I gladly accept your challenge!
rr
Gr
I'm prepared for battle!
rr
Gr
Myaano? Why?!
rr
Gr
What are you stuffing your
little punk face with now?
Miyano-san gave me sweets.
She said, "I'm happy you eat
my sweets, at least, Master."
That was obviously directed at me!
Damn it! Why's it gotta be you, Tanaka?!
Why did Myaano want to be
your apprentice in the first place?!
You don't know?
Miyano-san said there's someone she likes,
and she wants to be listless and mature
so she'll be a good match for them.
Really?
She never told me that.
Myaano likes someone?
Why didn't she tell me?
I thought we were friends...
Could it be that I was
the only one who thought
we were friends?
No, I don't think so.
If so, Miyano-san is a very good actress.
If you want to know,
hurry and make up with her so you can ask
who it is she likes.
B-But I can't! That's the problem!
Haven't you ever fought with Ohta before?
No, we're steady, like an old couple.
And you see nothing weird about that?
Actually, I think my personality inherently
makes me incapable of fighting.
Being angry consumes energy
and makes me tired.
So I'd rather apologize, even if I'm not at fault.
Not much pride, huh...
Besides,
we get along,
and we both want to stay friends.
Dragging out an awkward situation
out of stubbornness is just silly.
It's not that I'm being stubborn.
I'm seriously angry.
I did my best to make that cookie
so that Ecchan would like it.
Because I love Ecchan.
I made that cookie just for Ecchan!
That's why I'm so angry!
Wait, so the person you like...
Yes...
I...
Out of all mankind!
No!
Out of all life forms
in the entire universe!
I love Ecchan...
the most!
That's a larger scale of love than I had imagined!
She's so mature, to look good in a long skirt!
I see! I get it now, Myaano!
Ecchan!
I was wrong.
From now on, I'll eat everything you give me!
That's all I ask for, Ecchan!
Myaano!
Oh, I see those two made up.
Good, good.
So, I guess the person Miyano-san
likes turned out to be Echizen-san.
Really?
Emulating my personality to be a match
for Echizen-san is a total mistake.
We're not compatible in the least.
Nah, you say that, but I think
you two are hitting it off pretty well.
Here, Ecchan. I made you a cookie again!
Thanks, Myaano!
Looks like they're starting over.
Yep.
Master! Ohta-kun! I made you each one, too.
We appreciate that.
I realized Ecchan can't eat cute things,
so I made sure it's not cute at all!
I call it "Machoco"!
I won't even hesitate to eat this!
Really? That's great!
This is kinda...
...hard to eat.
Anyway, you two have made up,
so there won't be any apprentices
or letters of challenge from now on, right?
No! I want to be a listless, mature woman,
so I'll still endeavor to be like you, Master!
Tanaka, you heard Myaano!
Hurry up and teach her the
secrets of listlessness or whatever!
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
You two threatening him?!
We're good friends.
No we're not!
Everyday life is like a bothersome cat
How I wish I could ignore it and do as I please
I discreetly retreat into my own world of music
Maybe I have a talent for daydreaming
That so-called happiness
What exactly is it?
I tried acting on my own desires
Will I understand it now?
Dramatic listlessness
I want to put my life into its hands
Maybe a positive attitude is better
Is trying my best the right thing to do?
I can't hold a poker face
Everyday life makes me dizzy
My dear listlessness
Once more
Hell yeah! Alone at last!
Actually...
It's Shiraishi-san.
...I'm below a male to him?
Are you like that in private, too?
I said stop, Ohta!
Next Episode
Shiraishi-san's Se   _
Next time, Episode 4:
Shiraishi-san's Secret.