When it's cold, you can always
put on more layers of clothes,
but when it's hot,
there's only so much you can take off.
Thus, your only option is to go to the pool.
Come on!
Wait!
Wait up!
Though I can't swim.
What'd you say?!
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
After school I sit next to a window
And the spring breeze entices me to sleep
So I shut an eye against the dazzling world
While the sun makes the scenery dance upon my eyelids
I whistle vaguely at the blue sky
And I get more of a spring in my step
I remove my earphones in a bustling corner of the city
And look into the distance, where I hear a voice
Let's bask in the glowing sun
Ever so gently
Starting another day as usual
Napping in the sunshine
In this cozy place with you
With all these feelings booming in my heart
Episode 10
Tanaka-kun's
Summer
I didn't know you couldn't swim.
So why did you want to come here, then?
I was surprised when you invited me,
too, since you rarely do.
I'll be fine.
I brought my partner along.
I'll just use the water to cool down.
That's enough for me.
I see. That inner tube looks good on you.
Ohta...
No.
Don't give me that "I just had a great idea" look.
Okay... I guess I'll just go with this, then.
Wait, Tanaka!
You need to warm up before you get in the pool.
Loosen up your wrists and ankles,
and give the muscles in your body a stretch.
What if your leg cramps up in the pool?
Especially considering you can't swim.
I see your point.
Okay, I'll get nice and warmed u—
Cramp... Cramp...
Are you okay, Tanaka?
It's dangerous to suddenly move
muscles that are normally idle.
Guess I should stick to lifeguard duty today.
I hope nothing happens.
Hey there, you two!
No jumping in!
You think this is a hot spring?
You forgot your inner tube.
This is heaven...
I could spend the whole summer
drifting on the water like this...
He's older than us, but he's using a inner tube!
You can't swim? How lame!
Yep, I can't swim.
But it's okay.
It takes less effort to just go with the flow.
Yes, much like my life itself.
I don't get it!
What are you talking about?
Let's just take it!
Yeah!
No... Stop...
Hey!
Rumble
Don't ever do that to someone
who really can't swim.
Rumble
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing too, Tanaka?
My partner...
Did it get punctured?
Oh, no! What should we do?!
Mommy! Daddy! Help us!
Oh, this guy may look scary,
but he's as nice as an angel, so don't worry.
You can relax.
Ohta, those goggles look scary. Take them off.
Oh, right. Sorry about that.
Please, spare my life!
I'll do anything you want!
Shock
Public Pool
It's completely deflated...
We're sorry.
These things happen. Don't worry about it.
It was admirable of you to apologize.
But I guess you can't play
in the pool anymore, Tanaka.
What'll you do now?
It's no problem.
I'll just stand in the pool, or walk around.
Splish splash...
Wh-What the?
Tanaka can't swim, yet he's floating.
And so smoothly, at that!
Could it be...
Of course!
Tanaka is listless beyond imagination.
Listless
He's naturally floating
without even thinking about it
Buoyant
because he doesn't have an ounce
of strength in his entire body!
Amazing!
I've never seen anyone float so perfectly!
He's a pro floater! I wanna try!
You're amazing, Tanaka!
I'm getting all kinds of praise,
even though I can't swim.
It's scorching hot...
Maybe working both at Wac
and as a lifeguard was too much.
I wish I could swim, too.
Hey, teach me how to do that!
Me, too!
A high school kid teaching
grade schoolers how to swim?
How heartwarming...
Wait, it's you two again?
Are you trying to be ducks?
Swim normally, would you?
That was fun!
Hey, Coach, when are you coming back?
Teach us again sometime!
You're fine. You kids are already pro floaters.
There's nothing more I can teach you.
Coach!
We will work hard and continue
to live up to the title of pro floater!
Thank you very much!
Good luck.
Avoiding an annoying task
without hurting their feelings...
You have improved, Tanaka.
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye.
Tanaka...
My body feels unbelievably tired,
and I'm incredibly sleepy.
What a coincidence. Me too.
Let's go rest.
I can't move a muscle,
and I don't want to do anything.
I feel like I've turned into Tanaka.
Huh? Then who's going to carry me home today?
There's nothing you can do
but wait for a new me to appear.
Mister pro floater!
Coach!
Oh, the kids from before...
We meet again.
Hey, guess what! That thing is really
popular at our school right now!
Everyone says it's super fun!
That thing?
You guys are doing that during your swim class?
See ya!
Ohta, maybe I did something I shouldn't have...
Now I'm worried about the future
of competitive swimming.
You never know what will catch on these days.
Tanaka-kun Is Always Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
I seek your guidance, Master!
I wish to grow at least ten centimeters
taller within five days!
I must ask you to leave.
You're beyond unreasonable.
Miyano, just calm down.
Low Fat Milk
Milk
What brought this on all of a sudden?
Well, Ecchan invited me
to go see the fireworks show
in yukatas next Saturday.
Let's go, Myaano!
'Sup!
Ecchan in a yukata...
Hey there...
I'm sure she'll look very mature and beautiful!
I know I don't need to act more mature
than I really am to be with her anymore,
but since I'll be standing next to her,
I would like to look somewhat sexy, too.
But at my height,
I think I'll only look good in a children's
yukata with cartoon characters on it...
Yay! I wanna scoop goldfish!
I feel bad for thinking it,
but she'd probably look perfect in that.
I'd be like the complete opposite of sexy...
But thinking about it realistically,
it's not going to be easy to grow
ten centimeters in five days.
I see...
I thought we humans could do anything
we wanted if we tried hard enough.
How about asking Echizen to wear
a cartoon character yukata, too?
She likes cute stuff, after all.
It'd be nice to match,
but that option is out of the question!
We'd look like a pair of weirdos!
I don't think you need to worry so much.
There's a very simple solution.
What is it, Master? Please enlighten me!
Don't go to the fireworks show.
That's something you should watch
live on TV, in an air-conditioned room.
That's true!
If I don't go in the first place,
I won't need to wear a yukata!
You're a genius, Master!
You'll make Echizen cry.
Shouldn't you start by looking for
a yukata that'll look good on you,
regardless of your height?
There are plenty of sizes to choose from nowadays,
so you'll probably find yukatas both big and small.
Good point!
Now that you mention it,
I haven't actually checked out any yukatas yet.
If I go to a specialty shop,
they might have a mature-looking
yukata for me, too.
Okay! I must strike while the iron is hot!
I'll go to the kimono shop after school today!
Could you two come with me, please?
Me, too?
I don't mind, but are you sure
you want two guys along?
I'm not sure how much help we'll be.
D-Do you think people will
see me as a two-timing harlot?
The scent of a dangerous woman...
No, we don't smell it at all.
There's no need for you to worry about that.
Oh, yeah! Shiraishi-san!
Miyano-san? What is it?
If you'd like, could you come with us, too?
Wow... I didn't realize yukatas came
in so many shapes and sizes. Amazing.
It won't be easy to choose...
Let's do our best to find a perfect yukata for you!
It's reassuring to have Shiraishi's help.
She seems very reliable.
Y-Yeah, I'll try my best!
There are so many cute designs!
So people really do wear yukatas
when they go to see fireworks...
Maybe I should buy one, too.
Huh? Shiraishi-san, you don't wear a yukata?
No, for various reasons,
fireworks were always something I watched
live on TV alone at home up to now.
In my loungewear...
You don't even go to see the show in person?
You're the same as Master!
The same as Tanaka-kun?
You two would get along well!
Master, Master! I've made a discovery!
What is it, Miyano?
When I wear geta, I'm a little taller than usual!
You're right.
I'm so happy!
In that case, you'd be even taller in these.
Th-They're like high platform shoes!
Those would easily add ten centimeters!
Then these would definitely
add twenty centimeters!
Sorry, but no.
They have men's yukatas, too.
I bet Tanaka-kun would look good in one.
I know! Shiraishi-san, do you want
to come see the fireworks with us?
I want to introduce you to Ecchan, too!
You're free too, right, Master and Ohta-kun?
We should all go together!
I'm down. Sounds fun.
Really? I'd rather stay home and sleep all day...
So you two don't have any plans? It's decided, then!
Sorry, Miyano-san...
The truth is, Kicchan and
Miyo-chan invited me already,
so I can't go with you.
Enjoy yourself without me, okay?
Seriously, thank you! Don't worry about me.
Well, I guess we should buy yukatas, too.
Let's enjoy our Japanese summer.
I should've made up some
fictitious plan for that day.
Split into
two pieces,
so you can
wear them like
regular clothes!
Split into
two pieces,
so you can
wear them like
regular clothes!
Separated Yukata
Just insert the bow!
One
Snap
Obi
One
Snap
Obi
I like this kind. It looks easy to put on.
This looks like something that
was made especially for you.
But it seems they only have
women's yukatas in this style.
These are way too cute for a guy.
I see... Then I guess I'll have to compromise,
and wear a women's—
Wait, Tanaka.
That's the one thing you
should never compromise on.
I prefer
Effortlessness
over color
and pattern
Master! We're going to try
these on, so please wait here!
I'm glad they both found something they liked.
Yeah.
Sounds like Miyano's height issue
can be solved with a pair of geta, too.
I-I kinda feel bad for trying on a yukata, too,
when we're here to find one for Miyano-san...
Um... I...
Is that you, Shiraishi?!
Your hairstyle's so different, I didn't recognize you!
You do look quite different.
Ah, yeah. They put it up loosely for me.
I like it.
It looks very good on you.
Th-Thanks!
I'm so happy! I don't care anymore!
Even if I can't go with them, this is enough for me!
Thank you so much, Miyano-san!
No pair of geta can save that!
D-Don't worry, Miyano.
You still have time. Chin up.
No, I'm fine...
What concerns me more is that
Shiraishi-san's boobs are so big,
Boing
I'm losing my will to live...
M-Miyano-san?!
Huh...
Sigh...
That was the smallest size they had.
Well, I did all I could and it didn't
work out, so I guess that's that!
I'll go to the fireworks show
in a cute summer dress!
Yeah, that should feel much cooler, too.
Cheer up.
She says that, but I'm sure Miyano-san
wants to go to the fireworks
show wearing a yukata, too.
She's always helping me,
so I want to do something for her this time...
Miyano-san, don't worry!
If you can't find one that fits you,
we'll just make one!
Sh-Shiraishi-san, you can make a yukata?!
I've never made a yukata before...
But I'm good at sewing, so I'll make it work!
I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
I'll do my best!
Isn't that great?
Good for you.
Good thing I recklessly trained in all kinds
of things for my high school debut...
Making
sweets
PC
Sewing
Self-
improvement
Okay, let's pick out a fabric together.
All right!
I like floral patterns!
That would look great on you!
How about this one?
Wow! It's beautiful!
Tanaka-kun Is Always Listless
Yeah, I'm sure it'll be cute!
So many food stalls...
So many people, too.
Master! Ohta-kun!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Wow, is that you, Miyano?
It's perfect. The fit is just right.
Yes! All thanks to Shiraishi-san!
So not only can she make macarons,
but yukatas too.
I have a new-found respect for her now.
I've always hated being short,
but this time, it's thanks to my
short stature that I get to have
a one-of-a-kind, gorgeous yukata like this.
Sometimes, being short isn't so bad!
Yep.
I just imagined your head on Ohta's body,
but it didn't look good at all.
You should stay the way you are, Miyano-san.
What were you imagining?
I-I don't intend to grow that tall!
100 Yen
Ramune
Frankfurter
Grilled Squid
600 Yen
Ecchan! Over here!
Myaano! An angel?! Are you an angel?!
The buns are so cute, darn it!
Ecchan, I can't breathe...
What the... You two came
to see the fireworks together?
And you're even wearing yukatas?
Are you on a date?
No, we're here with you guys. You didn't hear?
'Sup!
Sorry, Echizen-san...
Hey there...
You're wearing that more neatly than I expected.
You guys are tagging along?
I thought it'd be fun to hang out as a group
once in a while, so I invited them!
All right, I guess.
I'll allow it this time,
on account of how cute Myaano looks.
You look much cuter, Ecchan!
Ohta is tall and has a strong physique,
so he looks good in a yukata.
Come to think of it, we used to go
to the summer festival together as kids.
Ohta's ma made us matching yukatas.
Brings back memories...
Echizen, I just remembered how
we used to go to the summer festival
together when we were kids,
in our matching yukatas.
Huh?! I-I don't remember that!
Wh-What? Don't glare at me...
That's really cute. You look good, Echizen.
Wh-Wh-What is he saying outta the blue?!
Y-You look better in your yukata
than you did back then, too...
Ohta, they say you can put as much condensed
milk syrup on the shaved ice as you want.
What'd you say?! There is a God!
Shaved
Ice
Shaved Ice
Unlimited Syrup
Should I go with the classic strawberry milk?
But mango sounds good, too...
Ohta...
Have you heard?
There's this trend called "shaved ice shampoo."
This will cool you off, idiot!
Ecchan?!
It went down my back...
Oh, good.
Echizen-san is back to her normal self.
So cold...
It's starting!
It's magnificent.
Yeah, it is.
I should've bought the Tengu geta!
I take it back! I hate being short!
Everyday life is like a bothersome cat
How I wish I could ignore it and do as I please
I discreetly retreat into my own world of music
Maybe I have a talent for daydreaming
That so-called happiness
What exactly is it?
I tried acting on my own desires
Will I understand it now?
Dramatic listlessness
I want to put my life into its hands
Maybe a positive attitude is better
Is trying my best the right thing to do?
I can't hold a poker face
Everyday life makes me dizzy
My dear listlessness
Once more
Will it be a table for one, sir?
Ohhhtaaa...
He was wearing underwear!
...to save you!
Eyelid eyes!
Next time, Episode 11:
Next Episode
Tanaka-kun's Cul...
Tanaka-kun's Cultural Festival.