Strawberry
Custard
Danish
Strawberry
Custard
Danish
Green Tea
I just remembered...
We're changing seats today.
I guess I'll be saying goodbye
to my seat in a few hours, then.
I guess...
Depending on where he's seated,
he might not be able to slack off carelessly,
so I figured changing seats would be
a life-changing event for Tanaka...
But he's calmer than I expected.
Wait no, he's cast some kind of spell on himself.
I see... So he is concerned.
I'm already getting excited to see which seat I'll get.
I can't wait.
I just hope I don't get the front row center seat.
Oh, please no!
As expected, the front row is the least popular.
Is the back corner seat the
most relaxing for you, Tanaka?
Tanaka, did you hear me?
This morning's horoscope said, "Talk during
a meal, and you will tempt misfortune,"
so can you be quiet, Ohta?
Oh. Sorry.
This isn't just some event for him...
His eyes look as though he's marching off to war!
I've never had a front row seat,
from middle school onward.
Yeah? Lucky you, man.
Yep.
Nice flag, Katou.
Don't wish misfortune upon others.
Everyone seems to be getting pretty complacent.
They won't stand a chance against
my feelings toward this seating change.
Long Homeroom
Seating change
Tanaka, don't be so openly listless
right after changing your seat.
You're going to make me cry.
I think he's probably drooping
actually, sir, not being listless.
Teacher, this is a disaster!
This seat is abnormally close to the blackboard!
Calm down, Miyano.
That's not a blackboard, it's Ohta's back.
So does this mean I can't see
anything at all from this seat?!
Sorry, Miyano. I never thought I'd
be seated in front of you, of all people.
If I stay here, I'll only be obstructing your studies.
If you'd like, we can—
Miyano-san,
please feel free to switch with me
and take the front row seat.
Really, Master?!
Would I lie to you?
Thank you! I'd love to take
you up on your kind offer!
You're so generous, Master!
Miyano-san, thank you for being small!
I get it now, Ohta.
It's not about how far back the seat is.
The best seat is the one right behind you.
You provide a defensive barrier
and a sense of security.
I have mixed feelings about that, but thanks.
Still, I can't believe a series of coincidences
resulted in such an ideal ending,
even though I had all but lost hope.
This must be a reward for my
consistently good conduct.
It's not because of the spell you cast?
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Episode 12
Tanaka-kun's
Happiness
It's been a few days since
I was seated next to Tanaka-kun.
Now that our physical distance has shortened,
I have a chance to get emotionally closer, too.
I'll try my best to talk to him more!
Later, Shiraishi.
Ah, yeah. See you tomorrow.
I only said, "Ah, yeah"...
And it was to Ohta-kun...
I can't let this go on.
It'll be time for the next seat change before
anything happens, and that'll be the end!
I need to come up with a plan.
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Morning greetings...
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
Steal a Teenage
Boy's Heart
10 Methods
greetings first!
Morning
I guess it is the most natural way to communicate.
I see... So making eye contact is the key...
Here's my chance to put it into practice!
T-Tanaka-kun, good morning!
Morning...
No good! His eyes are still closed
more often than not at this hour!
Get his attention
with your femininity!
Flick your hair back
with your fingers
Overly long sleeves
The cuffs will stretch out...
Sex appeal
As amateurish as I am, even I know this
is probably the least likely to work,
but it's worth a shot...
G-Gosh, it's so hot today!
I've got his attention...
That's the most piercing look he's ever given me!
This was the only thing he reacted to,
but it's more than I can bear.
I don't want to steal a teenage boy's heart...
I just want to steal Tanaka-kun's heart.
I know! Tanaka-kun tends to zone out a lot,
so maybe emphasizing my
devotion would work best!
My feminine appeal is gonna burst!
Here, tissue. It's the moisturizing kind,
so it's gentle on the skin.
Ta—
Thanks.
I didn't take notes during the last English class...
Here, I'll lend you mine so you can copy them.
Tana—
I forgot to bring the handout we're using
in Classical Japanese this afternoon...
Classical Japanese
Okay, I'll go make a copy.
Stupid Ohta-kun!
That was the flag for putting our desks together!
I have a feeling I was able
to talk to him more naturally
before he knew who I really was.
I want to go back to those days...
Oh, but he did mention that
I was too sparkly and bright,
which made me unapproachable.
Which means...
I should go back to that look.
Sacrificing everything
I've gained in the name of love
is one way to resolve this, I guess...
I don't really get it,
but it sounds very mature for some reason!
What a horrible thing to say!
I can't do such a thing!
Is something wrong?
M-Miyano-san...
Oh, it's no big deal...
Just having problems
getting along with someone.
Maybe I'm hard to open up to.
That's not true!
You're a wonderful person, Shiraishi-san!
Please have more faith in yourself!
Don't worry!
Good things come to those who work for them!
I'll cheer you on!
Miyano-san...
Yeah, you're right. Hard work will pay off.
Thank you, Miyano-san.
I'll try my best to make this roma—
th-this friendship a success!
That's the spirit!
Take the initiative and get closer!
3 days later
Um, Shiraishi-san...
Yes?!
I'm sorry to make you go
out of your way for me so much.
There's no need to bother yourself with me.
I like being alone.
It backfired miserably!
It's over... It's all over...
I always believed that if you try hard,
learn, and never give up,
you can accomplish anything,
and I've lived my life that way.
But I guess people's feelings
just don't work like that.
How do you overcome something
that can't be resolved with effort?
That's easy.
If it can't be resolved with effort,
then don't put any in.
T-T-T-Tanaka-kun, you were here all this time?!
I thought I was alone, so I...
I fell asleep...
And Ohta went home already
because his sister is sick.
I don't know exactly what's going on,
but isn't it okay to fail?
Because even if you fail today,
there's still tomorrow,
or the day after that, if necessary.
It may even get resolved a year from now.
Life isn't short, so even if you
can't do anything about it now,
it'll work out in the end, somehow.
You don't sound convincing at all.
That was just sort of flaky and unreliable...
Totally irresponsible.
Well, that's the kind of person I am.
But I'm starting to feel like things will work out.
I feel a bit better now.
To think I was in such a hurry
to get closer to someone this laid-back...
Guess I didn't know Tanaka-kun
as well as I thought I did.
Thank you, Tanaka-kun.
I'll take my time and stop rushing things.
Hey, hey, Shimura.
That's Tanaka, right?
N-No way!
Tanaka-kun Is Always Listless
Tanaka!
How dare you take the first step up
the stairway to adulthood before me?!
Huh? I don't know what you mean,
but I'd rather take the escalator
to adulthood if I have to go up.
I don't like stairs.
Don't tell me...
You've already reached the "kissing" step?!
No, I just purely meant
it's a pain to climb up stairs.
What?
Don't play dumb!
I'm gonna have to go all-out
to celebrate with you now!
Damn, I'm jealous!
Calm down, Shimura!
What in the world happened?
This bastard here... has a girlfriend!
Huh? A girlfriend?!
What?
Saw it with our very own eyes.
Tanaka was walking with a quiet-looking
girl with glasses and braids.
Braids? Oh...
No, that wasn't my girlfriend...
In denial, are we?
If she's not your girlfriend,
then who is she?
It was Shirai—
Um, can you keep this current
appearance of mine a secret?
A friend.
Just a friend?
I'm having trouble imagining you making the effort
to be friends with someone from another class.
And a girl, to boot.
Hm, good point.
Then she was my sister.
Come on. If you're gonna lie,
at least put some effort into it!
Wh-What should I do?
The old-model Shiraishi is suddenly
the one drawing attention!
And, on the other hand,
I'm kind of happy they thought we were a couple...
But...
You've got it all wrong...
Come on, come on. Spill the beans already.
Tanaka-kun needs help...
Sh-Shimura-kun!
Tanaka-kun is denying it,
so maybe she really was just a friend?
Non, non, non. No need for concern, my dear.
Our little Casanova here is only
saying that to hide his embarrassment.
The very fact that he keeps
denying it is concrete evidence.
A defiant teenager being
contrary for contrary's sake!
You see, men don't actually mind
these things as much as they claim to.
What the hell are you spouting,
you damn four-eyes?
I-I see... They don't actually mind?
I don't really know how a guy's mind works,
so this is very informative!
No, Shiraishi-san, don't be so gullible.
Tanaka, I never would've guessed
you had a girlfriend.
I had no idea.
But don't worry.
As your friend, I'll support you in any way I can!
No...
Oh, but I would appreciate it
if you'd invite me along
when you two go out to eat something sweet.
Ohta...
Still, it's a little sad to think that I'll
be walking home alone from today on...
You'll be fine, Ohta.
You can carry us both.
I don't know if a boyfriend should be saying that.
You had a girlfriend, yet you concealed it flawlessly.
You kept your cool all this time!
Again, I am in awe, Master!
Very mature!
Rawr!
Rawr
Here comes another annoying person.
But I can't be bothered to argue anymore...
Still, you could've at least told us, your friends...
When I think about how
a certain person must feel, I... I...
Stupid Master! You nincompoop!
Sting.
Sting
Going to see your girlfriend?
Introduce us soon, will ya?
I'm just going to the restroom...
Later, Tanaka. Say hi to your girlfriend for me.
Maybe I'll follow you.
Piss off.
Yikes...
I've never seen such a scary
expression from Tanaka before...
Maybe we went a bit overboard with the teasing?
O-Oh, no! Tanaka-kun had a fight with his friends!
I know! I'll talk to Ohta-kun and find a way
to tell the other two it's a misunderstanding!
Don't say anything!
You'll be okay, Shiraishi-san!
Let's go have a drink! Some juice!
Oh, yeah...
This version of me just got rejected!
This is so confusing!
Hey, Ohta.
It's unusual to see you alone.
Echizen...
Actually, Tanaka has a girlfriend now...
A girlfriend?! Him?!
Seriously?
Somehow, he suddenly seems so far away...
Yeah, but it's a happy occasion.
We should be happy for him.
Echizen, I know it's weird to ask
this of you out of the blue, but...
Could this be...
Should we start going out too?
Echizen,
can I carry you under my arm?
I can't help but feel something
is missing right here...
There's been a lot of drama lately,
so it hasn't been this quiet in a while.
I might as well spend a quiet,
relaxing day alone.
If only Ohta were here at a time like this...
Leave it to me!
Hello!
Could we get a moment of your time?
We'd like to talk to you about this great product!
If only Miyano-san were here at a time like this...
Well, let me tell you about how great this guy is!
If only Shimura were here at a time like this...
Hey there, my divine goddesses.
Wanna exchange email addresses?
Huh?
Sigh...
How odd...
I was planning to relax alone,
but for some reason, I can't.
That's strange. Tanaka is all alone.
He was definitely with a girl
with braids and glasses yesterday.
Braids? Glasses?
Something about that bothers me...
Inbox
Messenger
Incoming email
Shiraishi
Ohta-kun... Ohta-kun...
Sorry, but that's not his girlfriend.
She's a friend of ours and my
personal mentor, Master Macaron!
Master Macaron?!
I'm home.
What's wrong, Brother?
You look more listless than usual.
Rino...
I realized something today...
Like what?
Ohta is absolutely essential in my life.
Damn you, Ohta!
What have you done to my brother?!
I realized how much I appreciate everyone.
It's true that no man can live alone.
Sorry, Tanaka!
It was a misunderstanding!
I'm really sorry!
Now that I think about it,
we should've realized it was strange
when even Ohta didn't know about it...
As a token of our apology,
if there's anything we can do for you, just ask!
If you want, I can carry you in place of Ohta!
It's okay.
I just want you guys to be your usual selves.
You're very forgiving,
despite how you look, Tanaka!
I'm so relieved.
I thought you'd never speak to us again!
Master! I'm sorry I called you a nincompoop!
Master!
I will follow you for the rest of my life!
Tanaka! What have you done to Myaano?!
Thanks, Ohta-kun.
No, I'm sorry I didn't realize sooner.
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
I'm sorry, Tanaka-kun.
I've caused you a lot of trouble.
Don't worry about it.
It made me realize some important things.
But everyone's reactions when
they thought I had a girlfriend...
If it causes that much drama,
I'd rather not ever have a girlfriend.
What's wrong?
Nothing...
I know they say "you reap what you sow," but...
Not... Not ever?!
No, I decided not to rush things.
I'm going to take my time.
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
After school I sit next to a window
And the spring breeze entices me to sleep
So I shut an eye against the dazzling world
While the sun makes the scenery dance upon my eyelids
I whistle vaguely at the blue sky
And I get more of a spring in my step
I remove my earphones in a bustling corner of the city
And look into the distance, where I hear a voice
Let's bask in the glowing sun
Ever so gently
Starting another day as usual
Napping in the sunshine
In this cozy place with you
This is where my story begins
The sky looks listless, unlike in the forecast
A passing shower on an early afternoon
I yawn and gaze up at the blue sky
There's a rainbow forming an arch
The school bell rings, a hand waves from a window
When I look up, you call to me
Let's bask in the vibrant sun
Ever so gently
Starting another day as usual
Let's take a nap in the sunshine
Take a deep breath to this cozy rhythm
We don't need to say anything
What a weird friendship
I wonder why
That's all that I need
To feel like I can become stronger
Let's bask in the glowing sun
Ever so gently
Starting another day as usual
Napping in the sunshine
In this cozy place with you
With all these feelings booming in my heart