Nakata-kun
Is Always
Listless
Well, I guess either way is fine.
I don't think this is something you should ignore.
Well, this sure is unusual...
I wonder what happened.
Did he get sick for the first time ever?
Could be.
Tell us if you find anything out.
See ya.
Have a good practice, you two.
Yeah, you got it!
Right.
Echizen-san.
Perfect timing.
Ohta's absent today, and the teacher
asked me to take this worksheet to him.
But you live next to him, right?
And you've got the guts
to call yourself his friend?!
The guy takes care of you round the damn clock!
Take it to him yourself, you lazy bastard!
Ow...
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
After school I sit next to a window
And the spring breeze entices me to sleep
So I shut an eye against the dazzling world
While the sun makes the scenery dance upon my eyelids
I whistle vaguely at the blue sky
And I get more of a spring in my step
I remove my earphones in a bustling corner of the city
And look into the distance, where I hear a voice
Let's bask in the glowing sun
Ever so gently
Starting another day as usual
Napping in the sunshine
In this cozy place with you
With all these feelings booming in my heart
Episode 8
Ohta-kun's
Ordeal
Fine, I'll take it to him.
Can you at least take me to his house?
What? Why should I?
Go by yourself.
But I don't know where it is.
You accepted the worksheet
without knowing where he lives?!
Jeez, you're a lost cause...
I'm surprised you've never been to Ohta's place.
You guys are close.
No, I've been to his house a few times,
but for some reason,
I'm always there before I even realize it.
That bastard's spoiling you rotten.
If you consider him your friend,
you should know the guy better!
If it were me, I could reach Myaano's house
even if no one told me where it was!
Ecchan, you're amazing!
Doesn't that just make you a stalker?
Well, I do want to know, and I should know,
but I'll have plenty of opportunities.
Considering we'll be friends for a long time,
we don't need to know everything about
each other right this moment, do we?
Well...
I guess you have a point.
So I won't be asking you questions
that dig deeper into your character,
like, "why are you a delinquent?" and such.
Just so you know.
It ain't like I'm expecting you to do that.
Come to think of it, why do I have
to leave school with just you?
Don't get so close.
Walk further away!
Don't walk so far away from me!
Keep up or I'll leave you behind!
Please make up your mind.
Hey, hey, hey, Echizen!
I think I owe you some payback.
Inokuma!
Why today, of all days?!
Tanaka, stay back!
Huh?
Just keep your distance!
Seriously, you saved my ass.
If you hadn't lent me that money then,
I wouldn't have made it home.
I seriously owe ya!
N-No need to thank me...
Laters.
Oh, it's you, dear.
Thank you for carrying my things the other day.
Hey, it's Ecchan!
I got a new Golvanian Family,
so let's play with them again!
Seriously,
why do you
respect
delinquents?
Seriously,
why do you
respect
delinquents?
If I asked now, I'd feel like I lost, so I won't.
Shut your mouth!
Ohta
Here we are. Do your stuff.
Thanks.
Yes?
Tanaka?!
I brought you your worksheet.
All by yourself?!
Tanaka did this...
All for my sake...
No, Echize—
I never thought you would make it here alone.
You can do it if you try, Tanaka.
I couldn't go to school today
due to unexpected circumstances.
It sounds like you have a lot
going on, so I'll be on my way.
I just wanted to bring you the worksheet.
Yeah, thanks.
I think I can come in tomorrow.
Okay. Take care.
Why did you throw your shoe at me?
Dumbass.
Ohta was happy to see you,
so just take the credit.
I had no intention of doing so,
but in the end, I've dug deeper into your character.
You're actually a really good person.
Huh?!
But I won't know how to act around you
if you act like a good person at this point,
so I'd appreciate it if you
could stay somewhat bad.
Don't make demands of my personality!
All right.
I completed my mission successfully,
so I guess I'll head home.
Yeah.
There's no one to help you today, so go straight home.
See ya.
Mam, I'm home.
Welcome home.
I told you not to call me that.
It's not cute.
Why is she a delinquent?
Tanaka-kun Is Always Listless
That looks painful.
Are you okay to walk?
Yeah.
Walking's a bit tough, but it's not too bad.
How did that happen?
You even missed school yesterday.
When I was walking to school in the morning,
I saw this old lady carrying
some bags up the stairs...
I told her it wasn't anything serious,
but she was worried and took me to the hospital,
so I couldn't make it to school.
That's very like you.
The doctor said it'll be healed in a week.
H-Hey, Ohta's hurt!
It'll take a whole week to heal?!
No way...
Who will take care of Tanaka until then?
I wonder if I can carry him...
Maybe with two people...
No.
Ohta is always helping me out,
so I'll take care of him today.
Seriously, Tanaka?!
They grow up so fast...
Sorry. It's just not possible.
I can't carry you with my feelings alone.
Nah,
I wasn't expecting you to help
me in that way, so it's fine.
You thought you could do it?
You don't need to copy what I do.
If you help me in your own way,
that'll be more than enough.
In my own way...
Ohta always uses his strong physique to help me.
My best features and Ohta,
who can't move right now...
I know.
I'll be immobile with you.
Sorry, let me rephrase that.
Help me in a way that lets me move, if possible.
Everything feels so far when
you have difficulty walking.
It makes me think...
I wish we could make the hallway
a moving walkway,
the stairs an escalator,
and all the doors automatic.
That is such a good idea.
I'll go negotiate with the principal now...
I went too far with my wishful thinking. Sorry.
Okay, let's begin with vocal exercises.
Stand up, everyone.
Sensei, Ohta sprained his ankle
and standing is painful for him.
Would you let him remain seated?
Oh, really?
If that's the case, you may sit, Ohta-kun.
Thanks, Tanaka.
Also, since I'm taking care of Ohta today,
I'm starting to feel somewhat tired, so may I sit too?
Just do your best, Tanaka-kun.
All right. I'm off to buy bread for lunch.
You want something sweet, right, Ohta?
Yeah, thanks. The new flavor, if they have it.
Gooey Cream Bread and a cinnamon roll, please.
And a sandwich.
Coming right up.
I'm getting tired...
They say you should have
something sweet when you're tired...
"Tired?
Cinnamon
Rolls
Have something sweet."
I'm back.
Here's a sandwich.
What happened to the sweet bread?
Well, due to various circumstances, it's gone.
I see... Thanks, Tanaka.
Sure.
Tanaka, where's your bread?
It's also gone due to various circumstances.
I see.
Strawberry
Melon Bread
Here.
Are you sure? Isn't this your lunch?
I bought too much.
Just take it, will ya?
You're such a klutz, injuring yourself like that.
Be careful.
That's a get-well gift from Ecchan!
Wha—Myaano?!
She went all the way to the school store
to buy it for you because you like sweets—
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
It's a new flavor! Awesome!
Seriously, why is she a delinquent?
That day, all my energy ran away from home,
leaving me all alone...
It was a pretty dramatic farewell, huh?
Tanaka-kun Is Always Listless
5th period
English
Satou-sensei is out on business, so this will be
time.
Self Study
Turn in the worksheet after class!
Everyone, please fill out your worksheets.
Hooray, self-study time!
All right, let's do this.
Again?
I know how you feel,
but self-study is a time to study on your own,
not free time, Tanaka.
Wait, you're already asleep?
The sleepiest time of the afternoon,
and on top of that, no teacher on watch...
I guess I really can't blame Tanaka.
He's working hard today, after all.
He'll probably have a very pleasant nap.
That kinda makes me feel bad
for trying to wake him up...
Is he having a nightmare?!
Are you okay, Tanaka?
Ohta?
Thank goodness... It was just a dream...
This very passionate tennis player
kept cheering me on. It was horrible...
That's the worst kind of nightmare for you, huh?
Also, you were able to fall asleep
and have a nightmare in such a short time?
But it's rare for you to fail at sleeping
under such fortuitous circumstances as these.
The conditions are all perfect for listlessness.
You're right... But it's okay.
I won't let this opportunity slip by.
I'll make sure I achieve the ultimate in listlessness.
I won't lose to a nightmare!
You're very passionate too, in a way.
In any case, you need to turn in the worksheet first.
Try your best not to fall asleep until you finish it.
Seriously?
I can sleep once it's done, right?
He's solving them so quickly...
You can exert this much effort
in the name of listlessness, Tanaka?!
His passion towards
listlessness is truly frightening...
Done. Sleep time.
Hold it.
Translate the Japanese sentence into English.
Mary has never been to Japan.
You might be good now, but you're gonna
get called to the faculty office later for this.
Romaji is just using the Roman alphabet.
In the end, it's still Japanese.
Translate them to English properly.
I thought I could finish quickly,
without using my head.
I'm too lazy to speak Japanese as it is,
so it could take 100 years
for me to learn English...
Look, English is as important
as our native language.
English is a universal language
used in approximately 80 countries.
If you can learn it,
it'll certainly be useful in this
globalizing society of ours.
80 countries...
Rather than me learning English,
it'd probably be faster to change
the universal language to Japanese.
If it's only 80 countries,
it's not too late to start.
You're planning to set history in motion?
No matter how I look at it,
I think a reform on a global scale is impossible.
In our lifetimes, at least.
I see... No good, huh?
I can sleep once it's done.
He can't really sleep once it's done,
but it seems to be motivating him to finish
the worksheet, so I'll just let him be.
Ohta.
I can't figure out number 2 on problem 4.
What a coincidence.
I'm stuck on that one too.
Let's go ask the teacher.
Oh, right... He's not here because it's self-study...
Maybe we can ask Shiraishi to explain it.
We shouldn't bother her...
Today...
is just a bad hair day, I think.
Wow, check it out! The world is totally red...
I'm in no position to say this,
but they look unhelpful.
Present perfect continuous...
English Grammar
Have been...
She'll probably try her best,
but I don't think she'll know.
I-N-G... Since...
English Grammar
Has been...
You leave me no choice...
but to ask my sister.
No, the only option here
is to solve it on your own.
We will now conduct a fire drill.
A fire drill!
A fire has been detected in the building.
Please evacuate the building
in a quick but calm manner.
Everyone, evacuate the building calmly,
and don't run or panic!
Oh yeah, they did say it was today.
Katou-kun and Shimura-kun,
could you please help Ohta-kun?
Okay.
Leave it to us!
Ohta, you okay?
Yeah.
There's always the chance that an
emergency could happen while I'm injured.
It's a good opportunity, in a way.
Uh...
Tanaka-kun isn't here!
He was right behind us.
Tanaka!
Where could he be?
There he is!
You're late, Tanaka.
I'm glad you made it, Tanaka-kun.
Master...
Sorry.
Maybe it's because Ohta
usually carries me everywhere,
but I got lost in the building...
There was no one around that
I could ask for the evacuation route...
That's dangerous!
In any case, I'm glad you're safe.
If this had been a real fire...
It's okay! Master has Ohta-kun by his side!
Normally that's the case, but...
He's injured at the moment.
Sorry.
Don't get hurt anymore, Ohta.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I'll do my best to stay
in top condition all the time.
I'm really sorry.
Ohta...
I know it's kinda late to realize this,
but there's no way I can help others.
Tanaka...
I mean, my basic mode of thought is,
"if you can't move due to injury, then don't move."
You could call me Tanaka Antoinette.
I'm not sure whether he's depressed or enjoying this.
No, don't worry about it, Tanaka.
Your willingness to do something for me
was enough to make me happy.
Ohta...
I've realized all over again that
I can't do anything without you.
Seriously, thanks for everything.
Therefore, to express my gratitude,
I would like to make this day
"Ohta's Day," just like there's
a Father's Day and Mother's Day.
Ohta's
Day
Uh... Thanks.
He created a day for me all of a sudden...
But since I decided on it so abruptly,
I'll probably forget about it next year.
He created a day to honor me,
yet he doesn't seem that grateful...
It doesn't hurt anymore?
Nah. Sorry to worry you.
That's great!
Ohta.
Here... A bit late, but it's a present for Ohta's Day.
Even I couldn't believe I got
lost in the school building.
I'll walk by myself coupon
It's dangerous in emergencies.
I see.
I'll walk by myself coupon
That's very commendable.
Then I think I'll use this right now.
We're just in time to walk to the next class.
Okay.
Do your best, Master!
Just in the nick of time.
Well, that was somewhat pointless...
Yeah.
Everyday life is like a bothersome cat
How I wish I could ignore it and do as I please
I discreetly retreat into my own world of music
Maybe I have a talent for daydreaming
That so-called happiness
What exactly is it?
I tried acting on my own desires
Will I understand it now?
Dramatic listlessness
I want to put my life into its hands
Maybe a positive attitude is better
Is trying my best the right thing to do?
I can't hold a poker face
Everyday life makes me dizzy
My dear listlessness
Once more
Welcome!
With toy number 4.
...but eating together after school is very rare.
Limited edition dessert...
It's your d-doppelgänger!
Next time, Episode 9:
Next Episode
Welcome to
Wa_
Welcome to Wac.