Anime Specials
Episode Four
Shiraishi-san's Palm
Reading Love Fortunes
Here's your love fortune: "You'll most likely
meet your soulmate during your early twenties."
I can't wait!
I can't believe you can even do palm
reading, Shiraishi! You're amazing!
Oh, not at all.
I only researched a bit because I was a little curious.
It's not like I'm an actual fortune teller.
There's no way I can tell them
I studied seriously for girl talk.
Life line
Fate line
Marriage line
You even know how to tell fortunes, Shiraishi?
Amazing.
I-It's not that big of a deal, really.
Not at all. We're talking about
our hard-working Shiraishi here.
I'm sure you approached it very seriously.
Impressive.
Y-You think so?
I haven't a clue which lines tell what.
Same.
Can you tell me something about the lines?
S-Sure.
Wh-What should I do?
He wants me to take his hand, right?
Wait, my hands are all sweaty
and clammy, aren't they?
Can I really take his hand?
What's the matter, Shiraishi?
Ah, um, I'll take a quick look, then.
Please do.
I took Tanaka-kun's hand!
Calm down, me! Look at his lines.
But Tanaka-kun's a boy,
so his hands are really big...
Well?
Um...
Huh?
What happened, Shiraishi?
Do you see something bad?
Do you?
Um, about your lines, Tanaka-kun...
They're so faint I can't tell a thing.
I want to live a faint life,
not standing out, but reasonably long.
Maybe my lines reflect that.
Oh, but your life line is really long.
Everything's good then.