Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
After school I sit next to a window
And the spring breeze entices me to sleep
So I shut an eye against the dazzling world
While the sun makes the scenery dance upon my eyelids
I whistle vaguely at the blue sky
And I get more of a spring in my step
I remove my earphones in a bustling corner of the city
And look into the distance, where I hear a voice
Let's bask in the glowing sun
Ever so gently
Starting another day as usual
Napping in the sunshine
In this cozy place with you
This is where my story begins
The sky looks listless, unlike in the forecast
A passing shower on an early afternoon
I yawn and gaze up at the blue sky
There's a rainbow forming an arch
The school bell rings, a hand waves from a window
When I look up, you call to me
Let's bask in the vibrant sun
Ever so gently
Starting another day as usual
Let's take a nap in the sunshine
Take a deep breath to this cozy rhythm
We don't need to say anything
What a weird friendship
I wonder why
That's all that I need
To feel like I can become stronger
Let's bask in the glowing sun
Ever so gently
Starting another day as usual
Napping in the sunshine
In this cozy place with you
With all these feelings booming in my heart