Morning!
Did he like the nail clippers?
About that... It was kinda...
Morning, Ohta.
Yo. Morning, Tanaka.
It's cold again today...
When it's this cold,
it makes me want to live at school.
I'd expect a lazy person to think more
along the lines of "I want to stay at home".
You're oddly conscientious.
I feel like I should at least attend school every day.
Even if my sleepiness wins out
and I fall asleep partway,
I can claim that I went to the effort of coming.
Thanks.
No prob.
Anyway, I'm proud of you for coming.
To Tanaka-kun
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
After school I sit next to a window
And the spring breeze entices me to sleep
So I shut an eye against the dazzling world
While the sun makes the scenery dance upon my eyelids
I whistle vaguely at the blue sky
And I get more of a spring in my step
I remove my earphones in a bustling corner of the city
And look into the distance, where I hear a voice
Let's bask in the glowing sun
Ever so gently
Starting another day as usual
Napping in the sunshine
In this cozy place with you
With all these feelings booming in my heart
Episode 7
Tanaka-kun's Valentine
To Tanaka-kun
Are you giving him chocolate today?
Of course! I made it myself.
My heart is pounding already!
What's with that look of utter despair on your face?
Tanaka, that box... Judging by today's date,
I'm pretty sure it's Valentine's Day chocolate.
I know...
I don't want to get chocolate on Valentine's Day.
And if I do, I don't want something
with a strong presence like this,
but an obligatory one.
Must you distance yourself so much from it?
Why is that?
Don't tell me you don't like chocolate?
No, the chocolate's not at fault here.
It's just that I'm not confident I can give
a sincere response if the giver has feelings for me.
It's stressful.
In fact, I was voted the boy most likely
to not give anything back on White Day
in my middle school yearbook.
I see...
Certified by a class of around thirty, huh?
All the more reason you
should redeem yourself here.
Heck, I'm jealous you got
a genuine Valentine's Day chocolate.
Judging by the box,
it's obviously going to taste good.
I guess...
There's one for you too, Ohta.
What?!
To Ohta-kun
Post-It
Chocolate Bar
(98 yen each)
I think we'd both be happier if we traded.
No, we shouldn't.
The difference in the amount of love is too great.
It's obviously obligatory chocolate,
but it's better than getting none...
Empty?! Empty?!
Why...
Why... isn't there anything in my desk?
None... None! Chocolate?
I humbly accept.
Anyway, who gave you this?
Now that you mention it, there's no name...
Considering this person snuck it into your bag
while you were away from your seat this morning,
it's probably someone from this class.
True...
Oh, there's some sort of message on it.
I'm
the
Time
You
watch
ing
All
And then I put a spell on the chocolate.
How romantic!
Right?
She must be really shy to not
want me to see her handwriting.
I guess so...
I'm sorry, but this is starting
to look more like a crime.
I was so nervous!
You gave it to him. I'm impressed! So...
Girls come in all kinds,
so it'd rude to be suspicious
based on that message alone.
Come to think of it,
there's no doubt that card was handmade.
I need to make sure Tanaka
gives something in return.
A new chocolatier shop opened
by the station recently,
so we should look there...
Honestly, I don't want his response
or anything in return.
I'm too scared...
What?!
It's supposed to be three times the value
of the Valentine's gift! Take it, take it!
Really?
I'd love to get some stylish sweets, then.
But I'm kinda put off by boys who
know about popular candy stores.
I know, right?
This is hard...
The chocolate totally seized, so I panicked.
My heart was racing!
Hey, Tanaka! This morning...
Was it you?
Huh?
Are you the culprit?
Of what?!
Tanaka and Katou, what are you two doing?
I-I don't know!
Tanaka is saying stuff that doesn't make sense!
You're not the culprit?
Sorry.
Tanaka is in a complicated
situation at the moment.
Man...
I just wanted to brag about my sign, Sagittarius,
being ranked the luckiest on today's horoscope.
Jeez...
Katou, aren't you a Capricorn
and not a Sagittarius?
Tanaka, I've been thinking...
Do you think it could be
Miyano who gave you that chocolate?
It's Valentine's!
If so, the difference in quality
between yours and mine makes sense.
Now that you mention it...
The message makes sense too,
since she's watching me all the time.
I see.
I never saw her as a person of the opposite sex,
but if it's from Miyano-san, I guess it's all right.
Bang!
She's more like a "living bullet" to me,
but I guess she has a sweet side, too.
I guess so.
It seems the path to your becoming
a mature woman is still a steep one, Miyano.
I totally forgot to get chocolates
for Master and Ohta-kun!
Seriously? Even though you idolize them?
I was only thinking about you, Ecchan...
They are boys, so they might've expected
obligatory chocolate, at the least.
We were 100% wrong...
Yeah.
It's like, I don't really see them
as people of the opposite sex.
It's more like they exist on the
same plane as God or Buddha!
Even if it was from her,
it would be more like an offering.
Yeah...
What if...
this was just a prank?
Maybe this person is laughing somewhere,
watching us make fools of ourselves.
I really shouldn't accept this.
W-Wait! Don't be hasty, Tanaka!
Right, the inside!
You should taste it first!
She chose this chocolate to be
eaten by the one she loves.
I bet you'll feel her love once you try it.
Oh, in case you don't feel it,
I'll help you, so don't worry.
I'll describe her feelings
faithfully on her behalf—
Yeah.
If he wants some, he should just say so...
How is it?
It's great.
They do seem filled with love.
Really? That's good...
So you don't think about getting
a girlfriend or anything like that?
Well, of course the inappropriate curiosity
innate to boys is present in me,
but not enough that it's worth
the effort to act upon it.
In other words, I'm interested in the erotic,
but the process to get there is too much work.
There was no need to put it "in other words."
Also, I meant it as a more innocent question.
It'd be rude to get closer to a girl
just to satisfy that inappropriate curiosity.
I believe that when I meet a girl
who makes me want to put in the effort,
only then can I truly fall in love.
I see.
Why...
Of all things, this is...
What's wrong, Ohta?
It's dark chocolate.
The kind...
that isn't sweet...
Have some of mine.
D-Delicious! I can feel my
wounded heart slowly healing!
I'm glad.
Hey, now that I look at them...
Aren't these homemade?
What, really?
If so, she's really good at making sweets.
But this sensation...
I have a feeling I've tasted this before.
So is it store-bought, after all?
But it doesn't match anything
in my brain's sweets database.
I've got it, Tanaka!
It's Lady Macarons!
Macaron!
Who? That sounds like some
goddess from Greek mythology.
A relative of Apollo's?
S-Sorry. I meant Shiraishi.
Only Shiraishi can make
something this high-quality.
She's in our class and she's shy,
despite her looks,
so she must've snuck it into your bag.
Shiraishi-san...
I see. Shiraishi-san, huh?
Now that I know who gave it to me,
I'm starting to feel appreciative.
Good for you, Tanaka.
You should set a reminder for
March 14th so you won't forget.
Today is Valentine's?!
Shiraishi, don't tell me you forgot!
I was a loner for so long,
this holiday meant nothing to me...
Huh?
I mean, my mind was preoccupied
with studying for tests...
Seriously, who was it?!
The boys must be disappointed.
I bet they wanted obligatory chocolate, at least.
But you have someone to give
a true Valentine to, right?
That's right! You said you've
fallen in love with someone.
No, we're not like that yet...
I see.
But if you need someone to talk to, I'll be here.
We're rooting for you!
Thanks...
The moment I realized
it wasn't from Shiraishi-san,
my stomach started feeling queasy...
The more I think about it,
it's dangerous to eat something
given to you by a stranger
in this day and age...
It can't be that, Tanaka!
They tasted so good!
Don't worry.
Those chocolates tasted of
someone's pure love for you!
There's nothing disturbing about it at—
(Wiretap)
Voice Recorder?
A criminal case...
C-Calm down, Tanaka!
It's just a misunderstanding!
We don't know whether the chocolate
has anything to do with this yet.
Is something the matter,
Big Bro?
Master!
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
It was his sister!
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
D-Don't look, Tanaka!
It's your doppelgänger!
I'm his little sister.
That's right, you did say
you had a sister in the 9th grade...
Yeah.
I'm his sister, Rino.
Thank you for always
taking care of my brother.
S-Sorry. I freaked out
because you two look so alike.
Rino, what are you doing here?
I needed to go to the supermarket
near your high school.
I see...
I think I've mentioned him before,
but this is my classmate, Ohta.
Nice to meet you.
Everything just wears me out so much
that my body can't survive without Ohta.
That's how important our friendship is.
Can't you word that some other way?
It's misleading...
Anyway, what were you yelling about?
She ignored that?
You're not going to comment
on what he said, little sister?
Actually, we found a wiretap
of some sort in Tanaka's bag...
This. It's frightening.
Oh, that's mine.
I thought I lost it, but I guess
it got mixed up in your things.
I use this to record my teacher's lectures,
since he talks too fast.
I see. That's convenient
when you need to review later.
No...
My plan is to make him listen to it so he'll
be aware of his mistakes and correct them.
It's to point out his mistakes?!
Brother, why don't you invite your friend
to stop by for tea if he has time?
May I?
Good idea.
If you know where I live,
you can carry me home from now on.
Come over.
I'd prefer to be invited
for a better reason than that.
It's decided, then.
Let's all walk home, Otter-san.
Otter
It's Ohta. You put so much effort into that mistake.
I'm sorry. I'm not good at remembering names.
No, I actually enjoyed it.
I never had anyone make that mistake before.
You're very positive.
Tanaka-kun Is Always Listless
Please, go ahead.
Excuse me—
I had to leave this morning before
I could finish cleaning the leather shoes,
so it's a bit messy.
No worries.
Will I be able to rescue my own shoes when I leave?
I didn't know we had so many leather shoes.
You're still in middle school,
but you're already taking proper care of shoes.
You're very responsible.
Good girl, Rino.
They'll last longer if you take care of them.
Have some coffee.
Thanks. Sorry to ask,
but could I have some milk and sugar?
This coffee tastes best when you take it black.
Please drink it as it is.
Is it good? It's good, isn't it?
Yeah...
A man who usually puts
3 packets of sugar in
It's bitter.
Their faces look the same,
but his sister is very diligent.
Still...
Doesn't she ever yell at him
for being so gloriously lazy?
Rino, I'm here...
Oh, sorry.
I see... She's already given up on him.
Udder-san, are you always
with my brother at school?
Hang on!
That doesn't sound remotely
like "Ohta" anymore!
I'm sorry.
This is the first time my
brother's had a friend over.
I've heard about you,
but I'm nervous now that
I'm meeting you in person.
No, don't worry about it.
I understand.
She might have secretly worried about
her brother showing no sign of having friends.
She may seem dismissive, but she's probably
a kind sister who cares deeply for her brother.
I should make sure she knows
I'm good friends with Tanaka,
so I can offer her reassurance.
Tanaka and I are good friends.
We hang out together
pretty much all day at school.
I make sure he eats lunch
when he's too lazy to eat.
Ahh
I carry him to school
when he's about to be late,
and I go shopping with him after school.
I see.
Then, starting tomorrow,
please don't do any of that.
Leave him alone.
It's not helping him.
Huh?
Oh, your cup is empty. Care for some more?
No, I've had enough...
Don't be shy.
No, I really don't...
The chocolates I got today would go well with coffee.
That's right! I forgot about the chocolates.
They'll definitely go well with coffee.
Right, right?
Big Bro, you got Valentine's Day chocolate?
Yeah... But I found it in my bag,
so it wasn't really given to me.
I don't even know who it's from.
It's very suspicious,
but we decided there's no malicious intent,
since they tasted good.
Anyone who can make tasty sweets can't be bad.
See? They seem to be homemade.
They were very good.
I see.
Huh? "Tasty"?
Did Ohta-san eat the chocolate, too?
Yeah.
Ohta loves sweets,
but he got dark chocolate of all things,
so I gave him some of mine.
I see.
Well, he gave me one,
but it tasted so much better than I expected.
I ended up eating more than half of them.
Hey Ohta, go step outside why don'tcha?
Outside? Is there something outside?
Uh, no... The sun is setting,
so I thought you might want to
go home soon, before it gets dark.
Let's see, which ones are mine?
Here they are.
I'll walk him to the station.
Okay.
Thanks for having me.
If you don't mind, I'd love to visit again.
Oh, and the coffee was good. See you.
It wasn't good at all.
I did it on purpose because he likes sweets.
I gave him dark chocolate to be mean.
I invited him here because I wanted
to know about my brother's high school life,
but all he did was brag about
how close he is to him!
How infuriating.
No one is closer to my brother than me.
I won't let Ohta have him.
Do you remember the way to my place?
I won't be your taxi unless it's an emergency.
Ohta, I figured it out.
It was Rino who gave me the chocolate.
Seriously?!
She probably gave you chocolate too,
since you're always taking care of me.
To Ohta-kun
It was the wrong choice, though...
Besides, the homemade
chocolates she gave me were...
leftovers from the batch she made for
the boy she likes, and a sample for me to taste.
I finished those chocolates
after researching various flavors
my brother might like,
through repeated trial and error!
I worked hard on the wrapping, too,
but I'd be embarrassed if he knew it was from me,
so I made a card he'd never figure out...
So why did Ohta end up eating them?!
She looked relieved when she saw my reaction.
Big brothers are perfect guinea pigs.
I see... That's very true!
My sister sometimes gives me
homemade sweets to try
to get my opinion.
If it has your seal of approval,
it's a guaranteed success.
But those chocolates were good, too.
With that flavor, I'm sure the
boy she likes felt her love.
Yeah. I'm glad...
Oh, yeah...
The voice recorder...
Putting this in the wrong bag
really was an honest mistake,
but could it have recorded
my brother's voice at school?
Tanaka, that box... Judging by today's date,
I'm pretty sure it's Valentine's Day chocolate.
Must you distance yourself so much from it?
Why is that?
Don't tell me you don't like chocolate?
I can only hear Ohta's voice!
Ohta makes me so mad!
Everyday life is like a bothersome cat
How I wish I could ignore it and do as I please
I discreetly retreat into my own world of music
Maybe I have a talent for daydreaming
That so-called happiness
What exactly is it?
I tried acting on my own desires
Will I understand it now?
Dramatic listlessness
I want to put my life into its hands
Maybe a positive attitude is better
Is trying my best the right thing to do?
I can't hold a poker face
Everyday life makes me dizzy
My dear listlessness
Once more
Tanaka-kun isn't here!
Hey, Ohta's hurt!
If it were me, I could reach Myaano's house
even if no one told me where it was!
That's a get-well gift from Ecchan!
Well, due to various circumstances, it's gone.
Next time, Episode 8:
Next Episode
Ohta
Ohta-kun's Ordeal.