Anime Specials
Episode One
Tanaka vs Ohta
Battles Without Honor and Humanity
I managed to escape.
No, I can't let down my guard yet.
Tanaka ran away.
Why?
What's the point in running away from you?
Actually, isn't Tanaka the one
who's disadvantaged without you?
I think in his eyes, I'm an enemy right now.
I definitely won't let him capture me.
I'll keep fleeing for as long as it takes.
Tanaka's having a cavity filled.
He has an appointment with
the dentist today too, but...
He ran away.
What is he, a kid?
Can't say I don't understand, though.
Is that why you're searching for him?
I've secured Tanaka's bag,
so he should still be in the school.
Okay, then allow us to help!
Sounds fun, like a game of tag!
I agree.
Well, if we're talking about places he'd hide...
I'm sure he's sleeping in a quiet place under the sun!
Huh?
You're wrong,
he's definitely somewhere with
a comfy bed, the school infirmary!
Huh?
You were wrong too!
That's strange. He's nowhere to be found.
Was Tanaka always this good at hide and seek?
Why's he in such a place?
While we were running around
the school searching for him,
he came back here to hide,
but probably fell asleep on the spot.
You understand him so well.
I guess we really should just entrust
Ohta with taking care of Tanaka.
See you later, Katou, Shimura.
Bye bye!
Brush your teeth!
Get them fixed right up, Tanaka!
Exam Room
KKKK
of our teeth!
Let's take good care
KKKK
of our teeth!
Let's take good care
KKKK
of our teeth!
Let's take good care