Those Awaiting a Star
Part 3
The Lonely Little Star
Late Spring Insects
I want you to deliver that book to someone for me.
I'm not able to do it anymore.
Get going.
If you stay here much longer,
you'll never be able to go home.
Late Spring Insects
Miura—
These are my memories.
They're the regrets that have
been woven shut inside that book.
That night, I had a promise I needed to fulfill.
A promise?
Someone was waiting for me.
Niikura Mayumi.
The owner of that book.
Which one are you going to borrow today?
I can't decide.
The master's books are all so impressive.
When they talk about "bookworms,"
they must mean people like you.
The same could be said for you!
Hey, I...
The master told me...
that you were going to get married.
Congratulations.
Is that all you're going to say?
What more could I say?
My happiest moments are when
I'm reading the last page of a book.
The story ends...
But it makes me feel as if it's
going to continue on somewhere.
Late Spring Insects
You can borrow this.
M-Mayumi?!
Please don't forget to give it back.
I was nothing more than a simple student,
and she was the daughter of the
wealthy family I was indebted to.
I never thought our relationship
would ever bear fruit.
Late Spring Insects
But...
I'll be waiting
at the
final platform
I'll be waiting
at the
final platform
I'll be waiting
at the
final platform
I'll be waiting
at the
final platform
I'll be waiting
at the
final platform
I'll be waiting
at the
final platform
She extended her hand to me.
I had no choice but to go to her.
No matter what it took.
I have to go to her.
I have to go.
I have to go...
I have to go!
I was drawn to this library.
I became its prisoner.
Late Spring Insects
I don't even know how long I've been here now.
But...
Late Spring Insects
You reminded me.
When you smiled and said you
most enjoyed the last page of a book.
Late Spring Insects
Return it to her...
To Niikura Mayumi.
Hatori.
There's no one else I can ask.
Now, go.
Please.
Late Spring Insects
Go on, hurry.
So that no one ever wanders into here again...
Niikura
Um...
Are you Niikura Mayumi?
Are you looking for my great-grandma?
You're from this neighborhood, right?
Grandma Mayumi's in the hospital right now.
You know the huge hospital by the river?
She's there.
What did you need?
We just got here yesterday,
so we don't really know our way around yet.
If you need something...
Hey, hold on!
Niikura?
Excuse me for asking, but how are you two related?
I'm sorry, but I can't tell you her
room number unless you're related.
Niikura?
I think her grandchildren's families
were coming to visit today.
Oh, really?
Come on, then.
Come.
Niikura Mayumi
Niikura.
You're out of bed again.
I'm so bored.
I've read all the books I brought with me.
Your great-granddaughter's here.
Already?
She's here early.
Weren't you going to eat lunch first?
You're...
What can I do for you, young lady?
Are you Niikura Mayumi?
That I am.
My...
This book... Where did you...
There's no mistake.
This is my book.
This is our book.
Are you his granddaughter?
Or maybe his great-granddaughter?
Is he doing well?
I'm sorry.
I'm so glad.
This makes me really happy.
He never did come to me,
but he did fulfill his promise.
He gave this book back to me.
And for that, I'm glad.
Thank you.
Let me get a good look at your face.
Come over here.
What's your name?
Hatori Chise.
What a beautiful name.
Thank you, Hatori Chise.
Grandma, shouldn't you be asleep?
Hey, Granny, look!
I got second rank in swimming!
I got third rank!
Hurry up and get better, Granny!
Uh, hey...
Let's go to the pool.
Did a girl come by?
Red hair, about this tall.
Ow.
What was that for?
Let's go already.
Hey, are we really going to the forest today?
Are you scared?
It's not my fault if we get lost.
We won't!
The Lonely Little Star
I gave her the book.
Mayumi said, "Thank you."
"The child of a star asked, with a voice like a bell,
'God of the Stars, why do you leave
me here by myself in this dark night sky?'
'I have no way to talk to the other stars,
or to show each other our light.'
To which the God of the Stars replied,
'Look very carefully.'
And so the child looked very hard.
So hard that their eyes could have fallen out."
Then, off in the distance, a myriad of tiny,
twinkling stars could be seen.
'See? You can see them if you look really carefully.
The sky is endlessly connected.
Just try, and you'll see even the faintest of lights.'"
This is the book I need?
Hatori.
Hm?
You might see nothing but
pitch-black darkness right now.
But, you have to keep on trying,
and keep on gazing into the dark world.
Okay.
And then, one day, you'll surely find a guiding light.
Like the child of a star?
Yes. Like the child of a star.
And when you find the child of a star,
they'll surely find you, too.
And you'll brighten each other's worlds.
And thus, your world will no longer be pitch-black.
Really?
Just look.
There are so many stars out there.
I truly believe you'll meet a child
of a star who will illuminate your world.
Really?
Life is a lot longer than you think.
Live your life fully, and you will...
There's no way I could believe that...
Yeah.
We're ready when you are.
I truly believe you'll meet a child
of a star who will illuminate your world.
Boys, can you come help?
The Lonely Little Star
Okay.
You will.
I can't believe this book is here, even after I let it go.
Show me more.
Show me.
Elias?
Chise, may I?
Huh? Um...
Elias, what is it?
Found it.
That story you just told me...
I believe I've seen something like it before.
See?
"The Stray House"?
Yeah.
It shows itself in a spectacular form
to those who get lost in the forest.
So that's how it draws people in.
Huh.
That's rather odd.
How so?
Those who wander in are allowed
to bring home just one thing.
You don't normally see this kind of thing around here.
People often steal things by force, though.
I see.
That's probably the condition for
their returning to their own world.
That Miura man gave you something
every time you left from the library, correct?
A library card, a picture book, and that book.
I do have to wonder if it was given
to you as part of that condition.
What if you don't receive anything?
You'd likely be stuck there.
That's what it means to wander into the other side.
Though I'm not quite sure
how aware he was of that fact.
Miura-san...
He must have known everything.
He must have given the book to me knowing that.
What makes you say that?
If it wasn't that book that he'd given me,
I probably wouldn't have left that place.
Chise...
Yes?
Is this memory a painful one?
Angie really shouldn't have sent us this.
That's not true.
Is that so?
I don't mind this book, either.
Yeah.
You're right.
It's already getting dark.
We've really been talking away.
We didn't finish cleaning.
We can continue tomorrow.
Sure.
It's way past tea time, too.
Stare...
Silky.
You made tea for us?
Sorry.
I'll have those with dinner.
You sure you want to make a promise like that?
I-I'll do my best.
All right, it's time for dinner.
It's going to be chicken stewed with tomatoes,
tomato compote, and dried tomato muffins.
There sure are plenty of tomatoes
during the summer.
Chise, what are you going
to do with that picture book?
I think I'll give it another, proper, read through.
I feel like I can read it differently this time.
If you do, would you talk to me about it again?
Of course.
See the bunny bees
And puffs of steam
From singing kettles in the trees
Bread and butterflies
With forks and knives
Who like to make a meal of time
Life is clockwork quick, lightning slow
Faster on your toes, so
Eat your sugared dream
And taste the day before it runs away
There's more to this "The Stray House" folktale.
There's more to it?
It's said that anyone who takes something
from that house is met with good fortune.
That might well be true.