Ready? Ready?
Boom! Yo!
Here in Shuchiin Academy
It's really a well-known fact
Everyone loves the student council!
Poke, poke, poke, poke, poke, poke, pop!
We got the president and Kaguya
Plus Ishigami and Sec. Chika
Don't you think we're the perfect team?
Sec. Chika! Sec. Chika!
Yeah!
We live here in this disordered world
Where everyone hides their true nature
But Love Detective Chika is on the case!
I'll solve any problem!
My IQ might be 3, but I'll handle it!
Scribble, wiggle, secretary! Secretary solving secrets!
Boom!
Wink! In a blink you'll graduate, so do something now!
Poof!
Flutter, mutter, willy-nilly I'll tell you your love fortune!
Anyone, anytime can fall in love and be a heroine!
Be like Chika, shine like a superstar! Yo!
Shimmer, flash! Sparkle, shine! Superstar Chika!
Scribble, wiggle, secretary
Flutter, mutter, willy-nilly
Back to the forest you go!