I don't see any of the infants.
We're leaving 'em behind.
I thought about what you were telling me before.
I reconsidered.
We've got everyone five and above on board.
They were obviously shocked,
but I think it'll work out.
We're moving on to the next
stages of their training, too.
Thanks.
So, what now?
Do we tell the infants too?
Think they'll believe us?
And if they do, can they keep the plan a secret?
That's not all.
Can we really take them along?
Huh?
It's not that I don't believe in Norman's plan.
But there's the chasm,
it'll be winter, and Norman's gone.
Even after we escape, we'll have to expect
the unexpected out in the wild.
I know this is really late,
but I feel like Ray made a good point.
You mean...
We mustn't lead them to their deaths
by getting them out of here.
But if we leave them behind, they'll be shipped out.
I know!
I know...
We really can't leave 'em behind.
Ray's right,
and so are you, Gilda.
But I'm done with seeing people get shipped out.
Right?
We'll take our entire family along.
Let's run away, all of us.
"All of us"?
What's up?
Well, uh,
what about the kids in the other plants?
Is it okay for us to just leave them?
We've never met them,
but they're right here, aren't they?
Families just like ours that live
in ignorance, like we did?
S-Sorry! Forget it!
What do we do, Emma?
I agree, we can't just ignore 'em.
Get Phil for me.
Emma?
I need to tell you something
about this House and Mom.
I knew it.
So it was like that.
I've been wondering about that "harvest"
the Sister mentioned during tag.
I even saw her checking Ray's drawer.
And you...
The day Norman left, you looked afraid of Mom.
I thought it was weird.
I see now.
Norman got harvested.
Conny
and everyone else, too.
That's why you...
Phil...
We won't take 'em just yet.
None of the younger kids besides Phil
know about the House's secret or the fire.
I've asked him to handle all that.
Hey, Phil, listen up.
Right now, I dunno what decision to make.
Take everyone, even the toddlers,
or leave everyone below the age of five behind.
Only the kids who are six or older get harvested.
Even the oldest of the infants, Manya,
has a year and a half left still.
Besides, the House'll lose fifteen older kids.
Since they value quality over quantity,
they'll slow down the shipments.
It'll be harder for 'em to kill older kids
who could become high-quality produce.
Not just that, you and the five other
four-year-olds have decent scores.
I think you've got at least another two years or so.
Emma, are you saying...
I can wait!
So leave me behind!
But I'm not leaving 'em to die.
We'll be back here before their time comes.
And when we return,
we'll take Phil and the rest,
and all the kids from the other four plants.
Phil, where are the others?
Over here!
Mom!
Where are Emma and the others?
Aren't they with you?
I'll go get them right now.
Don't worry. I promise I'll be right back.
Be good kids and don't move from here, okay?
This is 73584 from Plant 3!
We have an escape! Sound the alarm!
That was sooner than expected.
What now?
We're still pretty far from the bridge.
Attention all units.
Urgent message from Plant 3.
Fifteen kids are making an escape following the fire.
Two of them are top-quality.
As such, we shall enter the highest alert mode.
You may kill anyone other than the top-quality pair.
But make sure there is nary
a scratch on any of their heads.
Capture them as soon as they're located.
Don't you dare let them escape!
Run away if you can,
Emma.
We'll cross the chasm from here.
Huh?
Cross the chasm?
But back then, Norman said...
The bridge is the only way out.
Or so they'd like you to think.
That trying to cross the chasm would be too risky.
That's why you'll ignore
the bridge and do exactly that.
I checked both the distance to
the other side and the terrain there.
It's risky, but there is one spot that looks promising.
Besides, you still have two months to prepare.
Relax.
We trained like crazy for this.
"Trained"?
Nat!
On it!
Hell yeah!
Emma, don't tell me...
This'll work so long as we get one person across.
Hey, wait!
He did it!
Okay! It's our turn now!
One, two...
It worked!
All good here!
Smell ya later, Ray!
You guys...
Yay!
When did you all...
Told you, didn't I?
Wipe that smug look off your face.
Hey, I got you hook, line, and sinker!
"I'll show you something good,
so shut up and come with," eh?
I was right, wasn't I?
Look.
This is something we thought we would never see.
Yeah.
I thought getting everyone out was impossible.
I looked down on them all as dead weight.
I hesitated too.
But I was able to decide in the end thanks to Emma.
Only Emma can make everyone
believe in and follow her.
She's rash and reckless,
but unwavering.
Someone who'd choose everyone
without a moment's thought.
You don't have to give up, Ray.
Found them?
No! Keep searching!
Have they not reached the bridge?
No, not yet.
Check the bushes! Find them!
Why?
It can't be!
Five more!
Emma, help.
M-My hands are shaking... Sorry!
Thinking about the chasm scared me!
What if I fall?
F-Fall?
Don't worry, Jemima.
We can cross together.
Ray?
Emma.
We still have the rope we used
to pull everyone up the wall, right?
R-Right.
Use it to tie Jemima to me.
Do you know how to cross?
I picked it up from watching them.
How about you guys?
You're not gonna say you can't do it, are you?
R-R-Relax!
W-W-We're all good!
Well said.
Let's go, Jemima.
Look, Jemima. We're here.
I lose, Norman.
Last one!
Come on, Emma!
Goodbye, Grace Field House.
Goodbye, our beloved home.
Goodbye, Mom.
Don't go, Emma...
My dear children!
Isabella?!
Don't scare me like that.
I'm sorry.
I heard this beautiful music while I was
up in the tree, so I had to come see.
Did you compose that, Leslie?
Yeah.
It's a wonderful tune.
What's it called?
I haven't given it a name.
It's amazing!
Play it for me again!
But don't tell anyone, okay?
Okay!
Starting next year, you will be in charge of Plant 3.
Certainly, ma'am.
Ray.
Where did you pick up that tune?
Hey, Mom.
Why did you give birth to me?
You see, Ray,
I did it to survive,
to live longer than the rest.
But I suppose this is enough.
I've finally lost.
Goodbye.
Take care on your journey.
I pray that a ray of hope
shines at the end of your path.
Mom?
Rest assured.
They got out.
Mom!
I'm sorry, everyone.
You must've felt so awful in this cold.
We did it...
We did it, Norman!
We're out! We got out!
We'll definitely be back to get everyone else!
This marks our first step...
Our new dawn.
How much more of our freedom do we have to sacrifice?
It's my turn now, and I'm batting first
And before I could figure out where I messed up
A burning fuse was lit inside me
And thus a fire blazed
There's no God to pray to nor are there stars to wish upon
But even so, I never stopped having a glimmer of hope
Or else I'd be taken over by my fear and regret
It'd burn me alive
The things I want to forget are the things I can never forget
The path to Heaven is one that passes through Hell
Even the smallest of sparks can turn into a mighty blaze
So let's chase after the path that leads us to a better future
We're cutting it right to the wire
To get to the place where we wished we could be
And there's no way we're gonna stop now!
We're piecing our hearts back together
After giving up and neglecting them for so long
Can we make a future for ourselves like this?
But there's no way we're gonna stop now!