15 Years Earlier
How are yours?
The same...
Hell yeah!
It's positive!
Go inside and register.
Wait!
I have a family.
We'll need to verify their DNA.
Please line up.
Let us in!
Is this what you do to people?
Dad...
Oh, sorry, Iroha.
It's okay. Look.
This baby...
Was he...
Aragami!
Dear!
Let's go!
Looks like the Aragami have left.
What do we do now?
Honey...
If we abandon this baby,
we're no better than them.
What shall we name him?
Can I pick a name?
Sure.
You're a big sister from today, Iroha.
We will now perform compatibility adjustments
on your revamped God Arc.
You will feel far greater pain than when
your bracelet was first mounted.
If you still wish to take part, then we will begin.
I do.
Time to switch, Lenka.
Was there anything out there?
Not a thing. No Aragami in sight.
This is for today.
Thanks.
Good work.
I'm back.
Welcome home, Lenka.
Sis, I got my duty rations.
Thank you.
You should give that to Mom though.
Mom.
Here...
Thank you, Lenka.
Mom!
This disease is going to spread and kill us all
unless we can find medicine.
There isn't much food left either.
Do we still have fuel?
A little.
We're barely surviving.
Anyone able to will have to go out and search.
Are you in a different group from Dad?
Yeah, we're going to split up and search.
Lenka will be with me.
Iroha...
Take this, and bring it along with you.
Are you sure?
It'll keep you safe.
Since I can't go...
Mom...
Watch over Lenka, okay?
Both of you, watch out for Aragami.
Okay!
Right!
What's that?
If an Aragami shows up, I'll kill it with this.
Sis...
Will Mom get better if we find medicine?
Yeah, I'm sure she will.
Look, I found some!
Lenka! Get up!
H-Help...
We have to run! Hurry!
Lenka, are you okay?
They're...
They're all dead.
Sis...
Hm?
Will we all be eaten by Aragami?
Is there something you want to do when you grow up?
Huh?
They say...
this world was filled with flowers and trees long ago.
But the Aragami have eaten them up
and there's hardly any left.
My dream is to restore the flowers and trees in this world.
So that families can all laugh together.
And you, Lenka?
What do you want?
I...
...want to become strong.
I want to become strong so I can protect everyone.
That so.
In that case, we have to make it through this!
Yeah!
Lenka!
I'll protect you, Sis!
Looks like I made it.
You killed the Aragami...
Who are you?
Me?
I'm...
a God Eater.
Leave!
All right...
I'm sorry.
Stop it.
We took the test eight years ago, but we all failed.
So that's why you're all here instead.
Did they take the test too?
Fenrir is looking for people who test positive.
If you pass, you can become a God Eater.
Those who fail can still accompany
family members who pass.
I'm grateful that you saved my children.
But I don't approve of the way Fenrir operates.
People choosing people...
That simply isn't right.
I'll leave this with you.
If you change your mind, take the test.
Lenka?
Excuse me!
Can I become strong enough to take down Aragami?!
Kid...
What do you think strength is for?
To protect others, of course!
Lenka!
Are you okay?
I-I'm fine!
I'm sorry.
What is it, Lenka?
You're blushing!
N-No I'm not...
Are you jealous?
N-No way!
You're very close.
Are you siblings?
Yes, I'm Utsugi Iroha, his older sister.
He's Lenka.
Thank you for saving us.
Um...
It's Amamiya Rindou.
Oh, by the way...
Hang on to this.
A compass?
It'll always lead you in the right direction.
His name's Rindou...
What a nice man.
What is it? Still jealous?
Oh no, it can't be...
Dad, this is...
We could only find a little medicine.
This is our share.
But this is only enough for one!
We have to go out again!
We can't.
Even if we had a vehicle, there's not enough fuel.
But!
Dear...
give the medicine to Lenka.
Mom!
Never mind... me.
What are you saying?!
Do the test on Lenka.
What if he passes?
It's positive.
Thank goodness.
It's decided.
You...
Mom!
Sometimes you have to choose.
No way!
You know I can't choose between people!
Iroha...
No.
I want us all to be together...
In a world with no Aragami.
Lenka has a future.
A future that just might end up saving this world.
Let him have his future.
That's my final wish.
Iroha, be strong.
There's no use in praying in a world that has no God.
It's okay.
Take care of those two, Iroha.
I will!
Iroha...
I hope your dream will come true.
Just watch me, Mom.
I'm gonna become strong.
I'm back.
Lenka, welcome back!
Where were you?
Just out.
Don't go too far by yourself.
Right.
I just banged it.
Be careful.
What if it gets infected?
Sis...
Sis.
Wh-What is it?
That tickles.
It's almost time to assemble.
We should go.
Sure.
Lenka...
You can have this.
But that's mom's gift to you...
I want you to wear it, so take it.
Okay.
But why?
It's like a good-luck charm.
This way, we'll always be together.
It looks good on you, Lenka.
We're low on fuel again.
We can't use the car.
Our reserves won't last long.
Are there any other locations?
We've depleted them all.
Dad, wake up.
What is it?
I can't find Lenka.
He might have headed out alone.
Iroha...
Lenka will turn fifteen tomorrow.
It might be time.
You're going to send Lenka to Fenrir?
We won't last much longer out here.
You can't...
I'm against it!
I don't want our family to split up!
Besides, even you don't—
Have you forgotten Mom's wish?
Sometimes you have to choose between two things.
Back then...
You knew deep down too, right?
But...
There's some left!
Just a little farther...
Almost there...
Why?
How...
God...
Lenka?
Lenka!
Sis!
Where's Dad?
He hid in a different shelter.
I hope he's okay.
I found fuel.
Let's go!
This way!
Dad!
You're both okay!
Don't move. I'll get this off you.
That's enough.
Just go!
I hid a motorbike, just in case.
Iroha knows where it is.
Run! And live!
What are you saying?!
I'm getting you out right now!
We're leaving together!
Iroha... You know what to do.
Let's go.
No! I'm getting Dad out—
Lenka...
You have to survive!
Iroha, take care of Lenka.
Dad!
Hurry!
Sis!
I'm okay!
As I drift quietly toward the bank of the river
Which way do we go?
South.
Head south.
I dreamt a lonely dream
I still reminisce about the distant past
even after coming this far in my journey
Sis!
Lenka, take this.
If we ever meet again
What's in the south?
Fenrir...
in a future far from now
Fenrir? Of the God Eaters?
I'll hold you close and never let you go
You'll be allowed in.
You tested positive.
If you're determined to stay strong
Then why?!
Why didn't we all go to Fenrir sooner?
in this world shadowed by cold mist
We couldn't... not us.
"Not us"?
I'll walk through any storm
You're not related to us...
Fifteen years ago...
We found you abandoned and we took you in.
to a future that lies in the skies above
We just couldn't tell you...
I'm so sorry.
You're not my family?
That's not true!
We didn't want to let you go.
Because we're family...
Go, Lenka...
I can't walk any further.
In this lonely dream
Are you crazy?
I can't leave you!
Sis!
You're such a hopeless brother.
my tears quietly mix into the gentle rain
Sis!
This is the only thing I can do.
This is the only way to make you leave me behind.
In the spiraling currents tainted by mud
Whenever something happened, we'd protect you.
That was what we all wanted...
For my sake?
there's a ray of light that pierces through its darkness
That day...
You'd just been abandoned in the mud.
that I want to embrace forevermore
But to me...
You were like the lotus flower that blooms in mud.
If you'll stay strong until the end
Did you know that I picked your name?
I'll rest my fate in your hands
Your life ties all of us of together
Your life ties all of us together
You have to go, Lenka.
Grow strong...
Don't pray to God in a world like this...
like a flower that grows in this polluted wasteland
And someday...
save this cursed world.
A huge flower blooms in a broken vase
I tremble as I hold back my tears
The memories of the deceased
Now I see...
I'm sorry...
call out to their loved ones
Mom... Dad...
But their cries foster a new life
A barely audible pulse
An assuring feeling of warmth
The hope they've entrusted has been heard
This is all for the future
If we ever meet again
Lenka...
I love you.
in a future far from now
I'll hold you close and never let you go
If you're determined to stay strong
in this world shadowed by cold mist
I'll walk through any storm
Utsugi Lenka.
You have acquired the ability to fight again.
Before you take that new God Arc,
tell us your purpose.
to a future that lies in the skies above
I'm doing this to fight against the Aragami!
So tell me, why do you want to kill them?
...because I want to save everyone.
...but your death is inevitable.
That Aragami cannot be exterminated.
It's a cycle of despair.
Then pass it on to someone.
And someday...
save this cursed world.
This time...
I'll be the one to create hope.
I will protect you.
How about we drink the night away?
I won't let any more people die.
Our family can live in peace.
My path is engraved within me.
I will destroy Pita.
We will now begin Operation Meteorite: Phase 1!
Devour every damn one of 'em!