You still have it with you, don't you?
Habu's phone, that is.
Let me search your pockets.
Um, so...
Y-You didn't find anything, right?
Episode 9: Survival of the Fittest
Nanna isn't the culprit after all, right?!
I couldn't find any proof.
Not yet, at least...
What do you mean, "not yet"?!
That was close.
What I wasn't sure about
was how to get rid of the smartphone,
which proved my connection to Habu.
The safest option I could come up with
was to leave the contacts
on Kaori's desk in the morning,
send the message then,
and get rid of the phone before
meeting up with Kyouya and the others.
However, then it would be clear I was able
to send the message before we met up.
And considering Kaori could teleport,
I couldn't risk her dying before I was with Kyouya.
She'd receive the message,
teleport back to her room, and die instantly.
In that case, we'd have a death during the time
when my whereabouts were unclear.
Plus, if Habu's body was found
among all the zombies,
it'd be weird if her phone wasn't found next to her.
My second idea was exactly
what Kyouya had theorized.
I'd hide the phone in my pocket,
and once I'd sent the message,
I'd dispose of it close to her corpse
while the others were busy.
This seemed like the safest option,
as long as I could distract Kyouya for a moment...
If I missed anything Hiiragi did,
it'd be when we discovered Kaori's body...
I believe I never gave her a chance
to dispose of the phone, though.
Hey,
I'm sorry,
Sorry, it was all my fault.
Your contacts are on the table.
I didn't use them, btw.
You can have the chocolates.
Also, I saw an enemy of
humanity. Crazy, right?
The last message was sent at 3 PM.
Hiiragi must've held onto
the phone until then, at least.
When?
When and how did she dispose of it?
Since I couldn't be entirely sure,
I chose to go with yet another plan.
Hey,
I'm sorry,
Sorry, it was all my fault.
Your contacts are on the table.
I didn't use them, btw.
You can have the chocolates.
Also, I saw an enemy of
humanity. Crazy, right?
Hey,
I'm sorry,
Sorry, it was all my fault.
Your contacts are on the table.
I didn't use them, btw.
You can have the chocolates.
Also, I saw an enemy of
humanity. Crazy, right?
Considering the terrain there,
the zombies would be directly exposed to sunlight.
Once the finger I placed
on the send button started to rot,
the message would be sent.
Hey,
I'm sorry,
Sorry, it was all my fault.
Your contacts are on the table.
I didn't use them, btw.
You can have the chocolates.
Also, I saw an enemy of
humanity. Crazy, right?
It was a very risky idea.
I accidentally sent two messages
while trying to position the finger.
Hey,
I'm sorry,
There was also a chance
some animal could mess it up.
And if Kyouya had examined the corpses closely,
he might've realized Habu
was among them if he saw the phone.
Each option had plenty of risk,
Hey,
I'm sorry,
Sorry, it was all my fault.
Your contacts are on the table.
I didn't use them, btw.
You can have the chocolates.
Also, I saw an enemy of
humanity. Crazy, right?
so I chose the most rewarding method,
knowing it would be worth it.
Hey,
I'm sorry,
Sorry, it was all my fault.
Your contacts are on the table.
I didn't use them, btw.
You can have the chocolates.
Also, I saw an enemy of
humanity. Crazy, right?
Hey,
I'm sorry,
Sorry, it was all my fault.
Your contacts are on the table.
I didn't use them, btw.
You can have the chocolates.
Also, I saw an enemy of
humanity. Crazy, right?
Everything went well, so I gained an alibi—
I couldn't've sent the message.
And I was able to burn up
both the corpse and the phone.
But it was very close indeed.
Maybe I was just tired, but I almost
went with my second idea instead.
Apologize to Nanna!
She was so hurt by what happened to Yuuka!
And yet you put her through this...
I-I'm sorry.
You for real?
That didn't sound like an apology at all!
This is so silly.
Wasn't it you yourself who said
that we should avoid a situation
where we all start suspecting each other?
Why would you even think Nanna
would do something that scary?!
It's fine, Michiru.
I'm sorry, everyone.
I let another one of us die.
Kaori was killed by Habu,
who was under the enemy's control.
I just...
I just heard Habu's soul...
She wanted to apologize
to Kaori and everyone here.
She wishes for us to get along...
For us not to doubt each other...
So you can tell, Nana?
Whether we're being controlled
by the enemy or not?
It'd seem so.
Don't hesitate to come to me with any problems.
I'll also try to act as soon as I notice something off.
Is that okay with you, Kyouya?
I'll take care of Kaori's corpse until morning.
I'll notify the school as well.
He probably won't be able to tell whether the poison
was from Habu's Talent or something I prepared.
I wanted to settle this quickly, thinking that cheap tricks
wouldn't work on someone who could read minds...
Something still bothers me.
I should get rid of this poison before it's traced to me.
I don't like how Kaori's death
brought it to everyone's attention.
We concluded that Tsunekichi died naturally,
so Kaori could be seen as
the first one to be murdered.
Her corpse made it clear how she died,
which really drove it home that it was a murder,
unlike with Nakajima's disappearance.
I'm sure more people are actually wary now.
This'll make things tougher.
Oh, this is where you were!
I'm sitting watch in case the enemy appears.
You must be tired from everything going on,
and yet you're still...
I need to act like a proper leader
and keep going on patrol day and night.
That way, it'll be easier to act at night, too.
Although I did want to get
a good night's sleep tonight at least...
I'll keep watch for you, so you can go get some rest.
I want to be of some use to you, Nana.
First she tries to save Tsunekichi and Kaori...
She's such a strange girl, really.
I'll close my eyes for a bit, then.
These people are the enemies of humanity.
Yuuka's the prime example of that.
But there were also people like Nakajima.
Who's good, who's bad...
That's not for me to judge.
Nana...
You can read minds, right?
Yeah, what about it—
Then why didn't you notice?
Wh-Why?
When you're being threatened,
you should let your assailant ask the questions.
What's your real Talent?
Like I said, I can read—
It'd be a pain to cut off your head with this.
I-I just heard it...
Deep down, you harbor fear towards me,
which you're not consciously aware of.
Oh really?
What if Hiiragi Nana's Talent isn't mind-reading,
but a deadly poison flowing through her body?
I understand the concern.
What if my blood gets into your eyes...
Truly fascinating,
considering we've just had a poisoning.
You came up with a perfect story on the spot,
and you're clearly used to fighting.
Sure enough, you're no ordinary girl.
I could just call for help, you know.
But you're not. Because you don't want
your Talent to be exposed in front of everyone?
I don't want to say that Michiru attacked me
while being controlled by the enemy.
But I want to see how you'd get through a situation
where I prove to everyone that you're a huge liar.
I'm the class leader.
And no one would believe that Michiru could be
trying to plot something against you, Nana.
Is something happening again?
No, everything's fine!
See you tomorrow, back to being friends like usual!
I got you a present to thank you
for all your hard work as leader!
What is it?
What's that?
She prepared a gift!
Try to guess!
What's wrong?
Can't you read minds?
I'm so sorry.
I must still be tired,
so I can't hear anything right now.
Then I'll ask you again during lunch!
I'll keep the present for later.
First during lunch, then I'll ask after school.
And then tomorrow.
You can tell everyone you just
can't choose what you hear,
but they won't buy that forever.
I have no way of telling what's inside.
I can't let her control the situation.
Her goal is to expose the truth about my Talent,
and damage everyone's trust in me as their leader.
First it was Yuuka, and now
Takanashi and Habu were killed as well.
Should we really be studying like nothing happened?
Trust me, I'm talking to my superiors about this.
Look, aren't there fewer and fewer
students coming to school?
Everyone's looking out for themselves.
What did the leader, Hiiragi, say?
I'm constantly thinking about what's inside!
You can read my mind, right?
Since we're all here together,
I'm hearing everyone's thoughts at once,
so it's hard to separate what you're thinking from—
Can't you tell?
If I were to guess based on the thought
I'm hearing the loudest right now...
It is a card?
It's actually a bath additive!
Oh, my.
You seem really tired...
Are you going to be okay when we need you?
Don't worry. I can definitely hear it.
Right now, even.
I hear an "I love Nanna".
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
AAAAAAAAAAA
Hey, Inukai.
Something's attached to your back.
Huh?
I love
Nanna
Well, we weren't sure if it was okay to bring it up...
I love
Nanna
Since, you know, you've been so passionately
preoccupied with Nana all day...
Well, it's true that we were all
thinking about this piece of paper.
Those must've been the thoughts she was hearing.
AAAAAAAAAAA
I love
Nanna
Oh, I see!
Your thoughts were so strong
I couldn't really pick out Michiru's—
Actually, who did this?!
Don't bully Michiru!
I was sure she just wanted to let
everyone know how much she loves you.
I mean, I admit I do love Michiru a lot, too...
But you'd never bully her,
so you're not involved in this prank.
If I'd known about that paper,
I'd have pointed it out already!
You didn't know about it,
but you knew what was written on it.
Clearly you read our minds.
That means Nana's Talent is actually working.
Yes, I wrote this.
I dare you to try and accuse me
of it in this situation, though.
That's great to hear!
Thank you so much for your little gift!
I'm not sure what's going on,
but who's responsible for this prank?
Can you chill out?
Still playing detective?
Eh, I guess this is just a harmless prank.
Are you even listening?!
I didn't get to prove anything last night.
I should focus on getting everyone's trust back.
Forget that.
I'm recruiting people to become best buddies
with and go eat lunch together.
I swear to god...
You managed to get through the day.
So what's the deal with patrolling way out here?
I'm continuing where I left off yesterday.
I figured.
I have one question for you first, though.
Where's the real Michiru?
Real?
Were you the real Michiru, you would've
healed your wrist with your Talent already.
Oh, now I remember.
Michiru calls you "Nanna", doesn't she?
You must be some sort of
transforming type, I'd assume.
Transforming into someone
as powerless as Michiru of all people
will only come back to bite you.
You keep raising my curiosity.
Why did you worry about the real Michiru's
well-being instead of getting rid of me first?
I don't understand your point.
At first glance, you seem
to murder people indiscriminately,
but really, Michiru gets special treatment?
My decision to transform into her was correct.
I got to learn something new about you.
Wait a second.
You mentioned murders?
I'm Tachibana Jin.
You've probably never seen me before.
My name should already be
erased from the class register.
You could say I'm sort of your upperclassman.
I'd like to make a deal with you.
I just slipped a sleeping drug
into her drink, don't worry.
How far are we going?
All I have is some coffee
I grabbed from the dining hall.
I'm sure you don't mind?
Much appreciated.
Don't tell me you actually live here?
I do, whenever I feel like having
some human food once in a while.
What?
It seems like Kyouya has already searched you,
but do you have your sewing tools on you right now?
I don't get what you mean.
I'm trying to say that I have
quite a bit of dirt on you.
The only problem is that there's
no one to replace you as a leader.
For the past five years, I've been trying to figure out
who it'd be beneficial to reveal myself to.
If you'd be so kind as to tell me
what happened five years ago,
I might just be able to help you
solve this problem, you know.
I invited you here hoping for exactly that.
Could you be a classmate
of those zombies in the forest?
I tried to give them proper burials,
since they were my friends.
Sasaki Yuuka dug them out
and raised them, though.
You might be a murderer through and through,
but I appreciate that you gave her
what she deserved, really.
You sure are well-informed.
Those who see what my Talent does
forget all about evolutionary theory
and want to start writing fairy tales.
Here's a fun fact:
most birds can see pretty well at night.
But their vision is somewhat distorted,
so I'd never gotten a proper look at you asleep.
You were watching me?
You saved my life once, after all.
That's what got me curious initially.
Could you tell Kyouya, actually?
I'm fed up with his packaged milk.
That cat was him?
Ah, the idiot cat that got stuck
in the drain was a real one, though.
You seemed to be in such a rush then,
but prioritized saving its life...
Is that who you really are?
Well, I don't know who you really are.
So far you seem like a degenerate stalker
who enjoys watching murders?
Judging by that response, it sounds like you won't
tell me anything, even if I pull out your womb.
I shall expose myself first, then.
She either used some unknown poison
produced by Habu's Talent,
or maybe...
She could've used this to poison Kaori.
It's not difficult to collect poison from these,
but purifying it to a high grade wouldn't be easy.
How did Hiiragi learn this?
It's easy to think you're not like the others.
That you're above ordinary humans.
And it's not healthy to suppress
those thoughts during adolescence.
Especially when we're talking about
those with special powers.
Five years ago, we naturally...
fought each other to the death.
First, a student like Nakajima,
someone with a lot of potential, went missing.
It became apparent later that
he'd been killed by a girl from our class.
She said she'd wanted to prove
that she was the strongest.
We decided to isolate her,
but I remembered that she'd
actually loved the one she killed.
And that it was an unrequited love.
I assume the murders continued?
She was the next one to die.
Then the girl who organized her murder
died by being sent into outer space.
The one who did it lived next door to me.
And soon you didn't have a neighbor anymore?
The strong inflict fear into those weaker than them.
We ultimately split into groups to fight each other.
Each group convinced themselves
that the others were under the enemy's control.
No one forced this thought onto us.
We were simply battling our delusions.
Did you run into a rusty shed when
Sasaki Yuuka chased you into the mountains?
Each group had their hiding spots,
and that was one of them.
As the conflict got worse, fewer and fewer
students actually attended school at all.
And the school didn't step in?
The teachers escaped the island
as if they knew this would happen.
Of course those who could fly or teleport
chased right after the ship.
I also tried to follow it, but quickly gave up.
I heard merciless gunshots
aimed at the beach from the ship's bridge.
We didn't achieve peace afterwards either.
It's because there's no clear
balance of power between the Talented.
The two conflicting groups were led
by someone who could freeze time
and someone who could predict the future.
Both kept bragging about being the strongest,
at the same time fearing
that the other might be stronger.
So you turned into a cat and led a carefree life.
Look at evolutionary theory.
It's not those who are the strongest
that get to survive,
it's those who are able to adapt.
Once all of my classmates were dead,
I used my Talent to get back to the mainland.
My elderly grandmother was my only relative.
She started praying as soon as she saw me.
Apparently I'd "died" in a battle
against the enemies of humanity.
What's more, some people
clearly didn't want me alive.
I said my goodbyes and left on a journey.
Eventually they started to bring
people to the island again.
What'd happened was still kept secret.
I admit we all killed each other out of stupid pride.
But it might've been part of
a scheme by the government.
I felt like it'd be weighing on my mind
for the rest of my life if I simply ignored that.
So I decided to return to the island.
And what did I see?
An irregularity that wasn't there during my time.
You mean me?
It'd be very easy to finger you as the murderer.
There're people who don't want you alive, you said?
You weren't sure about showing yourself,
so you dragged me out here.
I believe you'd need to solve
that problem before accusing me.
Worst case scenario, wouldn't that cause
a repeat of what happened five years ago?
Indeed.
As long as you don't explain your motive, at least.
So that's why you want to make a deal.
Nana.
I'll let you roam freely for now.
I believe you must've killed a friend or two as well.
So tell me your story now.
And if I refuse?
I'll forget everything that happened
and start a business overseas or something.
Though I'd do the students a favor
and kill the pretty murderer first.
Okay.
But if we're making a deal,
I'd like us to be on equal footing.
Anything you're upset about?
I'm sorry,
but I'm not sure how I feel about someone
who doesn't even notice their drink's been poisoned.
S-So you're a pawn in their scheme?
I'm a survivor from five years ago.
Who would you even report... my death... to?
Report, hm?
They all were given a gift
I admit this was unexpected.
The call of a power within
I'll need to tell the Committee about this.
Because of that one sin
Kyouya?
We brand them as monstrosities
I see now.
As if by a whim of the gods
This device can tell me about all your secrets.
Or maybe some mischief of time
Where did he come from?!
Skillful magicians make mistakes at the start of their shows
to get the audience to let their guard down.
What they all had thought was a gift
Brought with it unique agony
This wasn't what I hoped I would become
Little things like calling you Nana instead of Nanna...
But what good would struggling have done
Or putting a compress over wounds
that are already healed...
And pretending your wrist still hurts.
When it was clear that I never would be loved?
That's how I got you as well.
You had the wrong idea about my Talent.
So who should I direct this bitter rage at?
I mentioned earlier that there's no clear
balance of power between the Talented,
Was my life all a lie?
but there's one exception to that.
I am the exception.
Have you been on my side?
What if you being there helped surface all my doubts?
You not only copy their appearances,
but also their Talents?!
There might still be a chance
I can use as many Talents as there are Talented, yes!
Maybe a chance that I maybe could see that I've been misguided all along
There's no way I could've survived
a gory superhuman war
with a simple Talent that only
changed my appearance, is there?
He's...
I could leave the world the way that it is
truly an enemy of humanity.
A real monster!
Next Episode: Invisible Blade
"Invisible Blade".