Class duty:
Hiiragi Nana
Hey, transfer student!
About that shed explosion yesterday...
I hear that was from you playing with fire?
It wasn't my fault.
I got attacked by an enemy.
Good one!
Tell me, then...
Why is Nakajima absent again?
Class duty:
Hiiragi Nana
How would I know?
I bet you killed him or something.
As I'm drifting through an eternity
As
I'm
drift
ing
through
The souls of fragile beings crashing over me
The
souls
of
fra
gile
be
ings
crash
ing
o
ver
me
The heavens fracture
The
hea
vens
frac
ture
But clouds mask the broken sky
But
clouds
mask
the
bro
ken
sky
Using awkward circumstance to gain the upper hand
Us
ing
awk
ward
cir
cum
stance
to
gain
the
up
per
hand
I try to test the will of God
I
try
to
test
the
will
of
God
It almost felt as if I could deceive him
It
al
most
felt
as
if
I
could
de
ceive
him
When I found you at the end of my eternal search
When
I
found
search
I also found my lost tears
I
al
so
found
my
lost
tears
Kill all the enemies
of humanity.
Though I lie
Though
I
lie
To others
To
o
thers
Time after time
Time
af
ter
time
I don't need deceit to keep you
I
don't
need
de
ceit
to
keep
you
Smiling and pure
Smi
l
ing
and
pure
My one "talent" is my mercilessness
My
one
"
ta
lent
less
ness
I weave a tangled web of destiny and death
I
weave
a
tan
gled
death
My sins dispassionate and dull
My
sins
dis
pas
sion
ate
and
dull
Hidden deep down inside my soul
Hid
den
deep
down
in
side
my
soul
Sudden showers voice their assent
Sud
den
sho
wers
voice
their
as
sent
And mute the screams of those who meet their end
And
mute
the
screams
of
those
who
meet
their
end
The heavens warp but
The
hea
vens
warp
but
The clouds mask the broken sky
The
clouds
mask
the
bro
ken
sky
Immortality, of all things?
What a surprise.
It was a mistake to set a trap
without knowing about his Talent first.
Episode 4: Healing
Actually...
Nakajima aside, I wonder
what happened to Shibusawa?
The enemy probably attacked him
just like with me, and killed him.
You really don't know when to stop!
What is it, then? The enemies of humanity
are already on the island?
Calm down.
In any case, we might need to choose
a different leader soon.
A leader, huh?
I failed to finish Kyouya off,
so he's likely to keep claiming that he got attacked.
I probably won't be able to keep Nakajima and
Shibusawa's deaths secret for much longer, either.
Hiiragi.
Say something to these two morons, would you?
The problem here is Kyouya.
I need to start by getting him off my tail
if I want to advance in my mission.
My gosh, that's crazy!
There was a love letter in Michiru's shoe locker!
What does it say, let's see...
Once school's done today, are you free?
Tell me your answer at the flower beds.
I've finally mustered up the courage to tell you.
Once school's done today, are you free?
Tell me your answer at the flower beds.
I like you, Michiru. I've felt this way for a year now.
Despite being in different classes, I still always get to see you taking care of the flower beds.
I've finally mustered up the courage to tell you.
Once school's done today, are you free?
Tell me your answer at the flower beds.
I like you, Michiru. I've felt this way for a year now.
Despite being in different classes, I still always get to see you taking care of the flower beds.
I've finally mustered up the courage to tell you.
Once school's done today, are you free?
Tell me your answer at the flower beds.
I like you, Michiru. I've felt this way for a year now.
Despite being in different classes, I still always get to see you taking care of the flower beds.
I've finally mustered up the courage to tell you.
Once school's done today, are you free?
Tell me your answer at the flower beds.
"I like you, Michiru."
Hiiragi Nana
"I've felt this way for a year now."
"Despite being in different classes, I still always
get to see you taking care of the flower beds."
I like you, Michiru. I've felt this way for a year now.
Despite being in different classes, I still always get to see you taking care of the flower beds.
I've finally mustered up the courage to tell you.
Once school's done today, are you free?
Tell me your answer at the flower beds.
"I've finally mustered up the courage to tell you."
"Once school's done today, are you free?"
Class duty:
Hiiragi Nana
This is so stupid.
"Tell me your answer at the flower beds."
Sorry, don't mind us!
We're super happy for you, you know.
It's so cute how you got all red!
What's her deal?
Hiiragi Nanna, your leg...
Oh, I tripped over yesterday
and scratched it, that's all.
It looks painful.
Class duty:
Hiiragi Nana
Wh-What are you doing?!
The scratch is gone?
Geez, Michiru, you little angel!
Now, calm down a little there!
Doesn't it shorten your lifespan to do that?
You're Inukai Michiru,
right?
Correct!
Thank you!
You have a wonderful Talent!
Inukai Michiru.
Estimated kill count: over 150,000.
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
She enthusiastically heals people's wounds,
so I thought she might be a good person,
but it turns out a monster's always a monster.
Considering her Talent,
she'll definitely get in the way of my mission.
Were you looking for me?
Nah, not really.
I was about to go feed the cat.
He's following me around.
Good afternoon!
Oh, Nanna.
Are you waiting for the sender of the love letter?
Uh...
But you know,
they won't be coming.
Huh?
I know you're hiding there!
That's super lame!
She's trouble! She can read minds!
Screw you, Hiiragi!
You'll regret this!
U-Um...
Michiru, those two were just messing with you.
How did you know?
I like you, Michiru. I've felt this way for a year now.
Despite being in different classes, I still always get to see you taking care of the flower beds.
I've finally mustered up the courage to tell you.
Once school's done today, are you free?
Tell me your answer at the flower beds.
I like you, Michiru. I've felt this way for a year now.
Despite being in different classes, I still always get to see you taking care of the flower beds.
I've finally mustered up the courage to tell you.
Once school's done today, are you free?
Tell me your answer at the flower beds.
I've been hearing nasty thoughts all day.
I like you, Michiru. I've felt this way for a year now.
Despite being in different classes, I still always get to see you taking care of the flower beds.
I've finally mustered up the courage to tell you.
Once school's done today, are you free?
Tell me your answer at the flower beds.
I like you, Michiru. I've felt this way for a year now.
Despite being in different classes, I still always get to see you taking care of the flower beds.
I've finally mustered up the courage to tell you.
Once school's done today, are you free?
Tell me your answer at the flower beds.
I ike you, Michiru. I've felt this way for a year now.
Despite being in different classes, I still always get to see you taking care of the flower beds.
I've finally mustered up the courage to tell you.
Once school's done today, are you free?
Tell me your answer at the flower beds.
I thought they were my friends...
I'm sorry.
That was too blunt of me...
But thank you, Nanna...
Aw, it's nothing compared to you healing my leg.
Would you like to go have lunch together now?
A-Absolutely!
Dining Hall
She sure is talkative, which helped me learn a lot.
She's basically a dog.
Her Talent is simple too—
whatever she licks will heal.
She can restore not only skin and muscle tissue,
but even internal blood loss.
It can instantly treat any injury.
She can heal her own wounds as well,
but only if she can reach them with her tongue.
When I kill her, it has to be from behind.
Hey.
What are you doing here?!
I was worried about you, my dear.
I'm on the lookout for the enemy.
That's very kind, thank you.
It's really late, though...
I can't die, even if I don't sleep.
Uh, sure, but this is the girls' dorm...
You're all like dear little children to me.
I'm not going to do anything, don't worry.
Or would you rather sleep together?
I'll sing a lullaby just for you.
No thank you.
I've got my own music to fall asleep to.
Where was she trying to go this late at night?
Is she playing it this loud...
because she doesn't want me to hear her
as she escapes through the window?
What is she plotting?
Is something wrong, Nanna—
Michiru, run!
It's the enemy!
Regardless of whether
the enemies of humanity exist or not,
it's undeniable that people
keep dying around Hiiragi.
She kept following Inukai Michiru all day today.
She was all friendly with her,
just like with Nakajima.
She's using the same method...
But why?
To get her target to let their guard down?
I don't know her motive.
I don't know what it could be...
But if I assume that the enemies
of humanity don't exist...
Hiiragi is the most suspicious of all.
Nanna... Nanna...
Thank you, Michiru...
Don't move just yet!
What is this? What happened?
I'm sorry, Kyouya...
I was already in bed when I heard
the thoughts of an enemy from outside...
When I went out, I noticed it was targeting Michiru...
I just couldn't stand around doing nothing.
Nanna protected me and got attacked from behind...
Where's the enemy?
I don't know.
It might be the invisible type
we've read about in the textbook...
There's no way I was just overthinking things.
Hiiragi?!
Are you okay?!
Perfect. Keep thinking.
Why would I create such a commotion?
How will spilling my own blood
in front of the students
change the school from now on?
You've been suspecting me.
So as a killer, I'll just hide in the role of a victim.
It'd be difficult to keep hiding Nakajima's death
or the attack on Kyouya for much longer.
So I might as well lend some credence to
the rumor that the enemies are on the island.
And so,
I stabbed myself in the back.
Knowing that I could count on
the dog to save me afterwards.
Wait...
Is this for real?
I will be the leader from now on,
with the school in the palm of my hand.
I'm sorry, but something still bothers me.
Can we go over this again?
He's been like this since yesterday.
Yesterday night, while in your room,
you heard the thoughts of an enemy,
and jumped out of the dorm window.
Correct.
Then I heard a thought about
something attacking Michiru...
I was in the hallway.
Why didn't you tell me first?
Being fully aware I wouldn't die
even if attacked by the enemy.
Didn't it occur to you to rely on me?
I'm sorry.
I totally panicked.
I was just trying to hurry.
You wouldn't die?
Yeah, but just me.
I can't use it to help others
like you do, unfortunately.
Okay, so.
Hiiragi, you ran into Inukai's room,
and were stabbed by the enemy from behind?
Yes.
I thought the enemy would enter
through Michiru's window...
So the enemy never showed itself, right?
I really wonder, what was it that
the enemy was trying to achieve?
Huh?
Didn't it come to eat me like the textbooks say?
Why did it choose you as its target?
If it was invisible and could
sneak up on people in silence,
why did it escape just because we came running?
We all could've died there
if we'd handled the situation wrong.
I just caught a brief snippet,
but could you be thinking that there
were no enemies of humanity there?
I'm just pondering, what if there weren't any?
Inukai and Hiiragi were the only ones in the room.
It's a fact that Hiiragi was stabbed in the back.
Inukai definitely wouldn't do it,
seeing as she healed her afterwards.
Which means either that there
was another person in the room,
or Hiiragi stabbed herself...
It's pointless, Kyouya.
Still,
I can't figure out a reason
for Hiiragi to do such a thing.
Nor why she'd kill Nakajima or attack me.
It still seems more plausible that
there could be actual invisible enemies here.
Your deductions hit a dead end
whenever you try to figure out my motive.
Nana! I heard you got attacked
by the enemies of humanity?!
I heard so too, dammit!
Are you okay?
So the enemies really are on the island...
What's gonna happen now?
What are you getting scared for?!
In times like this, you've got me to follow!
Not so fast.
I was actually thinking we should
decide on a new leader soon.
You wanna be the leader?!
Nakajima must've been killed as well!
It's so frustrating.
My Talent lets me hear
the thoughts of the enemies...
Why didn't I notice sooner?
Nakajima was in danger, but I...
Nana...
Excuse me!
H-How about making Nanna the leader?!
She saved my life!
Sure, why not Nana?
She's cute.
I agree.
And she can hear the enemy's thoughts.
No one else has such a useful Talent!
Nanna is very brave!
She's kind!
I'm sure she'll protect everyone!
Okay, then Nana's the new leader!
No objections here either.
What do you think, Nana?
I'll be the leader.
Thank you for your support.
Let's all work together to face
the enemies of humanity!
It's about to be a long weekend, but...
Could you put together a list of
everyone's Talents and personalities?
There's no need to push them too hard.
I'd like to learn as much as I can, just in case.
Will do, leader!
All according to plan.
From now on, it'll be up to me when and where
the enemies appear and disappear.
Whoever I kill will be seen
as having died an honorable death.
Hiiragi.
I'm sorry for suspecting you.
You're a victim in all this too.
What, you were suspecting me?
He's basically saying he still is.
Actually, is your injury all right?
Yeah!
I only caught a glimpse,
but it must've been something sharp.
What must've been sharp?
Like a harpoon, or a screwdriver...
Or maybe something like an awl.
Oh, sorry.
I mean the tool used to attack you.
Ah, I see!
I thought it was a claw,
or some sort of spear-ish appendage.
We'll need to be ready for those, then.
Counting on you, leader.
So he was here just to show off his best bluffs...
He has a point, though.
An awl is too obvious a weapon.
If I keep using it,
it might seem off that the enemies of humanity,
who supposedly have very
strong bodies, use human tools.
Science Lab
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
If possible, I'd rather use a more magic-like method.
If she used something like a screwdriver or an awl,
she could've hidden it in her clothes.
Assuming Hiiragi stabbed herself,
she did it knowing that Inukai would save her.
The Humanity
Girl
She then acted like a victim,
gaining control over the class.
And she plans to kill us all one by one.
I should stop.
This is all nothing but
baseless speculation at this point.
I don't have proof, nor can I imagine a motive.
Which means that no one would believe
that the new leader is a murderer.
Do those enemies of humanity
really exist after all, like everyone says?
Kyouya keeps claiming he can't die,
but what if he was poisoned, I wonder?
Well, the class is already mine.
Their trust in me won't waver unless
they actually catch me in the act.
Hey, leader!
I need to talk to you.
Um, you were...
Hatadaira Tsunekichi, right?
What is it?
Michiru came asking about my Talent, you see.
And, you know, I kinda, you know...
I guess I kinda know the future.
Huh?
He knows the future?
Can you
explain this?
Apparently I'll be attacked, not by the enemy,
but by what appears to be our new leader?
This is our future?
Yeah.
Isn't that crazy?
Is he saying he can print photos of the future?
Um, is this the school gym storage shed?
The hand of the clock points at ten,
so does that mean I'll try to kill you at 10 PM?
Yeah.
I seriously wanna know what this is about.
B-But...
I can't really explain something
that I don't understand myself.
Come with me, then!
I'm hungry!
Huh?
Open up! Open up!
H-Hold on! It's super late!
The people working here are probably asleep!
Dining Hall
Shut up!
I can see the future, you know!
My Talent's way above anyone else in this class!
C'mon, treat me special!
See, they do get it.
So uncivilized...
I'll have a char siu bowl.
What 'bout you, Nana?
Well, chilled soba noodles, then...
So, about this picture...
You know, I used to be all prim and proper too.
Excuse me?
You know, back at school,
there was this super important test...
And I foresaw myself getting
a zero on that test, you see.
I-I see.
Mathematics
So I did my best! I studied super hard!
You studied really hard so you
wouldn't actually get a zero?
Mathematics
And what do you think happened?
It's super crazy.
Um, you got a really high fever
on the day of the test, or something?
That's so awesome!
You really can read minds, Nana!
I think that's a rather common turn of events...
No matter how hard you try,
the future's set in stone.
Fate's such a massive troll, am I right?
Ridiculous.
Just take a look at this.
I took this photo quite a while ago.
Yeah, no mistaking it!
It has to be today, it's this exact angle!
You're saying that the noodles I ordered
will end up on my head in a moment?
You don't believe me, do you?
I'm sorry, could I get a pork bowl instead?
What?
Well, what can I do...
Nice try, but nope.
I-I'm sorry!
I just cleaned the floors, so they're slippery...
Like I said, Nana, it's pointless.
The future in these pictures
will absolutely never change.
What do you want then, Tsunekichi?
I could ask you the same.
Why would you kill me?
I told you it must be some kind of a mistake!
Even though you killed Nakajima?
They
all
were
gi
ven
a
gift
The
call
of
a
po
wer
with
in
Be
cause
of
that
one
sin
We
brand
them
as
mon
stro
si
ties
As
if
by
a
whim
of
the
gods
Or
may
be
some
mis
chief
of
time
What
they
all
had
thought
was
a
gift
Brought
with
it
u
nique
a
go
ny
This
was
n't
what
I
hoped
would
be
come
But
what
good
would
strug
gl
ing
have
done
When
it
was
clear
that
I
ne
ver
would
be
loved?
So
who
should
I
di
rect
this
bit
ter
rage
at?
So
who
should
I
di
rect
this
bit
ter
rage
at?
Was
my
life
all
a
lie?
Have
you
been
on
my
side?
What
if
you
be
ing
there
helped
sur
face
all
my
doubts?
There
might
still
be
a
chance
May
be
a
chance
that
I
may
be
could
see
that
I've
been
mis
guid
ed
all
a
long
May
be
a
chance
that
I
may
be
could
see
that
I've
been
mis
guid
ed
all
a
long
I
could
leave
the
world
way
that
it
is
I
could
leave
the
world
way
that
it
is
Next Episode: The Talented vs. The Talentless, Part 2
"The Talented vs. The Talentless, Part 2".