Now, then...
Who might you have been trying to call?
Don't panic, Nana. Think.
Tachibana might be a few levels above
the other Talented you've encountered,
but he shouldn't be invincible.
The call ended almost instantly.
call ended
Do you need to start with a passphrase?
If he could really use each and every Talent
that exists in this world,
he wouldn't need to interrogate me like this.
He should be able to travel through time and space,
control people, and close in on the Committee...
Why didn't you turn into me?
I apologize for underestimating you.
But you've been sneaking around me
trying to figure out my Talent since last night.
If you wanted to know what my Talent was,
you should've just turned into me.
You can use the Talent
of the person you turn into, after all.
"Estimated kill count"?
As I'm drifting through an eternity
As
I'm
drift
ing
through
The souls of fragile beings crashing over me
The
souls
of
fra
gile
be
ings
crash
ing
o
ver
me
The heavens fracture
The
hea
vens
frac
ture
But clouds mask the broken sky
But
clouds
mask
the
bro
ken
sky
Using awkward circumstance to gain the upper hand
Us
ing
awk
ward
cir
cum
stance
to
gain
the
up
per
hand
I try to test the will of God
I
try
to
test
the
will
of
God
It almost felt as if I could deceive him
It
al
most
felt
as
if
I
could
de
ceive
him
When I found you at the end of my eternal search
When
I
found
search
I also found my lost tears
I
al
so
found
my
lost
tears
Kill all the enemies
of humanity.
Though I lie
Though
I
lie
To others
To
o
thers
Time after time
Time
af
ter
time
I don't need deceit to keep you
I
don't
need
de
ceit
to
keep
you
Smiling and pure
Smi
l
ing
and
pure
My one "talent" is my mercilessness
My
one
"
ta
lent
less
ness
I weave a tangled web of destiny and death
I
weave
a
tan
gled
death
My sins dispassionate and dull
My
sins
dis
pas
sion
ate
and
dull
Hidden deep down inside my soul
Hid
den
deep
down
in
side
my
soul
Sudden showers voice their assent
Sud
den
sho
wers
voice
their
as
sent
And mute the screams of those who meet their end
And
mute
the
screams
of
those
who
meet
their
end
The heavens warp but
The
hea
vens
warp
but
The clouds mask the broken sky
The
clouds
mask
the
bro
ken
sky
Tachibana is clearly an intruder.
I guess I could just run to the dorms
and get help from the class...
Episode 10: Invisible Blade
My bad.
I need time to get a feel for the Talents I copy.
There was a hopelessly delusional
student here five years ago.
She claimed she was a knight
chosen by the archangels in Heaven,
and was going to kill us,
the pawns of the armies of Hell.
She showed us the results of her delusions,
which mentioned this "estimated kill count".
I thought you might be knee-deep
in same cringey bullshit,
but there's no escaping the reality
that someone gave you this device.
Don't you think you should be
seeking help from that person right now?
Can't you transform into Sasaki Yuuka?
I'm sure you're aware she could apparently
browse through the memories of corpses.
If you want to know more about me,
why don't you turn me into a zombie already?
You're such a charming girl.
Even in this situation, you're trying
to look for a weakness to exploit.
What's your family situation?
What are you getting at?
I can't force you to talk by inflicting fear or pain.
Shouldn't we take our time
and build some trust between us, then?
Are you implying you'd let me go if I talked?
For tonight, at least.
Nana... You know, I'm quite fond of you.
Five years ago, I was killing people left and right
without getting to know them first.
You should be well aware that for a killer, being able
to treat people as things is of utmost importance.
I don't want you to repeat
the same mistakes I made.
I had a father, a mother,
and apparently a much-older brother.
Why "apparently"?
I don't remember him.
He moved out before I was
old enough to retain any memories.
And your parents?
My father worked for the authorities
dealing with general affairs related to the Talented.
My mother was a kindergarten teacher.
They were both killed.
By?
By a cruel and spiteful enemy of humanity.
Impressive how you talk about such trauma
without so much as batting an eyelid.
There's nothing we can do about what's in the past.
We're human, after all.
We shouldn't be allowed
to bring people back to life or turn back time.
By an "enemy of humanity",
you don't mean one of the Talented, do you?
Before you doze off, let me offer a bit of advice
as a token of my trust.
Children gathered on this island have
massive egos due to their Talents to begin with.
They don't have parents or teachers
who could set them up for failures and setbacks,
so it's only understandable
that they end up that way.
But once you throw a corpse into the mix...
The crazy really comes out of the woodwork.
Stay on your guard.
You might not be the only murderer on this island.
Michiru?
Nanna!
I've been so worried!
Um... Wh-Why am I here?
Well, I heard a loud sound in the middle of the night,
and I found you unconscious in front of my room...
Tachibana carried me all the way here?
Were you attacked by the enemy?
Y-Yeah.
I got really sleepy yesterday
on my way to school, too...
When I woke up, it was already dark outside...
I found that really strange, and then...
Huh? But you did show up at school, no?
What?!
Apparently an impostor posed as me all day!
I was chasing that impostor around
and had the tables turned on me...
Huh? I had no idea...
Thank you, Michiru.
For looking after me all this time.
I'm so glad you're okay!
I'm letting Michiru live
precisely for situations like these.
You're such a strong person, Nanna.
Nakajima went missing, Yuuka passed away...
Yet you're still working so hard all on your own.
It's what a leader has to do.
How are you able to put so much effort in?
Are you not scared of the enemies of humanity?
I could never be scared of them.
Damn it. I let my feelings show.
I'm sorry.
My parents were killed by one, actually.
And that's why...
Rather than feeling scared,
I just really want to get back at them.
At this point I don't feel any
resentment or sadness anymore...
I don't, but...
This kind of story is better kept simple.
It's also convenient to make her think that
if any of my future actions seem rushed,
it's because of these feelings.
Huh?!
I-I'm so sorry, I didn't...
I made you talk about something so horrible...
I-It's okay!
You didn't do anything to apologize for!
I'll go wash my face!
Nanna!
I... had no idea...
Help...
Please help me...
Please!
Save my mom and dad!
I'm sorry.
But I want you to know you can tell me anything.
You've been doing your best
ever since you transferred here.
And last night you worked so hard while injured...
So I just...
I thought it might be tough struggling all alone...
I know I can't really do much for you, but...
Long story short,
someone broke into our house late at night.
When I woke up, both my parents were dead.
Really?
And that person was an enemy of humanity?
Well, yeah... I think they were posing as a human.
So that's why you're working so hard, Nanna.
Yeah, but that's also what ends up
making Kyouya suspect me...
That's horrible...
I had no idea.
I see now why you're pushing
yourself so hard, Nanna...
You're such a genuinely nice person, Michiru.
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
Inukai Michiru
Estimated kill count
Over 150,000
I keep feeling like letting my guard down around her,
but she must have a hidden side,
like Yuuka did...
I think I've done something worse
than that enemy, though.
Huh?
It's my fault that my parents were killed.
What do you...
I'm sorry. My back still hurts a little bit, so...
I-I'll cure it!
Tsunekichi supposedly died of a disease,
but this is a genuine murder.
Aren't the adults getting scared by now?
Classes are suspended until
the next scheduled resupply shipment.
For now, we'll wait to hear
from the higher-ups and—
Tell me the next time they call you.
I'll handle it.
Is that clear?
What makes you think
you can boss me around like that?
I'm your teacher, you know!
Could you tell us, Nana,
if you forgot to lock the window that night as well?
Dad always told me to check
that it was locked before going to sleep.
He got angry at me a lot for not doing that...
I think it's safe to assume that the culprit
broke into the house through her window, then.
You moron! Don't say that
in front of the victims' child!
I not only talked too much in front of Michiru,
but also dredged up something I shouldn't have.
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing, don't worry.
Are you not feeling well?
I'm fine, really.
I was just thinking that if I'd honed my Talent better,
maybe I could've saved Yuuka and Takanashi.
Didn't using her Talent shorten her lifespan?
I don't know if her current state is related to that,
but if she says she's fine, I'll leave her be.
Well, then.
How do I proceed from here?
It seems none of the remaining Talented
are the type that would try to threaten me.
No,
there's this strange one here.
I'm glad to see you all healed up.
If you were going to save me anyway,
why didn't you heal my wounds yourself?
Are you implying I should've licked you all over?
That's a tempting offer,
but Michiru's Talent is somewhat of a miracle.
It takes a toll on the body
of a mere impersonator like me.
Can I take that to mean you don't just copy
your target's Talent, but also the price they pay for it?
Are you happy now that
you've learned one of my weaknesses?
I'd appreciate if you could also
give back my device, if you'd be so kind.
But of course.
As long as you let me take a little peek
into your heart again.
Nanna!
Could I talk to you, Nanna?
Sorry to bother you so late.
I was just worried about your injuries...
I'm perfectly fine now, thank you.
Is it okay if I come in?
I don't feel safe with all the incidents lately...
I don't really mind, but...
Oh, I wondered if you already
had a visitor, but it's a kitty!
Actually, isn't this the first time
I've been in your room?
I think it is, yeah.
What does she want now?
Did she notice something off about me?
Yeah, no way.
Your room is so clean.
How do I... It has this sort of
"smart person" feeling to it.
Does it?
H-Have you always been this way?
I can hear what you're thinking.
You want to hear more about
my childhood, don't you?
I'm sorry. What you told me this morning
has been on my mind all day...
You mentioned it was all your fault,
but I don't see how it could be...
I'm sorry I said something so enigmatic.
You're always such a cheerful person,
but you seemed different mentioning it.
But you might hate me if I explain, Michiru.
I would never hate you!
I want to help you in any way I can!
Look, the kitty wants to hear the story too.
Yeah, I'd sure bet he does.
I was just an ordinary girl like any other.
Did you have dolls, or play house and such?
What I liked the most back in
elementary school was games.
Like, video games?
No.
Shogi, go, chess...
Whenever my birthday would come around,
I'd get another set from my parents.
That's so mature...
Were those games popular
among your friends at that time?
No, I always played alone.
When I tried playing against the boys in my class,
they got mad and said they'd never play with me again.
I actually wanted to try poker and mahjong too,
but I couldn't play those alone, so I gave up on them.
I also came up with my own
strategy game based around marbles.
It was intended for solo play,
and I put so much effort into it...
An ordinary girl like any other... you said?
I had a bad habit of not cleaning up my games.
My room was always a mess.
Shogi and chess pieces, as well as marbles,
were scattered all around the floor,
so it was easy to step on things.
You were the type to get absorbed
in what you were doing, then.
I always got really engrossed in comics, too.
Just like I did that night.
What night?
The night my parents were killed.
I stayed up really late,
trying to get the most out of my games.
Then I waited until my parents were asleep,
and left the house through my window.
Your window? Where would
you go that late? What for?
The convenience store.
It always got one of my
favorite magazines really early.
I'd often sneak out of the house
and run there at night with a few coins.
I knew your sleep schedule wasn't great, but...
It's dangerous for a small girl to be outside that late.
After getting back to my room,
I'd get absorbed in my comic,
and fall asleep without even
changing into my pajamas.
I really had no discipline.
That's also why I was always
forgetting to lock the window.
You needed to do that?
I heard from the police later.
The culprit got in through my window.
I was so stupid.
They must've noticed that I was always
running to the convenience store at night.
Based on that, they probably figured out
that the house's security wasn't great.
My parents would always yell at me, too.
To clean up my room, to make sure
the window was locked before going to sleep.
But I cared less about their scolding
than I did about my games,
or what would happen next in my comics.
I couldn't help myself.
Then morning came,
and the living room seemed strangely quiet.
Normally dad would be watching news on the TV...
And I'd be able to smell
the breakfast my mom had made...
But instead I smelled blood,
and a severed head was waiting there for me...
S-So...
It was all... all my fault...
I let all that...
Michi—
I'm coming in.
Kyouya! I've told you multiple times
that this is the girls' dorm!
Were you with Inukai last night?
Huh? Ah, yeah...
Right, Michiru?
I spent the night here.
Well either way, come with me.
What happened?
There's no way that...
Look, he's back.
You didn't let anyone enter the room, right?
R-Right.
We were waiting for you like you said.
As you can see, we have another corpse.
What now, leader?
This wasn't me.
Does that mean there's another murderer?
They
all
were
gi
ven
a
gift
The
call
of
a
po
wer
with
in
Be
cause
of
that
one
sin
We
brand
them
as
mon
stro
si
ties
As
if
by
a
whim
of
the
gods
Or
may
be
some
mis
chief
of
time
What
they
all
had
thought
was
a
gift
Brought
with
it
u
nique
a
go
ny
This
was
n't
what
I
hoped
would
be
come
But
what
good
would
strug
gl
ing
have
done
When
it
was
clear
that
I
ne
ver
would
be
loved?
So
who
should
I
di
rect
this
bit
ter
rage
at?
So
who
should
I
di
rect
this
bit
ter
rage
at?
Was
my
life
all
a
lie?
Have
you
been
on
my
side?
What
if
you
be
ing
there
helped
sur
face
all
my
doubts?
There
might
still
be
a
chance
May
be
a
chance
that
I
may
be
could
see
that
I've
been
mis
guid
ed
all
a
long
May
be
a
chance
that
I
may
be
could
see
that
I've
been
mis
guid
ed
all
a
long
I
could
leave
the
world
way
that
it
is
I
could
leave
the
world
way
that
it
is
Next Episode: Invisible Blade, Part 2
"Invisible Blade, Part 2".