The temple had learned that Myne
suffered from the Devouring.
Myne. We'd like to talk with your parents.
To protect her from opportunistic nobles,
Benno employed contract magic,
and Myne prepared herself
to become part of the temple.
I have a wish, just one simple wish
Ascendance of a Bookworm
LOREM IPSUM DOLOR SIT AMET CONSECTETUR ADIPISCING ELIT FUSCE EFFICITUR LECTUS ID NISI RHONCUS PHARETRA NULLA QUAM VELIT TEMPUS QUIS ACCUMSAN EFFICITUR TEMPUS EU ANTE DONEC ULTRICES MOLESTIE MAXIMUS DONEC NON LOREM VITAE ANTE PRETIUM VESTIBULUM IN IN MAGNA MAURIS PHARETRA PLACERAT URNA AC FEUGIAT TORTOR AUCTOR EGET MAECENAS SIT AMET EROS FELIS ETIAM SAPIEN PURUS MALESUADA FERMENTUM VIVERRA VEL PORTA SIT AMET LECTUS CLASS APTENT TACITI SOCIOSQU AD LITORA TORQUENT PER CONUBIA NOSTRA PER INCEPTOS HIMENAEOS MAURIS VEHICULA DAPIBUS INTERDUM FUSCE SIT AMET NISI VENENATIS PLACERAT LIGULA ID CONDIMENTUM ODIO DUIS URNA JUSTO IMPERDIET UT COMMODO ID ULTRICES IN ELIT SED EGESTAS FACILISIS EX IN HENDRERIT IPSUM EGESTAS IMPERDIET
I hold it dearly in my heart and hope
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
It'll come true someday soon
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to
I don't have anything, nothing at all
But if I could have this one wish granted
It would fill the void inside my heart
I can feel the warm breeze blowing
And see shooting stars filling the sky
They make me feel as if
I can do anything, y'know?
In this wonderful world
Nothing is set in stone
Our as-yet untold future
Shines brighter than the sun
I want to take hold of my future
With my own two hands
And write pages filled with hope
Into the book of my life
Chapter 14
Confrontation
I'm home.
Myne!
So, what happened at the temple?
Um, I told the high bishop that I'd decided
against becoming an apprentice priestess.
But when they found out
that I had the Devouring,
they told me that they
wanted to talk with my parents...
So now we have this summons.
It's for the day after tomorrow, at third bell.
Myne!
What have you done?
I was told to touch a chalice at the temple,
and when I did, it lit up, so they gave me this.
After that, I went to Mr. Benno's store, and he taught
me all about the Devouring and about nobility.
He said that the heat of the
Devouring was actually mana.
Mana?
Apparently, as soon as they saw the chalice
light up, they knew that I had mana,
and because of that, I can't escape
either the temple or the nobles now.
What?
No way...
There are magic tools at the temple, though,
so I'd be able to continue living if I went there.
Really?
But if you join the temple,
we won't be able to see you anymore...
As things stand, that's probably true.
I don't want to give you over to them.
If you had to work at the temple, all alone...
Say, Dad.
Have you heard about what's
been happening in the capital?
There's been some political drama there,
and the positions of nobles have changed drastically.
Did you know anything about that?
That's got nothing to do with this though, right?
Actually, it does.
Because the number of nobles has dwindled,
there's a deficit of mana at the temple right now.
That's the reason they want me there so bad.
I'd heard some of this while working at the gate.
There's definitely no mistaking
that nobles have been leaving the town.
So what Benno was saying is true.
We might be able to work this out, then.
What do you mean?
Mr. Benno said I'm in a lucky position.
If I do a good job negotiating with them,
I might be able to be treated similarly to nobility.
How are you gonna do that?
First, think about what your
best-case scenario would be.
Then work out what you
need to know to accomplish this,
what you can offer, and what the other party wants.
What I want is...
To be able to enter their library and read its books.
You're still the same as ever, huh.
I-I mean, th-that in the best case scenario,
that would be ideal.
I-It'd be a nice bonus, right?
What I can offer is money and mana.
Yes.
If you can sell yourself well enough,
you'll be able to buy your way into better terms.
Depending on how negotiations go,
you might be able to join the temple
as an apprentice blue priestess.
And to that end, we'll register the Myne Workshop
and gain an outlet for your products.
That reminds me, in most cases,
you're not allowed to be part of
a guild when you enter the temple.
I wonder if I can join it despite being
the forewoman of the workshop.
The high bishop said he would try to
talk about it with the guildmaster, but...
Don't leave your own future in the hands of others.
You're already registered,
so take the initiative yourself and make sure
you can keep your workshop, even if you have
to throw some money around to make it happen!
From now on,
consider what you, as someone that's already in contact
with the Merchant's Guild, can bring to the temple.
Understood...
You could try saying something about wanting
to use your workshop to give the orphans work.
That you want to improve their
living conditions, stuff like that.
Come up with some basic pleasantries
that will get you what you need!
Also, emphasize how weak
you are and try to negotiate ways
to improve your working conditions
as much as possible.
Fight for your survival!
Forget about how it makes you look!
I understand!
I'll do my best!
That's what he said.
So there's room for negotiation then.
I think so.
That's why Mr. Benno told me
to fight for my survival.
"Fight to survive," huh?
Depending on how you think about it,
it might not be a bad thing.
I think that's what he's getting at.
Yeah.
What I can offer is money and mana.
I'll be emphasizing how weak my body is,
and will try to get them to treat me similarly to nobility.
I need them to let me keep my workshop running.
I also need them to let me commute from home.
If I'm able to make them concede on all three
of these points, we can consider it a win.
Let's make it happen.
I became a soldier to protect my family, after all!
What's wrong, Tuuli?
Having trouble sleeping?
What is it?
Is it really possible to negotiate with nobles?
Don't people get killed just
for speaking up against them?
If something happens to all of you, I...
Tuuli!
Mom!
Make sure to come home with Dad, no matter what!
And so, the day we were
to negotiate at the temple came.
Hey, Dad, protect me, okay?
With my life.
You could say it was the fancy of the gods.
Myne and her parents have arrived.
Good morning,
High Bishop.
Ah, Myne, it's nice to see you.
Myne?
Who are they?
They are my parents.
What? They are your parents?
What are their occupations?
My father is a soldier and my mother
works in a dyeing workshop.
A soldier?
Sheesh, who would have thought
they were straight from the slums.
What a complete waste of time.
Now, please take a seat.
No need.
Have them stand!
What's with this change in attitude?
Well, let's get this over with as fast as possible.
I believe you're well aware that Myne
wishes to become an apprentice priestess.
I understand that you are against this?
Yes, that is correct.
I'm not letting my precious
daughter live like an orphan.
However, Myne has the Devouring.
Those with the Devouring
cannot survive without magic tools.
We shall show our benevolence
by taking her into the temple.
Myne's body will not withstand living
through the same circumstances as orphans.
I would humbly request that you do not
work her like a regular gray priestess.
Exactly. Even without the Devouring,
Myne is still very weak and frail!
She wouldn't be able
to survive living at the temple!
Please, at least allow her
to commute from her own home.
What insolence!
Are you rejecting our act of charity?!
Hand your daughter over quietly!
What?
So this is what nobles are really like?
I refuse.
I will under no circumstances allow our precious
daughter to be taken into an orphanage!
Please! I beg of you! Grant us forgiveness!
How dare you?!
Have these impudent parents taken away!
Take Myne into the back and restrain her!
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Have these impudent parents taken away!
Take Myne into the back and restrain her!
Get behind me.
You mean to resist?
If you dare raise a hand against the temple,
I'll have you executed in the name of the gods.
When I resolved to protect Myne,
I readied myself to put my life on the line.
How dare you?!
Capture Myne already!
Seize this man first!
You worm!
You might be able to take on one or two,
but how long will you last
against much greater numbers?
I'll have you executed for daring
to defy the temple as mere commoners.
You'll be shot to death like the dogs that you are.
Get them!
I've had enough of this.
Myne...
Do not lay a finger...
on my Mom and Dad.
You summoned us here to talk things through,
and look at what you did instead.
S-Someone!
Myne, your mana is overflowing!
Control your emotions!
How exactly should I control them?
The same way... you always do...
How do you suggest I hold back my anger against
someone who wants to execute my family?
D-Don't come any c-closer!
Wait!
If you keep going, the high bishop's
heart won't be able to take it!
He planned to kill us,
so he should be prepared to die himself, right?
Myne!
You're in the way.
Calm down.
Let's talk about this.
You want to talk, you say?
Using force?
Or maybe...
using mana?
You must not kill him.
If you kill the high bishop here,
your family will forever be known as noble-killers.
That cannot be what you want, right?
Because of me, even my family would...
It seems you've returned to your senses.
Let us talk.
The way you wanted to.
You're saying you'll accept all of our conditions?
Yes.
But to do that, I must ask you
to contain your overflowing mana.
Can you do that?
Just like always...
I have to push it inside of the box.
Myne!
Are you okay?
I'm fine. This happens all the time.
I'm still fully conscious.
This happens all the time?
It almost never gets that out of control,
but it's happened a bunch before.
Really?
Um... Are you okay, High Priest?
This is a punishment that I deserved.
I stayed quiet as I watched
the high bishop anger you.
I didn't think your commoner parents
would dare to oppose a noble.
Myne's our precious little girl.
I've said this many times.
Myne, seeing your parents value you and love you
to this degree makes me feel deep jealousy.
Those working in the temple are
made up of both orphans and nobles
who were deemed unnecessary by their parents.
After that, we were brought to the
high priest's chambers to talk things through.
What exactly was going on with Myne earlier?
It's known as "Crushing."
"Crushing"?
Her eyes started glowing like a rainbow
and there was some sort of haze radiating from her.
What?
The heck?
I had no idea I looked like some sort
of mystical being when I lost control!
This will happen whenever she is unable
to suppress very powerful emotions.
Her vast dormant mana is activated,
which courses through her body,
and is then directed at those she considers enemies.
This happens most frequently with children
that have trouble controlling their emotions.
Has this not happened before?
Her eyes have changed color a few times.
What?
But when you tell her she's being selfish,
it fades away pretty quickly.
Now that you mention it...
Really?!
They did a pretty good job raising such a weird kid.
I had heard that those with the Devouring
have high amounts of mana.
I never expected you'd be powerful enough to leave
the high bishop at the brink of death, though.
I'm not sure how best to say this, but...
How are you still alive?
The more mana one has,
the more willpower it requires to keep under control.
It's unusual to see someone with
as much mana as you alive at this age.
I should have died already.
But a very nice person gave me
a magic tool that had one final use left.
Couldn't you have entered into a contract
with a noble through this person?
I don't think there's any point in continuing
to live if I'm forced to sell myself off.
I wanted to stay together with my family.
I wanted to make books.
If I can't live how I want to,
there's no point in living at all.
I cannot fathom your way of thinking.
Myne, I want you to join the temple.
This isn't an order, it's a request.
I am in charge of day-to-day operations here.
I shall accommodate you as much as I can.
Of course, there will be no
punishment for today's events, either.
The high priest kept his word and
accepted our demands more or less wholesale.
As a result, I was to become
an apprentice blue priestess.
It's over.
Yeah.
Mom, Dad,
thank you for protecting me.
Though you were the one who protected us
in the end, thanks to that Crushing thing.
I ended up getting so angry that the heat inside
me took over, so I don't remember much of it.
I guess the real deal starts from now, huh?
Yeah.
But I'm a little relieved.
With the high priest around,
I think you'll be okay at the temple.
Why do you say that?
He was the one who stopped
you killing the bishop, remember?
Having someone like him to tell you when enough is enough is important, after all.
Ah, no! I'm gonna get into constant trouble!
Myne's fine, I'm sure of it.
Her mom and dad are with her.
Yeah.
Tuuli!
You're back!
Myne!
Welcome back,
I'm home!
Tuuli!
Tell me, oh my angel
Oh my darling, let me dream again
I gently brush my hair
And put a hairpin through it
In the sea of green
A flower ornament blooms
It is a gift from my angel
It touches my forehead
Oh so gently
And it reminds me
Of the warm light that gathered
To bring my angel into this world
This fever is making me delirious
Ah, these times are so dear to me
There must have been something more
Some greater force that led me to you
Our fates tangle and unravel as we become family
I have been always living
Inside a book
But then my heart melted
And now I have experienced
The real world
Next Chapter
Apprentice Priestess
Wahoo!
Part One's
Over!
We've finally made it to the grand finale of part one!
I even managed to stay with my family!
It's a flawless victory!
High Priest, I'll be heading to the temple soon!
I'll finally get to read some books! Yay!
Heck yeah!
You're getting yourself too excited again.
Don't be taken in by those whims of yours.
Your head might be filled with nothing but books,
Nag
but you're joining the temple
as an apprentice priestess.
Nag
Rant
There's a lot of things you need to learn and do.
Nag
Rant
In the first place, despite being a commoner,
you are allowed to wear blue robes and...
Rant
Nag
Oh god! He's going off into a huge rant!
I don't wanna listen to this anymore!
Rant
Nag
Illustration:     Sunaho Tobe