In her efforts to fight off the Devouring,
Myne would need to spend a large sum of money.
To that end, she sold knowledge
from her previous world to Benno.
However, during her negotiations
with Benno, she suddenly collapsed.
Master, I've contacted the guildmaster.
Let's go, Lutz!
Okay.
The number of people wanting
to save Myne grows further.
I have a wish, just one simple wish
Ascendance of a Bookworm
LOREM IPSUM DOLOR SIT AMET CONSECTETUR ADIPISCING ELIT FUSCE EFFICITUR LECTUS ID NISI RHONCUS PHARETRA NULLA QUAM VELIT TEMPUS QUIS ACCUMSAN EFFICITUR TEMPUS EU ANTE DONEC ULTRICES MOLESTIE MAXIMUS DONEC NON LOREM VITAE ANTE PRETIUM VESTIBULUM IN IN MAGNA MAURIS PHARETRA PLACERAT URNA AC FEUGIAT TORTOR AUCTOR EGET MAECENAS SIT AMET EROS FELIS ETIAM SAPIEN PURUS MALESUADA FERMENTUM VIVERRA VEL PORTA SIT AMET LECTUS CLASS APTENT TACITI SOCIOSQU AD LITORA TORQUENT PER CONUBIA NOSTRA PER INCEPTOS HIMENAEOS MAURIS VEHICULA DAPIBUS INTERDUM FUSCE SIT AMET NISI VENENATIS PLACERAT LIGULA ID CONDIMENTUM ODIO DUIS URNA JUSTO IMPERDIET UT COMMODO ID ULTRICES IN ELIT SED EGESTAS FACILISIS EX IN HENDRERIT IPSUM EGESTAS IMPERDIET
I hold it dearly in my heart and hope
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
It'll come true someday soon
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to
I don't have anything, nothing at all
But if I could have this one wish granted
It would fill the void inside my heart
I can feel the warm breeze blowing
And see shooting stars filling the sky
They make me feel as if
I can do anything, y'know?
In this wonderful world
Nothing is set in stone
Our as-yet untold future
Shines brighter than the sun
I want to take hold of my future
With my own two hands
And write pages filled with hope
Into the book of my life
Chapter 11
The Final Decision and the Family Meeting
This feeling again...
This heat...
Stay in there!
I still haven't made any books yet!
Huh?
What's that orb?
It feels like the heat's being absorbed by that orb...
Yeah! Just go away, you stupid heat!
Where am I?
What a nice bed.
Huh?
What is this?
Have you returned to your senses?
Frieda!
Wait, is this your home then?
Yes.
How do you feel?
The fever's gone down and I'm feeling pretty good.
I'm not surprised.
The tool broke, after all.
It gathered as much heat as it could hold.
Frieda, what is this?
It is a magic tool.
A magic tool?
It is this very magic tool that sucked out
the heat from within you, Myne.
This bracelet, huh?
It was already close to breaking,
but absorbing heat from you
pushed it over its capacity.
So I was saved because this thing
absorbed the heat inside me?
That is quite true.
I spoke of it during our last encounter.
It may be impossible to cure the Devouring...
However, it is possible to curb the heat.
So that's what you meant back then.
So I really was saved...
Myne,
listen to me closely.
You see, we can liken what this magic tool did
to scooping a bit of water out of an overflowing cup.
As such, that cup is still very much full,
and as you continue to grow,
the filling of that cup will resume once again.
Wait, then...
In due time, the cup will start overflowing again.
When... will that be?
Please, Frieda, tell me.
I daresay you might have another year.
A year...
How can I get another magic tool?
What about this one, then?
Where and how did you get this bracelet?
Magic tools are the property of nobles.
The ones my family was able to acquire
are those that have nearly broken
or have otherwise served their purpose.
In fact, my grandfather bought all the
tools he could possibly find for my sake,
so you would likely have
a hard time finding any at all.
No way...
Even if you were able to find just one,
you would still require another eventually.
To us, the sufferers of the Devouring,
a life without magic tools is impossible.
There is but a single way to survive.
Huh?
Entering into a contract with a noble.
A contract?
Yes.
In exchange for a continued provision of magic tools,
you pledge to work exclusively for said noble.
Just like I have.
...what?
Once I have come of age,
I will be become a noble's mistress.
A m-mistress?!
As in you'll be a k-kept woman?
Yes. My grandfather is the guildmaster,
so he trades with nobles.
As such, we were fortunate to be surrounded by nobles
who wished to provide aid or form a connection to us.
We made a contract with the best terms possible.
You seem like you've come
to terms with your situation.
A commoner with the Devouring
has no other path open to them.
And if I didn't want to?
That would mean choosing death.
Hence, Myne, I urge you to give it much
thought before you make your choice.
Will you sell yourself to a noble and live?
Or will you breathe your last,
surrounded by those dear to you?
Thanks for providing me such a valuable magic tool.
Providing it? I did hear that you would
be paying for it from Benno, to be frank.
Huh?
Upon the request of Benno, I agreed to sell you
a magic tool if the worst case scenario came to pass.
I see, so that's what happened.
That's fine. I'll pay for it.
Three small golds.
Three small golds?!
You can't pay for it?
Oh, no. I can pay.
The price just startled me.
Myne, you are able to pay that?
Is there some sort of problem with that?
There certainly is. If you couldn't pay,
we would have had you register at our store instead.
What?
I suppose you escaped us this time.
To the past me who sold the Hairshine
manufacturing methods for three small golds:
Good job, you!
Myne!
Mom, Dad, Tuuli!
After all that, my family
came to see how I was doing.
Frieda had apparently sent
someone to contact my family.
I'm so glad you've woken up!
How do you feel?
I thought my heart was gonna stop
when Lutz told us you'd collapsed.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
I'm fine now though!
Good to hear. You can come back home now, right?
We'll take care of her for another night.
Her condition hasn't quite stabilized just yet.
But...
I suffer from the same illness so
I request you trust in my judgment.
Thank you for your patience and hospitality.
Right, I'm gonna go see
Master Benno and let him know.
Okay. Thanks for everything, Lutz!
With that young lady around, we can rest easy.
So Frieda also has the Devouring, huh?
The Devouring?
Yeah, it's the name of Myne's sickness.
She told me at some point before.
I've never heard of this Devouring.
The name doesn't really matter.
As long as she's cured of it, I'm happy.
Another year... That's all?
After everyone had left,
Frieda and I decided to spend
some girly time together.
This is our chef, Leise.
So, what will we be making?
Um...
Do you have sugar?
Yeah, we do.
We also have flour, eggs and butter.
With this, we'll be able to make pound cake!
What's pound cake?
You can make it just by mixing together its
ingredients in equal amounts and baking it.
Whisking the sugar and eggs
is the most important part.
I would fancy giving it a try!
Next, you add in the sieved flour in a cutting motion.
Myne, would you please take over?
Why, making sweets sure is a handful.
Next, you just add in the melted
butter and stir it gently, but...
Mrs. Leise, would you please take over for me?
You two young ladies sure are frail.
Yeah, it seems it's fully baked inside.
What bliss!
Myne!
Huh?
I shook off Frieda's and Leise's intense glares
and moved on to the second stop on our girls' day out.
This is amazing!
Grandfather had the baths
of nobles' manors recreated here.
He always says that if I am to join their society,
it is better I learn to live like they do.
He sure loves to dote on you!
It is an investment into the future.
You say that, but you don't want to be
torn away from your family, do you?
Once I become a mistress, I will be able to
have my own store in the nobles' district.
I will be able to pursue a career in trade,
a dream I had given up on due to the Devouring.
I'm looking forward to it!
You're so strong, Frieda.
After we'd talked, I washed Frieda's hair
using the Hairshine Tuuli had brought.
You are quite good at this, Myne.
I often do this sorta thing with my older sister Tuuli.
My, this is wondrous!
My hair is all silky!
Consider it thanks for the magic tool.
Getting down to some pillow talk
before bed was on the list, too, but...
The hot bath worked wonders and both
Frieda and I fell asleep right away.
And tomorrow is Frieda's baptism.
What utter beauty!
It's as if I'm looking at an angel.
Like the Goddess of Sprouts
who will bring spring to the land!
Huh?
Why?
Lady Myne, are you not feeling well?
No, it was just that looking at Frieda
made me want to see my family again.
Myne, you missed me, right?
Dad sure missed you, that's for sure!
Myne's gonna tell you off again.
I did miss you.
Just a little.
I see. You did miss us.
Since we have everyone assembled,
would you perhaps join us for dinner?
My grandfather proposed so.
I want to eat your food again, Mom.
I really wanted to try their food though...
Sorry, Tuuli.
Effa's food's the best in the world anyway.
There he goes again!
Dad's getting all lovey-dovey with Mom!
It was then that I noticed...
At some point,
this place...
had become my home.
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Master Benno's been super worried
while you were at the guildmaster's.
Mostly about you getting recruited somehow.
Nothing like that happened, but...
But what?
I'll get yelled at, so I'm not saying.
You can tell me at least!
Nope, my lips are sealed now!
Hey! Wait up, Myne!
Wh-What's up with you?
I was just thinking about how much you help me out.
I see.
The second winter since I came
to this world had begun.
Three small golds, you say?!
That damned geezer,
he told me it was just two small golds.
So that's why...
When I said I'd pay,
it really took them by surprise.
Well done. Catching them off-guard is good enough.
Thank you for everything.
By the way, Mr. Benno...
Hm?
I have a question...
You made them sweets using sugar?!
Is using sugar that unusual?
In recent times,
we've begun importing it from overseas.
It's been pretty popular among nobles.
You handed them the recipe too, didn't you?
A great product, which was ready to be
sold to nobles, given away free of charge.
Why are you literally shoving your head
into the mouth of the beast?!
I'm sorry...
It is wonderful to see you in good health.
I'm sorry for making you worry as well, Mr. Mark.
One more year, huh?
I won't believe it.
Myne's always made the impossible possible.
She'll do it this time too.
She's just gotta...
Mr. Benno,
business seems to be going well.
Winter is peak season for this store, that's why.
When everyone's cooped up indoors during winter,
wallets can become surprisingly
loose if it'll help kill time.
If I just need to come up with something people can play,
then there's playing cards,
Karuta,
Shogi,
or maybe even Reversi.
I should be able to make them by next winter.
I daresay you might have another year.
Will you sell yourself to a noble and live?
Or will you breathe your last,
surrounded by those dear to you?
Time passed, and I still wasn't able
to tell my family the truth.
During that time, my outfit
for the baptism was completed.
I'm back.
Welcome home, Dad!
How do I look?
This is my outfit for the baptism.
You look amazing, Myne.
Everyone will think you're
some rich girl, no doubt about it.
We remodeled Tuuli's baptism dress to make it.
I modified it the way Myne asked,
and now she looks like a rich girl!
Because I'm so cute?
Oh no, because I'm so good at sewing.
Myne's baptism is coming up soon, huh?
My small, fever-plagued Myne is finally...
You've really grown, Myne.
Dad...
She really has.
And she had her illness cured, too.
What's wrong, Myne?
Mom, Dad.
Tuuli.
I have something I need to tell you.
About my sickness.
What do you mean?
Wasn't your sickness cured?
They said there's no way to completely cure it.
Frieda was kind enough
to provide me with a magic tool.
Though all it's done is make
the symptoms subside for a little bit.
A magic tool?
Yeah.
To curb the fever of the Devouring,
you have to keep using magic tools to absorb it.
You did say before that treating it
would cost a lot of money...
Is that true?
What about the money, Myne?
I've already paid for it, so it's okay.
No secrets, okay?
How much was it?
Three small golds.
Three small golds?!
How did you get so much money?
I sold the methods and rights to make
both Hairshine and paper to Mr. Benno.
What's done is done.
I want to know what we can do from now on.
You said it would temporarily
take care of your fever.
That means it will inevitably return.
You've kept this to yourself because you
didn't want to be asked that question, right?
How could you tell?
I can tell
because I'm your father.
She told me that it's unlikely
I'll last longer than another year.
Myne... That can't be true...
I don't want you to die!
Tuuli... I don't wanna die either!
I don't wanna die!
Is there any other way besides using magic tools?
There are other ways,
but I'd have to move to the nobles' district.
But then our family...
I probably wouldn't be able to come home.
I don't want that either!
You can't go!
I know. I don't want to be separated from you either.
That'd be worse than dying.
Dad,
Mom,
Tuuli,
is it okay for me to stay with you, as a family?
Myne, you'll always be together with us.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Tell me, oh my angel
Oh my darling, let me dream again
I gently brush my hair
And put a hairpin through it
In the sea of green
A flower ornament blooms
It is a gift from my angel
It touches my forehead
Oh so gently
And it reminds me
Of the warm light that gathered
To bring my angel into this world
This fever is making me delirious
Ah, these times are so dear to me
There must have been something more
Some greater force that led me to you
Our fates tangle and unravel as we become family
I have been always living
Inside a book
But then my heart melted
And now I have experienced
The real world
Next Chapter
Baptism and Paradise
And what will you do about my store?
Ah! I hadn't thought about that!
I'm sorry!
Goodness, just how much do you not think about?
You
are
such
a...
Ow, Ow!
That hurts, Mr. Benno!
Go figure this out by next time, you hear?!
Fine! I get it! I get it!
Please let me go!
Illustration:     Kikuyarou