"I want to read books!"
Reincarnated into a world in which both
books and paper are way out of her reach,
Myne yet holds onto that wish.
If she can't get them,
she just has to make them herself.
With this resolution in her heart,
she embarks on her journey to make paper.
I have a wish, just one simple wish
Ascendance of a Bookworm
LOREM IPSUM DOLOR SIT AMET CONSECTETUR ADIPISCING ELIT FUSCE EFFICITUR LECTUS ID NISI RHONCUS PHARETRA NULLA QUAM VELIT TEMPUS QUIS ACCUMSAN EFFICITUR TEMPUS EU ANTE DONEC ULTRICES MOLESTIE MAXIMUS DONEC NON LOREM VITAE ANTE PRETIUM VESTIBULUM IN IN MAGNA MAURIS PHARETRA PLACERAT URNA AC FEUGIAT TORTOR AUCTOR EGET MAECENAS SIT AMET EROS FELIS ETIAM SAPIEN PURUS MALESUADA FERMENTUM VIVERRA VEL PORTA SIT AMET LECTUS CLASS APTENT TACITI SOCIOSQU AD LITORA TORQUENT PER CONUBIA NOSTRA PER INCEPTOS HIMENAEOS MAURIS VEHICULA DAPIBUS INTERDUM FUSCE SIT AMET NISI VENENATIS PLACERAT LIGULA ID CONDIMENTUM ODIO DUIS URNA JUSTO IMPERDIET UT COMMODO ID ULTRICES IN ELIT SED EGESTAS FACILISIS EX IN HENDRERIT IPSUM EGESTAS IMPERDIET
I hold it dearly in my heart and hope
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
It'll come true someday soon
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to
I don't have anything, nothing at all
But if I could have this one wish granted
It would fill the void inside my heart
I can feel the warm breeze blowing
And see shooting stars filling the sky
They make me feel as if
I can do anything, y'know?
In this wonderful world
Nothing is set in stone
Our as-yet untold future
Shines brighter than the sun
I want to take hold of my future
With my own two hands
And write pages filled with hope
Into the book of my life
Chapter 3
The Winter is Coming
It's been two months now since I became Myne.
Winter has fully enveloped the town.
It's the middle of the day...
But it's so dark.
Yeah, the blizzard's not helping with that.
Since the snowfall forces us to stay inside during winter,
we keep ourselves busy with work instead.
They call it "winter handiwork".
Tuuli weaves baskets.
And Mom sews clothes.
Come on, Myne, you should stop lounging
around and start making baskets as well.
Tuuli, would you teach her how to make them?
Okay.
I've already decided on my winter handiwork.
I'm making faux-papyrus out of these.
I asked Tuuli and the others to get me
grass with thick stems before winter.
Long live Ancient Egyptian culture!
I wonder what the best way
to split the fibers out of them is.
Whoa.
How did you make these, Tuuli?
You peel off the rind,
soak it in water, and then let it dry.
Huh, I see.
Thank you.
Okay then...
Tuuli...
Next, you need to split off the fibers.
Yay, I did it!
What's wrong, Tuuli?
And thus, my preparations were complete.
If I manage to weave them together,
I'll have my faux-papyrus.
Day
Hey Myne, you've worked
on this for three days now...
but what is it supposed to be?
Ugh.
Well?
I've had it!
I just can't do it!
You win this time, Ancient Egyptians!
You're being too loud, Myne.
If you have time to play with your grass,
use it to help make some baskets.
I will...
I'll teach you how to weave them!
It's okay. I already know how to make them.
What?
Back when I was still Urano,
I'd help my mom weave them out of advert flyers.
Whoa.
That's amazing, Myne.
Why are you so good at this?
What sort of older sister am I...?
N-No, I mean... It's not like...
You want to become an
apprentice seamstress, right, Tuuli?
Then you're gonna have to learn
how to weave before your baptism.
Come on, I'll teach you.
Sure!
Good save, Mom.
Tuuli is gonna turn seven in the coming summer.
After kids are baptized at seven,
they start their apprenticeships.
Apprenticeships usually require
some sort of introduction by an adult.
That's why most kids take up jobs
similar to those of their parents.
You'll need to learn to weave too, Myne.
Thanks, but I'll be okay.
We can't be having that.
Being able to make charming and practical
clothes for yourself and your family
is a skill any refined woman must have.
"Refined woman"?
Yes. A refined woman must have
mastered her cooking and sewing skills.
I'm not planning to become
an apprentice seamstress though.
Do you wanna become
an apprentice carpenter, Myne?
Those baskets were pretty impressive.
What do you wanna do then?
Naturally...
I'm gonna make books.
But Ancient Egypt didn't cut it, clearly.
Then, next up is...
Mesopotamian culture!
Well then, once Spring comes by,
I'll start working on clay tablets.
Good mornin'.
Morning, Myne.
Huh? Where are Tuuli and Dad?
They've gone to pick some parues.
Parues?
Tuuli, are you okay?
Yeah, I can go for a bit longer.
We're back!
So these are parues?
Myne, get a bowl ready.
Got it.
So sweet!
You can try drinking a little.
Sure!
It's syrupy and kind of like coconut milk.
What a heavenly taste.
Man, that was so good!
Tuuli, your hands are red.
What's wrong?
They always get like this when you gather parues.
Huh?
You have to warm the branches
with your bare hands to soften them.
With your bare hands, despite the cold?
You'd probably catch a cold in no time, Myne.
Why couldn't you just go around noon?
Wouldn't they get soft faster around then?
That'd never work. You can only gather
parues from morning until noon.
Once the sun starts rising,
they start stretching up toward the sun,
then the parues shoot off into the sky!
They disappear?
Sounds like a pretty weird tree.
Once Dad got some oil and dregs from the parues,
he headed off for his night shift.
It looks kinda like soy pulp.
Myne, that's bird food!
This...
is edible.
What?
Good evening.
Can you trade us some of
your parue dregs for these eggs?
We're a little short on bird food.
Sure, just a second.
Food tends to run a little short
in a house full of growing boys.
If you're hungry you could just eat this.
I'm not gonna eat bird fo—
It's... good.
I could make it even tastier, actually.
Once it starts simmering, you flip it.
That doesn't look safe.
Let me do it.
And over it goes!
Ta-dah!
One serving of "plain parue pancakes", ready to eat!
Delicious.
Oh man! They're so good!
These are great, Myne.
Where did you learn how to make these?
You put so much work into
getting the parues for us, Tuuli.
We can use all of the parue like this,
rather than wasting parts of it.
Yeah! Thank you, Myne!
You're amazing.
Not only are they easy to make,
but they're pretty filling, too.
Let me help you next time.
Huh?
You're kinda frail, so you tire out easily, right?
So I'm gonna help you.
Consider it payment for the parue pancakes.
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Myne made these, huh?
She called them "parue pancakes".
Well, then. Let's see.
Holy—
You wouldn't think these were
made from the dregs, right?
I've gotta wonder where she learns to make
things like this and the shampoo, though...
Speaking of which, she made those perfect
baskets without anyone teaching her, too.
Yeah, Myne has been really weird recently.
She can be as weird as she likes, for all I care.
Huh?
Her constant fevers had her on the brink of death.
Seeing her alive and well
is enough to make me happy.
I agree.
Yeah.
I ran out of slate pens!
Oh, so nothing serious.
This is serious.
Dad, can you take me to the gate?
Why the gate?
I have to get them from Mr. Otto.
Oh, and he has to teach me
more of the alphabet as well.
You really do like Otto, don't you?
Yeah, I love him!
Not until spring.
Huh?
You can't leave the house until spring!
You'll end up coming down with another fever!
I won't let you take a step outside until spring!
You got that?!
Dad?
Oh what a handful he is...
Christ, you're such an overbearing parent!
The next day was perfect
parue-picking weather too.
This time Mom and Tuuli went out.
I had to stay at the gate with Dad.
Everything's covered in snow, huh?
Myne.
What's wrong, Dad?
Otto's already married, you know.
And... what about it?
Otto's a man with eyes only for his wife.
So what you're saying is that he's a loving,
devoted man that truly cares about his wife?
No.
This is so annoying!
Oh, Myne!
It's been a while.
It has. Nice to see you again, Mr. Otto.
Once she's picked the parues,
Effa will come and pick her up.
She'll be in your care until then, Otto.
Y-Yeah, but I hav—
Did you get that?
Make sure she doesn't catch
a cold like last time, you hear?
Huh?
I've still got a financial report and
budget calculations to do on top of this.
I was complimenting you a lot
and Dad got jealous over it.
Goodness.
But it's nice to see you again, Myne.
From there, Mr. Otto gave me more slate pens
and taught me more of the alphabet.
I'm getting the hang of these now.
Mr. Otto.
I think there's a mistake here.
Oh, and this one's wrong, too.
You're able to do calculations, Myne?
Despite not knowing how to read?
I don't know all of the alphabet,
but Mom taught me the numbers at the market.
Mom, what's that? What does that board say?
Oh, those are prices.
They let you know how much
you need to pay for something.
Myne, I'll swallow my pride and ask—
Would you help me?
Huh?
Okay.
I'll help you out if you continue teaching me
the alphabet and giving me more slate pens.
What?
I'm not the sort of woman who'll work for free.
You sure are something, Myne.
Why the slate pens though?
They get used up in no time.
I see.
Then I guess we've got a deal.
Can I ask you to take care
of these calculations, Myne?
Oh, here's your calculator.
I don't know how to use one of these,
but I'll be fine without it.
Huh? But how will you do the calculations?
I'll be fine as long as I have my stone slate.
Color me impressed.
You managed to get all these
done without a calculator.
This is bad.
Did I overdo it?
I'm glad I could be of help.
I'm the one who should be thanking you.
Myne!
We're going home now.
Ah, Tuuli, Mom!
And so, the snowy days continued.
Okay, it's all done.
This is your dress for the baptism.
Cute, isn't it?
Yup!
Thank you, Mom!
Ah, so she used her extra time during winter
to sew Tuuli's dress for the coming summer.
Tuuli, what about your hair?
I thought I'd just pluck a flower
somewhere and put it in my hair.
Oh no, that won't do!
What?
I'll make you something even cuter!
If hair ornaments don't exist, I'll just make them!
I'll show you the lacework skills
I acquired back in the Urano-era.
Wait.
There's probably no crochet needles
thin enough for tatting here...
In that case!
Dad.
What?
Yikes, he's still in a bad mood...
Um, Dad, I have a favor.
A favor?
Yeah.
Could you make a needle that's
thin enough to use with thread?
Please?
You can count on me.
You're awesome, Dad!
Something like this?
Could you make it even thinner?
Sure can! Leave it to me!
Dad's finally cheered up.
Yeah, what a relief.
How about this?
Dad, you're amazing!
I've won, Otto.
Could I have some of your thread, Mom?
Sure, but what do you plan on using it for?
And done!
Isn't that a little too small?
I'm gonna make a bunch of these
and then bundle them together.
Can you give me a moment?
I guess those are the sewing
skills of a refined woman, huh.
Dad made a pin to hold it all together, too.
With that, the hair ornament was complete.
It's done, Tuuli.
It looks great on you!
You're so cute, Tuuli!
Really?
Wow, it's great!
Consider it a thank you for helping
me out with those plant fibers before.
Thank you, Myne.
I'm so happy!
Dad's happy, too!
Myne's really nice to her older sister!
And Tuuli's grown up to be a great older sister!
You two are my pride and joy!
Tell me, oh my angel
Oh my darling, let me dream again
I gently brush my hair
And put a hairpin through it
In the sea of green
A flower ornament blooms
It is a gift from my angel
It touches my forehead
Oh so gently
And it reminds me
Of the warm light that gathered
To bring my angel into this world
This fever is making me delirious
Ah, these times are so dear to me
There must have been something more
Some greater force that led me to you
Our fates tangle and unravel as we become family
I have been always living
Inside a book
But then my heart melted
And now I have experienced
The real world
Next Chapter
First Time in the Forest and Clay Tablets
You have a good father that cares
very much about his family.
He can get pretty overbearing.
By the way, when will you
start actually making paper?
You keep saying you will,
but it's been going nowhere.
Hey, I did make that faux-papyrus!
Though, it ended up a failure, admittedly.
Next time, I'll make clay tablets.
For sure!
Clay tablets still aren't paper.
Illustration:     Namino Ryou