Through the use of one of Frieda's magic tools,
Myne was able to narrowly escape death.
However...
I daresay you might have another year.
When Myne learned that her only chance to
escape death was to form a contract with a noble,
she immediately spoke to her family about it.
Is it okay for me to stay with you, as a family?
Having made the decision to die at home,
surrounded by her new family,
Myne resolves herself to live her last year to
the fullest so she can die without any regrets.
I have a wish, just one simple wish
Ascendance of a Bookworm
LOREM IPSUM DOLOR SIT AMET CONSECTETUR ADIPISCING ELIT FUSCE EFFICITUR LECTUS ID NISI RHONCUS PHARETRA NULLA QUAM VELIT TEMPUS QUIS ACCUMSAN EFFICITUR TEMPUS EU ANTE DONEC ULTRICES MOLESTIE MAXIMUS DONEC NON LOREM VITAE ANTE PRETIUM VESTIBULUM IN IN MAGNA MAURIS PHARETRA PLACERAT URNA AC FEUGIAT TORTOR AUCTOR EGET MAECENAS SIT AMET EROS FELIS ETIAM SAPIEN PURUS MALESUADA FERMENTUM VIVERRA VEL PORTA SIT AMET LECTUS CLASS APTENT TACITI SOCIOSQU AD LITORA TORQUENT PER CONUBIA NOSTRA PER INCEPTOS HIMENAEOS MAURIS VEHICULA DAPIBUS INTERDUM FUSCE SIT AMET NISI VENENATIS PLACERAT LIGULA ID CONDIMENTUM ODIO DUIS URNA JUSTO IMPERDIET UT COMMODO ID ULTRICES IN ELIT SED EGESTAS FACILISIS EX IN HENDRERIT IPSUM EGESTAS IMPERDIET
I hold it dearly in my heart and hope
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
It'll come true someday soon
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to
I don't have anything, nothing at all
But if I could have this one wish granted
It would fill the void inside my heart
I can feel the warm breeze blowing
And see shooting stars filling the sky
They make me feel as if
I can do anything, y'know?
In this wonderful world
Nothing is set in stone
Our as-yet untold future
Shines brighter than the sun
I want to take hold of my future
With my own two hands
And write pages filled with hope
Into the book of my life
Chapter 12
Baptism and Paradise
I see.
So you've decided to give up your
job at Master Benno's store, then.
Yeah.
I talked to Otto about it, and...
Myne, you bring in tremendous profits to his store.
So much so that the money you're making
likely exceeds that of senior employees.
I have a bad feeling that it could end up
causing tensions between you and them.
I'd barely be able to go to work
because of my health to begin with.
He said all that could make things tense there.
I could see that happening, yeah...
Sorry... I wish I could work together with you.
It'll probably be better this way anyway!
Well hey, if you're giving up, then Lutz can too!
He still has time to swap to a crafting job instead!
Just stop with that already!
I want to be a merchant.
Whether Myne is there with me or not,
I'll still become a merchant!
Lutz.
Do you really think you can go against your
parents' wishes and become a merchant?
If it really comes to it,
I'm prepared to become a live-in apprentice.
Live-ins usually end up in attics.
It's an awful living arrangement.
You practically end up living
like a slave until you come of age.
That's what I've heard being a live-in is like, at least.
There's no way you could make it as a live-in.
Says who?!
I've been preparing myself for it for ages now!
Is becoming a craftsman really
that big of an issue for you?
Yeah! 'Cause if I become one,
nothing's ever gonna change for me!
What do you mean?
My brothers just take things from me
whenever they want and I'm left with nothing.
If I become a merchant though,
then I can earn my own money for my own things.
I want to see what I can accomplish on my own.
If you've thought that far ahead,
then I guess it can't hurt tryin'.
Really?
Thanks, Mom!
And so, come spring,
Lutz and I were to go our separate ways.
Blessed be the melting of the snow.
May the Goddess of Spring's
boundless magnanimity grace you both.
What was that?
It's a celebratory greeting
that merchants use come spring.
Blessed be the melting of the snow.
May the Goddess of Spring... what was it?
May the Goddess of Spring's
boundless magnanimity grace you both.
That was pretty good for a first try.
Thanks.
Good job, Lutz.
After that, I informed Mr. Benno
of my plans for the future.
I see.
I'll withdraw your apprenticeship.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
What about this?
Keep it.
If you sign an exclusive contract with my store,
you'll be able to keep things pretty
similar to the way they are now.
And so, the busy days continued apace.
The workspace we were lent before
is being turned into the Myne Workshop.
I also sold the manufacturing methods
for plant-based paper to Mr. Benno.
The Parchment Guild tried to
interfere with our business soon after.
Compromise
Vested Interests
The paper we make is plant-based,
so it shouldn't be an issue, right?
Well, if our plant-based paper sells too well,
it'll start reducing the market share of parchment.
That's why I put in an application to create
a Plant Paper Guild to shut them all up,
but that damn geezer refuses to approve it.
If you agreed to make parchment the
exclusive medium for official contracts,
it'd guarantee them a set market share,
which might stop them complaining.
What a relief.
The guildmaster gave his approval.
Yeah.
With that finally out of the way,
we can set up a new workshop.
Oh, Dad!
I'm Benno of the Gilberta Company.
Ah, so that's you!
Thanks for taking care of my daughter.
Mr. Otto?
Benno totally looks like he's your father
when he's carrying you like that.
I'm single.
And that's my daughter!
Let's go.
You're single, Mr. Benno?
Is there an issue with that?
You run a large store,
so I figured people would be nagging you about it.
When I was interested in marriage,
I had my hands full with supporting Corinna.
When Corinna got married and I didn't
have any other family to take care of,
the woman I'd wanted to marry had died,
so I was left all alone in the end.
Unless I can find a woman out there
better than her, I won't be getting married.
That's all there is to it.
What on earth are you doing?
It seemed like you needed this.
As the time passed while we taught
Mr. Benno to make paper...
Took the first steps toward
bringing the Myne Workshop to life...
And got Lutz ready for his apprenticeship...
Spring had gone, and summer had arrived.
It's nice to see you, Myne.
I baked a pound cake for you.
Thank you, Mrs. Leise.
Please make sure to share your thoughts.
Her pound cakes had gotten
much better than before,
and in exchange for a bag of sugar,
I shared more ways to improve it.
So, apfelsige peels, you said?
Okay. I'm gonna go give it a try!
Well then, once again...
It has been a good while, Myne!
I was really surprised to see you
at the Merchant's Guild.
Once I open my store in the Nobles' Quarter,
I will be entirely on my own.
I am taking on apprentice work so that I may learn
how best to deal with any issues that may arise.
You have incredible foresight, Frieda.
You're planning so far ahead into the future...
By all accounts, you should be too.
It is in your best interests to come work for us,
rather than stay with Mr. Benno, no?
Otto—an acquaintance of mine
also mentioned that the best way to get in contact
with nobles would be to work for the guildmaster.
If you are able to understand as much, then why?
I have waited so very long!
Summer has come and yet
I still know naught of your decision.
You know, Frieda...
I've...
decided to die at home, with my family.
I cannot believe this.
Why?
'Cause I can't make magic tools, I guess?
"I'll just make it myself."
That mantra describes how I've gotten
hold of all the things I've wanted.
Magic tools are something
I can't make, though, right?
Yes, that is why you must—
However, I don't want to enter
into a contract with a noble.
Myne, do you have no sort of fear for death?
It's not that I chose to die,
it's just that I chose to stay with my family.
I've made them worry so much until now,
so I want to earn as much
as I can and leave it all to them.
In that case, I shall be purchasing
the recipe for pound cakes from you.
Would you allow me to do at least that much?
Thank you, Frieda.
I sold a one-year long exclusivity deal
on selling pound cakes to Frieda.
A single year, correct?
Yeah.
After a year, I'd like to make the recipe public.
That way, wonderful sweets
can spread without any restrictions.
That is, if I'm even around in a year's time anyway...
If I'm not, I guess I'll leave it up to you, Frieda.
If you do not wish for me to have a monopoly on it,
make sure to publicize the recipe yourself next year.
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
You really do look like a rich girl dressed like that!
It seems like you grew a little, too.
The skirt length is perfect now!
Everyone keeps calling me tiny,
but it turns out I can still grow.
The way your hair ornament sways
back and forth is super cute as well!
It's 'cause you helped me make it!
Myne will be the cutest girl at today's baptism!
Dad, you said the same thing at Tuuli's.
'Course I did. My daughters are the cutest around!
Lutz!
What's wrong?
Oh, well, uh...
My, you look just like a little rich girl, Myne.
Thank you, Aunt Karla!
Okay, let's go.
Myne! Lutz!
Congratulations!
That's a new hair ornament!
Parents aren't allowed in.
Lutz, take care of her.
Will do. Leave it to me!
Hey, Myne.
Yeah?
That dress and hair ornament
look really good on you.
You looked so cute that it caught me off-guard.
Wh-What are you saying...
Let's go.
My, how cute.
It's like a little wedding.
Myne!
Oh, you're not gonna like this.
What?
They're making everyone sign with blood.
You're right...
It looks like they're registering something.
City Citizenship!
Next.
Come closer.
Hold out your palm.
Y-Yes.
Mark this medal with your blood.
That is all.
Myne, over here!
Sure! Coming!
The high bishop has entered.
Lutz!
That's a book!
He has a book!
That's a book?
It looks completely different
from what you were making.
That thing looks really expensive...
A book...
Well then, let me tell you of the gods
that have created this world.
The lonely God of Darkness
encountered the Goddess of Light.
From their love, the Goddess of Water,
the God of Fire,
the Goddess of Wind,
and the Goddess of Earth were born into this world.
One day, the God of Life fell in love with the
Goddess of Earth at first sight, and they married.
However, the God of Life stole
the powers of the Goddess of Earth
and sealed her in a prison of snow and ice.
That is what we know as winter.
The Goddess of Light melted the ice
and the Goddess of Water swept away the
God of Life along with the melted ice and snow.
This brought about spring, which allowed
their children, the seeds, to bud.
Then came summer, when the God of Fire
helped nurture the newly-sprouting life.
The Goddess of Wind, in an effort
to protect her sister from the God of Life,
brought about the season of harvest, fall.
And finally, the God of Life reaches
his beloved once more, bringing winter.
The guardian deity of summer is the God of Fire.
He guides his patrons and
grants them divine protection.
I wanna read it myself!
Now, let me teach you how to pray.
Pay close attention.
Praise be to the gods!
G-Glico?!
Why is it the Glico Man pose?!
Then straight into prostration?!
Not good. I can't stop giggling!
Now, rise and join us!
Praise be to the gods!
I can't do this, it's too ridiculous!
Myne? Why didn't you say something sooner?
Are you okay?
I'm okay...
What's wrong?
I think she's feeling ill. She collapsed all of a sudden.
You must get some rest immediately.
This room is clearly for someone very rich.
I guess the outfit really sold it.
I can't stay here forever.
I mean, the baptism ceremony's gonna end.
Huh?
Did I pass by this before?
No, it's not this way...
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm kinda lost.
I see.
I will accompany you to the ceremony hall,
so please wait here for a moment.
Sure, thank you very much.
There's so... many... books.
It's a chained library, too.
A library!
Praise be to the gods!
Thanked be the gods!
Now then, if you'll excuse me...
Ouch...
What is this?
An invisible wall?
The books are so close and yet so far...
Why...
Let me in!
Let me in as well!
You can't.
I want to read all those books but it won't let me in!
The only ones that may enter are members
of the temple with special permission.
So if I become a member
I'll be able to read those books?
I'll become one!
I really want to be one!
How do I become one?!
Can you explain to me why it is that
you would like to become an apprentice priestess?
Because there's a library here.
A library?
I think you may be under a false impression.
The temple is a place to worship the gods.
The priests and priestesses exist to serve the gods.
In the first place, if a girl of your
standing wanted to join the temple,
a donation befitting of your
passion would be necessary.
A donation, you say?
I guess I really do look like I'm rich.
I can donate as much as one large gold.
One—
One large gold?
Was that too much?
That's my upper limit though.
Well, um, have your parents approved
of you choosing to join the temple?
I was gonna talk to them about it when I get back.
If they are against it,
make sure to come and see me immediately.
I'll offer any help I can.
Thank you very much.
You also have permission to read from
the Sacred Book, so feel free to visit any time.
Really?
Yay!
Praise be to the gods!
I got too excited...
Tell me, oh my angel
Oh my darling, let me dream again
I gently brush my hair
And put a hairpin through it
In the sea of green
A flower ornament blooms
It is a gift from my angel
It touches my forehead
Oh so gently
And it reminds me
Of the warm light that gathered
To bring my angel into this world
This fever is making me delirious
Ah, these times are so dear to me
There must have been something more
Some greater force that led me to you
Our fates tangle and unravel as we become family
I have been always living
Inside a book
But then my heart melted
And now I have experienced
The real world
Next Chapter
The Choice to Become an Apprentice Priestess
You finally made your appearance, High Priest!
My appearance is of no consequence right now.
More importantly, you shouldn't have rushed
into the book room at the temple like that.
Please maintain your composure better in future.
No way that's happening.
I mean... There's a library!
Libraries are a gift granted to us by the gods!
They're truly paradises!
There's no way I can't get excited.
Calm down.
It's not a done deal just yet.
Illustration:     Kaya Kuramoto