Myne and Lutz's bond deepens
as he accepts her for who she really is.
Their paper was finished, and as a result,
they were accepted as Benno's apprentices.
However, another fateful encounter awaits them...
I have a wish, just one simple wish
Ascendance of a Bookworm
LOREM IPSUM DOLOR SIT AMET CONSECTETUR ADIPISCING ELIT FUSCE EFFICITUR LECTUS ID NISI RHONCUS PHARETRA NULLA QUAM VELIT TEMPUS QUIS ACCUMSAN EFFICITUR TEMPUS EU ANTE DONEC ULTRICES MOLESTIE MAXIMUS DONEC NON LOREM VITAE ANTE PRETIUM VESTIBULUM IN IN MAGNA MAURIS PHARETRA PLACERAT URNA AC FEUGIAT TORTOR AUCTOR EGET MAECENAS SIT AMET EROS FELIS ETIAM SAPIEN PURUS MALESUADA FERMENTUM VIVERRA VEL PORTA SIT AMET LECTUS CLASS APTENT TACITI SOCIOSQU AD LITORA TORQUENT PER CONUBIA NOSTRA PER INCEPTOS HIMENAEOS MAURIS VEHICULA DAPIBUS INTERDUM FUSCE SIT AMET NISI VENENATIS PLACERAT LIGULA ID CONDIMENTUM ODIO DUIS URNA JUSTO IMPERDIET UT COMMODO ID ULTRICES IN ELIT SED EGESTAS FACILISIS EX IN HENDRERIT IPSUM EGESTAS IMPERDIET
I hold it dearly in my heart and hope
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
It'll come true someday soon
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to
I don't have anything, nothing at all
But if I could have this one wish granted
It would fill the void inside my heart
I can feel the warm breeze blowing
And see shooting stars filling the sky
They make me feel as if
I can do anything, y'know?
In this wonderful world
Nothing is set in stone
Our as-yet untold future
Shines brighter than the sun
I want to take hold of my future
With my own two hands
And write pages filled with hope
Into the book of my life
Chapter 9
The Guildmaster's Granddaughter
Whoa.
I've never seen this much money before.
Um...
I've never used money myself,
so I don't know how it works.
Are you serious?
Since she usually collapses when she tries,
she's never run any errands.
Mark,
teach her about the various lyon denominations.
Certainly, Master.
A small copper coin is worth 10 lyon.
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Ten small coppers make 100 lyon,
which equals a medium copper coin.
10 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
Ten medium coppers equal
a large copper coin, worth 1000 lyon.
Medium Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
10 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Small Copper Coin
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
100 Lyon
I see.
Then ten large coppers would be
10,000 lyon, which would make...
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
100 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
Medium Copper Coin
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
Large Copper Coin
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
A small silver coin.
Small
Copper Coin
Medium
Large
Copper Coin
Small
Silver Coin
Large
Gold Coin
Small
10 Lyon
100 Lyon
1,000 Lyon
10,000 Lyon
100,000 Lyon
1,000,000 Lyon
10,000,000 Lyon
Ten small silvers is 100,000 lyon, or one large silver.
Ten of those is 1,000,000 lyon, one small gold.
And lastly, ten small golds is
10,000,000 lyon, making one large gold.
Precisely. Well done.
Let's calculate your pay for the
trial batch of paper you provided.
Your share is one small silver
and eight large coppers each.
We made this money ourselves, didn't we?
It doesn't feel real, does it?
I'll begin mass production of the paper next spring.
You'll be making more small silvers in no time.
Oh, speaking of making money...
Do you think something like this would sell?
So you were the one behind it. Figures.
Huh?
If you don't mind my asking,
can you make something like this alone?
We said that I'd do the thinking
and Lutz would do the making, so...
I can make the decorations, but I need
Lutz to make the wooden pin for me.
Right?
Well...
Uh...
Yeah.
I was thinking of making more
as part of my winter handiwork.
That sounds good.
With that done...
Do you two have it in you to
accompany me somewhere right now?
This is the Merchant's Guild.
The Merchant's Guild, huh?
Anyone who wishes to partake in any of the trading
industries must register at the Merchant's Guild.
If we don't register you, we won't be able
to sell the paper or your hair ornaments.
Unregistered trading is subject to severe punishment.
Upstairs. The three of us.
Your identification, please.
It disappeared!
Is that a magic tool as well?
Yes.
This place has ties to nobility.
Hopefully we can get through
your registrations painlessly...
A carpenter's son and a soldier's daughter, huh?
Please wait over here.
That's a bookshelf, right?!
Bookshelf? No, it's just a shelf.
All you'll find on there are scrolls and wooden tags.
Don't they count as books too?
They have writing on them and everything.
No, they don't.
Books are luxurious goods
that have proper bindings.
I don't really care what it is, so long as I can read it.
I knew this'd happen.
I bet that old geezer's responsible.
He's probably making up some
inane reason to use to turn us down.
Did he say "geezer"?
So these are annual reports
relating to trade with nobles...
Oh? What's this?
It's a map!
This is Ehrenfest.
Ehrenfest?
Yes. A town is named after its lord.
And where does the lord live?
His home is in the nobles' district to the north.
Merchants gather in the east
as the main roads lead into there.
To the south you'll find farmland,
the forest, and various smaller townships.
Finally, to the west is the river.
Cross over that and you'll reach
the territory of a neighboring lord.
The territories trade regularly as the
two lords have an amicable relationship.
In the future, the two of you
will also be able to sail there.
Really?
Yes. If we can get you registered, that is.
Mr. Benno, is getting registered
really that complicated?
Master Benno, the guildmaster
is ready to speak with you.
Let's go.
It's good to see you.
So this is the "old geezer" he was talking about...
Well then, Benno,
I'll get straight to the point.
Temporary registrations are usually
done for kids before their baptisms
to allow them to help family businesses.
You share no blood relation to these kids,
so I can't approve your request.
That just means there's no precedent, right?
What if I were to be clear about my intentions?
What are you trying to say?
I think you'll change your mind once
you know what these kids will be selling.
Huh? What could it possibly be?
Myne, show it to the guildmaster.
It's this.
No way, th-that's—
You'll be selling those?!
Wasn't this the hair ornament
you were searching high and low for?
Oh, so that's what this is about.
Did you see that hair ornament?
That'd sell like crazy!
Bring me the artisan that made it!
These wonderful ornaments are what they had
planned to work on for their winter handiwork.
I see.
Oh, how tragic it would be
if they were unable to sell them
because their temporary
registrations weren't approved.
Man! Such a waste!
I'll approve their temporary registrations.
Thank you very much.
After that, Lutz and I were issued guild cards.
They act as proof of our registrations.
Allow me to formally introduce myself.
I'm the guildmaster, Gustav.
My granddaughter Frieda
will be baptized this winter.
I'd like one of these ornaments by then.
How does that sound?
There's only a single month
until the winter baptism.
If we were paid extra,
we might be able to prioritize your order.
The most I'm paying is this much.
Thank you very much.
Well then, we have a deal.
I'd like one just like the one you showed me.
Wait, what about having it themed
around her hair and outfit?
I'm actually planning to make it a surprise.
Figured. He's ruining the present
by trying to make it a surprise.
But, if she's already prepared
a different hair ornament,
you might end up making her make a hard choice.
Wouldn't you rather see her happy about such
a special present, instead of torn between two?
Plus, if I sew it specifically to her wishes,
wouldn't she treasure it even more?
Very true...
You said your name was Myne, correct?
Won't you come work at my store?
Huh?
Absolutely not!
It's bigger than Benno's store and the
employment terms would be much better.
I owe Mr. Benno more than I could ever repay.
Then I'll repay it for you.
U-Um...
Myne! You have to give him a clear no!
Say, "I refuse."
I-I refuse.
I get it. You can't give me a real answer
with someone like that over your shoulder.
Once we'd made plans for me to meet the
guildmaster's granddaughter, we returned to the store.
Welcome back.
That old geezer jumped at the ornament immediately
so we were able to get this much out of him.
So, um, what does that mean?
It means four small silver coins.
What? Four small silvers?
You're totally overcharging him!
When money comes your way, you don't question it.
You take it and you take as much as you can.
But...
You need to learn to understand
the true value of things.
Every item you've brought me is a luxury good.
If you don't know how to price your products,
you'll end up ruining the market.
I see...
After that, Lutz and I deposited the small silvers
we earned from the paper onto our guild cards.
The Merchant's Guild also functioned as a sort of bank.
Your battle starts tomorrow!
Don't let your guard down.
She's just a little girl.
Frieda is said to resemble that old geezer
the most of all of his grandchildren!
Make sure Myne doesn't get taken in
by their poaching attempts again.
You got that, Lutz?
Yup!
I don't think you need to be that worried...
Okay, see you tomorrow!
Supporting my family through my own income
is a dream I've had since my Urano days.
What?!
Where did you get all that, Myne?
I finished my paper, so Mr. Benno bought it from us.
We've gotta prepare for winter soon, right?
Put it towards that.
Great work, Myne!
You really went all-out, huh.
Lutz helped out a whole lot, too.
That's right, you two did
seem to be up to something.
I'm so happy for you, Myne!
I don't really get what's going on,
but well done, Myne!
Dad, that hurts!
Mom and Dad praised me all night long.
What'd your parents think, Lutz?
They were happy I'd earned some money, but...
When I told them I'd earned it making paper,
Dad said I should become a papermaking artisan.
I see...
But I want to become a merchant
and get out of this city.
You wanna start making books soon too, right, Myne?
Yeah.
Once the books are covered,
next up will be opening a bookstore.
Still got a long way to go for that, though.
I wouldn't mind opening a bookstore with you, Myne.
Huh?
I had an interesting thought
while looking at that map yesterday.
If we were selling books, we'd get to visit
nobles in other cities to sell to them, you know?
Isn't it a great idea?
Yeah! That sounds great!
Would you happen to be Ms. Myne?
Oh... yes.
My name is Frieda.
Wonderful meeting you.
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
I was able to tell immediately.
Your hair stick is very unique.
It made for a perfect landmark.
I-It's a pleasure to meet you.
Well, then. Let us be on our way to my residence.
You can tell just by looking at her
that she's a well-raised young lady.
Mr. Benno was just needlessly worried
about her resembling her grandfather.
We've arrived.
The Ottmar Company...
So this is the guildmaster's store.
They're definitely wealthy people.
So, shall we begin discussing the matter at hand?
Yes, please.
Ms. Frieda, this is a sample of the hair
ornament the guildmaster has ordered.
Why, how beautiful!
You see, I quite fancy the baptism marches.
I always make sure to watch them.
During this summer's baptism, that beautiful
ornament stood out to me like nothing else.
That's when I begged my dear grandfather for one.
Let me show you my dress!
From there, we decided on a color
that would fit with her baptism dress,
and she provided us with
the thread used for that dress.
The problem is...
If you're going to put up your hair the same
way as today, then you'll need two ornaments.
Why, I suppose we'll have to pay you double then.
It's totally fine.
You supplied us with the thread to use,
I'm happy to make two for the price we agreed.
No, that will not do.
We shall pay you the proper fee for both.
Please, don't worry about it.
We're paying.
I'm serious, please don't worry about it.
Absolutely not. Please let us pay for it.
Why not just make the second one half-price?
Huh?
Myne, you want to give her a discount
because she provided the thread.
Frieda wants to pay for both.
So why don't you just make the
second one half-price as a compromise?
Lutz, you're a genius.
Would you be okay with that, Ms. Frieda?
I do not have any objections. However...
When money comes your way, you don't question it.
You take it and you take as much as you can.
Huh?
That's the golden rule of commerce.
Hold on a sec...
This girl really isn't so average after all.
This is fallold squash.
It's a beverage made from fallold juice
mixed with honey, and then thinned out with water.
Oh, it's made from that raspberry-looking fruit.
Oh, it's so sweet!
Yeah, it's super good.
Did you make this, Frieda?
Oh, no, our chef prepared it.
Right... You don't really have
any need to cook, do you?
What do you usually do then?
Huh?
The activity I enjoy most...
It would probably be counting money.
Excuse me?
Not just counting it, but also amassing it.
Feeling its weight through a pouch fills me with joy.
Oh, and hearing the coins rub against
each other is as beautiful as any symphony.
I-I also liked it when my
piggy bank would get heavier...
Oh my, you understand my hobby?!
What?
Why, Myne, would you not
care to join our company?
Absolutely not!
Our store is bigger than Mr. Benno's and
the employment terms would be much better.
I owe Mr. Benno more than I could ever repay.
Oh, worry not. I'll have it paid in your stead!
Myne, you have to turn her down bluntly!
This conversation's giving me
a strange sense of déjà vu.
You don't become an official apprentice
until after your baptism, you know!
Here, you love sweet things, right?
Yes...
I mean, I must reject your offer!
My, what a shame.
We shall be seeing each other at the
Merchant's Guild plenty from now on though.
I quite look forward to it.
M-Me too...
What? You sold the second one for half the price?
Are you an idiot?!
The next customer could come in saying that they want a second one for free.
I told you that when money
comes your way, you don't question it.
When we returned to the store,
we were chewed out by Mr. Benno.
You take it and you take as much as you can.
At the very least, you managed to have her
pay for the second one, so it's fine for now.
So, how was she?
That old geezer's granddaughter.
She seemed even more
cunning than the guildmaster.
She reminded me of Myne.
What? How so?
When she started talking about money,
she made the same expression
you do when you talk about books.
Not just that. She looks cute on the outside,
but deep down she's a weirdo, just like you.
What?!
And so, one month later...
Why, how incredibly charming.
Would you mind me trying them on right now?
Go ahead.
Let me help you.
B-But...
All done.
Pray tell, does it suit me?
Yes, my Frieda! You're very cute!
Just like a flower fairy.
It suits you very well, Ms. Frieda.
Thank you, Myne!
The guildmaster and Mr. Benno
left to speak about business,
and Frieda paid us for the ornaments.
Thank you very much for your patronage!
It was a pleasure to work for you, Ms. Frieda.
Myne, I already consider us friends.
Just call me Frieda, please.
F-Friends?
Though I must say, you've pioneered
a wonderful new sewing method.
Pioneered a new method... What?
Yes. I've had beautiful embroideries
produced for me in the past,
but I've never seen a three-dimensional
flower made entirely from thread like this.
This is revolutionary.
Oh, so that's what Mr. Benno meant before...
I might have made a rather big mistake.
Myne, we should get going.
Oh, right. I'm rather frail and often collapse,
so Lutz manages my health.
Huh?
Could you perhaps suffer from the Devouring?
"The Devouring"?
Yes. Does it feel like a fever
is eating you up from the inside?
You know about this sickness?
I also have experience with it.
What?
That's why my body is so small.
I also realized that your body seemed small, but...
How do you cure it?
The Devouring...
can't be cured.
What?
It's because the Devouring isn't a sickness.
You can keep the fevers down,
but it costs a great fortune.
It's always money...
As long as you have something
you want to put your all into, you'll be fine.
Conversely, it will flare up once again
if your willpower wanes, so please take care.
I see.
Thank you for telling me, Ms. Frieda.
This is clearly a sign that you
must come work for me, Myne.
Together we'll market a myriad
of goods and become very wealthy!
Why, doesn't that just sound wonderful?
Goodness, Ms. Frieda...
I told you. It's simply Frieda.
Okay, Frieda.
Tell me, oh my angel
Oh my darling, let me dream again
I gently brush my hair
And put a hairpin through it
In the sea of green
A flower ornament blooms
It is a gift from my angel
It touches my forehead
Oh so gently
And it reminds me
Of the warm light that gathered
To bring my angel into this world
This fever is making me delirious
Ah, these times are so dear to me
There must have been something more
Some greater force that led me to you
Our fates tangle and unravel as we become family
I have been always living
Inside a book
But then my heart melted
And now I have experienced
The real world
Next Chapter
The Second Winter Approaches
So you finally learned of the Devouring.
Yes.
When I heard I'd be fine so long as
I have something to keep me motivated,
it felt like I'd become a migratory fish.
A migratory fish? What is that?
A fish that dies if it ever stops swimming somewhere.
I've never heard of a fish like that.
I'd love to see one.
What?!
Can you worry about me
instead of the fish, High Priest?!
Illustration:     Akisaki Rio