Now, please put this on.
Excuse me, but what is this, High Priest?
It should be obvious.
It is a magical tool.
I was asking what you use it for.
Could you please ex... plain...
Only Myne puts her hair up with something like this.
And it's not just this hair stick.
Myne has invented a myriad of things.
But most surprising is her passion for books.
She loves books above all else,
and even made a picture book for children.
She's unusual no matter how you look at it.
What is it that makes you so special?
I shall peer into your past, Myne.
Before I became Myne,
I lived in a different world as Motosu Urano.
Psychology, Theology, History,
Geography, Pedagogy, Ethnology,
Math, Physics, Geoscience,
Chemistry, Biology, Art,
Health, Language, Fiction.
I adored books.
I loved the sheer amount of knowledge
and history contained within them.
I lived a blissful life surrounded by books.
But even so...
Then, on the verge of death, I prayed.
"Dear God, please allow me to continue
reading books in my next life."
I have a wish, just one simple wish
Ascendance of a Bookworm
LOREM IPSUM DOLOR SIT AMET CONSECTETUR ADIPISCING ELIT FUSCE EFFICITUR LECTUS ID NISI RHONCUS PHARETRA NULLA QUAM VELIT TEMPUS QUIS ACCUMSAN EFFICITUR TEMPUS EU ANTE DONEC ULTRICES MOLESTIE MAXIMUS DONEC NON LOREM VITAE ANTE PRETIUM VESTIBULUM IN IN MAGNA MAURIS PHARETRA PLACERAT URNA AC FEUGIAT TORTOR AUCTOR EGET MAECENAS SIT AMET EROS FELIS ETIAM SAPIEN PURUS MALESUADA FERMENTUM VIVERRA VEL PORTA SIT AMET LECTUS CLASS APTENT TACITI SOCIOSQU AD LITORA TORQUENT PER CONUBIA NOSTRA PER INCEPTOS HIMENAEOS MAURIS VEHICULA DAPIBUS INTERDUM FUSCE SIT AMET NISI VENENATIS PLACERAT LIGULA ID CONDIMENTUM ODIO DUIS URNA JUSTO IMPERDIET UT COMMODO ID ULTRICES IN ELIT SED EGESTAS FACILISIS EX IN HENDRERIT IPSUM EGESTAS IMPERDIET
I hold it dearly in my heart and hope
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
It'll come true someday soon
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to
I don't have anything, nothing at all
But if I could have this one wish granted
It would fill the void inside my heart
I can feel the warm breeze blowing
And see shooting stars filling the sky
They make me feel as if
I can do anything, y'know?
In this wonderful world
Nothing is set in stone
Our as-yet untold future
Shines brighter than the sun
I want to take hold of my future
With my own two hands
And write pages filled with hope
Into the book of my life
Chapter 1
A World Without Books
It's so hot. I can't breathe...
Make it stop!
Sucks, doesn't it?
It's really hot... Please help me...
Yeah, it's hard to bear.
Anyone, please help.
Huh? The voice is fading.
Hey, wait!
Where am I?
Wait, are these my hands?
I definitely died, didn't I?
Is this some kind of weird near-death
experience I'm going through?
Well, it's definitely actually
happening, so what's going on?
Why am I here?
Who is this? Her hair's green.
Huh? I can't understand her.
Someone else's memories are flooding into my head.
Myne?
No, I'm not Myne! I'm Motosu Urano!
Are you okay, Myne?
I can understand her now?
How are you feeling, Myne?
Mom...
It was in this moment that
Motosu Urano became Myne.
That's when it struck me.
My mother was so happy for me
when I finally got my librarian gig.
But now I might never see her again.
Mom...
I'm sorry.
I wish I had a book right now...
Wait, hold on.
As long as I have books I can
survive in any environment.
No, I will survive.
I better find some books.
Wait, where are the books?
Myne, are you feeling better already?
That's my older sister Tuuli, isn't it?
Perfect.
Hey, Tuuli. Can you bring me some books?
Books?
Yeah, I wanna read some books.
What are "books"?
Huh?
Does Tuuli not know what books are?
Wait. What do you mean
she doesn't know what a book is?
It can't be that there are no children's books
and that's why she doesn't know, right?
Are you okay, Myne?
Myne, how's your fever?
Mom, I think Myne has a headache.
Her fever went down a little bit but she
still doesn't seem to be feeling so great.
Be a good girl and rest until dinner, okay?
Tuuli, come and help me.
Okay.
It's now or never. I've gotta find some books.
Anything for books...
Clothes, huh?
What's this supposed to be?
Man, it'd have been great if there
had been books right here in this room.
I guess life's never that easy, though.
Okay, let's move the search on to the next room.
Does it really have to be this difficult?
It's for the books. I have no choice.
I did it!
Ouch...
This counts as a battle scar, right?
I got in.
I guess this is the kitchen.
There's probably none in here.
A storage room?
This one is locked.
Maybe it leads outside?
I searched the whole house
and couldn't find a single book.
Why's that?
Could books be expensive in this world?
In the world I'm from, books used to
be very expensive until the invention
of the printing press brought
about their mass production.
If you weren't part of the upper class
you probably never got to read a book in your life.
Well, nothing I can do for now.
But there should at least be
words written somewhere, right?
Surely I can find a newspaper
or calendar lying around.
Nope.
No.
Nothing.
Nor here.
Absolutely nothing.
Why isn't there a single word
to be found anywhere?
Am I really supposed to live here now?
We're home.
Myne, I told you to rest, didn't I?
And what a mess you've made.
There are no books.
Huh?
What's wrong, Myne?
Does something hurt?
There are no books!
I want books. I want to read books.
That's all I need...
Who should I talk to that'd understand my pain?
Just please tell me where I can find books to read...
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
It's been three days since I became Myne.
Three brutal days.
I'm telling you, this life is the worst.
The "bathroom" is just a chamber pot
in the bedroom that they then throw out.
My "father", a man I barely knew,
forced me to let him change my clothes.
Good grief!
Woman`s Dignity
Sense of Shame
I have to abandon these or I'll never last!
Now I've given up and even
get them to wipe me down.
Tuuli is giving me strange looks for it,
but it's made me feel much better.
Oh, and also...
What are you doing?
I was trying to do my hair up because it gets
in the way, but I can't really tie it properly.
It's cause your hair is super straight, Myne.
Yeah, this ribbon keeps
coming undone when I try it.
Oh, actually...
Can I break this off?
That's my doll!
I love it so much! How could you?
Oh, sorry.
I wanted a hairpin...
though you don't know what that is, right?
I wanted a thin stick like this doll's leg.
If that's what you want, I can carve you one myself.
Something like this?
That's perfect, Tuuli!
How does it look?
You can't do it like that, Myne!
Only adults put all of their hair up like that.
Oh, huh.
Is this okay?
I think so.
If you look at it from the front it looks like
you got pierced by a stick though.
That's fine, don't worry about it.
My hair itself is another issue, though...
It's all sticky, I hate it.
Myne, how are you feeling?
Your fever's gone down a little more.
You're not feeling sluggish?
I'm okay.
Do you wanna go shopping
together with me, then?
Shopping?
There weren't any books at home but
maybe I'll find a bookstore if I go outside.
If I had books...
"If I had a book, I wouldn't be lonely anymore.
I'll stay home every day and keep watch, okay?"
If I say that, she'd totally get me one, right?
Yup, I wanna go.
Oh, you've gotten really energetic all of a sudden.
Cause I really wanna go!
Okay, let's head out then.
Cold! Narrow! Smelly!
Myne, come on, climb up.
Huh?
You can't walk all the way to the market, so get on.
O-Okay...
I see, Myne's body is pretty frail,
so Mom's always given her piggyback rides.
But I think I could manage this much, to be honest.
So we live on the fifth floor.
This is what apartment buildings are like here.
That's where they're getting water from.
Wow, this looks exactly like the old
European towns I've seen in photobooks.
Mom, is that a castle?
It's the temple.
When you turn seven
we'll go there for your baptism.
Those are pretty big gates.
Those are the city walls.
Inside there is the archduke's palace,
and the nobles' mansions.
We don't really have any business there though.
What about those walls?
These are the outer walls. They protect our city.
Dad works at the southern gate, remember?
Huh?
Ah, right.
Yeah, I know.
That being said,
with all this stuff about archdukes and nobles,
I can presume this is actually a pretty big city.
And despite that, I can't find any writing anywhere.
Could it be that this world
doesn't have a writing system?
I never even considered that.
Myne, we've arrived at the market.
I'd like three of those, please.
Thanks for yer business!
These are all fresh vegetables! How about one?
I never considered that written
communication might not be a thing here.
It'd make sense for books not
to exist in a world like that.
Mom, what's that? What does that board say?
Oh, those are prices.
They let you know how much
you need to pay for something.
Numbers!
Hooray, there are numbers!
What does it say, Mom?
This one is 20 lyon.
And this one says 23 lyon.
So this one is 30 lyon?
Correct! I'm impressed you managed
to remember them that quickly.
Good job, Myne!
What is this smell?
What's wrong, Myne?
There are dead birds!
Myne? Hang in there, Myne!
Mom...
I got worried after you suddenly passed out.
Are you okay now?
Yeah, I am... not okay.
Oh, that's unfortunate.
I won't be able to go shopping like this either.
I'll wait here, so go ahead, Mom.
But...
Ma'am, can I wait here?
I don't feel very well but I promise
I'll stay put and not cause any trouble.
My, aren't you a polite young lady?
Sure, please go ahead and finish your shopping.
You wouldn't want her collapsing again, right?
If you're worried about her,
I can let her stay in the back of my stall.
Nobody will be able to kidnap her there.
I'll be good, I promise.
Thank you very much,
I'll be back in just a few minutes.
Don't go anywhere.
Okay.
Again, thank you.
I guess that was a little too raw for me.
Thanks for letting me stay here!
Wait... could it be?
Hey, Mister! That!
What is that?!
Oh, that? It's a book.
Yahoo!
Finally! I've found one!
An actual book!
Is this your first time seeing a book?
Yes.
Say, would you know of any
shops that sell books, mister?
Book shops? None that I know about, no.
Huh? There are books but not bookstores?
Books have to be copied by hand, you know.
That makes them far too
expensive to just be sold regularly.
Even this book was something a noble
in debt pawned off, so it's not for sale.
The only ones with enough money to afford
something like it would be nobles in the first place.
Damn those nobles!
It seems I have no choice.
Please let me touch that book!
Prostration
A kneeling posture of traditional
Japanese origin used to show
deference or to curry favor.
A kneeling posture of traditional
Japanese origin used to show
deference or to curry favor.
I understand that I cannot buy it,
but at least let me touch it!
I want to at least enjoy the sweet fragrance of ink.
Please, I beg you.
I don't quite understand what's going on,
but I don't think letting you touch it is wise.
Huh?
P-Please, wait.
Just let me flip through the pages for just a moment.
Sorry, no can do.
Understood...
Thank you for taking care of my daughter.
Let's get going, Myne.
I couldn't even touch it.
I bought you some of your favorite foods today.
Are you still feeling sick?
So it seems there are no bookstores here.
Could it be that this world
just doesn't have any, period?
I can't get any books if there are no bookstores.
What am I gonna do?
I'm just gonna have to make them myself!
Make what?
Myne?
What are you gonna make, Myne?
N-Nothing.
I will stop at nothing now.
I will absolutely get my books.
No matter what!
Tell me, oh my angel
Oh my darling, let me dream again
I gently brush my hair
And put a hairpin through it
In the sea of green
A flower ornament blooms
It is a gift from my angel
It touches my forehead
Oh so gently
And it reminds me
Of the warm light that gathered
To bring my angel into this world
This fever is making me delirious
Ah, these times are so dear to me
There must have been something more
Some greater force that led me to you
Our fates tangle and unravel as we become family
I have been always living
Inside a book
But then my heart melted
And now I have experienced
The real world
Next Chapter
Life Improvement and My Stone Slate
So your obsession with books
remained with you even after death.
This is making my head hurt.
Please don't say that with a straight face.
It's not like you didn't get
any screen time because—
No spoilers, you fool!
Illustration:     You Shiina