I lovehate you, lovehate you, baby, yeah!
Hacka Doll
The Animation
You won't find anything ordinary around here!
You have so much information at your fingertips!
Don't be shy and don't run away!
Bang! Bang! Just leave it to us!
C'mon, just be true to your feelings
and let yourself be taken with the flow!
This freedom is finally letting me see
that there are so many choices in front of me
Which one do I pick? Won't you help me choose?
Let's keep touching today, baby!
How do you want to feel?
I can be in the minority or the majority
They're both just as fun to me!
Let's keep touching today, baby!
So won't you softly touch me, baby?
I just can't wait to be with you!
I lovehate you, lovehate you, baby, yeah!