I lovehate you, lovehate you, baby, yeah!
Hacka Doll
The Animation
You won't find anything ordinary around here!
You have so much information at your fingertips!
Don't be shy and don't run away!
Bang! Bang! Just leave it to us!
C'mon, just be true to your feelings
and let yourself be taken with the flow!
This freedom is finally letting me see
that there are so many choices in front of me
Which one do I pick? Won't you help me choose?
Let's keep touching today, baby!
How do you want to feel?
I can be in the minority or the majority
They're both just as fun to me!
Let's keep touching today, baby!
So won't you softly touch me, baby?
I just can't wait to be with you!
I lovehate you, lovehate you, baby, yeah!
Hey...
What am I to you, Ikuo?
Am I just a girl you grew up with?
Childhood Friend
Hey... What am I to you, Ikuo?
Am I just a girl you grew up with?
Ikuo
「そうだよ。ただの幼馴染」
"Yes. Just a girl I grew up with."
「違う。俺の恋人だ」
"No. You're my girlfriend."
「無関係。赤の他人さ」
"Nothing. I don't even know."
「・・・・・・」
"......"
「そうだよ。ただの幼馴染」
"Yes. Just a girl I grew up with."
「無関係。赤の他人さ」
"Nothing. I don't even know."
「そうだよ。ただの幼馴染」
"Yes. Just a girl I grew up with."
「無関係。赤の他人さ」
"Nothing. I don't even know."
「そうだよ。ただの幼馴染」
"Yes. Just a girl I grew up with."
「違う。俺の恋人だ」
"No. You're my girlfriend."
「・・・・・・」
"......"
「違う。俺の恋人だ」
"No. You're my girlfriend."
「・・・・・・」
"......"
I'm so happy!
Childhood Friend
I'm
I'm so
I'm so ha
I'm so happ
I'm so happy!
So now we're boyfriend and girlfriend!
So
So no
So now
So now we
So now we're
So now we're bo
So now we're boyf
So now we're boyfri
So now we're boyfrien
So now we're boyfriend a
So now we're boyfriend and
So now we're boyfriend and gi
So now we're boyfriend and girl
So now we're boyfriend and girlfr
So now we're boyfriend and girlfrie
So now we're boyfriend and girlfriend!
As if it'd ever happen like that.
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if I come to your place?
Childhood Friend
Hey
Hey,
Hey, Ikuo
Hey, Ikuo, is
Hey, Ikuo, is it
Hey, Ikuo, is it o
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if I
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if I come
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if I come to
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if I come to yo
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if I come to your
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if I come to your pla
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if I come to your place
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if I come to your place?
Your parents aren't home today, right?
Yo
Your
Your pa
Your pare
Your parent
Your parents
Your parents ar
Your parents aren
Your parents aren't
Your parents aren't ho
Your parents aren't home
Your parents aren't home to
Your parents aren't home today,
Your parents aren't home today, ri
Your parents aren't home today, right
Your parents aren't home today, right?
An unexpected plot twist!
Well, if this were real-life,
I wouldn't even get to know any girls.
Well, I'd better be a gentleman.
Childhood Friend
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if I come to your place?
Your parents aren't home today, right?
Childhood Friend
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if I come to your place?
Your parents aren't home today, right?
Childhood Friend
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if I come to your place?
Your parents aren't home today, right?
Childhood Friend
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if I come to your place?
Your parents aren't home today, right?
Childhood Friend
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if I come to your place?
Your parents aren't home today, right?
Childhood Friend
Hey, Ikuo, is it okay if I come to your place?
Your parents aren't home today, right?
Huh?
What the heck?!
I was just getting to the good part.
We are the Personal Entertainment
AI that syncs to you:
Hacka Dolls!
Wait, what?
It's just me?
A girl?!
I wonder what happened to the other two.
A girl suddenly appeared in my room...
That sure is strange...
Wh-What sort of eroge is this?
Well, whatever.
Is there anything you wish
for me to advance for you?
Whoa... What do I do now?!
Episode 4: Take a Shower First
Calm down, Ikuo.
I'm not sure how it happened,
but this is my chance to get to know a girl!
First impressions are key!
Excuse me...
Yes?!
Hacka Doll #2
Would you tell me your name?
Wo
Woul
Would
Would y
Would you
Would you t
Would you tell
Would you tell me
Would you tell me yo
Would you tell me your
Would you tell me your name
Would you tell me your name?
Ikuo
「・・・・・・」
"......"
「郁夫っていいます。よろしく！」
"My name is Ikuo. Nice to meet you!"
「黒龍院異苦雄様と呼べ」
"Call me Kokuryuuin Ikuo."
「個人情報なんでちょっと…」
"I can't give away personal information..."
「郁夫っていいます。よろしく！」
"My name is Ikuo. Nice to meet you!"
「個人情報なんでちょっと…」
"I can't give away personal information..."
"My name is Ikuo. Nice to meet you!"
「個人情報なんでちょっと…」
"I can't give away personal information..."
「郁夫っていいます。よろしく！」
"My name is Ikuo. Nice to meet you!"
「個人情報なんでちょっと…」
"I can't give away personal information..."
「郁夫っていいます。よろしく！」
"My name is Ikuo. Nice to meet you!"
「個人情報なんでちょっと…」
"I can't give away personal information..."
「郁夫っていいます。よろしく！」
"My name is Ikuo. Nice to meet you!"
「個人情報なんでちょっと…」
「郁夫っていいます。よろしく！」
"My name is Ikuo. Nice to meet you!"
「個人情報なんでちょっと…」
「郁夫っていいます。よろしく！」
"My name is Ikuo. Nice to meet you!"
「個人情報なんでちょっと…」
「郁夫っていいます。よろしく！」
"My name is Ikuo. Nice to meet you!"
「・・・・・・」
"......"
What the hell am I doing?!
In a game, this'd be a piece of cake!
Excuse me...
Hacka Doll #2
Ex
Excu
What should I call you?
Excuse
Excuse m
Excuse me.
Excuse me...
Wh
What
What s
What sho
What shoul
What should
What should I
What should I ca
What should I call
What should I call y
What should I call you
What should I call you?
Ikuo
「郁夫でお願いします」
"Call me Ikuo."
「イクちやんだよ☆」
"Call me Iku!"
「マス夕一さんと呼べ」
"Call me Master."
「そもそもハツ力ド一ル２号って何だよ？」
"What the hell is Hacka Doll #2 anyway?"
Ikuo
This time for sure!
「マス夕一さんと呼べ」
"Call me Master."
「郁夫でお願いします」
"Call me Ikuo."
「マス夕一さんと呼べ」
"Call me Master."
「郁夫でお願いします」
"Call me Ikuo."
「マス夕一さんと呼べ」
"Call me Master."
「郁夫でお願いします」
"Call me Ikuo."
I-Ikyuo ish my name.
This isn't working!
I thought I chose my words perfectly, too!
Ikuo, huh?
Nice to meet you!
She's so cute...
Still, what about him shall I advance?
Uh, wait...
Let me clean up this mess.
Oh, yes! Cleaning!
I can do that for you.
Huh?! No, you don't need to...
U-Um...
Ikuo
「ご､ごめん！」
"S-Sorry!"
「オレ様の言う事聞かないとダメだろ？」
"You'd better do as I say."
「すげぇかわいい」
"Damn, you're cute."
「フヒヒ、これ壁ドソですよ｡壁ドンキ夕コレ」
"Heh, look, a wall slam! Didn't see that trope coming!"
Never mind! Just sit there!
Um, here, read this!
Damn it, this isn't working
like it does in games!
It almost feels like
he's the one advancing me.
I need to advance him at least a bit...
Excuse me, Ikuo?
Huh? Yeah...
What shall I do after this?
I can advance anything for you.
Shall we both lie down and relax?
Just kidding!
I-I'll get some drinks!
Ikuo?
I can advance anything for you.
Shall we both lie down and relax?
That smile is totally unfair.
"Shall we both lie down?"
Oh, crap... I haven't even done anything,
and yet it's all going so smoothly,
even in real-life... Is that possible?
Anyway, I've gotta be a gentleman...
I-I'm back...
Oh, thank you.
Oh, dear... Look what you did to me...
S-S-Sorry!
I'm all wet.
Oh, well...
Uh, you should take a shower first!
Huh? O-Okay...
I'm supposed to be advancing Ikuo,
so why am I taking a shower instead?
Wh-What should I do next?
And why was I even summoned
here in the first place?
You should take a shower first!
O-Okay...
Wait... Could it be...
Is this really what I think it is?
What?! No way!
What should I do?
Oh god, what do I do?
What am I supposed to do?
Is that what I'm supposed to be doing here?
Sorry, that was all I had for you to wear.
It's okay...
Um...
Oh, you first.
No, uh...
L-Let's watch TV...
Stare...
Don't mind me. Please continue.
Sorry for the wait!
I'm sorry! Gosh, you're all wet! Um, erm...
I'm sorry about what #1 did.
Oh, it's okay...
Change of clothes.
Oh, thanks.
No peeking!
No touching, either!
Ikuo, I bought some pork buns!
Wait...
What are you...?!
Ikuo
「孫ヽ見せてやりたくてサ…」
"I just wanted you to have grandchildren..."
「先シヤワ一浴ぴときました」
"Don't worry, we showered first."
「あ一いや一その…」
"Uh, well, um..."
「これは違う！違うんだ！」
"This isn't what you think! Really!"
Hey boy! If you want to realize your dreams,
「孫ヽ見せてやりたくてサ…」
"I just wanted you to have grandchildren..."
"Don't worry, we showered first."
Hey boy! If you want to realize your dreams,
「あ一いや一その…」
"Uh, well, um..."
「これは違う！違うんだ！」
"This isn't what you think! Really!"
Hey boy! If you want to realize your dreams,
Listen here, Ikuo...
Just because you're legally an adult now,
Then don't wait around! Just let me know!
that doesn't mean you can bring home girls
in the middle of the day on a weekend...
And to your parents' house...
I mean, I don't mind!
Your dreams will one day
I really don't, but I'd be
so humiliated if the neighbors saw...
create a whole new story for you
And wait, isn't this that "cosplay" thing?
Cosplay? I dunno, but if it were
at least something more normal...
And we'll be there together!
Dad, say something to him!