I lovehate you, lovehate you, baby, yeah!
Hacka Doll
The Animation
You won't find anything ordinary around here!
You have so much information at your fingertips!
Don't be shy and don't run away!
Bang! Bang! Just leave it to us!
C'mon, just be true to your feelings
and let yourself be taken with the flow!
This freedom is finally letting me see
that there are so many choices in front of me
Which one do I pick? Won't you help me choose?
Let's keep touching today, baby!
How do you want to feel?
I can be in the minority or the majority
They're both just as fun to me!
Let's keep touching today, baby!
So won't you softly touch me, baby?
I just can't wait to be with you!
I lovehate you, lovehate you, baby, yeah!
Episode 5: #4 Isn't Just for Show!
Oh, cabbage! How round you are.
Let me tell you a story that started...
Remaining Time
Oh, dear... Look what you did to me...
What are you...?!
They never do anything useful.
Overall Rating
Looks like they need some shoring up.
Our newest model, developed using
cutting-edge technology...
Go forth, Hacka Doll #4!
Find Dolls 1 through 3
and show them how it's done!
The network is vast.
But...
The real world is seriously vast, too!
Where, oh, where could they be?
Hang on a sec, Granny!
Now you can cross all you like!
Wow! I advanced so far!
For real?
Well, what do you know?
Advancing things is super easy!
Okay, let's keep going!
I'll complete my mission while I'm at it!
Convenience Store
Your change is 141 yen.
Did I help advance you?
Huh? Isn't it supposed to be,
"thanks for your business"?
Uh, right...
My change.
Sorry!
I advanced you, didn't I?
Frankfurters
What's going on?
Why do we have so many frankfurters?
Well, you ordered them, didn't you?
Oops! I think the number I ordered
was off by a couple of digits.
You're killing me here!
What if we can't sell all these?
Why don't you eat them?
Don't you giggle at me.
Let me have that.
Found you!
Welcome to our store!
High-spec Personal
Entertainment AI, Hacka Doll #4!
Hacka Doll #4?
So you're #4, the one they say
can advance anything?
Dang right I am!
So they finally finished you! Amazing!
Well? What are you all doing?
The manager asked us to help
advance this convenience store.
It's a part-time job!
We get paid 890 yen per hour.
It's a very at-home work environment.
But we mess up so much that
we can't seem to advance anything.
Advancing things is super easy!
I guess I'll have to show you how it's done, then!
Component Analysis!
Wow! Amazing!
Since you love mobile games, you'll need this!
Wow!
Want to gaze at the sky from Aff with me?
High "Crimson Moai" spawn rates!
So many ultra-super characters!
Since you're hungry...
Delivery for you!
There! All the money you can grab!
Supercars!
Road Roll—
I mean—Supercar!
Amazing! She's advancing left and right!
Convenience Store
#4 isn't just for show.
Mom! I wanna see a shooting star!
Convenience Store
Okay, when it gets dark, we'll look for one.
No! I wanna see one now!
F-F-F-Found you!
The satellite's orbit has mysteriously changed!
The satellite's orbit is changing wildly
Look! It's a shooting star!
How pretty!
What is that?
It's gonna crash into Earth!
Oh, no! This is bad!
What should we do?
We must run.
Sister 0!
Oh, I was just showing them
how advancing is do—
You call that advancing?!
Satellite
#4
Oh. It's back to normal.
The satellite has returned to a stable orbit
#4
Oh man, that hurts...
Hey! Why is my phone bill so high?
How do you expect me
to eat 100 pizzas by myself?
I'm gonna get arrested!
You'd better take responsibility!
Whoa! Wh-Wh-Why?!
Convenience Store
Now then...
W-Welcome to our store...
What's wrong with being happy all the time?
We've got all the time in the world
Let's take that big, first step
and leap into the endless refrain
One, two, three, let's go!