I lovehate you, lovehate you, baby, yeah!
Hacka Doll
The Animation
You won't find anything ordinary around here!
You have so much information at your fingertips!
Don't be shy and don't run away!
Bang! Bang! Just leave it to us!
C'mon, just be true to your feelings
and let yourself be taken with the flow!
This freedom is finally letting me see
that there are so many choices in front of me
Which one do I pick? Won't you help me choose?
Let's keep touching today, baby!
How do you want to feel?
I can be in the minority or the majority
They're both just as fun to me!
Let's keep touching today, baby!
So won't you softly touch me, baby?
I just can't wait to be with you!
I lovehate you, lovehate you, baby, yeah!
Huh?
Huh? It's gone!
It's gone! Totally missing!
Erased from existence!
It's gone! My thing is gone!
Oh, #3!
Oh, #1, this is terrible!
My arms turned into drills!
#3!
#2... Wait, what?!
Are you okay?
I'm not okay!
Indeed. This is an emergency!
The Hacka Doll system
is totally bugging out.
Thanks to this idiot!
Sorry, guys!
We need to restore the system.
Damn it! A call at a time like this?
#3, since you're still okay,
you can go handle it by yourself.
Huh? But I'm not okay.
What's wrong? You look normal to me.
Mumble, mumble, mumble...
What?
Wait, what? What's up?
Your thing?!
There's nothing there!
What thing?!
Am I going to stay a girl forever?
It's definitely a thing of the past now!
That aside, we need to hold out
until the system is restored!
Now, get going!
Episode 6: A Thing of the Past
Young master, I have brought
you some new toys.
There we go.
Who are you?
Let's see... Synchronizing to you,
I'm, erm, Hacka Doll #3.
I, uh, came here to advance you...
or something like that.
Advance...
Um, I came here to help you do
whatever it is you want to do.
So you'll do anything I ask?
Yeah... I guess?
Then play with me!
Huh? That's all you want?
Oh, then I'm totally cool with that.
Butler, put her in normal clothes.
Right away.
Right away!
I'm definitely a girl now...
You look... pretty.
Shut up! I said you look pretty!
I think a flag just went up.
Shut up!
Oh, it looks like we'll be back
to normal by the end of the day.
So until then, be a convincing girl.
So, what are we going to do?
Anything!
Anything fun!
Hey, wanna see me give it everything I've got?
But that just makes me so tired...
I can do it when I try!
Take that!
Remaining until recovery: 5%
Su
shi
Honey, I'm home!
Welcome home.
Dinner isn't ready.
Your bath isn't ready. Nothing's ready.
What? What have you been doing all day?
Sleeping, mostly.
I'm, uh, sorry, darling.
What a hopeless wife you are.
That's right. I'm a hopeless wife.
Today you're playing with
Mom and Dad all day!
#3, everything's sorted out here.
You should return to normal soon.
I guess I'll get going, then.
Young master, the young miss
needs to return home now.
No!
No arguing it.
Don't leave!
But I think I've played enough.
But I'll be alone again!
Alone?
Mom and Dad are always gone,
and I don't have any friends at school.
Do you get lonely?
Of course I'm not lonely!
Hey, stay here a bit longer.
But...
Isn't it fun playing with me?
It is fun, but...
Then live with me forever!
I know! You should marry me!
Huh?
I'll buy you anything you want!
So let's live together forever!
Young master...
Shut up!
Let's go!
We're eloping right now!
Young master!
Hey... Wait a minute!
I... I'm not...
Huh? What's wrong?
Your body is glowing!
I don't think I can stay with you.
Wh-Why not?
Because, well...
Do you hate me?
It's not that...
What is it, then?
You're gonna leave me all alone, too?
Huh? I'm back to normal.
You're...
Hey... Uh...
Look, I'm... actually a...
Huh?
I'm sorry.
Hold on to it until we meet again!
Huh?
Okay.
You better not lose it.
Okay. I won't.
See you later.
Yeah.
That's a promise!