The Altar of Abyss?
That's probably what Felia saw.
Really?
Yeah.
I saw a red castle and a shining ring...
back then!
A red castle...
A red castle, huh?
Well then, why don't we go
to this Altar of Abyss?
Moura, do you know where it is?
But of course.
Sogo!
Are you serious?
We might learn more
about Felia if we go.
How's sitting around and
doing nothing going to help?
Let me accompany you.
No, Kaon!
I cannot approve of this!
Yeah!
Then you two can
twiddle your thumbs here.
In any case, no means no!
We mustn't make
your parents worry any—
Are you listening to me?
Roman... Otto...
I'm really sorry!
A warm light shines upon the ground
With it, that seed can sprout from the earth
There's a magic that can overcome
cold rain, heavy winds, and anything else
So why does it push our backs?
You know we've all had days where we almost gave up
But then a strange power surges from within us,
and we forge ahead like a boy chasing the sun
At the end of the long winter,
spring's warm breath embraces us with the good news
I've been searching for you,
having waited the entire time for this day
Never be afraid of the trust held in your heart
It'll surely come to ease the loneliness one day
So even if you do return to the stars,
let's plant more seeds
Flower Boy
So if we go to this Altar of Abyss,
Felia will stop growing?
She started growing because
her powers began gushing out.
They gushed out!
The spring at the Altar of Abyss
has a fountainhead of highly concentrated
Giftdium, which can replenish her powers.
You can't find that anywhere else!
A fountainhead of Giftdium?
Actually, Moura, weren't you supposed
to be keeping her powers in check?
Sogo, Kaon...
Thanks for coming with me.
No problem.
I can't seem to leave you alone, either.
Yeah.
I'm hungry!
I'm not surprised,
considering how much you've grown.
Grown...
What's got you all mesmerized?
What? Nothing!
Lies. You were staring at her,
like a beast eyeing its prey.
D-Don't be ridiculous!
We should reach a village shortly.
Why don't we grab a bite there?
Look.
It's a wedding.
Wedding?
Er...
It's a ritual that unites
two people in love, I guess?
"In love?"
Love...
Love?
You're such a nice person, Do Mon.
This is our order after all,
so carrying it is the least I can do.
That isn't all.
You've raised Sogo for all these years.
I actually thought he
was your very own son!
No woman would want to
marry a guy like me.
Th-That isn't true!
Keep back!
Roman! Otto!
Who did this to you?
Sogo and the others!
They rode off on our Air Rider,
saying they were going to the Altar of Abyss!
The Altar of Abyss?
Yes, it's me.
Prepare the Valov R7 at once.
I shall explain to Father later!
We've received intel from Honeybee.
I'll have one of our units head over at once.
Target has left Garden Indigo
and is moving towards the Bolvia area.
As you can see,
it's pretty much a direct path.
Their first stop will likely be...
Garden Mauve.
So pretty!
That reminds me...
You've also worn a wedding dress
at some point, right, Kaon?
What are you saying?
Don't be stupid!
Kaon, you're married?
No, I'm not!
She ran away during the fitting.
That was because...
my prince never came to my rescue.
Your prince?
Make way!
A-Are you okay?
Can you stand?
Did you twist your leg?
Are you okay?
I think it's sprained...
You can't walk?
What will we do about the ceremony?
We don't have a replacement
for the flower boy.
An adult doing it would break the tradition.
What do we do, Elene?
Sorry to make you do this.
We know you're busy with your trip.
It's not a problem.
It was our fault to begin with.
We're really sorry.
I've never been a flower boy before...
Good luck, Sogo.
This is for you, then.
Who, me?
If the flower boy and girl are already close,
it's considered more auspicious.
Many couples have gone on
to get married themselves.
Couples?
You're in. Right, Kaon?
Wait, why are you so laid-back?
You're not doing it?
I mean, you and I are...
Friends, right?
It's a huge responsibility.
And the outfit's so frilly and girly.
Then how about Felia instead?
That's a great idea.
I'll do it!
Okay, that's that. Let's do our best.
Um...
Yeah!
Come this way, please.
Let's get the outfit fitted.
I'm sure it'll look great.
No!
I-I mean... It's a wedding, you know?
What if you mess up?
Don't worry. All that's left is to
hold the offerings and walk.
Still...
Should I not?
No, it'll be fine.
I'll teach you what to do!
Please think of it as doing us a favor.
No objections, right, Kaon?
No...
Why'd I have such a rash outburst?
ETA to Garden Mauve?
Approximately two hours.
I'm not about to let
a greenhorn hog all the glory!
I'll have this wrapped up
before Gus shows up.
Our backup hover got hit by
an airstrike en route to here.
We're the only ones still alive...
What do we do?
You're a madman.
They've made their move, Gus!
We got a report from Honeybee.
They're near Garden Mauve.
Dudley's unit went off in pursuit.
We're heading out.
Figures.
You won't let anyone else take out
that mysterious Bipedal Armor, right?
That and I've gotten a tad curious
as to why Zoneboyle's after those kids.
Wow, this is pretty different
from weddings in the city.
Show some self-control.
I can't. It's too delicious.
Kaon?
Not eating? The food's really great.
Oh, thanks.
Think Felia's eaten yet?
No way. She's still changing.
But she was already starving.
Then why don't you go
give the food to her instead?
Felia's a much better match
than a savage like me, right?
What are you talking about?
This isn't like you.
Maybe you're right.
Kaon?
Hey, Kaon!
Even I can tell I'm not being myself.
Still...
I don't know why,
but I can't do anything about it!
You look great, Felia.
Yeah, you're like a princess!
A princess?
Pretty, like a princess.
Um...
What is love?
When you feel as though
someone's joy is your own,
and likewise with their sorrow,
that means you love them.
Who are they?
Felia!
Nobody move a muscle!
We're only looking for someone.
So long as you don't interfere,
we won't harm the people of this Garden!
The Administrative Bureau's Bipedal Armors?
You, the girl with the blue hair!
You're coming with us!
What's the meaning of this?
What has Felia done?
That's classified.
What—
Kaon!
Run for it!
Catch!
Target is escaping through
the church's rear exit!
Tulpa Two, circle around to the west.
Don't let them escape!
Moura!
Is that the unidentified
Bipedal Armor from the reports?
I'm not letting you take Felia!
Thanks, now I can kill
two birds with one stone!
Eat this!
How did they know we were here?
Where'd they go?
Felia, let's swap clothes.
I'll keep them occupied,
so take that chance to flee the village.
Kaon...
I'll be fine.
Even if I get caught,
I'm not the one they're after.
Kaon, I love you!
Elene told me that when you feel
as though someone's joy is your own,
and likewise with their sorrow,
that means you love them.
Felia...
I'm so sorry, Felia!
Kaon? Are you sad?
Was I wrong?
No, I love you, too...
A lot.
Yeah. Same here, Kaon.
Found you!
Blue-haired girl, secured!
Looks like Gus' assistance was not required.
Felia!
Sorry, but you're stuck with me!
Kaon!
Get your hands off my friend!
Hey, now.
I've been ordered not
to hurt any civilians, but...
Kaon!
What?!
Is that...
Sorry to have kept you waiting, gentlemen!
What the heck?
My name is Roman Valov!
In the proud name of the Valov family,
I have come to save the bride!
You're so awesome, Roman!
Quit posing and save Felia already!
Leave it to me!
You moron! What if you hit Felia?
Oh, good point.
Will he come from the right?
Or from above?
Take this!
Valov
Valov Rolling Storm!
Rolling
Valov
Storm
Rolling
Valov
Storm
Rolling
Valov
Storm
Rolling
Valov
Wait, wait—
Felia!
Valov Ultra Super Mount—
Man, that hurt...
Not bad.
You must be their ace pilot!
What?
Secure the target!
On me! Formation Pantera!
Two units coming at once!
Moura!
Take this!
Now!
What?!
All right!
What the hell?
The reports said it's specialized for CQC!
How dare you interrupt my wedding!
Yeah! Get out!
Didn't your mother
teach you any manners?
Curse you!
Get out of here!
Fall back!
All hands, retreat!
Are you all right, Kaon?
Would you look at that?
It's a prince and his princess.
Yeah.
The guys that ran ahead
had the tables turned on them.
I can't say I'm too fond of spies,
but work is work.
Isn't that right,
Agent Honeybee?
Waking up to a new morning every day,
The first thing I tell myself
Is that I love this world
I really, really do
When the light calls for me
I want to reach it even if it's on my bare feet
Don't stop me
I'll go further and further
One step at a time
To look for it
Let's go on an adventure
Past this door that our hearts dream of
Another fun day starts, so let's go
I want to chase those clouds I saw
I wonder where it went?
I want to catch it soon
Let's go as all this fun bursts out
I'll run after it no matter how far it is
I think I'll be able to do it if it's with you
Because with you by my side,
I won't be scared of anything
In the midst of the journey,
the long arm of evil closes in.
What lies hidden in
human hearts, in their feelings?
Next time, on Comet Lucifer:
Place of Warmth.
Place of Warmth
Grab a ticket and join us on this adventure!