Welcome!
My, what an adorable little mascot!
Two more lunch set A's please.
Got it.
The Napolitan's almost done.
The Napolitan wait is over!
Wow.
What an amusing magic trick.
Thanks for the wonderful service.
How did you do that?
Yummy!
We interrupt this song
to bring you breaking news.
For the first time in forty years,
the Meteorological Department
has announced that it has
detected a typhoon forming.
The typhoon is predicted to hit
Garden Indigo within two or three days,
and the Meteorological Department
urges utmost caution for all residents.
What to do? What should I do first?
I repeat...
For starters, we should stay closed tomorrow.
No time to waste!
What's wrong, Do Mon?
It's coming.
A typhoon is coming!
A warm light shines upon the ground
With it, that seed can sprout from the earth
There's a magic that can overcome
cold rain, heavy winds, and anything else
So why does it push our backs?
You know we've all had days where we almost gave up
But then a strange power surges from within us,
and we forge ahead like a boy chasing the sun
At the end of the long winter,
spring's warm breath embraces us with the good news
I've been searching for you,
having waited the entire time for this day
Never be afraid of the trust held in your heart
It'll surely come to ease the loneliness one day
So even if you do return to the stars,
let's plant more seeds
Storm
What about you?
Have you figured out where Lima is?
Storm
You think you can get away with this?
Talk about a bait-and-switch!
Seriously, are you gonna be of any use at all?
How dare you disrespect me?
Oh? Any signs of movement since then?
Keep mouthing off like that...
And I'll kill you.
Yeah, that should be more than enough intel.
We'll handle the rest.
The typhoon is maintaining its course.
It is predicted to hit Garden Indigo
the day after tomorrow.
I wonder what's going to happen...
Look how badly Do Mon's panicking.
Things might get crazy!
Where are my boots?!
I won't be going anywhere without them!
Hey, hey!
Oh, it's the costume
we bought the other day.
You look adorable.
Could you return those to Do Mon?
He says they're important.
Important?
Those boots.
No!
What's a typhoon, anyway?
Well...
Massive clouds will cover the skies,
and from within them,
monsters will appear...
Monsters are the least of our worries.
I was eight when it happened...
Rain pelted down like bullets.
Thunder pierced the heart.
Howling winds shook entire buildings!
And in the midst of that storm,
I was heading home, dripping from head to toe,
when a girl offered me her umbrella.
She had the most charming smile.
Oh...
So charming...
Wait, it's already this late?
Felia's nodded off, too.
I never imagined I'd meet her at a
neighborhood café when I was sixteen.
Her name was Michiko.
Such a sweet name, right?
What am I gonna do with her? Come on...
I couldn't even look her in the eye.
It was what you'd call a first love...
I'm turning off the lights.
But in hindsight, it was the
typhoon that sparked it all.
Ah, the memories!
Michiko!
You guys just don't get it.
While it may be analog,
this is the most efficient method.
Here's the footage from
security cameras all over Indigo.
For now, I'm looking at
footage from three days ago.
So...
What's this Lima of yours look like?
Zoom in on that!
Oh, my sweet little kitten...
Huh? Who cares about that?
That's the Lima.
Huh?
Seriously?
Okay!
Shall we begin?
Sogo and Kaon,
chop the wood over there to measure.
Yes, sir!
Gotcha.
Felia, could you take those
potted plants inside?
Potted plants!
I wanna knock-knock, too!
Felia, quit using your powers
for every little thing!
What was that?!
You used your powers, didn't you?
Wood coming up.
I don't need this.
By the way,
you kids haven't gotten mixed up
in anything dangerous, have you?
No, we're okay.
Really? Glad to hear it.
Good day, miss.
I have to go pick veggies for dinner.
Could you lend me a hand?
Veggies?
Okay!
Yummy!
That's an idea...
Pick some for everyone.
Some for everyone?
Okay!
Oh, it's Vee.
Huh? Vee—
Ow!
S-Sorry about that!
Sorry?
Oh, Do Mon!
I've brought your usual order.
Oh, thanks.
What are you doing up there?
Preparing for the typhoon.
I'll take a look at your place later, too.
Really? That would be great!
I'll leave the bread inside, okay?
I hear you are repairing the roof.
Why was I not called?!
What is that thing?
The pinnacle of the Valov family's technology.
I present the Valov R7!
No, not that...
Wh-What's going on?
This is a black cow of
the finest breed, Alexandra III.
Having been fed on the highest quality grain,
her meat is as tender as possible.
Right...
There you are.
Did you find something good, my little kitten?
We've found the Garden where Lima is,
but narrowing down the exact location will take time.
And you do look so sweet
while you work, mademoiselle...
If there's no time,
then do your part and gather intel, too.
What a degenerate.
It lacks visual impact.
Allow me to demonstrate my aesthetic sense!
Okay, listen carefully, Roman.
First, hit the startup switch at the top right.
Startup switch, on.
The right lever...
The right lever, roger!
...launches the R7 at high-speed, so don't touch it!
Watch out!
The brake is on the left lever!
Run for it!
In the end, we finished before dinner.
Thanks, you guys.
This calls for a celebration party then, right?
Yeah!
Party!
Now, partake of this meat I barbecued.
Surely, it must be delicious,
for I was the one who barbecued it.
Right now, I'm in the mood for veggies.
I'll save the meat for later.
You mustn't!
This freshly barbecued meat will get cold.
Huh?
I'm free to eat what I want, aren't I?
No, such selfishness is unbecoming!
For you are my fiancée.
Didn't I tell you to stop
talking to me like that?
I haven't agreed to that!
Felia, did you just eat some?
Nope!
But your mouth...
Cheers!
Like I care about what our families wish for...
To hell with that nonsense.
Something on your mind?
Well,
I finally thought I'd found it, you know...
Oh, crystals again?
You've got it good, Sogo.
You can immerse yourself
in something you love.
No, not yet.
There's something I want to do.
Don't hold back! Eat all you want!
Okay.
So good!
You picked these veggies, didn't you, Felia?
Yep!
Oh, right. You missed something amazing.
The veggies were, like, dancing!
It was such a pretty sight...
They were going wild in mid-air!
Dancing? Mid-air?
You have such an ability?
Do demonstrate for me, won't you?
I wanna see, too.
Yeah, make something fly again.
You have some explaining to do!
Felia!
All that anger's made me hungry.
Is there any curry to end the party?
This is the perfect way
to mark the dawn of a new era.
Truly the winds of change.
Such is the will of the heavens.
May our Gift be blessed by prosperity.
And who better to lead it
than you, brilliant sages of the Council?
The gates have been opened.
It is our fated duty to welcome
the angel of the celestial land,
along with the child of miracle.
Hurry up, Sogo.
Hey, that's my breakfast!
It's your fault for waking up so late.
Why, you little...
We won't make it unless we leave now!
Okay, I get it!
Felia?
Party!
Sorry, we've got school today.
Party! No school!
No can do.
Let me go, Felia.
Felia, we must go to school today,
no matter what.
See you later.
Bye.
Stop it!
What have we here?
Looks like you have a naughty side, Felia.
Sogo at school. No party.
Yeah.
Yesterday's party was fun, right?
Yep...
Well, another time.
I need to take a look at Vee's place, too.
Felia, could you keep watch for a while?
I'll put up a "closed" sign,
so I don't think any customers will come.
Keep watch?
Yeah, keep watch.
I'm counting on you.
Okay!
Sorry.
Wow!
Something wrong?
No, I was just remembering something.
It says school's closed today.
Huh?
But we can't go home in this rain...
Let's take shelter here for a while, and then go.
Oh, what did you remember earlier?
Ah...
A memory of Mom.
I remember her talking
to me in a place like this.
About what?
A red crystal.
But nobody believed her.
That's why...
I'll prove to them
that it's out there somewhere.
So this is a typhoon.
Sogo?
What's this? All alone?
Let's get to it, then.
What? Are you scared?
Be gentle, Pack.
She's an important guest of ours.
Okay...
Watch this crumble.
Don't!
I love the sound of those cries!
What's wrong?
I need to hurry home.
You're gonna get soaked.
No biggie!
Sogo!
No!
Stop right there!
Felia must be terrified.
I'm back...
Wha—
What the hell happened here?
Sogo, Felia's in big trouble!
These sounds filling up my heart
wouldn't form into words
I just kept staring at you
But even then I felt a connection
and I wanted to always stay by your side
so I reached out with my hands
Even just touching you
fills me with so much joy
Where do these feelings come from?
I don't understand them
Tell me, my one and only
There are so many fun things to do
It just makes me want to dance
I'm so excited I think I'll just let myself go
So hold me, hold me
With all you've got
The doors of fate are unlocked,
by the two who care for each other.
Next time, on Comet Lucifer:
Embracing Souls.
Embracing Souls
Grab a ticket and join us on this adventure!