We have to make our way
through a place like this?
It's really slippery, so be careful!
Hey, Sogo...
What are these floating stones?
Maybe they're related to that ring.
Felia?
It feels strange.
I don't remember any of this,
but it all seems so familiar.
Are you sure this is the right way, Moura?
Hmm... It should be, but...
A warm light shines upon the ground
With it, that seed can sprout from the earth
There's a magic that can overcome
cold rain, heavy winds, and anything else
So why does it push our backs?
You know we've all had days where we almost gave up
But then a strange power surges from within us,
and we forge ahead like a boy chasing the sun
At the end of the long winter,
spring's warm breath embraces us with the good news
I've been searching for you,
having waited the entire time for this day
Never be afraid of the trust held in your heart
It'll surely come to ease the loneliness one day
So even if you do return to the stars,
let's plant more seeds
The Altar of Abyss
Felia!
Are you all right?
Y-Yes.
Are you sure you're okay?
Your face is all red.
Maybe you have a fever.
What the...
Hey, what's going on? This looks bad.
Hey, Roman! Shouldn't we stick together?
You're looking pretty flushed.
Are you sure you're feeling all right?
I'm not sure... My face feels hot.
Do you have a fever?
No.
When Sogo touches me, I feel hot...
And it feels really fluttery here!
I see.
Am I sick?
Don't worry.
It probably isn't the bad kind of sickness.
You'll understand eventually.
Do Mon's car...
Do Mon?
Do Mon!
It's amazing!
That's the Altar of Abyss?
Apparently, yes!
We can trust you on that, right?
Our destination lies right before us!
Let us make haste!
W-Wait, Roman.
It's getting dark, so trying to get
down this ledge is dangerous.
He's right. Let's rest tonight
and depart in the morning.
Second that. My feet are killing me!
Indeed.
You haven't walked at all!
God damn it!
Incoming transmission from Honeybee.
Bring it up.
Wha—
Do Mon's... dead?
Sogo!
Sogo?
Oh, Felia... Gimme a sec.
Ow...
Are you okay?
Yeah...
What's that?
I had Otto look it up.
If you boil this and drink it,
it apparently lowers a fever.
You got this for me?
Yeah. I'll make it for you later.
Sogo...
Are you awake, Kaon?
Huh?
There's something I'd like to discuss.
What? You sound all serious.
We have no idea what lies ahead.
Of course, our safe return
is far from guaranteed.
That is precisely why
I want to set things straight.
Kaon, I am calling off our engagement.
Eh?
I would like you to respect your feelings.
You're honestly saying that now?
But thank you.
You should also be with someone you love,
rather than marrying for family, Roman.
Indeed, that is my every intention.
However, the one I truly love
is you.
If we are able to return safely,
I plan to court you once more.
So please be prepared!
We finally made it this far.
Yeah, it's all thanks to you, Sogo.
It's not just me. It's because of everyone.
And most importantly,
it's because you never gave up, Felia.
The rocks are moving again!
I don't think you need to be worried.
R-Really?
They're beautiful.
Ever since I was little,
I've been searching for the red crystal.
At first, I thought you might be a clue to it,
and nothing more.
If I had stayed in Indigo,
I'd never have been able to see this.
And not only this...
Snow-covered plains.
Strangely colored forests and valleys.
And the town in the oasis...
The bride was so pretty!
We've been in some scary situations,
but I'm really thankful I met you
and was able to go on this journey!
Sogo...
You'll understand eventually.
When we get back, there's somewhere
I want to go with you, Felia.
We haven't gone to the Verdant Valley yet.
Sogo...
I-I... Sogo, I think I...
Whoa! I found even more!
See? Even more are blooming over here!
What's wrong?
Oh, it's nothing.
Weren't you trying to say something?
I'll tell you when we get back.
We're finally here...
That doesn't mean we're done.
Don't lower your guard.
I'm sure the Altar lies beyond these doors.
All right! Sogo and Otto, let us push!
Right.
Okay.
Ready... push!
Felia?
So the entrance was here?
Felia!
What is this place?
These ruins...
Is that the Red Palace?
Felia!
Sogo, are you all right?
Are the ruins rejecting us?
What's happening?
I have no idea.
At last, the time has come
for my power to be realized.
How long have I waited for this very moment?
All that remains is for you to come to me.
I welcome you,
Lima!
What the...
That's...
A black Moura?
Felia!
Let's go, Moura!
What the heck was that?
I have no idea.
Anyway, we're going after it!
Don't forget that Felia is in there!
I-I know that!
Where'd it go?
Sogo...
Sogo!
Can you still move, Moura?
Of course!
Now!
Sogo!
Stop!
I am the angel's guardian.
Therefore, you will not be harmed.
However, I must inquire...
Why do you obsess over one human so?
Sogo is important to me.
That's why...
Do you mean you wish to save him?
Please... If you save Sogo,
I'll do whatever you say.
So please!
Come with me.
I have but one goal: to acquire you.
Okay.
I'll go with you...
Felia, I'll save you soon, just wait...
Don't follow me.
Huh?
Please, just leave me alone!
Felia... Why?
Why?!
Moura, please tell me...
Each planet has only one angel
and one guardian, right?
Then who was that?
Who the hell was that?
I... I...
I don't know, either!
You don't know?
Then, why did Felia say that?
Vee?
Sogo, there's a call from Vee.
Sogo?
Please listen to this calmly.
Do Mon is...
It can't be true.
The people you're going
up against are soldiers.
If you keep going, you'll die.
It's all my fault...
It was just like Do Mon said.
I was just a naive kid...
I was never capable of
protecting Felia in the first place.
Do you really mean that?
Does the resolve you showed
Do Mon break that easily?!
Say what you want...
I can't do this anymore!
If I'd only listened to Do Mon,
he wouldn't be dead right now!
It would've been better
if I had died instead!
Listen up.
The childhood friend I know
is justice personified.
He did everything he could
to save those dear to him,
and I love him because of that!
That's why I don't want to see you...
depressed and crying like that!
Right now, I'm going to go save Felia!
What about you?
Do you even have to ask?
Moura!
Will you help me one more time?
But of course!
Don't leave
This warmth
Which lies within me
Don't leave
My memories
Light up the path to tomorrow
Even if my wish to be with you
Will lead to nothing but loneliness
I'll still embrace you
Because I want to become one with you
Even if the day comes
For these hands that once connected us to separate
I'll continue to embrace you
Our lives will remain connected
Even if we're separated
We'll meet again some day
For the sake of the planet, for everyone.
That is why there is nothing to fear.
However, just one more time...
Next time, on Comet Lucifer:
The Fallen Angel.
The Fallen Angel
Grab a ticket and join us on this adventure!