Don't follow me.
Huh?
Please, just leave me alone!
Why?!
Right now, I'm going to go save Felia!
Moura! Will you help me one more time?
Do help yourself.
It seems I have grown quite senile.
Here I am, playing house with a stone.
Are my friends all right?
Intriguing.
It's almost as though you have a heart.
What is this place?
Why did you bring me here?
I am not the one who needs you.
It's all of us, the humans on this planet,
Lima.
I never thought you'd have such
a lovely appearance. You truly seem alive.
It is a shame that I shall have to destroy you.
A warm light shines upon the ground
With it, that seed can sprout from the earth
There's a magic that can overcome
cold rain, heavy winds, and anything else
So why does it push our backs?
You know we've all had days where we almost gave up
But then a strange power surges from within us,
and we forge ahead like a boy chasing the sun
At the end of the long winter,
spring's warm breath embraces us with the good news
I've been searching for you,
having waited the entire time for this day
Never be afraid of the trust held in your heart
It'll surely come to ease the loneliness one day
So even if you do return to the stars,
let's plant more seeds
The Fallen Angel
Jupiter to Ibis One and Two.
Weapons hot! I repeat, weapons hot!
Use of firearms authorized!
Ibis One and Two are poised to intercept.
Proceeding to engage—
Is that it, Moura?
Yes. I can sense Felia's thoughts!
Is she all right?
She is...
But she seems frightened.
I'll be there right away, Felia!
Behind us, Sogo!
Thanks, Roman!
Don't get complacent, Sogo!
There are more on their way!
An area shield?
Vee was right.
Felia has been captured by Fongerufu.
But what would the Bureau's
research division want with her?
We didn't anticipate
their use of an area shield...
How do we get inside now?
However we can!
I'm sure Felia is waiting for us!
Can you sense it, too?
I don't need to be able to sense it to know!
That'll do.
Now's our chance! We're charging in!
It's starting to regenerate!
Hurry, Moura!
They won't make it!
Open up!
What's wrong, Moura?
Sogo! Moura!
Can you hear me?
Please answer!
As soon as they breached
the area shield, we lost contact?
Ow... The hell?
Quiet.
A Bipedal Armor is incoming!
Uh...
Why are you spacing out?
Mind if I ask something?
What is it?
You are Miss Moura, I presume?
Why are you acting so distant?
Wh-Wh-Wha—?
What the heck?!
So you came.
I see...
Those two should be okay, right?
They haven't been taken out or anything?
I cannot tell.
Then we should go in, too.
They have deployed an area shield.
We cannot enter.
Finally found it!
The shield's being generated
by a facility west of the Bureau!
If we destroy it...
Is Felia in there?
I can sense her.
But why did you take that form?
That shield is interfering
with my exoskeleton transformation.
Right...
No!
Stop it...
How amusing.
Her cries are exactly like that of a human's.
But that, in itself, is an impurity.
A blemish on the pure crystal,
blessed with the power to elevate our motherland,
Gift, and humanity to even greater heights.
I'm a stone?
We are almost at the antenna.
If we destroy that thing, the area shield
covering Fongerufu will disappear, right?
Yeah.
Step on it, Roman!
Understood!
Hostiles detected!
What do we do?
Stop right there!
I'm glad I made it in time!
Vee!
Why are you here?
Covering in Do Mon's stead, I guess?
Felia's probably being held on the top floor!
Go!
Got it!
Here we go.
Right.
It was the least I could do
to make it up to him.
Though I suppose it's a bit late for that.
Man, I should have told him sooner.
You are a blighted pebble.
Thus, I shall cleanse your body of the
impurities it has come in contact with,
and return it to its purest form.
Me? A stone?
No!
I mean, they taught me
about so many emotions!
Happiness,
enjoyment,
cheerfulness,
excitement,
and then...
And then...
Such things are naught but deceit.
Sorrow, anxiety, anger, and fear.
They are all fabrications
that were planted within you,
filthy vestiges of humanity.
But once the power hidden
within you is cleansed,
you can lead this planet,
and humanity, to great prosperity.
Once you are returned to your true form.
My true form?
The concentrated crystallization of the angel—
a fragment of Lucifer.
Lucifer?
We're getting closer.
Felia is in this building, for sure.
Let's hurry to the top floor!
Damn it!
That Bipedal Armor...
The humiliation you caused me back then...
Let me repay you in kind, right here and now.
These guys followed us all the way here?
What the hell is the meaning of this, Gus Stewart?
Have you lost your mind?!
I'd say that I've regained it, actually.
I'm no longer serving as the Bureau's lapdog!
Are you sure that Do Mon's murderer
is somewhere in this facility, Al?
From intelligence satellites
to vehicle drive recorders...
All the sensors on this planet are my eyes.
None can escape my gaze.
I'm not doing this to help you!
I merely wish to walk down
the path I've chosen.
Hey! Quit dawdling around by my feet!
Get going!
Let's go, Moura!
All right!
This is nothing compared to
the opponents we've faced up until now!
Lucifer is the highly purified,
concentrated crystallization of the angel's spirit.
And its fragments can transform Gift
into a planet without conflict or disparity,
an unblemished world where
all are equal and prosperous!
I see.
I can't go back to them anymore.
And I went and said something so stupid,
without even knowing that.
Sogo...
Felia's feelings are fading fast!
Damn it all!
Felia...
It was the warmest of voices.
Sogo released me from the cold darkness.
He was kind and gentle.
The wish that has endured for millennia.
At last, my longstanding desire will be fulfilled.
The time has come for Lucifer to descend upon us!
It appears we are under attack.
Sogo...
You came for me?
Sogo?
The intruder is Amagi Sogo,
Ena's son?
This, too, is a meeting of destiny
that our planet arranged.
Or, perhaps, a twist of fate.
Anatolia,
he is my honored guest.
Treat him as such.
Y-You...
How laughable...
Truly a sight befitting
the people of a foolish planet.
Felia!
Sogo...
I shall take this boy's life before your very eyes.
Bereft of all hope, Lucifer will be purified.
Allow me to grant you the ultimate despair.
To bring about a more
prosperous world and to unleash
your true power.
Sogo!
Even without using that power,
Felia's helped make Gift plenty prosperous!
Who said I was talking about Gift?
You insult me by lumping me in
with Zoneboyle and his ramblings!
What I wish for is paradise.
To bring light to a new, utopian planet...
A new planet?
Do you not see it?
It is already almost upon us.
Felia!
Sogo?
Just wait! I'll save you right away!
Stop!
Stop, damn you!
Hang in there, Felia!
Back then, I should have chased after you!
I'm such a fool!
Indeed.
For is it not natural that a foolish
planet be populated by fools?
How unfortunate for you.
Gift's angel has fallen.
Felia!
Fall into ruin, fools,
together with your foolish land.
You're...
Sogo!
I'm going to save Felia, no matter what!
Don't leave
This warmth
Which lies within me
Don't leave
My memories
Light up the path to tomorrow
Even if my wish to be with you
Will lead to nothing but loneliness
I'll still embrace you
Because I want to become one with you
Even if the day comes
For these hands that once connected us to separate
I'll continue to embrace you
Our lives will remain connected
Even if we're separated
We'll meet again some day
There are precious people
who must be protected.
For the sake of the day
when I can see you smile.
Next time, on Comet Lucifer:
The Boy and the Planet.
The Boy and
the Planet
The final destination,
and also a new beginning.