Love Tours
Takumi and Natsuko   Part 1
In May, the ski resort
is still covered in snow.
It looks like we can keep it open for a while longer.
The paths on the snow-covered
mountains around here
serve as fantastic beginner courses
for us new to skiing.
As for the parking lot in front of the lodge,
it's used for time-trial practice during the off season.
Um, excuse me.
I think the vending machine is broken.
Um...
Did it have any contact information?
Huh? Good question, I'm not sure.
I believe the supplier operates it directly.
Come on, have a quick look, pretty please?
You don't look very busy anyway.
Well, I'm not, but...
What about the vending machine?
This thing's one of the largest in Japan, right?
Though it's Swiss technology.
The gondolas were constructed
entirely in Switzerland.
It's incredible.
I'd love to see it in action.
Why not come here to ski?
It seems to be in operation the entire winter.
Yeah, that sounds like a good idea.
By the way, when you get on a gondola here,
make sure you sit on the ski slope side.
Huh?
There's something amazing to see there,
on a clear day, if you're lucky.
Oh right, the vending machine.
Yup. My 130 yen.
Warm
You like machines, right?
If only you were a bit more familiar
with how vending machines work.
Once the money's inserted, press a button.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
It's moving!
Let me on!
I can't do that.
I don't have permission to let people on as I please.
Pretty please! I want to go up!
There's something I just have to see!
Huh?
Just this once!
You're good at driving cars, huh?
Oh, please.
I know you think I'm bad at it.
Not at all!
I could never drive like that!
Yeah, that's true.
And I couldn't drive a motorbike like you do.
Motorbikes and cars are just
means of transportation.
They're more than that to me.
Well, it's not like I don't understand
what makes machines fun.
I guess so.
Otherwise you wouldn't be doing a job like this.
And I like nature, too.
I work at the Inokuchi Camellia Hall.
What? Really?
It's amazing how many camellias they have.
I love the camellias there!
Yeah, it comes across.
But in the end I don't like to rely on machines.
You prefer to climb using your own legs.
Huh?
I see you climb up every now and then.
On the ski slope.
You were watching?!
Hey, I don't go around spying on people.
I just happened to...
That was a lie. I was looking at you the whole time.
And I really wanted to see this.
The view you love so much.
Huh?
The vending machine
breaking down was a lie too.
Sorry.
What?!
On a snowy hill where red flowers bloom
You almost seem like pure light to me
A cold breath
Brushes past
On a white hill that goes on forever
You almost seem like you're infinite to me
Our hands meet
Let's stay like this
If you ever feel like crying, come to me
It would be our very own secret
Just like the wide sky and the sun
I want to stay next to you forever
And ever