Love Tours
Takumi and Natsuko   Part 2
Inokuchi Camellia Hall
Oh, hello.
Hm? If you're looking for Natsuko,
she's in the greenroom.
I can't believe these camellias were
collected from all over the world by the same person.
It must have taken a lot of time, work, and money.
And even more important than any of those:
A tremendous amount of curiosity.
He must have been a serious eccentric.
Huh? You're here already?
Oh right, it's already this late.
Hang on, I'll wrap up the remaining work real quick.
Then I can head out.
That scared me.
He just appeared out of nowhere.
Did he see me?
I first met him by the gondola lift at a ski resort.
He's a big fan of nature.
And not just nature,
but nature that's been touched by humans.
I can't put it very well, but he's a bit strange.
Lately I've started to understand
how he thinks and acts better.
Looking at this, I stop caring about how
much is nature and how much is artificial.
It feels stupid to even try to make the distinction.
This is so great.
I love stuff like this.
I've heard that a million times before.
Yes, I know very well that he likes this.
But there's something that I'm not so sure on.
Look, there's something there!
What is that?
There you go again.
Last time it was just a shrub.
And before that,
it was something floating in the water.
How does he feel about me?
This is the first hobby we've shared.
In free climbing, you climb natural or artificial
rock walls without aids like pitons or ladders,
using just your own arms and legs.
The rope you attach to your body is just for safety.
Does he really love me?
He's very cautious.
It won't get him much higher,
but he'll use the safer red grip by his left leg and...
He didn't.
He's different from usual today.
What's gotten into you?
You've never been this adventurous...
Th-This is...
Right, that thing.
Uh... Huh?
That thing, as in that thing?
He saw me!
Well...
I...
I wanted to try it too.
Pervert.
What did you just call me?
Pervert!
I'm not a pervert, okay?
I just... I just...
I just love you!
I just really love you!
I'm not a pervert in any way!
R
V
Wild Camellia Garden
Greenhouse
Entrance
On a snowy hill where red flowers bloom
You almost seem like pure light to me
A cold breath
Brushes past
On a white hill that goes on forever
You almost seem like you're infinite to me
Our hands meet
Let's stay like this
If you ever feel like crying, come to me
It would be our very own secret
Just like the wide sky and the sun
I want to stay next to you forever
And ever