Love Tours
Haruki and Aoi   Part 2
Man, this sucks.
So our group is going to Taira and Kamitaira...
Not exactly exciting.
Don't complain!
This is a good opportunity
to learn some local history!
Whatever.
It's pretty intense looking on this close.
Weren't you complaining
that it was gonna be boring?
Shut up.
Wow.
The kokiriko dance originates from traditional
dengaku dance, and is a form of harvest dance.
To pray for a good harvest,
and as a display of gratitude to the farmers,
professional dancers referred to as dengaku monks
would perform it while the rice farmers rested.
The lyrics were originally improvised.
Some would sing of love, others of their parents.
They reflected the feelings of the commoners
and farmers as they went through—
Love songs, huh?
Isn't this cute?
It's painfully obvious she's avoiding you.
Aoi, I mean.
It's been, what, three months
since you started dating?
Four months!
An Inami Specialty
Inaka
Manju
Before we'd go to school together,
but now she goes alone.
We've only been on a date twice,
and she seemed kind of distant during both.
Love, huh?
Maybe I shouldn't have told her.
Huh?
Wow, that's crazy.
Check them out.
Something's definitely going on there.
I know it'll suit you! You should buy it!
Y-You think?
Okay, guess I'll buy it!
Excuse me, we'd like these!
All right, the next hour is free time.
Okay!
This place is really amazing.
Like something out of a folk tale.
Yeah...
Are you looking for Haruki?
Huh?
Hey, Aoi.
You're not worrying about me and Haruki, are you?
N-No! That's not...
Reception
If you are, please stop.
He turned me down.
And I have someone else I'm interested in.
No, you've got it wrong.
That's not it.
Huh?
You see, I've actually liked Haru
ever since we were little.
But I didn't think he had any interest in me.
So I thought it was best not to tell him.
Because I didn't want to ruin our friendship.
But now that we're actually going out,
it's nothing like how we were before.
I'm too embarrassed to even look Haru in the eyes.
I'm happy that I'm his girlfriend now,
but I can't help feeling our
relationship really did change.
Maybe it really was better not to tell him.
It made me really happy, though.
I was happy too, but...
Huh?
What?!
N...
No, no, no!
Pretend you didn't hear anything!
I refuse.
What's wrong?
I'm so embarrassed.
Just bury me in the snow.
In that case...
I'll do something even more embarrassing.
What?
Kokiriko, Haruki here
Huh? What?
Wait, stop!
What's gotten into you, Haru?
is in love with Aoi!
N-No, stop!
This is too embarrassing!
Go away.
Who cares if they hear?
I mean, I...
...am in love with Aoi!
No, no, stop!
Haru!
That hurt...
...less than I expected.
Snow's pretty neat, actually.
Oh, you...
Nothing's changed between us.
H-Haru?
Being boyfriend and girlfriend...
means wanting to be closer
to each other than anyone else, right?
But that's how we were
even before we started dating.
Nothing's changed.
Free time is about to end!
C'mon, let's hurry, Aoi.
I love you as well!
This is not a mistake
In that moment
I felt my pulse change
Do you know?
Are you waiting for it?
Despite its cowardice
My heart can take to the sky
Why do I feel a nervous sensation
Running through my whole body?
I can't express it very well
But I need to tell you
Today, tomorrow, and forever more
I'm drawn to you
When I'm next to you
My feelings start to take shape
With your special tune
Let me hear it once again
Our new lives have left the starting line