Love Tours
Yoji and Chiaki   Part 1
We've decided to break up.
It's not that we've fallen out of love.
"It depicts the 49 days between
death and rebirth", huh...
It's really intense.
Hey, check this out, Chiaki.
Hm?
Those statues are doing it.
You're asking for trouble.
Come on, doing it is a sacred act.
You've just got lewd goggles on.
That's my Chiaki.
An unfaltering elbow.
Why, thank you.
Yoji, don't just leave your slippers like that.
Oops.
Are you going to be all right on your own?
Well, I'm sure I'll figure something out.
Come on, we gotta hurry.
They're probably serving
tempura at the restaurant, right?
Don't want it to get cold.
We've been together for five years.
I had forgotten that a day like this could come.
Huh?
A transfer?
Yeah, we've already sorted it out.
The terms are pretty good.
I've always wanted to try living by the ocean.
I grew up in the mountains, after all.
Oh?
So, what do we do?
What do you mean?
I can't do long distance.
I just can't.
That caught me off guard.
I hadn't considered Chiaki at all.
You make it sound worse than it is.
It's just an hour by car.
Besides, we've already been together for five years.
So... You want to break up?
I guess so.
Yes.
I was caught off guard.
And...
Huh...
Well, if you say so.
And now we're on a break-up trip.
We're not breaking up because we dislike each other.
We're ending it on a bright note.
We're going to the first place
we visited together: Toyama.
The travel plans...
Was it really a good idea to leave it all to you?
Don't worry, I've got it.
You've always handled our trips before.
It's my turn to take care of...
Crap, this thing's got fern in it.
What? Fine, I'll eat it.
Oh, you can't eat this either, right?
The butterbur.
I ate so many wild plants as a kid
that my body started rejecting them.
Why didn't you check what food
they're serving in advance?
Here, you can have this instead.
Awesome, nice trade.
Toga
Soba
Museum
Well what am I supposed to do?
Let's eat.
Yeah, let's.
Yeah, this is good.
I love butterbur.
How can you not stand this?
Gottsuo-kan
Nakajimaya
You sure are obsessed with me.
What that's supposed to mean?
We've been together for so long I know things
about you that I didn't even want to know.
That's all.
Hey.
Hm?
Are you wearing make-up today?
Huh? Well, yeah...
You just look so pretty.
Don't give me that.
Well, whatever.
So? Where are we?
Well, I heard they do plays here.
That's strange...
It's not like they perform every day, you know.
Oh, that's true.
You really don't research enough in advance.
What's the decisive factor
that caused us to break up?
Well, that'd be my transfer.
That much is obvious.
But what should I have said?
But... Then...
She was saying that it felt like
her work was finally paying off.
I can't force her to come with me.
I am in love with you.
Please, won't you marry me?
I had hoped you'd ask!
Yoji!
Let's get going.
It's getting chilly.
You're not used to those boots, are you?
Sorry.
What do you say about holding hands for a bit?
Huh?
Just one last time.
Yeah.
This is our last time.
As though I had forgotten how to speak
I thought everything had disappeared
The view I saw though the window
Started shining more gently than ever before
Things like promises or rules
We hadn't made any, yet
Despite how awkward we were with each other
Our feelings always resonated so well
Our own little world
And the path we walked to get there
Forever may they go on
Now I can tell you how I truly feel