A Certain Magical Index
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
Carrying a ticking time bomb
The Earth keeps on turning, so hurry up!
No one can pretend it's not their business anymore
Suddenly common sense is out the door
Opposing fates fail to reach each other
Drenched in the rain of resentment
But why? Fear and doubt keep building up heavy in my heart
My racing heart is flooded with ambition
Ready!
Everyone that's drawn to this place
Has gone beyond the meaning and color of desire
My heart wants to stay strong
I feel it deep inside me
With all my soul, this one thing
Dive into a heart
C-Document
My, my! What's wrong?
I expected you to provide
some more entertainment.
Change precedence.
The air before the spear's movement.
Shit!
I'm alive!
How?
Was this a different kind of attack than before?
Flour?
Does that weapon work by interacting
with the Body of Christ?
Oh, so even Easterners are aware of this?
Normally there should be no way
for a mere human to kill the Son of God.
But the Son of God needed to be killed
in order to atone for the sins of humanity.
To achieve that, the precedence of the Son of God
and normal humans needed to be changed.
Yes, that secret technique that was used
to complete the legend of the Son of God
is what constitutes my spell
"Execution of Light".
I get it now!
Because the blade of flour
was given precedence over the wall,
it gained a lot of destructive power.
Because the air was given precedence over the spear,
Itsuwa's charge was stopped in its tracks.
So this is what God's Right Seat can do?
Faced with that spell, strength
and weakness lose their meaning.
What's wrong?
Attack me or run away. Do something.
I'll give you ten seconds.
Use it to form a plan.
If you can come up with anything, that is.
Ten seconds are enough
to come up with about three plans.
Change precedence!
Human skin before magic!
Tsuchimikado!
Sorry I took so long, Kamiyan.
Don't tell me you thought
that could possibly defeat me.
Sorry, but your back's against the wall.
My next move will be a checkmate.
You think you can hurt me with that toy?
Change precedence!
Human skin before bullets!
I told you. That's checkmate.
Damn it! Did they have to do that?
I see.
So that's your move, Aleister?
It's normal sorcerers who are using
the C-Document at the Palais des Papes.
A straightforward large-scale military assault
is going to be a pain to deal with.
I guess I have no choice.
Wait!
A-Are you okay?!
Kamiyan, let's get ourselves
to the Palais des Papes as well.
Those powered suits were
made in Academy City, right?
I thought they weren't going to attack!
First things first, we need to go after Terra.
In this situation, God's Right Seat
will likely focus on getting away.
This is our only chance to destroy the C-Doc—
Do you just attack everyone?!
Kamiyan, go on ahead.
I'll stop these Academy City fools.
Tsuchimikado!
We don't necessarily need to fight.
I'll look for a way to make a deal.
But you two go!
Damn it!
They rendered the rioters unconscious and
are taking them out of the city in those balloons.
Tsuchimikado wouldn't do such a thing.
I can't accept people doing
things in such a shitty way!
There doesn't seem to be anyone in here.
But where did all those powered suits come from?
What is Academy City planning to do?
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
OPTIONS
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
OPTIONS
Misaka, do you have a moment?
Wh-What's with you?!
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
OPTIONS
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
OPTIONS
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
OPTIONS
You never even message me,
and then you call out of nowh—
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
OPTIONS
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
OPTIONS
Can you turn on the news?
On TV or on the web?
Can you tell me if there's anything
about a city called Avignon?
What are you talking about? All the TV stations
are ablaze with breaking news about Avignon.
Military intervention to suppress protests in Avignon, France
Some religious organization has created
a weapon forbidden under international law.
Military intervention to suppress protests in Avignon, France
Academy City is lending its assistance
for a search-and-destroy operation.
Where even are you?
Oh, you see...
Misaka Mikoto
What was that?
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
Hey!
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
Are you even listening?!
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Where the hell are you?
Everything went silent.
Hello?
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
Hey!
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
Itsuwa, do you—
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
OPTIONS
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
OPTIONS
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
OPTIONS
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
OPTIONS
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
OPTIONS
Ongoing Call
Misaka Mikoto
OPTIONS
You really outplayed us here.
We didn't expect you to use subduing the riots
as an excuse to march onto the scene.
I guess that means
Academy City is serious about this.
That's the C-Document!
Well, they were going after the regular
human sorcerers who were using it,
so I had to secure it.
I can't use human spells,
so the smart decision would be
to put an end to the operation.
And you think we'll just let you leave?
Very well.
To be honest, I'd also prefer to get some more
entertainment value out of you before I leave.
You blockheads! At least make yourselves useful
as shields!
I'll never get used to these side effects.
Now wake up, you shitheads!
Otherwise I'll just dodge it all and sneer at you!
I surrender.
Do whatever you want with me.
If you can, that is.
You wanna know what happened?
Those HsPS-15 suits are equipped with a new type
of autonomous movement assistance devices.
However, they're just bug-ridden prototypes.
If they receive too many conflicting
inputs in a short window of time,
the autonomous program freezes up.
Plus, the unit fills up its internal database
with overly-detailed records.
So it accumulates errors over time
until bugs start manifesting.
All right, I have you immobilized, but—
Those are the supersonic stealth bombers
produced by Academy City, HsB-02s.
What are you thinking, Aleister?!
Those won't be enough to destroy the C-Document...
Do you still have something else up your sleeve?!
Part A of the operation successfully executed.
Moving to part B.
Prepare your parachute!
I don't need one.
These idiots, shooting up the place for no reason...
A Certain Magical Index
Commencing part B of the operation.
The Earth Blade could slice all of Eurasia in half
using just three kilograms of iron dust.
They sure built an interesting toy.
Isolation of the operation area confirmed.
Commencing bombardment of all sectors.
Change of plans.
After all, our objective is the Palais des Papes.
Concentrate fire there first.
B-But—
Change the instructions!
There are different kinds and degrees of evil.
First rate villains don't go
after the lives of honest people.
I don't presume you'll just
hand over the C-Document.
Change precedence.
The flour before the atmosphere!
Human skin before blades!
Change precedence.
Flour before human flesh!
Are you at your limit already?
Must be hard to fight with her holding you back.
But I finally found an opening.
There was something unnatural in your movements.
I see.
However, you won't have
the time to make use of that!
Change precedence.
The flour before the roof.
Itsuwa!
I guess that's all she's got.
You bastard!
Imagine Breaker.
I expected more of it,
but you're just too underdeveloped.
If you were to make use of its full potential,
you could have easily protected that sorceress.
What do you mean full potential?
Oh? Could it be that you're unaware of it?
No way, of course you—
Wait, could you have forgotten what you must have known?
You bastard!
Did I hit the mark?!
Were you hiding it?
But to what end?
It might be interesting to investigate
how you lost your memory.
Misaka Mikoto
OPTIONS
Ongoing Call
Damn it!
For her sake as well as mine,
I had decided to tell no one!
It doesn't really matter.
You'll die here either way.
I can't let him get to me!
Precedence.
I have to find that ability's weakness.
What? You're not going to come at me?
Then I will.
Change precedence.
Human skin before stone!
What's the matter?
You reflected Itsuwa's spear
and Tsuchimikado's spell.
So why didn't you defend against
a mere wallet using precedence?
It got me thinking.
We got hit by your white blade,
yet we're still alive.
I don't imagine you went easy
or wanted to keep us alive.
Then there's only one explanation left.
It's not that you didn't want to kill us.
You just couldn't!
You can't affect multiple targets at the same time.
Right?!
Yeah, because I haven't honed the spell for that.
But what do you think you can
achieve with this information?
Terra of the Left isn't going to be defeated so easily!
Terra!
Change precedence.
The flour before the floor!
What drives you to go this far?!
Is it really something worth
wrecking an entire city?!
I'd say most of the chaos in
the city was Academy City's fault.
There's something I simply must determine.
Is humanity today worthy of the ultimate
promise of Christianity, the Kingdom of Heaven?
Is that the salvation you offer?
The god of the Roman Catholics
didn't give you his teachings
for you to start such conflicts!
If you're going to redefine
salvation to fit your desires,
then I'm going to destroy that
stupid illusion right here and now!
Change precedence.
Too late!
You...
You filthy heathen!
Change precedence.
The flour before the human body!
It could cut through a human body,
but not through a shotgun.
That's a pretty inflexible ability!
You're not strong at all.
You just pretend to be
and then keep yourself at a safe distance.
You can never be as strong as me and Itsuwa,
who stand on the battlefield!
I see.
It seems the Imagine Breaker
really is a tough match for us.
It feels like it's making all our efforts meaningless.
Aren't you going to ask me?
About the Imagine Breaker.
Do you know what it is?
If you're not certain,
that means you really have lost your memory.
It's simple.
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
The Imagine Breaker really is just—
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
OPTIONS
Misaka Mikoto
Ongoing Call
What's happening?!
Terra!
Man.
If I don't find anything in ten minutes, I'm leaving.
You guys take over when the place cools back down.
Apart from eliminating the original sin,
which binds all humans,
they're also searching for means to become angels.
How does that relate to their name,
God's Right Seat?
Among the angels,
only Lucifer and his counterpart Michael
have the right to sit to the right of God,
the position that signifies equal standing.
So their ultimate goal is to
reach the level of Michael?
No.
They believe that once they achieve
the position of God's Right Seat,
they can evolve into something that's not an angel.
La Persona Superiore a Dio.
Those above God.
I heard that Avignon was torn up,
but I see you're unharmed, Terra.
Well, it's trivial for me to defend against
a single attack by manipulating precedence.
I also heard you lost the C-Document.
Yet you seem to be in a rather good mood.
Acqua, I'm sure you've heard that
the Russian Orthodox Church
has decided to officially ally with us.
That gives a firm base to launch
an invasion into Japan.
We have to discuss troop deployments
with Fiamma of the Right.
I see.
But before that,
I want to speak to you about something.
Is it true that you've been
using tourists and children
from the outskirts of Rome to continue
honing your Execution of Light?
Yes, it is.
Is that really something to make a fuss about?
Weren't you supposed to act to save
all human kind without discrimination?
I was only using heathens for my experiments.
Now then, I found something I need
to improve in my Execution of Light,
so I'll need to make some further adjustments.
Before that, there's something else you need to do.
Remember this: you will never be God's chosen.
God knows all.
You can ask for the details on the Day of Judgment.
This is the Cathedral of Saint Peter.
I would appreciate it if you were
to refrain from destroying it,
at least in the presence of me, the Pope.
My apologies.
So what do you plan to do now?
Vento cannot make a move.
Terra was purged.
That leaves us with one other possibility.
Do you intend to raid Japan
via Russia, like Terra mentioned?
These recent events made me realize something.
Only soldiers should take up arms on the battlefield.
I see.
So you, as a Saint and member of
God's Right Seat, shall fight this battle yourself.
Right, Acqua of the Rear?
Do you know what it is?
If you're not certain,
that means you really have lost your memory.
What the hell was that?!
Did he really
lose his memory?
When I least expect it, you're gone
And loneliness hits me hard in the chest
In the night filled with signs I look up at the stars
I bite my lip and pray
Every time the dawn comes I run to you
You try to hide behind a smile that you're covered in wounds
But I notice, because I'm not a child
I'll protect you even if I have to make an enemy of the entire world
This strength comes from the light you've given me
I don't want to just wait for a miracle
I want to start a revolution that changes who the two of us are
And this is the night before it starts
Next Time
A city loses its principles.
An organization moves in the darkness.
Who can slip through the maze
of roars and bullets alive?
Next time: "The Dark Side of Academy City".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.