Wh-What are you doing, Your Holiness?
I have to hurry.
The citizens have started marching towards
the Vatican, driven by their anxiety.
I'm aware.
You don't have to say any more.
Hi to the dandy gentleman.
Would I still be correct in
calling you the Pope of Rome?
Is that Vasilisa?
The cardinals are planning to elect a new Pope.
They have likely decided
that my authority is no more.
The words I speak do not hold
enough power to end this war.
Even so, you rose to action.
Oh, so sorry.
I'm in the middle of making the rebels
who sold out our beloved Sasha weep.
Show some restraint.
They are your brethren.
I knew you'd say that.
So, how exactly do you plan to end this war?
I will simply do what I can.
Not as the Pope of two billion believers,
but as a single believer
of the Roman Catholic doctrine.
I made a promise with that mercenary, after all.
It appears that the Lord
still has trials in store for me.
What will you do now?
A being not unlike yourself
has been identified in Russia.
The Archangel's Power of God, Misha Kruetuev.
Once the devastation begins,
tragedy will strike all humans in the land.
What are you going to do?
Nothing.
I only take action when it interests me.
I suppose I could go.
However, I have one condition.
Please don't hurt any of my friends.
Gladly, as long as they remain uninteresting.
If you do, I will become your enemy,
even if it means our mutual destruction.
You're far too naïve to be making threats.
But conversely, you may have piqued
my interest with that statement.
Wh-What was that?
An angel?
A Certain Magical Index
The Star of Bethlehem
Imagine coming all the way
to Russia to eat VVDonald's.
It sure is nice that some things taste the same
no matter where you are in the world.
We made it here by sneaking in
with the illegal immigrants,
but this is probably as far as we can get by car.
Let's find another route to storm
the Russian military base that Fiamma is hiding in.
What's wrong?
It's just...
Do you think there are a lot of people fleeing
to the Elizalina Alliance of Independent Nations?
It could also be the opposite.
No one wants to be a citizen
of a country that just lost a war.
Let's just put an end to this war.
Huh?
Either way, it's Fiamma pulling the strings, right?
Let's just go and kick his ass, put an end to the war,
and bring about world peace.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's go sock Fiamma in the face and save Index.
Now that's been decided, let's hurry up
and finish replenishing our nutrients.
Now's my chance!
I'll make up for that with my body!
Why are you licking your lips
with your eyes all sparkly?
What happened here?
He crushed the privateer base in an instant!
Is he one of those esper guys from Academy City?
No, he isn't.
I suppose that takes care of that for the time being.
Sorry for asking again, but who are you exactly?
Acqua of the Rear, ex-mercenary brute.
Something's coming this way.
They're Academy City's troops.
It looks like they're coming to occupy this area.
What shall we do?
Destroy them?
Nah.
If they're just here to protect that village,
we should just leave them be.
I still don't know who you're supposed to be,
but it's not like you have time
to fortify a base, right?
Indeed.
So we should just let the Academy City
troops station themselves here.
We'll lose the territory for the time being,
but they can guard it for several months.
I see.
Weren't you on the run
from Academy City, Hamazura?
That's a different matter.
This is to protect that village.
Anyway, we're gonna run.
Oh, I forgot to say.
Thank you.
All of us—me, the villagers, the girl
I've fallen for—survived because you came.
I'll repay you for this one day.
This looks like an instruction booklet.
That's...
Do you know what it is?
N-No!
I just thought it looked a bit like
a list of conditions for converting spells.
It's what we do to use Roman Catholic
magic in the Russian Orthodox Church.
What?
I'm not very familiar with magic,
unlike Miss Elizalina.
Magic?
What the hell is this guy on about?
Does this mean there's something
out there that I can't comprehend?
If so, that could be exactly what I'm looking for.
Who's Elizalina?
A sorceress—or was she a magician?
Whatever.
She can read what's written on this, right?
Yeah.
If you're able to speak to her, that is.
Right now, she's bedridden in a field hospital.
I didn't plan on staying too long or killing anyone.
When's sleeping beauty going to wake up?
Probably in one to three hours, if things go well.
All right.
They're spies.
I'm going to have to clean up this place
and make sure it's nice and pretty
if I'm going to leave the kid here.
The position you guys are in isn't the only Hell.
This level of darkness is still pretty mild.
How pathetic am I?
Bailing on them halfway through
ended up being the best course of action.
Don't worry about that.
Even now, you're fighting to keep me safe.
You're not pathetic at all.
What's this?
He said it's the key for the car parked just up ahead.
We can't take this.
You'll become accomplices aiding our escape.
He said to just start the engine
without using the key.
You got me there.
Hamazura, behind us!
There's 500 meters until the border!
W-We made it.
No way!
Is this the end?
Accelerator?
Damn it,
here I am just looking for spies and you have to
go and bring in more crap for me to deal with.
Start talking.
A Certain Magical Index
I want to hear it all.
This has me beat.
If we had healing magic, I'd love to use it
on myself to restore my mental state.
Healing magic?
This is what I can do.
I can probably take care of the girl in the tracksuit,
but this smaller one will prove much more difficult.
That is all.
What do you mean?
They each have different types
of toxins building up inside them.
The smaller girl appears to be
in a state where the toxins are
continuously injected into her system,
so even if they're removed from her body,
they'll be back in no time.
On the other hand, the tracksuit girl will probably
be fine once we remove the toxins from her body.
S-So you're saying Takitsubo will get better?
Right.
This is great, Takitsubo!
I can't breathe, Hamazura.
Sorry, I'm just so happy...
I'm not surprised, panicked, or even angry.
I could scream and stamp my feet on the ground,
but that wouldn't change anything.
I've known that time was
of the essence since the get-go.
I just have to do what I need to.
You can treat them however you want,
but answer me one thing before that.
Can you read this?
There's a chance I could, given enough time.
Do you want to leave it with me?
No, I just needed to know that you can read it.
You focus on treating them.
Umm...
I don't have all the time in the world.
I'm leaving now.
Do you have any leads?
If I don't, I'll find one.
What did you do with the spies that I weeded out?
They're being interrogated,
but we aren't making much progress.
Oh yeah?
Would you like to see?
Nah, I'm going to go see a more
reliable source of information.
How can I be of assistance today?
Work with me.
On what?
Why should I?
How should I?
I found a bunch of listening devices.
The spies are slowly leaking
fragments of information.
Go and collate all of that information.
Why should Misaka have to work with you?
The guys in Academy City are planning
to use the MISAKA Network for something.
You came for me and the kid while they
were fixing all of the bugs in the network.
But you lot are going to meet the same fate.
It's the end of the road.
That's how people who call it a success
when you kill twenty thousand dolls think.
I'm sure you realize that you're not
going to be used for anything respectable.
And that's why I should work with you?
The most evil villain, of all people?
All right, time to negotiate.
The Dark May Project.
No way.
It's the project that came about to enhance
the personal realities of other espers by
adopting the method I use to control my power.
Come up with some special ability
to make yourself irreplaceable.
What will it be?
You might find a way out of this
if you observe the way I fight.
I see how it is.
That does sound like something fitting for Misaka.
I'm going to find a way to fix the kid.
You're going to find a path to take that doesn't
end with you getting pumped and dumped.
That's why we'll fight Academy City.
We're going to outsmart them.
This benefits us both.
Got it? Then stop throwing
a tantrum and get to work.
This really is a surprise.
Misaka never thought the day would come when
she would force a smile after being hurt like this,
despite being tuned specifically
to kill Academy City's Rank 1.
Sorry about that.
That was my fault for falling for their shit.
What was that?!
I feel my reason for existence fading away
when I see the villain making such a sweet face!
"Villain" my ass.
Even after putting so much effort into perfecting
that persona, I still couldn't protect that kid.
I no longer have a reason
to care about being a villain.
Just picking a clear-cut side isn't going to cut it.
Academy City set both you and me up to be evil.
We're monsters.
Perfecting our evil wasn't an act of opposition.
We were doing exactly what they wanted.
That's why I'm going to get back
at them for real this time.
So I don't care if I end up losing
my character in the process.
Please.
Are you stupid?!
This is great!
This really is great, he's the king of the dolts!
This applies to Misaka as well,
but isn't this the first time you've
held someone's hand like this?
No.
I've done it plenty of times up 'til now.
With an annoying kid that looks a lot like you.
Are they under attack by Academy City?
The Russian army has started fighting back.
Now's our chance!
Let's take advantage of the chaos
to sneak into Fiamma's base.
Why do you think the Russian army
is defending the base alone?
It's because Fiamma doesn't want to come out.
Either he doesn't want people
to find out he's hiding here,
or he's in the middle of some kind of magical ritual.
So what do we need to do, exactly?
I'll steal a powered suit!
If you want to compliment me on my great idea,
I'll listen in bed with you while you pat my head.
Hey, wait!
Damn it.
Something's off.
Last time we snuck in,
there were a bunch of Russian sorcerers.
So how come there aren't any here?
Why are they making it look like
they're luring Academy City closer?
Isn't it obvious?
It's to lure you and your precious right arm in.
It would spell trouble for me too,
if you got caught in the crossfire and lost your arm.
I intentionally left an opening
so that I could quickly retrieve it.
I was surprised he left so suddenly last time,
but he was just letting me go?!
That wasn't much of a challenge.
That bunch of crybaby spies was no fun.
Deceiving someone is the same as it's always been.
Just take away any chance they
have to make reasonable judgment.
What do you think of that crying bastard's story?
It was full of inconsistencies.
The Russian army was always planning
to take advantage of this war
to invade the Elizalina Alliance of Independent Nations,
which they've had their eyes on for a while.
It's strange that they'd even
send spies in that kind of situation.
That just means it's the kind
of situation that calls for such methods.
They had to transport this classified document
to a certain place before
launching a full-fledged air strike.
So if we go there,
we'll find someone that needs this.
Which means someone who
knows how to read and use this.
Misaka is getting all hot and bothered,
being ordered around without a say in the matter.
Shut up!
This document was meant to be
brought to the Russian Army's
frontline base near the border, right?
I'm going to storm it.
Go and do whatever you want.
What are you going to do with Last Order?
What would happen if I left her with you?
Things you couldn't even begin to imagine,
just to keep myself entertained.
There are two remote-control
mystic artifacts for her.
Fiamma took the royal family's,
but the church's is still safe.
And it's clear as day who has it.
You're trying to keep Fiamma from obtaining
the knowledge of the 103,000 grimoires
by interfering with his artifact, aren't you?
Intentionally messing around with her body.
Let's suppose your delusions are reality.
I'm the head of this organization.
What can you do all on your own?
I can destroy the control tower, at the very least.
I see, I see.
Not bad.
But do you think the situation will remain
stagnant while you work on that?
What?
Warning.
Chapter four.
Connection from remote user confirmed.
Commencing automatic elimination
of potentially-malicious parties.
Stop wasting time.
If you've collected Sasha Kreutzev,
then hurry up and hand her over.
I've finished the preparations for the attack.
You will once again be unable
to observe the occupation.
Academy City will lose control over the situation.
This will become a true war.
Whatever the case may be,
I have no issues if I can achieve my objective.
Why would you go to such lengths to become
the Patriarch of the Russian Orthodox Church?
Forget about me, where are you right now?
I doubt you're at that military base.
Your signal has disappeared from those coordinates.
You'll find out soon enough.
Whether you like it or not.
What's going on?
What?!
I wasn't preparing a large-scale
mystic artifact or facility.
I was preparing a space to put this together.
D-Don't you realize how much danger
you're putting yourself in by doing this?
It's not a matter of how much danger I'm in.
There are people trying to kill
an average high schooler,
and there are people trying
to save an average high schooler.
Which side would you rather help?
Which would you be more proud of?
Man, I'm really not cut out for this.
What the hell is that?!
No way! Why is he there?!
What?
You've gotta be kidding me!
The pilot is safe.
Now, then...
How am I going to get up there?
Why are you here?
"MISAKA's serial number is 10777,"
says Misaka kindly to her sister,
who is lost for words.
Were you part of the cooperation pact
between Russia and Academy City?
"The withdrawal has been completed,
so I decided to make use of my free time,"
says Misaka while holding a dangerous-looking rifle
in one hand as she reports her free-time mood.
Free time?
"Isn't this your free time as well?"
asks Misaka to gain confirmation.
Well, I guess I'm not here for work.
Next Time
Wings of ice cover the night sky.
A giant floating fortress.
The commencement of divine punishment.
What are the stars and angels trying to say?
Next time: "Gabriel".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.