What's up with their power?
It disintegrated instead of getting reflected.
And not into water, ice, or vapor, but into light.
Is it the never-before-seen, completely different Law
that shithead Aiwass was talking about?
Such a hassle.
Let's just get them to spill the beans.
Electricity?!
Who are you?
Does it help if Misaka says "Third Season"?
What?!
Misaka doesn't care what happens to the war.
No orders of that kind have been input.
Misaka's only purpose is to obliterate Rank One.
That is the one and only purpose for which
Misaka was extracted from the culture fluid.
A Certain Magical Index
If your mind's too clouded by the madness going on around us
Then just admit that you've had enough of it
You can't keep hiding your doubts and waiting for salvation
Heaven's Killer
Signals the coming destruction
Surely one day we'll look back on this with a smile
But I'm just kidding myself
I can hear it!
I will figure out the answer!
Wake up and breathe in! Feel both me and you! We'll make it through this!
Point and lead us to a brighter tomorrow
Wake up and breathe in! Feel both me and you! You can decide your future!
I'll hold it tight in my palm
Loneliness may weigh us down now
But my belief is that one day
We can bring about a pure and just world
Misaka Worst
Wasn't your mystic artifact destroyed?
Still, I doubt you've recovered to the point
of being able to use Divine Punishment.
And even if you have,
that methodology can't defeat me.
Ha! You're bound to Michael.
You can't tap into your full power
under these conditions.
You're right.
That's why I want Sasha Kreutzev
and Imagine Breaker.
There's a limit to how much
you can use that Right Arm.
And because you already had
some fun with these small fry,
it's probably already dissolved in the air.
Surely you don't think that's enough to make
up for the difference in power between us.
The fun is just getting started.
Are you aware of how Biagio Busoni commanded
The Queen of the Adriatic Sea and its escorting
Queen's Fleet near the Italian town of Chioggia?
I was able to readjust that Holy Spirit spell
to the point of being able to use it in combat.
Using the entire armada is beyond me,
but I do have the affinity to control
at least a part of the Queen's Fleet.
And I can also do this.
You wasted too much of your strength, you dimwit!
Though you probably can't hear me anymore.
You think so?
See, I actually take better care
of my things than you think.
I can't see a way to avoid
the arm dissolving in the air,
but I've managed to fixate it in that state.
In other words, I now have no limits
as to how much I can use it.
Fiamma!
I need no destructive power.
A touch is all it takes, so I need not spare
any effort into trying to break my target.
Vento!
What in the world is going on?!
Shut your trap!
I need no speed.
A touch is all it takes,
so I need put no effort into precision.
Vento!
No!
Come on, it's not like I ripped
your whole tongue out.
I just tore it a bit. You're overreacting.
What are we even fighting?!
He's way too strong!
What have you—
It's simple, actually.
What I have possession of
is not the Right Arm itself.
It's the power of the Right Arm.
That means I can freely use any supernatural
phenomenon associated with the Christian religion.
I'm sure you know what that means.
You're not that incompetent.
Impossible!
You're right, it's imperfect.
But as you can see, it's still useful.
It's because this entire world
is becoming more and more ambiguous.
Haven't you noticed that it's
distorting the four great elements?
No!
Are you saying that the after-effects
of Angel Fall are that powerful?!
It's the opposite.
The defect which that nonsensical
spell exploited only arose
because the great Law
had distortions in it to begin with.
And now you understand.
So let's finish this.
How many people have you stood up for now?
You're such an amusing character.
And the most amusing thing
is how you constantly jump head-first
into danger for the sake of someone else,
and yet, all the rewards
and benefits accumulate within you.
What are you trying to say?!
Are you confident that what
you're doing is really the right thing?
I use my Right Arm to solve my own problems.
You use your right arm to resolve
the events that occur around you.
You smash others' greatest efforts
to dust with a single blow.
We're basically the same.
However, I am confident
that my actions will bring about the absolute good.
And you're telling me to let
Index suffer just for that?!
Go to hell!
So do you think stopping that
would serve the greater good?
It's not a matter of good or bad!
Index is suffering!
How many people do you think are crying,
because of this stupid war that you started?!
Is it that bad to fight for a girl
who can't even wake up?!
How amusing!
Could you repeat that in front of that nun
you've been deceiving all this time?
Through this remote control mystic artifact,
that girl's consciousness and mine connect at times.
At times, the information
I learn is transmitted to her.
No! He didn't!
So, knowing that,
can you still make the same claims?
Why do you keep playing innocent in front of her?
It seems you're protecting her
to satisfy your own conscience,
but I'm looking forward to seeing
if that's really what that girl needs.
That's one.
Fiamma!
I'd love to take another, too,
but it'd be hard to carry both at the same time.
Your right arm would obstruct the transportation.
Don't go dying on me.
I still have business with that right arm of yours.
Wait!
Damn it!
I'm looking forward to seeing
if that's really what that girl needs.
A Certain Magical Index
How is she?
Doc says it's the adverse effects
of the Academy City drugs.
We don't have any way to treat it
in such a small facility.
I thought as much.
Still, I couldn't even give her a bed to sleep in.
I guess I'm one of the Russians' worst enemies.
Your fuel is helping us.
Don't let it bother you.
Besides, even before World War III,
this was already a dangerous region.
We're right next to the border with
the Elizalina Alliance of Independent Nations.
The Russian army plans to destroy our village
to build a front-line military base.
Under the pretext of preventing any invasions
from the Alliance of Independent Nations,
they've sent planes to drop
land mines around the area.
No way!
Well, they're using them like voucher points.
They'll later gather them up and exchange
them for food and materials at some NGO.
What am I even trying to find in this war zone?
This is bad.
It's privateers.
Pri—?
They're like endorsed bandits.
It's an empty force in the Russian military.
Meaning it has no official members.
It's a bunch of ex-military thugs
hired to do the dirty work.
Why are they here?!
Wait, don't tell me they...
Yes, they probably plan to use the war
as pretext to level the village.
We need to leave, now!
We have no fuel for the cars.
Then what?!
Where could we possibly go?!
I'm trying to figure that out.
She's an extra clone, made to gather and concentrate
all the ill will of the MISAKA Network.
Damn it!
I'd decided I'd never hurt them again.
I can't reflect her shots.
What is this bullshit?!
Third Season?
So the lot at Academy City made more of them
just to put me in this situation
and try to break my conscience?!
Don't tell me you think you're
protecting Misaka or something.
Nobody asked you to.
Hey, wait a moment.
All Sisters connected to the MISAKA Network
can be completely immobilized
by a command from Last Order.
Would they send a clone
like that after me? Impossible.
In other words, she's a fake!
She's not a fake?!
Misaka has a mechanism to reject a halt command
from Last Order installed in her body.
You can't stop this Misaka by relying on that girl.
Fighting with the intention to kill is the only way.
But you can't, can you?
If you do, all your efforts will have been for naught.
Then just shut up and take the beating!
I'm scared. Spare me.
I'll play with you until your mind
is in shambles, so enjoy the ride!
Run around some more!
Haven't you killed over 10,000 Misakas,
on over 10,000 occasions?!
We can't settle that account unless we trample
over your human rights at least 10,000 times!
And if we include the interest,
you need to pay more than threefold!
Here, one more!
Why do you think Last Order and the other
Misakas haven't denounced you so far?
The answer is simple.
It's not that they freely decided not to blame you.
It's just that they weren't capable of
understanding and expressing those feelings,
and dealing with them like a normal human would,
so it just never showed!
But we're slowly becoming more and more human!
Soon many of them will learn of hatred.
They they'll realize their
legitimate right to take revenge!
Oh, I guess I should start
by eliminating that defective unit.
That would be more efficient.
Third Season will reform the Misakas.
With the expansion of the Network
and the re-deployment,
the Misakas will have new ability
enhancements and make vast progress.
Last Order, the old generation's
command tower, is no longer needed!
I see where this is going.
There's no way to end this
without anyone dying, is there?
I can't hold back anymore.
But this isn't the end, is it?
They'll just send another Sister.
Or maybe they'll use Yomikawa or Yoshikawa.
Will completely unrelated villages
and towns be completely demolished?
Whatever.
I can't take this any longer.
Help...
Someone...
It's all... your fault.
Fuck you all!
Who do you think you are,
fucking around with me like this?
Was this girl created for the sole
purpose of getting killed by me?!
That's all part of the plan of those
shitheads in Academy City, isn't it?!
This kid dies no matter how much she struggles!
And my mind gets broken!
And someone somewhere is sitting in a warm room,
drinking booze and laughing at us!
You planned out the whole thing, didn't you?!
It's all going the way you want, isn't it?!
Then I'm going to wreck it all!
If your plan can't succeed unless she dies,
I'll ruin it, by single-handedly saving her life!
Just you watch, shitheads!
I'm going to wipe those smirks off your faces!
You slimy, shitty, shitheads!
You look down on me,
thinking my power is only for killing.
You bastards are rotten to the core!
I'll show you that I also have the power to protect!
A Certain Magical Index
Fear never loosens its grip on me
But I hold back my tears
It's a lonely battle in this never-ending night
I wonder where you went
Just as the courage I was relying on was breaking down
I heard a voice calling me from afar
Your smile, so sincere it's almost awkward,
Makes the lonely night turn into day
Spread throughout the whole world
Are hope-filled lights
As they connect, the future smiles upon us
I feel like this sad journey is
Coming to an end
Your voice will be what changes me
I'm not alone
May this never-ending song shine brightly
Next Time
Black wings stain the snowy fields.
Clenched blood-stained fists.
The strongest and the weakest will clash again.
Next time: "Reasons to Protect".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.