I got Last Order back and
wrecked that damned Kihara,
but then I got involved with
this organization called GROUP.
I had to deal with the riffraff that sneaks
around in the darkness of Academy City.
Such a pain in the ass.
Who gives a damn about our orders?
I'm doing whatever the hell I want.
A Certain Magical Index
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
Carrying a ticking time bomb
The Earth keeps on turning, so hurry up!
No one can pretend it's not their business anymore
Suddenly common sense is out the door
Opposing fates fail to reach each other
Drenched in the rain of resentment
But why? Fear and doubt keep building up heavy in my heart
My racing heart is flooded with ambition
Ready!
Everyone that's drawn to this place
Has gone beyond the meaning and color of desire
My heart wants to stay strong
I feel it deep inside me
With all my soul, this one thing
Dive into a heart
The Dark Side of Academy City
Welcome!
These days most orders come in online or by mail.
Janitor's Closet
It's rare for someone to come in person like you.
I can give you a deal on some
sensor jammers for lock breaking.
Our best sellers are currently
our money-laundering products.
What are you looking for?
Sorry, I'm not into those,
"Employee Transfer Specialist", Mr. Management.
I'm not here as a customer.
I'm here to arrest you.
Bastard!
Damn you!
Is he out of ammo?
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
CLEANING SOLVENT
DANGER
HIGHLY FLAMMABLE
Wh-Whoa, hold on there! Wait!
I'll cooperate!
Y-You bastard! I said I'd cooperate.
Need someone picked up. Contact our people.
No, no need for an ambulance,
a paddy wagon will suffice.
Where's Accelerator?
He's gone?!
All right, fine.
I'll have Unabara go to Management's place.
Musujime, you'll continue to act as support.
Understood.
Man, where's our newbie
slacking off at?
Already back from Avignon?
Where the hell did you get that info from?
How about you start with a "hello"?
I need information.
The blueprints for my electrodes.
If your choker's acting up, I can fix it for you.
I'm not into letting someone else
hold the power switch to my life.
Not the higher-ups, and not you.
I see.
You've come prepared.
My job is to prepare what my patients need.
By the way, Last Order has been asking to see you.
If you'd come by just a bit earlier...
I don't think this is the right direction,
says Misaka as Misaka tries to point this out.
This is the right way.
I want to get to the amusement park in District 6,
says Misaka as Misaka tries to repeat
the declaration of her aspiration.
And regardless of how much you repeat that,
I'm driving you home.
Doctor's orders.
This damn hurts! Shit!
Oh, they sent you.
Sorry, I messed up.
Could you cut off my handcuffs?
So what kind of dealings
was Management involved in?
He helped form some kind of criminal
organization a day or two ago.
He helped fill a position
that they didn't have anyone for.
They brought in mercenaries from outside the city.
They're surely planning to make a move soon.
Our job is to investigate and prevent that.
So when did GROUP become a champion of justice?
Just get any and all data
that seems like it may be related.
Understood.
Hmm, what should I do?
Man, why can't you finish your job by yourself?
Is this where that idiot Unabara disappeared?
Take a look at this.
It's Aztec magic.
Unabara has a special ability where he
uses human skin to impersonate people.
I don't really know much about those things.
Are you saying he used this guy?
Yeah.
He snuck in among the people who stormed
the place to clean up any clues and is biding his time.
Found it.
This must be Unabara's parting gift.
The Japanese Yen issued by the
Academy City Bureau of Printing
have embedded smart-card chips.
Downloading...
Cancel
Download Complete
Close
Open File
There it is.
Management's sales list, huh?
Looks like he hired...
a professional sniper.
His name's Sunazara Chimitsu.
Oh, look, it's the plan for the sniper attack.
It'll be at District 7's open-air concert venue.
The target is...
What's wrong?
The target is Board of Directors
member Oyafune Monaka.
She's giving a speech.
"Voting rights for the students who
comprise 80% of the city's population".
Well, this isn't good.
The speech is about to begin.
Musujime, use your Move Point.
Wait, we still don't know where he'll be firing from.
Don't put me to sleep.
Something blew up!
Run!
We just wreck the speech, and we're done.
See?
Pull out.
Not yet. The job's not done.
I said, pull out.
And don't make me repeat myself again, Sunazara.
That was dumb.
They just gave up.
I have the name of the group who hired Sunazara.
SCHOOL.
They're probably a small unofficial unit like us.
An organization lurking in
the shadows of Academy City.
SCHOOL?
That's not all.
What?
I don't know exactly how
they're involved in this incident,
but I also got the names of several
other similar-sounding organizations.
MEMBER, BLOCK, and ITEM.
A Certain Magical Index
Huh?
Today's salmon lunch looks
a bit different from yesterday's.
Huh...
So mackerel cans sure are in these days.
Curry, huh?
Curry's the best!
An ultra-controversial C-grade movie
by Hong Kong Red Dragon Filmworks Company.
That sounds super-intriguing.
What do you think, Takitsubo?
Receiving a signal from the south-by-southwest.
So, this morning there was
an assassination attempt on
Oyafune Monaka of the Board of Directors, right?
Not even a "thanks"?!
Hamazura, send everyone a text
with the details of the incident.
Yeah, okay.
No, that's not—
Wait! Let me send it again!
That must have been some sort of glitch!
Um, this must be it.
Hamazura!
Hamazura sure is gross.
So are bunny girls super-in
your strike zone, Hamazura?
It's fine, Hamazura.
I hope you find happiness the way you are.
Oyafune Monaka Assassination Attempt
Date: October 9 (Academy City Independence Day), morning
Location: District 7 open-air concert venue
Target: Board of Directors member Oyafune Monaka
Speech topic: "Voting rights for the students who comprise
80% of the city's population"
The speech was suddenly cancelled due to the explosion of an
air-cleaning vehicle. The perp is thought to be a sniper from
SCHOOL. Since Yumiya Rakko is dead, it's assumed that they
have a new sniper.
Reply
Forward
Delete
Date: October 9 (Academy City Independence Day), morning
Location: District 7 open-air concert venue
Target: Board of Directors member Oyafune Monaka
Speech topic: "Voting rights for the students who comprise
80% of the city's population"
The speech was suddenly cancelled due to the explosion of an
air-cleaning vehicle. The perp is thought to be a sniper from
SCHOOL. Since Yumiya Rakko is dead, it's assumed that they
have a new sniper.
Location: District 7 open-air concert venue
Target: Board of Directors member Oyafune Monaka
Speech topic: "Voting rights for the students who comprise
80% of the city's population"
The speech was suddenly cancelled due to the explosion of an
air-cleaning vehicle. The perp is thought to be a sniper from
SCHOOL. Since Yumiya Rakko is dead, it's assumed that they
have a new sniper.
Oyafune was prepared with four special vehicles equipped
Oh, it's the thing that those
SCHOOL lot were super-planning for.
Target: Board of Directors member Oyafune Monaka
Speech topic: "Voting rights for the students who comprise
80% of the city's population"
The speech was suddenly cancelled due to the explosion of an
air-cleaning vehicle. The perp is thought to be a sniper from
SCHOOL. Since Yumiya Rakko is dead, it's assumed that they
have a new sniper.
Oyafune was prepared with four special vehicles equipped
with Wind Defense (a device that causes strong winds around
Speech topic: "Voting rights for the students who comprise
80% of the city's population"
The speech was suddenly cancelled due to the explosion of an
air-cleaning vehicle. The perp is thought to be a sniper from
SCHOOL. Since Yumiya Rakko is dead, it's assumed that they
have a new sniper.
Oyafune was prepared with four special vehicles equipped
with Wind Defense (a device that causes strong winds around
a VIP, obstructing sniper aim) as a sniper countermeasure, but
80% of the city's population"
The speech was suddenly cancelled due to the explosion of an
air-cleaning vehicle. The perp is thought to be a sniper from
SCHOOL. Since Yumiya Rakko is dead, it's assumed that they
have a new sniper.
Oyafune was prepared with four special vehicles equipped
with Wind Defense (a device that causes strong winds around
a VIP, obstructing sniper aim) as a sniper countermeasure, but
they were all incapacitated. Thumb-sized holes were
The speech was suddenly cancelled due to the explosion of an
air-cleaning vehicle. The perp is thought to be a sniper from
SCHOOL. Since Yumiya Rakko is dead, it's assumed that they
have a new sniper.
Oyafune was prepared with four special vehicles equipped
with Wind Defense (a device that causes strong winds around
a VIP, obstructing sniper aim) as a sniper countermeasure, but
they were all incapacitated. Thumb-sized holes were
discovered on the outside shells of the devices. It's assumed
The speech was suddenly cancelled due to the explosion of an
air-cleaning vehicle. The perp is thought to be a sniper from
SCHOOL. Since Yumiya Rakko is dead, it's assumed that they
have a new sniper.
Oyafune was prepared with four special vehicles equipped
with Wind Defense (a device that causes strong winds around
a VIP, obstructing sniper aim) as a sniper countermeasure, but
they were all incapacitated. Thumb-sized holes were
discovered on the outside shells of the devices. It's assumed
that the perp destroyed them before proceeding with the
air-cleaning vehicle. The perp is thought to be a sniper from
SCHOOL. Since Yumiya Rakko is dead, it's assumed that they
have a new sniper.
Oyafune was prepared with four special vehicles equipped
with Wind Defense (a device that causes strong winds around
a VIP, obstructing sniper aim) as a sniper countermeasure, but
they were all incapacitated. Thumb-sized holes were
discovered on the outside shells of the devices. It's assumed
that the perp destroyed them before proceeding with the
assassination attempt.
SCHOOL. Since Yumiya Rakko is dead, it's assumed that they
have a new sniper.
Oyafune was prepared with four special vehicles equipped
with Wind Defense (a device that causes strong winds around
a VIP, obstructing sniper aim) as a sniper countermeasure, but
they were all incapacitated. Thumb-sized holes were
discovered on the outside shells of the devices. It's assumed
that the perp destroyed them before proceeding with the
assassination attempt.
have a new sniper.
Oyafune was prepared with four special vehicles equipped
with Wind Defense (a device that causes strong winds around
a VIP, obstructing sniper aim) as a sniper countermeasure, but
they were all incapacitated. Thumb-sized holes were
discovered on the outside shells of the devices. It's assumed
that the perp destroyed them before proceeding with the
assassination attempt.
Didn't we take care of their sniper three days ago?
They must have hired a new one.
In other words, they ignored our warning.
Oyafune might be a board member,
but she sure is useless.
She has almost no influence.
She's not worth killing.
And yet...
...SCHOOL went ahead with their plan.
Why is that?
Tell the class, Hamazura.
Um, well...
Gimme a second.
It's on the tip of my tongue.
I almost have it!
It's that. You know?
Seriously, Hamazura...
Yeah, the thing!
The way you freak out is so gross!
There are super-many types of grossness,
but Hamazura's is the worst kind.
It's fine, Hamazura.
I hope you find happiness even
if you keep getting called gross.
Damn it!
I'm the leader of a Skill-Out organization
with more than a hundred members!
So you are. What of it?
Hamazura, get the bill.
Where are you going?
To slaughter all the shitheads from SCHOOL.
What do you think happens when a VIP
has had an attempt on their life?
People are called in from other places
to protect the hospital where they're treated.
Any necessary researchers, equipment,
and materials also get gathered there.
I see.
It messes with normal security arrangements.
That's what SCHOOL wanted to achieve.
They'll make use of that to get at their true goal.
Oyafune was selected because
she's a VIP with minimal security.
That's the answer.
Right after the Oyafune assassination attempt,
an elementary-particle
engineering lab had an incident.
In other words, that's where SCHOOL went.
Wow!
Mugino is as scary as ever.
She doesn't hold back on the Level 5 stuff.
Hamazura!
Yes!
So it's really you.
I heard you got taken in.
What are you doing here, old hag?!
I was about to ask you the same thing.
Don't tell me you're involved in you-know-what.
What's this bus here?
Is it stolen?
I took out a loan on it! A loan, okay?!
Got a license?
Of course I do.
Hey! Watch how you're driving!
That car...
Hamazura!
Stop awkwardly hitting on
women and start the engine!
I'm not hitting on her!
We're going after that car!
Hurry up!
Hey! What's going on here?!
Man, everyone wants a piece of me.
Hamazura! Step on it!
Damn it!
Where are Kinuhata and Frenda?
That's not enough to kill them.
How did this happen?
You're ranked fourth in the city, aren't you?
They had a Level 5 too.
Kakine Teitoku.
The shithead ranked second.
But we didn't just get beaten back all the way.
Wha— Hey!
But if they get away with what
they loaded up in that car, we lose.
We can't allow that.
Don't worry.
My AIM Stalker won't lose track of a person
once it has recorded his AIM Diffusion Field.
Even if he leaves the solar system,
I can still get a read on him.
Shit!
Takitsubo!
We're splitting up!
Aren't you gonna fight?!
My target is the car's cargo.
Also, that girl's ability is kind of annoying.
Damn it!
Why are you chasing me?!
How do you like that?!
Oh, shit!
U-Underdog, away!
Are you hungry?
Um, excuse me...
I'm the kind of heroine who falls from the sky!
It's dangerous here. Please get away quickly.
I lost the target.
Do you think there's the possibility that
the man has disguised himself as
a young mother, or as a baby stroller?
Fuck off, moron.
Getting this was a pain in the ass.
The super-fine-particle
object-interference-absorbing manipulator,
also known as the Tweezers.
My way to get to Aleister.
Kakine!
The computer virus storage center
in District 5 is under a cyber-attack.
The facility holds many not-yet-analyzed viruses,
as well as experimental ones
created by Academy City's researchers.
District 5 Computer Virus Storage Center
If the viruses get out,
all infrastructure will go to hell.
It'll cause a huge panic.
If they get how far out exactly?
Academy City's security is more focused on
keeping things in than on keeping things out.
So I'm sure there are means
of preventing such breaches.
The external connection terminals, you mean?
District 5 Computer Virus Storage Center
External Terminal
Commencing emergency cutoff
of external connection terminals.
North terminal in District 3, successfully cut off.
South terminal in District 2, successfully cut off.
What's going on?
The west terminal in District 13 is not responding.
District 5 Computer Virus Storage Center
External Terminal
Could not confirm cutoff.
CONN_ERROR
Yet another painfully obvious move.
They're most likely baiting us to it.
I don't know who's behind this,
but they seem to want to get slaughtered.
What shall we do about the attempt
on Oyafune Monaka's life?
We'll deal with it later.
What about Unabara?
I was never planning to save him.
It's Unabara.
Where are you dicking around?
With SCHOOL?
No, with BLOCK.
I'm sure you've already noticed,
but the hacking attempt on the external
connection terminal is nothing but a diversion.
The real target is the Aerospace
Engineering Lab's satellite control center.
I trust you can handle that.
Bye.
He said it's the satellite control center.
I see. I can imagine what they want.
District 5 Computer Virus Storage Center
External Terminal
CONN_ERROR
The satellite Altair II is equipped with
a high-power Earth-targeting laser.
But still, we can't allow
the viruses to leak out either.
It's not my style to dance to those shitheads' tune.
Wh-Who are you?!
The satellite control center.
O-Okay.
When I least expect it, you're gone
And loneliness hits me hard in the chest
In the night filled with signs I look up at the stars
I bite my lip and pray
Every time the dawn comes I run to you
You try to hide behind a smile that you're covered in wounds
But I notice, because I'm not a child
I'll protect you even if I have to make an enemy of the entire world
This strength comes from the light you've given me
I don't want to just wait for a miracle
I want to start a revolution that changes who the two of us are
And this is the night before it starts
Next Time
Some strive to escape from the control of others,
while others choose to make
themselves part of a group.
People's mismatching goals cross
paths and bring forth new battles.
Next time: "Dark Matter".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.