I might be able to do something about it.
What?
It was on September 30.
A friend of mine called Index removed a virus
from her head by singing a special song.
The contents of that song
are now stored in my mind as well.
If we adjust its parameters, it will likely help.
To that end, you have to find out
the parameters stored in her mind.
Still alive?
Unfortunately.
You heard what the girl said just now, right?
The data for a song used to eliminate a virus
has remained in Last Order's memory.
If we can get that data, it might help cure her.
Yes.
And that finally gives me a solution to pursue.
You should be able to dig into the Sisters' Network
where her memories are backed up.
But even if I find the song there,
where do you intend to find the additional
parameters needed for the adjustment?
Academy City, and other technology
developed elsewhere.
If I put the two together,
I may be able to find the solution.
A Certain Magical Index
Index
Takitsubo!
Takitsubo! Where are you?!
Hamazura...
Long time no see, Hamazura!
Mugino Shizuri!
Body Crystals?!
Are you still trying to make her take those?!
Takitsubo?
Why do I have to concern myself with that nobody—
Say, Hamazura,
how much damage do you think the
fourth-ranked Level 5 overloading would cause?
I can't even get close to her.
Damn it! She's more like a furnace
or a star than a human now.
Hamazura!
See how far I'm willing to go?
I've made considerable sacrifices to get here.
You don't think you can resolve this situation
without sacrificing anything yourself,
do you now?
Hamazura...
Hama...
I get it now.
Even just standing upright in this condition
took her a great deal of effort.
Why? Why now? Damn it!
Where are the Body Crystals?
I only needed ten more seconds
to finish up everything properly.
Don't you look down on me, you piece of shit!
I'm going to kill you no matter what!
Ever since you shot me back at that factory,
everything's gone to shit!
Why did I become such a horrible monster?
Mugino...
Mugino!
What are you doing?
I've had enough of it.
Why do we have to try to kill each other?
You, and Takitsubo, and Kinuhata, and even Frenda.
You were all friends, weren't you?
I can't believe that you just
killed Frenda in a fit of rage.
If the higher-ups of Academy City were
actually in control even of that fighting,
that'd mean they'd already predetermined that we'd
kill each other and we had no choice in the matter!
If you want to see me being miserable,
I have enough of that to show you.
I'll do whatever you want to stop this fight!
So
let's stop this.
Let's stop the killing.
Are you listening to yourself, Hamazura?
You chose Takitsubo.
And to save her, you've shot me. Twice.
And now you're saying you'll save me?
That's true.
I chose Takitsubo.
I swore I'd protect her with my life.
And that hasn't changed.
I turned my back on you in order to save her.
You self-centered bastard.
I killed Frenda.
And I tried to kill Takitsubo several times.
How are you going to save me?
I don't think we can get away with it.
Not me, and not you.
So apologize with all you have to Kinuhata,
bow your head to Takitsubo,
shed tears over Frenda's grave,
and beg for forgiveness.
Then...
Then we can be ITEM again! I know we can!
And until that happens, I'll protect you.
I'll put my life on the line
to have everyone back in ITEM.
So stand up, Mugino!
Stand back up on your own once more! Mugino!
You, a Level 0, are going to protect me, a Level 5?
Ridiculous.
I haven't fallen that far.
Looks like I was disposable all along.
Plan B is coming for us.
What now, Hamazura?
I told you already, I'll put my life on the line.
Pretty gutsy.
Are these adverse effects of the remote control?
Due to her lapse in consciousness,
her precision and speed are reduced.
This is my chance!
Chapter 32, verse 44.
Counter-attack preparations complete.
Personal opinion:
It's highly likely that Fiamma and the
Star of Bethlehem are connected by magic.
Indirect attacks via the Star might—
Dun-du-du-dun!
You're from the Russian Church, right?
You looked troubled,
so I came to explain the payment plan to you.
That seems to be an emergency escape device.
Fiamma seemed like he was planning
to toss aside the Russian sorcerers
the moment he got what he wanted from them,
so I thought I'd lead you there.
First question:
What do you mean by "payment plan"?
I don't want any money.
You just need to pledge to help
Britain in a moment of need.
First response:
Those who wish to withdraw from
the front line should do so at once.
I have no intention of leaving
before I strike back at Fiam—
Te-he-he! I got you!
So, how do you plan to strike back?
Second answer:
I have no reason to tell you.
A Certain Magical Index
The Star of Bethlehem has risen.
The adjustment of the heavenly bodies
by Gabriel's power is complete.
The Four Elements have returned
to their proper places.
Everything is prepared.
Now it's time to take that right arm of yours.
That will mark the completion of Project Bethlehem.
Are you that hellbent on giving
the Roman Catholic Church the victory?
I do not care about the Roman Catholic Church.
My actions are, to their core,
actions for my own benefit.
Can I destroy it?
No.
Oh, I see eliminating what you touch isn't your only trick.
You've learned to parry as well.
Academy City's optical weapon, right?
I've demonstrated it already, haven't I?
My Right Arm optimizes its power output
to match the ordeal I'm facing.
Things like lasers are no match for me.
You're messed up!
You should be proud of yourself.
You've made my Right Arm uncertain about
how much power it should use against your fist.
Warning: Psalm 22, verse 1.
Designation "Eli Eli Lama Sabachthani".
Begin invocation.
Of course simple spells are no match for you, but...
Warning: Chapter 29, verse 33. Begin invocation.
Wha—
He's using his powers from God's Right Seat
together with the knowledge from Index!
Warning: Chapter 35, verse 18.
"Fire and Brimstone will
Scorch the Earth". Begin invocation.
Oh, my.
The deviation from the theoretical
value is unacceptable.
How disrespectful of the enemy I must defeat.
An enemy you must defeat?
This world is warped.
As if the world itself is getting
worn out and showing its age.
This God thing is supposed to have
set up all the cogs to move correctly.
But why then has it warped so much?
The answer is simple.
Several of the cogs have begun to break down.
So we need to return things to how they were.
I'm going to adjust the mechanism as needed,
change the cogs, clean out the muck,
then reapply the machine oil of Christianity,
and things will start moving nicely once more.
So you're going to use magic to rearrange
people's minds to match your desires?
It's much simpler than that.
I'll make them realize the truth.
Just one swipe of my
completed arm will be enough
to make humanity realize
the insurmountable difference in power.
And then they'll know that so long as they obey me,
they'll be able to witness the moment when
I bring salvation to all humans around the world.
They'll know that the moment
the Star of Bethlehem rose up into the sky,
a new era had already began!
You're going to bring salvation
to all humans around the world?
Are you saying you've been
to all the places around the world?
Have you seen how many people
are smiling in all those places?
I see. That's an intriguing point of view.
But I'll spare it some more thought
after I've saved the world.
I've seized it!
Imagine Breaker must have once
been a type of purification function,
naturally possessed by the sacred Right Arm.
But by accepting my power
that it was originally part of,
the role of that unnecessary feature has now ended.
Now my Right Arm is complete.
Now I just need to wield the power inside of me
to its full extent, the power as it should be,
and the salvation of all shall be ensured.
People may call me The One Above God,
but to me it doesn't matter.
All I want to do is gather all the
power I can and save the world.
I am going to save this world.
You should feel honored, lump of meat!
I've successfully harvested the worth of your life!
What the—
I've absorbed your right arm.
So why do you still possess power?
Something's there.
Something invisible...
I don't...
I don't care who you think you are.
And I don't give a damn about
what you were trying to do.
But pipe down!
I'm going to take care of him!
You cast it away?!
You threw that much power to the wind,
just to get Imagine Breaker back?!
I've finally begun to understand a bit.
Understand what?
Why did you have to make
the Star of Bethlehem this large?
If Fiamma of the Right really
was the most powerful being,
there would be no need to gather parts
of churches and temples from across the world.
Why did you have to spark World War III?
Your power changes according
to how strong your enemy is.
In other words, the more powerful the enemy,
the more power you can draw out.
But why do you need to force that much power out?
Why did you want power so much that
you allied with another branch of your religion?
If you were really invincible,
why did you need any underlings?
The truth is,
you were scared, weren't you?
Because you didn't know if you really had
in you enough power to save the world.
The world hasn't ended.
I've never heard of society collapsing,
at least in modern times.
That meant you'd never get the opportunity
to manifest enough power to save the world.
Just like how my Imagine Breaker looks powerless
unless I get involved with espers and sorcerers.
That's right.
Someone who has never saved the world even once
has no way of knowing
if they have the power to do it.
That's why you had to do all this!
And what of it?!
Do you have the right to accuse me?!
Are you saying that you've actually
experienced the power to save the world?!
Of course I have.
It may not be something grand,
but I've saved it.
Small as it may seem, I've witnessed
the moment when a person's world was saved.
A person who tries to become
the world's savior can't protect it.
Our world isn't so weak as to
need such a bastard to save it.
I guess that does it.
Good thing tanks move faster than I thought.
"That one-sided violent outburst
really rubs in the sense of inferiority,"
says Misaka, feeling slightly disheartened.
Nonsense. If all of you gather up—
"That's only a property of our group as a whole.
Being that strong alone would be preferable.
You wouldn't understand."
mumbles Misaka under her breath.
By the way, you have skills for using
various weapons installed, right?
If necessary, acquiring any missing parts
from the MISAKA Network is possible.
I'm not sure if it's meant for aerial
combat or just transportation,
but we have a VTOL unit over there.
If we use that,
we can probably get to that fortress in the sky.
Next Time
People have good in them, not just malice.
Fighting for those they want to protect,
they pray, and rise up.
They need no reason for that.
Next time: "Wings".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.