Hmpf, magical hacking, huh?
Impressive.
But isn't your body struggling from the strain
of doing combat at such a quick pace?
Misha Kreutzev also possessed the power of Gabriel.
She couldn't make use of the full power of the angel,
but I sense something beyond
mere proficiency in Acqua.
Could a human really gain that much power?
It has been a long time since
I had such a good workout.
But I think it's time to finish this.
THMIMSSP.
The holy mother's infinite mercy softens severe punishment.
What?
TCTCDBPTTROGBWIMAATH.
The compassion and the conviction directly beg appeal to
the righteous God to be with mercy and ascend to Heaven!
Where is the Imagine Breaker?
Or maybe I'll eventually encounter him
if I keep breaking through these layers?
Acqua!
You're no longer in any state to fight me.
I won't let a coward like you,
who has nothing but natural talent,
trample over the conviction that
boy showed me to risk one's life!
A Certain Magical Index
Divine Mother's Worship
What in the world were we doing?
Our most desperate efforts seem insignificant
when compared to what Saints can do.
Ugh, damn it!
What's with this sudden system malfunction!
Not only did that low-oxygen warning delay me,
but now I can't go back to the surface
at all because of a gate failure!
Geez!
Wha—! You! What are you doing here?
Misaka?
I need to go.
W-Wait!
You idiot. Why are you dressed like that?
Don't tell me you slipped out of a hospital again?
I need to go.
They're probably fighting as we speak.
So I need to go fight too.
Why won't you just say it?
Something like "I need help!" or "Lend me a hand!"
No, even "I'm scared", or "I'm in trouble".
You should tell me such stuff!
Misaka. What are you—
I know that you've lost your memories.
I understand that you have
some big issues to deal with,
but do you really have to deal with them alone?
Why do you need to keep fighting by yourself
after getting so battered and losing your memories?
I can fight too.
I can help you!
So tell me!
Where are you going?
Who are you planning to fight?
This time I'll fight with you.
I'll bring back your peace of mind!
Misaka...
Anyway, I'm coming with.
Talking to you does no good,
so until I see you back in the hospital—
I see.
So you found out.
But you've got it wrong.
I don't remember what I was like before,
but I don't think I put my life on the line
just to turn around and ask for help.
The me from the time I don't remember
is still driving me now.
He still remains.
Not in here, but in here.
That's probably why I'm here.
And why I know exactly what I need to do.
I'm sorry, Misaka.
You should go home as soon as you can.
I haven't changed.
Even if some gears had turned differently
and I hadn't lost my memories,
that wouldn't change what I need to do.
Kamijou Touma isn't a man who's shaken
by the absence of memories.
I didn't say anything wrong.
He has to go back to the hospital right now.
And my choice to join him
in his battle is also correct.
However,
he probably feels that it's important
to stand up on his own two feet here.
I can't stand in the way of that!
The right thing to do is to let him go on his way.
What do I do?
I can't accept this at all.
That's right...
Are you done already, Saint of the Far East?
How is he able to use such power?
Drawing out that amount of power should,
both physically and magically,
disintegrate a human body.
Not to mention that he's also under
the strain of the power of God's Right Seat.
This shouldn't be possible.
This is far beyond the scope
of natural talent or aptitude.
Holding two extraordinary natures
within one body shouldn't be possible.
He must have some trick.
Something to allow the use of powers both
as a Saint and as a member of God's Right Seat.
You want to continue this fight?
I'm sure you must be enraged at me
for involving normal people and the
Amakusa Church in a battle between Saints
despite the insurmountable difference in power.
But that's what a battlefield is like.
Attacking with a clear difference in strength,
weapon quality, and numbers is the norm in battle.
If you don't like that, don't come
to the battlefield in the first place!
There is no need to make the powerless fight.
It's enough for true soldiers
to face each other in battle!
What an arrogant mindset.
I was being stupid.
What course of action must I take?
What course of action would save my comrades?
What course of action would correct
the errors in the ways of Acqua of the Rear?
What course of action would undo this weakness
and resist his overwhelming power?
Lend me your strength!
I need your help!
Let's go!
To where the Amakusa Christian Church is needed!
Yeah!
What?!
You're asking the weak to save you?
Are you that frightened of death?
Is that how it looks to you?
It's true that I've had comrades
hurt while fighting by my side,
and that made me want to distance myself
from the Amakusa Christian Church.
But those tragedies did not occur
because they were weak.
I had labeled them as weak,
and so I couldn't trust their strength.
Somewhere deep inside, I was looking down
on them and not really relying on them.
That hubris, that sense of superiority,
that I'm the one protecting them,
those were the real causes of those tragedies!
And I'm going to overcome that now!
I'll believe in and rely on them!
And by letting each other
manifest our utmost strength,
I'll take back my Amakusa Christian Church!
Baseless hope is nothing but delusion!
Do you truly think you can surpass me with that?!
A Saint is a person born with bodily
traits similar to the Son of God,
which allows them to use some divine powers.
But even then, a Saint cannot
use as much power as you do.
You clearly possess power far beyond mine.
Why is that?
The answer is simple.
It's because of your Divine Mother's Worship.
You also possess bodily traits
similar to the Divine Mother,
so you can also use powers coming from her.
By combining the nature of a Saint
and of the Divine Mother,
you managed to forcefully rein in the powers
that would otherwise overwhelm you.
And what if you are correct?
That means that you have a weakness.
You're far more vulnerable to anti-Saint spells
than any other Saint in the world!
The Saint Destroyer.
The Saint Destroyer is a spell
that destroys the balance of the bodily trait
that makes you similar to the Son of God,
thus unleashing the powers within
the Saint's body from their control.
If you, who possess both the traits of Saint
and of the Divine Mother, get hit by it...
Spontaneous discharge.
So that's why the only time he used any
magical defense was when we attempted that.
I see. So that's your plan.
The symbols of the execution of the Son of God.
Longinus, add the final key to the execution now!
Fascinating!
The Amakusa Christian Church.
I deem that name worthy
of etching into my memories.
THMIMSSP.
The holy mother's infinite mercy softens severe punishment.
TCTCDBPT
The compassion and the conviction
directly beg appeal to the righteous God
TROGBWIMAATH.
to be with mercy and ascend to Heaven!
Now!
Leave it to me!
Saint Destroyer!
Mr. William, glad to see you're well!
That's the power of William Orwell!
That was for deceiving me and
taking all the glory for yourself.
So, do you really intend to leave England?
Yes.
You're made to be more than a mere mercenary.
Here I used my connections to get
you knighted, and you just refuse?
What are you trying to achieve?
I've never wanted to achieve anything special.
Neither knight nor mercenary works for me.
I'm sure you understand that.
You...
I'll protect from the outside
and you protect from the inside.
That allows us to have the widest range of options.
So there's no use in trying to stop you.
That's right.
You've probably ordered me a coat of arms
from an artisan on the outskirts of London.
Please cancel that order.
How could I?
How could I let go of that?
A Certain Magical Index
Damn it.
You're awake!
Yeah.
Here, use this.
Oh, don't work yourself too hard.
You need to recover after that fight.
I remember almost nothing
after sneaking out of the hospital.
Really?!
We defeated one of the handful
of Saints in existence!
That was so magical,
it felt like Santa had tripped
and scattered presents all over!
No?
So basically, you and the Amakusa Church
are awesome for beating Acqua, right?
No, that's not how I meant it.
Although it's kinda true.
But that's not what I wanted to say.
Wait, what day is it?
Don't tell me I'm getting held back
because I've missed too many classes!
I've been involved in way too many incidents lately.
No! You shouldn't get up!
Oh! Uhm... I...
Touma!
I was the one sitting there until just now.
It's not what it looks like!
You still haven't apologized for sneaking
out of the hospital without telling me!
Yes, she's right!
Seriously?
I can't believe you went to fight Acqua in that state!
Acqua?! The one from God's Right Seat?!
Why didn't you get me to help
against such a powerful enemy, Touma?!
What?
Wait, when did Itsuwa switch to Index's side?
Is this the famous Amakusa
adaptability to their surroundings?
Hi there, missy!
The sun's gonna set before you make up your mind.
You have to thank Kamiyan for helping
out the Amakusa Church, don't you?
I-I know that.
But—
And? I hope you brought
a fallen-angel maid costume.
H-How could I bring such a thing?!
I could never do that with other people around,
not to mention the girl's photographic memory!
I suspected you'd need one!
Ta-da!
I brought an improved sexy
fallen-angel maid costume for you!
See how it shows the cleavage,
and how revealing the skirt is!
Huh? What are you going to do, then?
How are you going to thank him, missy?!
I hope you're not planning to just
tip your head to the side and say
"I'm grateful for what you did", are you?!
S-So what should I do, then?
All I can do is thank him from the bottom—
Pf! Aren't we self-important!
Here's a question for you!
What is the purpose of those things you have?
Those mammalian features,
otherwise known as boobs!
I'm asking what those are for!
Wh-What?
Missy, are you sure about going at such a slow pace?
Wh-What are you talking about?
I'm talking about Itsuwa.
I'm saying she'd put on a sexy
fallen-angel maid costume for him any day!
What? Really?
In other words, you're way behind her in femininity!
Man, this woman is all pride. She doesn't know
selfless effort for the sake of others.
I don't think I deserve that!
Can you really guide the lost sheep like that?
So, what are you going to do?
What are you gonna do?!
What are you gonna do?! What are you gonna do?!
You have no mercy for my head
even when I'm this beaten up.
It's all your fault, Touma!
Excuse me.
How in the world did they defeat Acqua?!
That just means that they've grown stronger too.
Did you just come from inside,
Fiamma of the Right?!
That reaction was not befitting
of the one holding the post of Pope.
What do you intend to do?
First, I'll strike at Britain.
What?
Don't you get it?
We basically have control over
all of Europe, apart from Britain.
We'll have the other countries starve them out.
I don't see how that would hurt Academy City.
Forget Academy City.
We want a certain thing that's in Britain.
What are you talking about?
We need to set a great power
in motion in order to obtain it.
That's madness.
And you call yourself a Christian?!
What do you think?
Shit!
That's really inappropriate
language for your position.
Scoundrel! Do you really think
I'm going to overlook this?!
Are you going to fight me?
Me, the leader of God's Right Seat?
Don't underestimate me.
I call upon the twelve apostles!
I beseech the Lord, who is beyond all numbers!
Grant me power!
I know how to use it righteously!
I wish for nothing but that power
to defeat our enemy!
You shall be held for forty years.
Experience this long period
with nothing but your own thoughts
and use the time to study
and improve your immature mind.
That power! How?!
Yes, the right arm is the symbol of miracles.
And Michael's right arm
holds the strongest weapon.
My right arm holds the manifestation
of the power I am to wield,
but it lacks an output terminal
that could amass and control it.
So in that state I can only wield
a tiny amount of that power.
Tell me, wouldn't you like to have it?
The Holy Right that is the symbol
of numerous miracles.
It can't be!
I can use it.
In order to rein in overwhelming power,
you need overwhelming knowledge
beyond what humans can have.
Th-The Index of Prohibited Books!
Those Brits made a nice compilation for me.
I won't allow you!
An overwhelmingly lopsided
fight is so silly. I quite enjoy it.
He took the entire force of it.
I'll admit he has guts.
Hah! You took the entire force of that blow?
You wouldn't have ended up like that
if you'd let it destroy the town.
Fiamma's target is in Britain. Go!
You have no right to order me!
But I'd also love to off that shithead,
so I'll let it slide.
I have news to report.
There has been some infighting
inside the Roman Catholic Church.
The Pope was involved
and has been severely injured.
Based on the amount of magic power observed,
there should be massive damage to Vatican City,
but that's just speculation at this point.
You do-gooder.
Even so, I bet you still laughed, you do-gooder.
The restoration of the UNDER_LINE information
network will take another few hours, huh?
Integrate and process the information
received the moment before it went down.
Compare the data from brain functions
and from AIM Diffusion Fields to establish
the quality and amount of power of the right arm.
Point central 0 maintains stable level of 3.
The center is still in idle mode.
Default rotation rate confirmed.
Subject designated "Imagine Breaker":
influence coefficient 98%.
The main plan axis is currently aligned to position 1
in Academy City and operating according to plan.
Next Time
Index and I head for Britain
on the order of the Archbishop.
The sorcerers put their insidious
secret plan in motion on the airplane.
Next time: "Sky Bus 365".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.