Sorry to call you in so late at night.
Oh, it's no problem.
Did something happen?
Actually, there's something I want to tell you.
That's a lot of stuff.
I'm sure Sana will be hungry,
so I brought lots of her favorite foods.
I see.
I've already informed our clients,
but I'll need you two to watch
the shop while I'm away.
Can you do that?
Of course!
Leave it to us.
Thanks.
Oh, there he is.
All right!
Mirror, mirror, on the wall
I want to change this world
The streetlight brightens up the night
And brings forth a sea of light
That reaches far into the distance
I dream upon a restless star
As I wait for the night to end
So I can continue searching for the future
The curtains covering a new stage
slowly part
as I wake up
Wonder drive! Let's start running now!
Wonder drive! To the world ahead of us!
Uncertainty, hesitation, and confusion
Just throw it all away!
Wonder drive! Keep charging along this path
Replace that clock's rhythm with your own
We are walking along a road
No one has yet dreamed of
Mirror, mirror, on the wall
I want to change this world
The Queen and the Witch
ERROR
NO SERVICE
It's no good. There's no service.
"No service"? The thing that happens underground?
Yeah. I've never actually seen it before.
I think we're in the deepest part of Wonderland.
We fell from up there, right?
I think so...
Then, if we go up, we can get back
to that last door, right?
I don't know...
What do you mean?
You know, don't you?
Don't be mean! Just tell me!
I really don't know!
I can't use the power that I normally use,
and I've never been to this part
of Wonderland, either...
Where are you going?
Where else? To look for the exit.
I don't think that'll work!
Hey!
You're kidding, right? You'll tire yourself out!
Hey! Wait for me!
Hey!
Wait...
CAUTION
BIKE LANE CHANGE
I told them everything.
Including where Sana came from
and what kind of power she possesses.
Sorry.
I know Naitou told us to keep it as quiet as possible.
In this situation, you had no choice.
I would imagine that they were quite surprised.
SLOW
DOWN
Nah, seems they already had their hunches...
What did they say?
Hardly anything.
"Sana's still just Sana, isn't she?" That's it.
I'm sure that would make her really happy.
Hold on!
This is pointless!
Sana was born in Wonderland,
but we still don't know much about it.
Please be very careful, both of you.
Wow...
The name sounds kinda like
an amusement park, doesn't it?
Are you worried?
What about you?
When Sana was taken before,
I was really worried.
But it all worked out in the end, didn't it?
So I'm gonna believe that it'll be okay this time, too!
I see.
Besides,
I'm from planet happy-ending!
But that time, Naitou was the one driving...
Oh? Would you have preferred Naitou?
Nope, I prefer you.
That's a relief.
Mom!
No way...
I told you... it wouldn't work.
I think the exit disappeared
when my power stopped working...
That can't be.
I have to stay with my mom forever!
Send me home right now!
I... I want to go home too.
I don't think anyone's in there!
I'm telling the truth...
We believe the girl currently with Sana
was responsible for the Harajuku incident.
Imai Pharmaceutical Corporation
There's no cell signal where they are,
so we lack detailed intel.
Wonderland is constantly changing.
Though, since we successfully
confirmed they're both there,
we've been unable to learn anything
else about what's going on inside.
It's possible that we could
encounter unpredictable dangers,
so please be very careful.
We still can't see it?
We can verify there's a signal, but that's all.
The energy signal coming from inside is stronger.
Does that mean it's expanding?
Most likely.
Will it affect this world?
Calculating that now.
Please enter your twelve-digit passcode.
So this is where Sana was born?
And those two girls are somewhere in here?
Yes.
Ma'am!
That form is second to none...
Yamada, what is your job?
To back you up and to collect data on Wonderland!
Good. As long as you know that.
Wait, Grandpa!
Mr. Kashimura, please wait!
Excuse me! Is anyone here?
If so, please answer me!
Is anyone here?
What's wrong, Grandpa?
That's Sana...
with Asahi and Yonaga, isn't it?
Seems so.
Is that...
the stuffed pig I bought for her?
Oh! The spotted pig!
I bet if we follow that pig, we'll find Sana!
Isn't that a bit of a shot in the dark?
Huh? Is it?
Sounds like our best option to me.
Right?
Maybe we should consider this further.
Mr. Kashimura? Mr. Kashimura!
Is this another of Sana's memories?
No idea.
I'll see if I can get a birds-eye view.
#41.
Huh?
What?!
Ichijou?!
Mom...
I'm sorry.
I was only trying to get you
guys back for what happened.
I had no idea we'd get stuck in here.
Sorry.
This is all my fault.
I'm really sorry.
No...
This might have been my doing.
Hey, Grandpa...
Do you think Ichijou is okay?
I thought you were a happy alien.
Huh?
Aren't you?
I am!
Ichijou's really strong, isn't she?
Yeah, she sure is.
What now?
It's almost like someone's mocking us.
This Wonderland place is going
to need a stern talking to later on.
Wow!
You're gonna give Wonderland a lecture!
Hey, what is that?
I think it's practicing.
Practicing what?
The things it's learned.
The things it's learned?
Wonderland wants to know
what the world is made up of.
Not just things like colors,
shapes, smells, and flavors...
I think it wants to know about all of its rules.
Like the kinds of mechanisms that make it up,
what life is made of,
and how humans see the world.
I think it gathers all of those things from our world,
and it imitates them.
Maybe the Mirror Gates are the peepholes
that Wonderland uses to do that.
At first, I think Wonderland was
only a bit bigger than this room.
But eventually, I think it'll become
a whole universe of its own.
Strange...
Everything you say is so unbelievable,
but for some reason, I don't think you're lying at all.
You're a mysterious girl.
I'm not weird!
I didn't say you were weird.
I'm not lying!
I didn't say you were lying, either.
You're so funny.
I'm not funny!
Then, wouldn't this world have to have thought
of something really amazing?
It's really weird and beyond my comprehension,
but it's absolutely beautiful.
If this world
will eventually become a different one,
then maybe I could just live here forever.
I've succeeded in running away.
Are you sure about that?
About what?
U-Uh...
Well, if you stay here forever, you'll be bored!
And didn't you say you wanted
to go back to your mom?!
Leave me alone.
You wouldn't understand.
I'm sorry.
That was a mean thing to say.
I'm not sure where to start.
You see,
my mom hates me.
By "mom," do you mean your mother?
That's right.
I see...
My Sanae has a mother, too,
and that mother's father is Zouroku.
But I don't have either, so I don't really get it.
Really?
Yeah.
Hey... Can I tell you something?
Sure.
My parents have been fighting for years now.
Why?
I failed my elementary school entrance exam,
and I disappointed my mom.
Ever since then, Mom won't even look me in the eye.
So I think it's best if I'm not there.
That way, Mom and Dad won't fight,
and they can always be happy.
Also, sometimes Mom looks at me
as if she's looking in from
a universe of endless darkness.
When I see her like that, it makes me think...
I love my mom...
but she probably wishes I weren't her daughter...
I don't want to go home!
I should never have existed at all!
H-Hey...
This might make you mad...
But I think it's good that you exist.
Thanks.
I think you're wrong.
I don't think there's anyone
who should or shouldn't exist.
That's why it scares me
to think about those things...
You know, I...
was born here.
...huh?
I'm not human like everyone else.
I think I'm Wonderland itself.
That's it for practice!
Thank you!
Wanna go somewhere?
Let's get ice cream!
Okay.
Oh, I've got cram school now.
The number you have dialed
is out of the service area or—
Hatori
No Response
Hatori...
You're not human?
Yeah.
H-Huh?
W-Wait, what are you...?
L-Listen...
The truth is, I was told not to tell anyone about this.
When I was first born here, I was something else...
Something I can't explain or describe.
I don't think I was even shaped like a human.
Then, before I knew it, I had eyes and a body,
and I looked like this.
But I'm pretty sure I was a part of Wonderland.
You don't believe me?
That's not it.
I'm just surprised.
I figured it out after hearing about you.
I was similar, and it made
me feel frazzled for a long time.
I'm pretty sure I'm still connected
to this place, somehow.
The outside world and real humans
are what Wonderland wants to know about.
I guess I must be some kind of
communication device for Wonderland.
If that's true, many others
could take my place, though.
Maybe my existence isn't really necessary,
and I don't matter at all...
Maybe it's wrong for me to care about
anyone when I'm not actually needed.
U-Uh, I mean...
I don't have a mom, so maybe you
don't like it when I compare myself to you!
Um, want me to wipe your tears?
No.
You know, since I left Wonderland,
I found lots of new things I like.
I've met so many people,
and found things that are
delicious, fun, and exciting,
and things that won't leave my mind,
even if they're really annoying.
Maybe the things that make me
feel frazzled are actually all wrong,
and I shouldn't worry about them at all.
I can't prove it,
but I do worry about them!
That's why I decided to insist that they are necessary!
So hearing you say it'd be better if you weren't around is just...
I mean, it's kind of...
You really are a mysterious girl.
Really? I'm mysterious?
Huh? What are you doing?
My Sanae does this to me a lot.
"Your" Sanae?
Yeah.
All the people I know are big.
So even when I talk about stuff like this,
they don't listen.
I always feel so frazzled,
but they just say I'm doing great,
or that I'll understand when I'm older.
How old are you?
Uh, I don't know.
Between eight and ten.
We might be around the same age, then.
Really? I think I'm older than you!
No, I'm older than you.
No, I am!
Can I stay like this for just a little bit?
When I was little, my mom held me like this a lot.
I introduced myself,
but everyone laughed and said I was weird.
When the teacher said I didn't have to
introduce myself when I enter the classroom,
they all laughed at me again!
And then... And then...
You don't need to worry about any of that.
You introduced yourself, just like I told you to.
Oh, my little crybaby Hatori...
I'll have to squeeze you real tight.
Do you remember, Mom?
I was sad then,
yet so happy.
I felt truly blessed.
This is just like back then.
I can hear her heartbeat...
Listen...
I'd like to see my mom once more.
Will you help me?
Yeah.
Thanks.
Hidden beneath this scab
Are a great many things all working in unison
So please hold on just a little bit longer
Because I'll change myself starting from there
When do I start
To truly become myself?
Let's go meet the people who deserve my affection
We'll find them scattered across the world
I want to learn so much about them
One person, another person, more and more people
Three, four, five, six, the number rises and rises
Finding out the truth
Can sometimes be painful, but...
The world will keep moving
On and on, forever and ever
Even far into the future
Remaining unchanged
Next Episode
I'm Home
I'm Home.