Shikishima
Well, Hatori... I'm going home for today.
Okay. Sorry.
Shikishima
What is this power?
What am I supposed to do with it?
When I use my magic, I get so hungry
that I can't think about anything.
Even standing up is a hassle.
I can't be like that...
I know I can't be like that, but...
Hatori?
What are you doing over here?
Do you feel sick?
Can you stand?
You're so kind, Mom.
Hatori?
Which "Mom" are you right now?
What are you talking about?
I'm your mom.
What's wrong with you, Hatori?
What do I do, Mom?
I...
What?
It's all okay.
Your mom is right here.
No, Mom...
I'm not...
For failing to follow her orders,
the little girl became an evil witch.
And then, she was burned at the stake.
Mirror, mirror, on the wall
I want to change this world
The streetlight brightens up the night
And brings forth a sea of light
That reaches far into the distance
I dream upon a restless star
As I wait for the night to end
So I can continue searching for the future
The curtains covering a new stage
slowly part
as I wake up
Wonder drive! Let's start running now!
Wonder drive! To the world ahead of us!
Uncertainty, hesitation, and confusion
Just throw it all away!
Wonder drive! Keep charging along this path
Replace that clock's rhythm with your own
We are walking along a road
No one has yet dreamed of
Mirror, mirror, on the wall
I want to change this world
Where the Cheshire Cat Smiles
U-Um...
I really think we should help...
Oh, no, don't worry about it.
You're our guests.
Just have a seat and wait.
Zouroku...
Zouroku!
You guys, where... Where's Zouroku?
Oh, you're up, Sana?
What's wrong?
You're all right?
You won't go all weird again?
You're back to normal?
Something really did happen, then?
Zouroku!
Okay, I'm off.
If anything happens, call me!
Even if nothing happens, call me!
All right, I get it.
I'll be home late, so if anything happens,
you guys call me, too.
B-Be well!
Okay.
Well, it's cold. Let's hurry back inside.
Yeah...
Huh? Why are you two here?
Why?
Unreal!
They waited for you to wake up
because they were worried about you.
I was worried, too.
Is that true?
W-Well...
Coming all this way,
only to leave, would be a waste!
Oh, come on, Sis!
Today's
Chores
Meal (Morning)
Meal (Night)
Take Out Trash
Laundry (Dry)
Laundry (Fold)
Sanae
Grandpa
Sana
Okay, I'll start cooking right away.
Today's
Chores
Meal (Morning)
Laundry (Dry)
Laundry (Fold)
Sanae
Grandpa
Chores
Meal (Morning)
Meal (Night)
Laundry (Dry)
Sanae
Grandpa
Meal (Night)
Laundry (Dry)
Why don't you girls take a bath,
and then relax a bit?
Okay.
Huh?!
Sana, you take baths?
Wh-Why are you surprised?
Because you never took them before!
W-Well, these days, I do... sometimes.
Wow!
Your voices were in perfect sync!
Lately, Sana likes using bath additives, you see.
Huh...
She says the bubbly stuff feels really nice.
And she likes hot spring bath salts, too.
Her favorite is—
Hey!
When do you two want your bath?
Want one after we eat or before?
Oh, either one's fine.
We normally take ours together.
Oh?
Well, that's fine, too.
Y-You idiot! You didn't have to tell her that!
Huh?
Hey, why are they talking about taking a bath?
Well, you see,
Grandpa told them to stay over tonight.
Stay over?
Oh, they're sleeping here?
That's right.
Wow! Really?
Yes, really.
Okay, Sana, show them where the towels are!
Sure!
I'm in charge of the towels, you know!
Every day!
Oh, want some juice? Or there's milk, too!
When you drink, you put one hand on your waist!
You have to, or it's wrong!
Sana is actually washing herself...
And without using her power, either.
Of course! You're supposed to wash
yourself before getting in the bath.
If you don't, there's more bacteria!
Get in up to your shoulders,
and don't get out until you count to 100.
It's a crow's quick bath!
What's a "crow's quick bath"?
A crow's quick bath is a crow taking a quick bath!
You have to dry it thoroughly, or you'll get sick!
You three, dinner's ready!
Let's eat!
Thanks for the meal!
That was fast!
Today's
Chores
Meal (Morning)
Meal (Night)
Take Out Trash
Laundry (Dry)
Laundry (Fold)
Sanae
Grandpa
Sana
Kashimura Sana
Sana is washing dishes...
Not only that...
She takes care of the flowers, does laundry,
and even takes out the trash when it's her turn.
Oh, wow...
Kashimura Sana
There.
Hello, Grandpa?
Okay, got it.
Is that Zouroku?
Yep, everything is fine.
Hey, what's Zouroku saying?
Just a second.
I'll pass the phone to Sana.
Here.
Hi, Zouroku?
Yeah, much better!
No, we aren't fighting at all!
It's true! I'm not lying!
I haven't used my power, either!
I ate lots at dinner.
And I'll brush my teeth before bed!
It's too small!
The futons won't all fit in here!
Are we really gonna sleep together?
Well, they said we could, right?
You two, it's late already. We need to be quiet.
Oh, it's fine. It's just a little fun.
It isn't fine!
Hey, you guys switched places.
Huh?
What do you mean?
What?
S-Stop!
Time to get you back, for what you always do!
Whoops...
Sana, right here!
Huh, what?
What's going on?
Come on... Hurry up!
No! Not there!
I don't get it, but I'm gonna do it, too!
There! Take that!
Shh.
R-Right.
Oh, gosh, that's so nice!
Twins, huh? Sisters, huh?
I wish I could've joined in!
Zouroku's late...
G-Guess being a florist is hard work.
Usually...
Well, sometimes. He's not busy.
But today...
because of that girl...
We don't remember anything about it.
A Dream of Alice that can freeze people...
Were you scared?
Scared...
Yeah.
I was really scared.
Everyone stopped moving.
Only I could.
Then, I wonder...
...if she was scared too.
She's...
She's evil.
I'll never forgive her!
She made weird things happen to you, too.
Since you guys were coming over today,
Zouroku was supposed to get off work early.
It's all her fault.
She makes me feel all frazzled!
Zouroku...
Oh? You're still awake?
I was asleep, but I woke up.
Hey, cut that out.
Are you done for today?
You won't go anywhere else?
No, I'm not going anywhere.
Hey, don't cling like that.
You'll end up smelling of cigarettes,
and Sanae'll get mad.
No!
All right, all right...
I'll take a bath. Let go, just for a bit.
Are your friends asleep already?
Zouroku...
Don't go anywhere else...
Don't turn all weird again.
All right already.
Come on, move...
I never would've imagined Sana acting like that.
Yeah.
Thank you for having us.
Come visit again sometime.
We will!
Asahi! Yonaga! See you later!
Come stay over again.
Promise you will!
We promise!
Well, I should go, too.
Huh?
Aren't you off today?
I have to redo all the arrangements
that went bad yesterday.
I'll be home early.
It must be rough for Grandpa...
It's her fault.
I'm gonna get her good.
Shikishima
Welcome.
Um, is Hatori here?
She's upstairs.
Shikishima
Here you go.
Oh, thank you.
Well, take your time.
Thanks, Mom.
Hatori, why haven't you been at school?
I won't be going to school anymore.
Sorry.
But you know it's for the best.
No, it isn't.
Why are you apologizing?
None of this is your fault!
The police have come by several times.
But I sent them away.
I'm a witch, so no one can do anything to me.
I'm an evil witch.
I'm sorry, Ayumu.
I won't be running away, after all.
I realized that I need to stay with my mom and dad.
I didn't tell you before,
but they'd been fighting for a long time.
Because of me.
Because I couldn't live up to Mom's expectations.
When I use my magic, they're like they were.
But once the magic wears off,
they go back to fighting.
So I have to stay with them forever.
Even if it's all a lie, I don't care.
Harajuku Station



Why?
I know this can't be right.
I don't want to accept that there's nothing I can do...
I won't accept it!
I'm back.
Welcome home.
Welcome back!
What's she doing?
I have no idea, but she's been at it all day.
Just watch me, you guys...
Shikishima
Shikishima Hatori, age 9, third grade.
Shikishima Hatori
An only child, living with her parents.
Harajuku security cameras
made it easy to identify her, but...
Yes?
This is Yamada. We spoke on the phone earlier.
I'm sorry?
Would you be Shikishima Hatori's mother?
I'd like to speak with you concerning Hatori.
Is Hatori at home right now?
U-Um...
What is this?
Do you want something from my daughter?
Uh, no, just to talk about...
Well, that's over.
Time to head back, Yamada.
Yeah.
Wait.
What's "over"?
Huh?
Well, it was... you know, that thing.
Oh, well.
Let's go eat! I'm starving!
Huh? I don't want beef bowls again.
You should be more considerate toward women.
Toward women!
What do you mean?
|
Why did you suddenly stop? That scared me!
Yamada, we've been had.
This is the fifth time.
Damn...
That girl's really something.
The only people who can go near
her house are those she allows.
The power to control others.
Then it's true.
If she'd only let us talk to her,
Miho Ayumu
we might be able to help her
with her problem, at least a little bit...
That girl the other day
used magic just like Hatori's.
If I can see that girl again,
maybe I can figure something out.
Hatori's magic hadn't ever been broken,
but that day, it was.
What is this magic?
Can she never get rid of it?
If I can find that girl, I'm sure...
Sorry, Ayumu.
Please don't ever come back.
Hatori!
I might end up hurting you.
B-But I don't care!
Because... Because you're—
Did you know, Ayumu?
If a bear comes down from the
mountains and attacks someone,
it can never be returned to the mountains.
It's killed.
When I was little, I used to wonder why
people would do something so cruel.
But now I understand.
Because it's the same with me.
I can't be among people anymore.
So, I'm sorry, but please don't come again.
I won't accept that, Hatori!
Hm? A foreign girl?
Saying she's blonde doesn't help much...
Why? Are you searching for someone?
There are lots of people like that around here...
I see.
Sorry.
Maybe this won't work, after all.
Too many people are here,
and I don't even know her name.
Wow, that looks good!
Okay, I'll have the usual.
Really?
The shop we went to.
What we did there last time was wrong.
Ow...
I-It doesn't hurt...
Where am I?
Huh? Wh-What is this?
Where did that hole go?
I finally found you!
Huh?
You evil, frazzling meanie,
I'm gonna teach you a lesson!
Hidden beneath this scab
Are a great many things all working in unison
So please hold on just a little bit longer
Because I'll change myself starting from there
When do I start
To truly become myself?
Let's go meet the people who deserve my affection
We'll find them scattered across the world
I want to learn so much about them
One person, another person, more and more people
Three, four, five, six, the number rises and rises
Finding out the truth
Can sometimes be painful, but...
The world will keep moving
On and on, forever and ever
Even far into the future
Remaining unchanged
Next Episode
The Little Queen
The Little Queen.