Yukishiro
It makes me so glad
that I wound up meeting you
as the blossoms bloomed.
Th-That's him, right? Eiji Busujima?
Even the Devil of West Junior High
can get beat up, huh?
Morning. Did you oversleep again, Nanako?
Words silently float down, I start to feel lighter
As my feelings begin to take shape
It looks like love's in the air
It feels as though the rain is more calming than ever
Whenever I'm with you
Which are the words I need to write out
To make them last and for them to never fade?
If nothing changes, this'll be nothing more than a distant memory
Isn't that right, God?
The moment before a droplet breaks, or before the train comes
I pray they will never end
"Please let it go on forever"
Is that too much to ask?
Verse 1
The 5-7-5 Girl
Who wants to solve this problem?
Let's see... Yukishiro?
Nanako Yukishiro, do you think you can solve it?
Oh, right. Sorry.
I forgot you didn't like to talk.
Just write your answer down
and show me when you're done.
To tell you the truth,
I did not get any of
the last five problems.
Then tell me that five problems ago!
Hey, Nanako, why do you only
communicate in writing?
'Cause I find it hard
to organize all my thoughts
when I try to speak.
Really? I guess a syllable limit helps, then.
But what do you do if you
have to go to the toilet?
Right, makes sense.
Nanako, did you decide what to have?
Beef bowl, eh? Comin' right up.
Oh, how much do you want?
You can have a large portion for no extra cost.
If you want, I can just add some extra meat.
Large portion?
Do you want an egg and pickled ginger?
Just extra meat?
You can have extra stock too.
Ginger eggs...
Extra stock... I can't eat that much!
Just give her the standard portion of everything.
Aren't you glad it all worked out?
Yukishiro's just adorable.
I like how she's so meek.
I wonder if she's got a boyfriend...
Hm? What's wrong?
I just remembered
that I don't like eating things
with onions in them.
Want to trade for my rice omelette?
I also like how she's kinda
absent-minded sometimes.
"Kinda"?
Busujima got himself hurt again.
He's way too scary for me to talk to.
Huh? Whaddaya want?
Already time for club, eh?
Oh, right. Busujima is in
the literary club with Nanako.
How'd he end up there?
Beats me.
Hm? Oh, you're wondering how I got hurt?
It happened when I was playing with my little sister!
She just gets cuter and cuter every day!
Oh, I wrote a verse about my
feelings at the time. Ready for it?
My little sister
is so super-duper cute
that it's kinda nuts.
What'cha think? I'm pretty proud of it myself.
The "super-duper" perfectly captures
how super cute she is, don'tcha think?
Ah...
I can't help it. This is just how my face is...
How about you try
relaxing your face a bit
with a nice big smile?
Oh, that could work. Something like this?
N-Nanako, heading to club? W-Work hard now...
One of Nanako's old pals? I gotta say something.
First impressions are important.
Pleased to meet ya.
I'm Nanako's pal! Busujima's the name.
H-He's got it in for me!
Literary Club
THEME
Oh, you're finally here.
Heya, President Amane!
How's school treating you so far?
I just had my first chat with someone
from my year other than Nanako!
Wow, way to go. What did you talk about?
No! Keep him away from me!
Wait! Don't run!
How was that a chat?!
Seriously, your self-introduction is meant to
let people get to know you, not scare them off!
Good point.
Let's introduce ourselves with senryu instead!
Yes, ma'am!
Does this seem right?
Hello, good morning,
it's very nice to meet you,
my name's Eiji Bu.
Hello, good morning,
it's very nice to meet you,
my name's Eiji Bu.
Hello, good morning,
it's very nice to meet you,
my name's Eiji Bu.
Hello, good morning,
it's very nice to meet you,
my name's Eiji Bu.
Hello, good morning,
it's very nice to meet you,
my name's Eiji Bu.
Hello, good morning,
it's very nice to meet you,
my name's Eiji Bu.
Hello, good morning,
it's very nice to meet you,
my name's Eiji Bu.
Hello, good morning,
it's very nice to meet you,
my name's Eiji Bu.
Hello, good morning,
it's very nice to meet you,
my name's Eiji Bu.
Hello, good morning,
it's very nice to meet you,
my name's Eiji Bu.
Hello, good morning,
it's very nice to meet you,
my name's Eiji Bu.
Hello, good morning,
it's very nice to meet you,
my name's Eiji Bu.
Hello, good morning,
it's very nice to meet you,
my name's Eiji Bu.
Hello, good morning,
it's very nice to meet you,
my name's Eiji Bu.
Hello, good morning,
it's very nice to meet you,
my name's Eiji Bu.
Well, I respect you for sticking to the syllable limit,
but if it's incomplete that defeats the purpose.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Please check out my blog
if you'd like to see more and
learn all about me.
Come on now, take this seriously.
Hang on, you've got a blog?
THEME
Anyway, we'll leave the self-introductions there.
Let's try making senryu based
on the theme "April" instead.
THEME
April...
You don't need to think too hard about it.
For instance, try just putting
the view you see into words.
The sky, birds and trees,
a forest and power poles,
and cherry blossoms.
How about you think a little harder than that.
Eighty-five up top,
a bit over fifty-nine,
eighty-two below.
Pardon?
Y-Yo, Prez, your chest's that stacked?!
I'm not part of the view!
Senryu sure is difficult.
You don't need to be so serious about it.
If you can't think of anything, try word associations.
Let your imagination run wild,
and instill more depth into your verse.
spring
entrance
ceremony
encounters
love
in the air
I see...
spring
get into
a fight
beat 'em up
get into
another fight
beat 'em up
It didn't run very wild.
spring
I think you need a more open mind.
And lay off the beating up part.
Come to think of it, Prez, ever since we first
met you've never seemed that scared of me.
Huh? Well, I guess not...
Heya! Busujima's the name!
I mean, you certainly did give me
a fright when you first stopped by.
TODAY'S
THEME
FAMILY
But...
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Me, my pet rabbit,
my mom and little sister,
and then my old man.
Well, how do I put this...
He seemed very easy to handle.
'Sup?
spring
Hey, Nanako, you're supposed
to have a more open mind.
spring
That's not the problem here!
Hey, Ei, please tell me,
what was it that made you choose
to pick up senryu?
Huh? Well...
He's unstoppable! This is what
the Devil of West Junior High can do?!
Who're ya callin' a devil?
You're the one who picked a fight with me!
I'm sick an' tired of fighting!
You should spend your days
spreadin' joy instead of blood!
Throw punches no more!
Heh, I just kinda got caught up in this great rhythm
and ended up saying something real cool.
Huh? Isn't that guy Busujima,
the Devil of West Junior High?
Shut up! He'll hear us!
My name's gotten around.
Hey, Nanako. Put some distance between us.
Else they'll start getting scared of you too.
I don't care at all
how other people see me
when I am with you.
Huh? Wait, you... Are you saying...
Ya moron, save that shtick for the guy you like!
Although, they do say not
to look a gift horse in the mouth.
Ow! That hurts!
Hey, ouch, come on...
Huh? What the heck are they up to?
Yukishiro
Welcome home, Nanako.
I heard some delinquent joined the literary club.
How did it go?
He's not good with words,
and when he does try to smile,
he makes the girls flee.
We two are so different that it's funny
Even our reflections in the display window too
When you smile, it's like the sun
And I can feel a gentle wind begin to blow
Even these ordinary uneventful days
Start shining when I'm with you
No matter what might happen
Even if we sometimes hurt each other
I'll keep believing in these unremarkable days
The next episode
of Senryu Girl is titled:
"Nanako Tries to...
...Lose Weight!"
Next Time, Verse 2
"Nanako Tries to Lose Weight"