Is Busujima crying?
Did someone bust up the other dudes in his gang?
Hey, Eiji!
You left your gym clothes behind this morning.
I couldn't sit idly by and leave
my cute little brother without them.
Wha—I told you not to come by my classroom, Koto!
Oh my! Aren't we the cheeky one.
Whatever, just get out already!
What did I do to deserve this?
The older sister
of the delinquent looks like
a total hottie!
- Classmates
The older sister
of the delinquent looks like
a total hottie!
- Classmates
The older sister
of the delinquent looks like
a total hottie!
Words silently float down, I start to feel lighter
As my feelings begin to take shape
It looks like love's in the air
It feels as though the rain is more calming than ever
Whenever I'm with you
Which are the words I need to write out
To make them last and for them to never fade?
If nothing changes, this'll be nothing more than a distant memory
Isn't that right, God?
The moment before a droplet breaks, or before the train comes
I pray they will never end
"Please let it go on forever"
Is that too much to ask?
Verse 2
Nanako Tries to
Lose Weight
Verse 2
Nanako Tries to
Lose Weight
So, for today, by his own request...
Getting people to like Eiji
We will now convene this very special meeting!
Thank ya kindly!
It seems he just can't shake this scary image of his.
I'm a nice guy under it all, though...
Then how about a verse that
expresses just how nice you are?
I prefer to give
away the larger part when
splitting popsicles.
That's just lame!
Getting people to like Eiji
On the online forum the students use,
they posted a "Karai High Rankings" list.
Eiji got #2 on the "Biggest Incongruity
Between Looks and Choice of Club" list.
Who the heck was #1?!
Getting people to like Eiji
You might have been able to use that
to present yourself as "unexpectedly cute",
but not with that weak second place standing.
"Unexpected"?
Huh?
Girls are fond of boys
who have sides to them that they
had not expected.
Getting people to like Eiji
Nanako, can you think of anything?
For example, something
you wish Eiji would stop doing.
But I think that Ei
is perfectly fine and good
just the way he is.
But if you really had to pick something?
Occasionally
he will pull an angry face
when he is thinking.
Occasionally
he will pull an angry face
when he is thinking.
Occasionally
he will pull an angry face
when he is thinking.
Occasionally
he will pull an angry face
when he is thinking.
Wait, for real?
Getting people to like Eiji
Yeah, that always spooks me a little.
Yo, I've got no freakin' clue
what you're talking about!
You sure? Try thinking back.
Have I really done that...?
There it is! You're doing it right now!
Well, getting people to like me
was always a lost cause...
I don't think that's true
'cause I can think of lots of
good things about you.
Huh?
You prefer to give
away the larger part when
we're sharing donuts.
You prefer to give
away the larger part when
we're sharing soda.
Wait...
When you put it that way, it is super lame!
Getting people to like Eiji
Hello there, literary club members.
Thank you for all the kindness you've shown Eiji.
I'm Eiji's sister, Koto Otsuki.
Don't introduce yourself with a lie!
You're just a childhood friend!
I changed your diapers, you know.
How? You're only two years older!
Anyway, Eiji.
Are you attending all your classes?
Oh, look at you. Let's take care of that eye crud.
Do you have tissues?
Getting people to like Eiji
I'll give you mine!
Oh, and if your tummy hurts,
I've got medicine, so tell me right away.
Quit it! You're embarrassing me! Get outta here!
I feel like I could watch this all day.
If you would like to,
we should totally go out
for tea together.
My, I'm happy you'd ask.
But I'll have to decline.
I've got club activities to attend to.
What club are you in, Koto?
I'm in the close-quarters combat club.
I think we just found out who
#1 on that incongruity list is!
Ei, I'd like to know,
do you have a girlfriend yet,
or are you single?
What?! Why are you asking something stupid like—
Huh?
Oh, don't be gettin' embarrassed
over something like that.
We all let one loose occasionally.
Hey, Nanako,
how 'bout we go grab some food?
I thought you hated onions.
I did all I could
to overcome my dislikes
and enjoy more food!
Wow, that's great.
You sure can put it away.
Oh, right. Is it just me,
or have you gotten a little chubby?
Nanako, breakfast is ready!
Hey, Hiro, tell me,
do you think I've put on weight,
or is it just me?
N-Nanako is trying to lose weight?!
C-Could she be doing it for some gu—
What? I dunno about your appearance,
but you definitely eat way too much.
You eat more than that one
sumo wrestler that I saw on TV.
Maybe you should cut ba—
Help!
That's a weird way to get angry!
Just eat without thinking about it too much.
You're still a growing girl.
D-Dad?
Oh, don't mind your father.
...I don't want that.
Huh? Weight loss help?
Well, I do have some tips.
Who is it that you want to
show off your new, slim self to?
Well, it's probably Eiji as usual.
You've got it all wrong!
The one I'm showing it to
is you, President!
What? M-Me?
Well, I can't say I'm opposed to the idea.
What? Secrets to getting into shape?
You're super slim though, Nanako.
Oh, I know! It's for Eiji, isn't it?
You're just so cute.
In that case...
If you want a firmer stomach,
how about some sit-ups?
I'm good to go, Coach!
I'm ready to go through Hell,
so give me your worst!
Let's start off with thirty.
Go as slowly as you need to.
Go.
Let me hug you just for a bit!
Nanako!
It's Nanako and Koto.
Are they exercising?
I kinda feel left out here.
That's how you break the neck
of someone with a knife.
What are you teaching Nanako?!
Hey, Koto.
What are you doing with Nanako?
That's a secret.
Wh-Why?
Oh, you're so dense, Eiji.
Huh?
It's for your sake, you know.
My sake?
You mean...
Nanako wants to break my neck?!
One Week
Later
Heya.
Huh? What's the deal with that look?
Don't tell me you're gonna break my—
Huh?
So, what do you think?
My stomach is firmer now
than it was before!
Well...
I can't really say...
I mean, this is the first time
I've touched your stomach.
President? What are you doing?
Huh? Um, well...
A disguise?
By the way, how come you don't have a boyfriend?
That came out of nowhere.
I'm just genuinely curious.
You're cute and in great shape.
You could have your pick of any boy around here.
Oh my, President.
You trying to hit on me?
Wh-Why would you think that?
I don't have it as good as you think I do.
There are tons of girls cuter than me out there.
You think?
Could it be that there's already
someone you're interested in?
Well...
I'm Eiji.
And you?
Nah, there isn't.
Then...?
Even if there were, it's best if things
between us stay the way they are.
Huh? Why would you say that?
You see, I'm...
his big sister.
So who are you supposed to be?
Hey! That's not a very nice way to ask.
Why's that?
Because you should respect your elders.
Well, my bad. So what's your name?
Hm...
I'm Koto, you can think of me as your big sister.
My big sister...?
Well, I guess things are fine just the way they are.
We two are so different that it's funny
Even our reflections in the display window
When you smile, it's like the sun
And I can feel a gentle wind begin to blow
Even these ordinary uneventful days
Start shining when I'm with you
No matter what might happen
Even if we sometimes hurt each other
I'll keep believing in these unremarkable days
The next episode
of Senryu Girl is titled:
"Let's Go to the A—
—musement park!"
Next Time, Verse 3
"Let's Go to the Amusement Park"