Kunahama Institute High School
How come you're taking
Asuka-senpai's handouts to her?
Well, why not?
You don't have practice because of the rain, right?
Go with me.
You're asking me to go out with you?
Less talk, more walk.
Misaki-senpai, my answer is a resounding "yes"!
Your answer is surely up in the sky!
This voice...
Break through the darkness and the endless world...
Asuka?
She's singing.
May your wishes shine eternal,
Master of the Heavens, Zephyrion!
Four Rhythm Across the Blue
The birds and the wind
Pat my hair as if inviting me into the sky
And steal my attention upwards
As the sunlight burns my cheeks
I could look into the sky
If only I could fly like them
Open your ears and listen to the starting whistle
It shakes the wings of my heart as it resounds through the blue skies
Let's soar past these boring, monotonous days
The miracle we've been looking for is just ahead
With it, we can reach the future we've dreamed of
It lies just beyond our fingertips
Episode Nine
The Answer Is Up in the Sky!
I feel like I wasted my time.
That was the Zephyrion theme song.
What's that?
A mecha anime that aired when we were kids.
The weak, no-good protagonist—
wait for it—
What?
is unstoppable when he pilots Zephyrion!
Send
Enter your message
Unread messages
My mother passed them
on to me. Sorry for not noticing
you came by.
Thanks for bringing
me the handouts.
Sorry! (>_<;) Look up!
Waiting at the
school gates atm
I'm so sorry!
I'm too useless (>_<;)
Asuka
Madoka
Mashiro
Asuka
Kunahama FC Team
It's from Asuka.
"Thanks for bringing me the handouts.
My mother passed them on to me.
Sorry for not noticing you came by."
Could I borrow that for a second?
What for?
"You were singing Zephyrion's
theme song just now, weren't you?"
"Let's Zephyr it sometime."
She replied.
Read (1)
Enter your message
Sure!
Zeph, zeph!
You were singing
Zephyrion's theme
song just now, weren't you?
Let's Zephyr it sometime.
Fyurie, pls...
Asuka
"Zeph, zeph"? Seriously, what?
I think she's saying, "Yes, yes."
That's not what I mean.
I guess I had nothing to worry about.
Good morning!
Oh, morning!
You seem fine. Thank goodness.
I am. Sorry for making you worry.
Misaki-chan, thank you for yesterday.
No problem. Morning.
Sorry I couldn't make it to
practice yesterday, New Captain.
Don't be. It was raining anyway.
And could you drop the "new" already?
Morning.
Good morning, Coach.
Are you all right, Asuka?
Yes. Sorry to have worried you.
Think you're good for practice today?
Yes!
Bring it on, I say!
You don't have to get that worked up.
Asuka really is different.
No! Bring it on, I say!
Compared to me.
You just recovered, so take it easy.
You think?
No, no!
I don't think I'll last five hours without
falling asleep if I don't get worked up!
That's the Asuka I know.
A-Asuka-senpai?
S-Sorry. I can't fly too well.
Fix your posture and try to fly straight.
O-Okay!
Uh, try a high yoyo next.
Maybe try a low yoyo.
O-Okay!
Asuka?!
I wonder what's wrong with her.
Come here, Asuka.
Coming!
Asuka-chan.
Sorry. I'm totally hopeless.
Seriously. It's like your save data got wiped.
Yeah...
I wonder why.
Just do some stretches and call it a day.
Coach...
Try doing some image training once you get home.
Picture yourself flying correctly.
And give it another shot tomorrow.
Got it.
And that's a wrap!
Sorry guys.
Well, they say even the best
athletes have their off-days.
Even when I try to light a fire and stand up again,
I'm only reminded of my weakness.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Huh?
Zephyrion?
Where are you from? Are you lost?
I'm...
I'm not lost.
Then what's up?
I'm a crying, sulking, weak, and hopeless girl.
Isn't that line from Zephyrion?
Let's play together, then.
Come on, let's go.
R-Right...
You're leaving already?
Yeah.
But we only just became friends...
You can have this.
But...
Just take it!
Thanks!
It's okay. That part was already broken.
Whatcha doing?
I heard you couldn't fly,
but it seems you got here just fine.
Misaki-chan...
Here, your lunch.
You left it in the classroom.
Th-Thank you.
You're welcome.
You're not wearing it, huh?
That hairpin.
For some reason,
I felt like I shouldn't.
My wings might not have been my own.
I've wanted to fly ever since I was a little child.
I wanted to change the weak,
hopeless girl that I was.
So when I came to this island
and got to fly for the first time,
I was really happy.
I picked up FC, gave it everything I had,
and met a lot of amazing people.
It was all very fun.
I found Inui-san's FC incredible, too.
The fact that someone
was capable of doing that
made me feel like I could
reach even greater heights.
But I was just getting carried away, wasn't I?
I couldn't do a thing in my match against Inui-san.
Nothing had changed.
I was still the weak, hopeless girl I'd always been.
The wings that let me fly until now,
I'd just borrowed from you and Coach.
So I got scared of my weakness...
...and you couldn't fly anymore, huh?
I see.
Practicing solo feels so pointless.
What can ya do? Asuka-chan said
she wanted to keep image training.
Notice of Absence
Kurashina Asuka
(>口<;)
time off from the team!
Asuka-senpai is taking
Mashiro
Her mother phoned and said
she wasn't home yet!
Mashiro
Enter your message
Asuka...
Where are you now?
Please respond!
Misaki
Asuka
Four Rhythm Across the Blue
Tobisawa
What am I doing here?
What're you talking about?
You were the one standing outside
my house with a blank look on your face.
Well...
I wanted to reply to your message,
but my phone ran out of power.
I didn't know what to do,
and before I knew it...
It's just like you to show up to respond in person.
That aside...
Why are you even here, Mashiro?
That's because you told me
Asuka-senpai was at your place.
So I rushed over as soon as I could.
I most definitely am not here to take advantage
of the situation to sample your home cooking!
Sorry to have worried you.
Let's just eat.
Yeah, let's eat!
Let's eat.
I tried making gyoza tonight.
With flying fish dumplings and lots of flyer stock.
It's great!
Flying fish gyoza, made with your love!
Love was not an ingredient.
Th-This is...
...delicious, right?
It's really good.
Asuka.
Y-Yes?
Stay the night, okay?
"S-Stay"...
M-Misaki-senpai...
Please use me as your personal body Mashillow.
Like, you gonna eat or what?
I need to clean up.
Anything for you!
Wait, Senpai!
No, you can't!
Please...
Gimme a break.
I'm sorry.
I ended up causing you trouble.
No problem, I guess.
Why?
Why are you taking time off?
Well...
What about you?
Me?
I...
A total hottie, no matter how
many times I look at it!
Get lost, Mashiro.
What? Am I not welcome here?
I feel like an abandoned cat right now.
Yeah, I'm abandoning you.
Ack!
Fine. Since I'm such a bother,
I'll get out of your way now.
Shoo, shoo.
You two feel free to flirt to your hearts' content.
Where did she even pull these pictures out from?
I wanna see, too!
Hey, wait.
Who is this boy?
Me.
Sorry.
I often got mistaken for a boy, so I'm used to it.
Grav-Shoes?
I got them as a birthday gift.
I was so happy, I kept flying around by myself.
After a point, that couldn't satisfy me anymore,
so I challenged random people to matches.
You look like you were having fun.
But I get bored easily, you see.
Before I knew it,
I stopped caring about Flying Circus.
After you showed up,
I started playing again on a whim.
But this time,
I ran away.
I thought I put up a good fight
against Shindou-san,
but I really hadn't.
He got serious against you, though.
I was so upset.
I couldn't understand why.
And then he lost the match against Inui-san.
I didn't want to believe it.
"What does that make me?"
I wondered. It really scared me.
But you...
You said it was incredible.
I couldn't understand you.
I felt like you were out of my league.
And even after losing so badly,
Shindou-san hadn't let it get to him at all.
In fact, it only made him more motivated.
Because the fear of losing something
shows that you enjoy it.
I can't enjoy that sort of thing.
That's why...
I decided to quit.
Misaki-chan...
What can you even say?
I'm so pathetic.
That's not true!
You're awesome!
Sorry.
Asuka?
I mean,
you're the one who took me
to the world in the sky.
Looking at your pretty flying form
made me wish I could fly like that, too.
Th-Thanks.
Oh, no need.
You'll be fine.
I know you're flying with your own wings.
Not that I have proof, though.
You don't?
Wow, it's really late.
Please pick me up
Shall we turn in?
Yes.
I'm Mashiro, the abandoned cat.
I guess they're not coming to pick me up.
Jeez.
Not that I blame them.
Fly across the starry sky
with your unrivaled wings.
Your answer is surely up in the sky.
Break through the darkness and the endless world.
May your wishes shine eternal,
Master of the Heavens, Zephyrion!
You two totally forgot that I existed, huh?
Oh, is that so?
You two were so engrossed
in your own little world, huh?
Oh, I'm sorry for being the fifth wheel—
Are you even listening to me?
Sorry, Mashiro-chan.
Well, it's fine.
Step on it, or we'll be late!
I know!
H-Hey!
What is it? Less talk, more walk!
Misaki-chan!
Wh-What?
Take me on...
in a match!
Asuka-senpai?
The answer is up in the sky!
Wait, that was just a leave letter?
Yes. I wanted to take a day off.
And you, Misaki?
I'm gonna play Asuka in a match now.
Beat me, and I'll come back.
"The answer is up in the sky"?
You're too naïve, Asuka.
The only things that are up there
are victory and defeat.
And I'm gonna win, no matter what.
I'll give it everything I've got.
To be honest, I'm a bit scared of taking Asuka on.
If I win, Misaki-chan will come back to the team.
I can't afford to lose here.
Get ready...
Set!
She can fly again!
Her own way of flying must've come back to her.
Point to Asuka-senpai!
Here I go!
You're not passing me!
No way!
Let's zipzap, Misaki-chan!
Asuka, don't steal... my catchphrase!
Point to Misaki-senpai 1—
1-2!
Too reckless!
Point to Misaki-senpai. 1-3.
Misaki-chan really is amazing.
But I have no intention...
of losing!
Point to Asuka-senpai!
Let's do this, Asuka!
Let's!
They're so high up.
Is that Delta Force?!
Did Asuka use it in the spur of the moment?!
You know, I realized something.
I was scared because I'd found
something to take seriously—
something to dedicate myself to—for the first time.
And I think I'm still a little scared.
You?
The only thing on my mind...
is to look upwards and fly.
I really do think the answer is up in the sky.
It may well be.
Misaki-senpai...
For personal reasons.
Notice of Withdrawal
Club Activity:
Team
Flying Circus
Tobisawa Misaki
Team
Cut Here
Class:
Full Name:
Reason for Withdrawal:
You won. What are you going to do with this?
For personal reasons.
Notice of Withdrawal
Club Activity:
Team
Flying Circus
Tobisawa Misaki
Team
Cut Here
Class:
Full Name:
Reason for Withdrawal:
Notice of Withdrawal
Club Activity:
Team
Flying Circus
Tobisawa Misaki
Team
Cut Here
Class:
Full Name:
Reason for Withdrawal:
For personal reasons.
Notice of Withdrawal
Club Activity:
Team
Flying Circus
Tobisawa Misaki
Team
Cut Here
Class:
Full Name:
Reason for Withdrawal:
For personal reasons.
Notice of Withdrawal
Club Activity:
Team
Flying Circus
For personal reasons.
Tobisawa Misaki
Team
Cut Here
Class:
Full Name:
Reason for Withdrawal:
Club Activity:
Team
Class:
Full Name:
Cut Here
Reason for Withdrawal:
Tobisawa Misaki
For personal reasons.
Got a pen?
Here.
Thanks.
There we go.
Registration
Notice of Withdrawal
Club Activity:
Team
Cut Here
Class:
Reason for Withdrawal:
Full Name:
Flying Circus
Tobisawa Misaki
For personal reasons.
Flying Circus
I'm not "coming back." I'm flat-out rejoining.
Ah.
So you're our newest member!
Oh, I guess.
Call me "Mashiro-senpai" from now on.
In your dreams.
Fly across the starry sky with your unrivaled wings.
Oh, so this is Jephyrion?
Your answer is surely up in the sky.
You're not pronouncing it right, Senpai. You can't Zephyr like that.
So that wing of yours was Jephyrion's, Asuka?
Break through the darkness and the endless world.
You're still not pronouncing it right.
A boy from this island gave
it to me when I was a child.
May your wishes shine eternal,
Master of the Heavens, Zephyrion!
A boy from this island?
Who could it be?
Like a female version of Coach.
Gross!
Well, it was a long time ago.
Wait, I think I once played
a similar kid in an FC match.
Maybe it was the same person?
Who knows?
To Be Continued
And who cares?
A single lonely cloud
Floats in the sky I gaze up at
My friends' laughter and voices are growing distant
Just like how I was today
I hide away
My small sighs between the waves
I could do it so well today
But now I can't even catch up to them
You used to be so unreliable but now you've gotten so much stronger
The colour of the sky changes too
The wind knows all too well
What regret and sadness feels like
Let's take to the skies again
This is where everything begins
It won't be the same as yesterday
Look, the view from here just keeps expanding
I'll fly over to those cheeks of yours
That I can see nodding in the distance
Spread out these hands you've clasped together
And let's fly together
Preview
Our FC is beautiful.
6 AM? Seriously?
Coach?!
Is that for FC, too?
Episode Ten
Is That for FC, Too?