Hey, Kakeru.
Yeah?
What're you listening to?
You might not know it, Hagita-kun.
I'll know it.
Don't underestimate me.
Not sharing.
Come on.
Lemme think...
Let me listen to it a sec.
Why?
Huh? Why not? What's the problem?
Come on, give it to me!
Why?
Look, I said...
Wanna listen?
Our eyes meet at last.
I canceled my plans to meet my Tokyo friends.
Huh?
I made plans with Suwa instead.
I thought it'd be more fun.
I see.
Seriously, let me listen.
Kakeru, you sure love being mean to Hagita, huh?
Yeah, it's fun. Sorry!
It's fun?
Okay, that's good, then...
Like hell it is!
I was able to tell Kakeru how I felt.
Takamiya Naho
Thanks to that letter,
I've also been able to change.
Takamiya Naho
Beads of all shapes, sizes and colors
Sat on a table, shining
Shining at each other
Sparkling in a rainbow of colors
Even if our days shatter, breaking bit by bit
Those broken pieces still shine on
Sometimes coming closer, sometimes separating
The matching fragments connect
Even the sad things we've gone through
Even all the tear-filled memories
Make up your smile's colorful glow
The setting sun shines against the orange sky
Making our matching shadows sway
I wanted to tell you something but I couldn't
And with time, our light slowly dies
Naruse, pass!
Naho.
Naho, is there something you're hiding from us?
Huh?
N-Nothing at all!
Stare...
I wasn't really trying to hide it...
But yesterday, I told Kakeru how I feel about him.
Attagirl!
Congratulations on your very first boyfriend!
Huh?
Let's celebrate with red beans and rice!
Boyfriend?
But we didn't say we were dating...
Or anything, really!
So? Anything else?
Anything else you're hiding?
Anything else?
Kakeru!
You okay, Kakeru?!
Naruse!
Get a hold of yourself, man!
Talk about a shock!
You just passed out all of a sudden!
Sorry, guys.
Are you okay?
I just got a little dizzy.
Have you been eating right?
Yeah, though not as much as you.
Suwa's a glutton.
But seriously, you need to be careful.
Your girlfriend might laugh at you.
My girlfriend?
Naho, silly! This 'ere Naho!
She's not my girlfriend.
Huh?!
We haven't said anything about going out, right?
What are you talking about?
If you love each other, you should date!
I just feel like it's not that simple.
Huh? Love each oth—
Hagita, stop making things more complicated!
If Naho and I were going out,
I'd probably hurt her somehow.
If we can be happy and have
a good time without dating,
I feel like that would be better.
So that means you're actually thinking
about Naho's feelings, right?
Of course I am.
But I really...
really do love you.
Yeah.
Oh, my. Thanks for coming by.
Naruse-kun, your grandmother
is here to pick you up.
I think I understand how Kakeru feels.
If Kakeru and I started dating,
the future may take a completely different course.
If that happens, we might not be able to save him.
Sorry, Naho.
Sorry for what?
For not being able to tell Kakeru to go out with you.
I'm fine with that.
It said in my letter
to give you both a supportive push,
so things would work out between you.
But I couldn't do it.
Are the instructions in the letter from
my future self really correct, I wonder?
Huh?
Did your letter say anything
about Kakeru collapsing today?
No.
Then that's a new future
that was born only in our world.
I think it happened because
he joined the soccer club.
Huh?
He's still a newbie in the club.
So every day, he works twice
as hard as anyone else.
And because of that...
I guess he wore himself thin.
If the club is putting a burden on Kakeru,
then was it right to invite him to join?
Of course it was.
I can tell Kakeru's having a great time.
Just because his fainting wasn't in the letter
doesn't mean it's the club's fault.
Even if the letters can change the future,
we don't know what's gonna happen.
It's making me a little nervous.
Right now, I kind of understand why Kakeru was
scared to make a choice.
I'd never thought about it before.
Takamiya Naho
But I know the letter's not mistaken.
It's helped me out time and time again.
October 1st
During P.E., everyone's times are recorded in the 100-meter dash.
Runners for the relay race in the athletic meet are chosen.
Six people from our class, both boys and girls, are going to do it.
October 1st
During P.E., everyone's times are recorded in the 100-meter dash.
Runners for the relay race in the athletic meet are chosen.
Six people from our class, both boys and girls, are going to do it.
All right. Everyone here?
Okay, I'm gonna announce the runners for the relay.
First, Naruse.
You had the fastest time, so you'll be the anchor.
What?
That's awesome, Kakeru.
Good luck!
As for the other members,
for the boys, we have Hotaka and Nagasaka.
No way. Me, too?!
For the girls, we have Ootsuki, Shiojiri, and Okaya.
I wanted to be in the ball-toss game.
There's no ball-toss.
Seriously?!
Kakeru had been anxious about the race
since he was chosen as the anchor.
But on the day of the meet, during the relay,
Kakeru is running in the lead when he suddenly
twists his ankle and falls.
As a result, the class comes in last. Kakeru felt responsible for the loss.
But on the day of the meet, during the relay,
Kakeru is running in the lead when he suddenly
twists his ankle and falls.
As a result, the class comes in last. Kakeru felt responsible for the loss.
For Kakeru's sake,
do something so he's no longer a
member of the relay team.
For Kakeru's sake,
do something so he's no longer a
member of the relay team.
Dear God, dear Buddha, dear Naruse!
If we win, I'll treat you to all you can eat at McD's!
Counting on you for number 1!
Good luck!
With you on our team, we got this in the bag!
We're counting on you!
Kakeru.
How about I run in your place?
There's no need to force yourself.
Huh?
Th-That's right!
If it's too much pressure, you can drop out.
I'm actually kind of looking forward to it.
It made me think maybe I can be useful, too.
I was happy to be picked.
Are you sure?
You really want to do it,
from the bottom of your heart?
Huh?
Let him do it.
You don't want to let him run?
No, I mean...
Kakeru collapsed the other day.
I'm just worried. What if something happens?
I understand that, but...
The man says he wants to do it.
Maybe I shouldn't do it, after all.
If I fell in the middle of the relay,
I would ruin it for everyone.
Suwa, will you run for me?
Y-Yeah, sure thing.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah.
Maybe I shouldn't have done that.
I didn't expect Kakeru to say he wanted to do it.
Maybe we should've let him do the relay.
But it was written in the letter.
Suwa. Come here for a sec.
Huh?
Me?
Is there something you're hiding from us?
About Kakeru.
Suwa.
Sensei.
What is it, Naruse?
I'd like to talk to you about the relay.
I...
What?
You don't want to be the anchor?
Yeah.
Sensei.
I would like to be in the relay.
Huh? What? What's going on?
Has Taka-chan gone mad?
Sensei!
I wanna run in the relay, too!
Well, whether you want to or not...
We talked about it beforehand.
Honestly, representing the class
is kind of a heavy responsibility,
so I'd like one of them to take my place.
Where's this coming from, all of a sudden?
It's the first athletic meet since
Kakeru transferred here.
We thought it'd be fun to do it together.
What? That's kind of unfair.
Someone take my place, too!
See what you've started?
I'll treat anyone who will!
Stop trying to solve everything with bribery.
This is why I chose people based on times...
I'll...
I'll take his place.
I'd like to run in the relay with Kakeru, too.
There's no need to get caught up in
whether the letter is right or wrong.
What I should do is...
M-Me, too!
I want to run together with him, too.
With Kakeru!
Hey, Hagita.
Earth to Hagita!
Hagita!
May I participate as well?
Not that I'm confident in my speed.
Kakeru is the anchor.
We'll keep the baton going until it gets to him.
All right.
We'll have these six run
the relay in the athletic meet.
Today, I chose a path that differed from the letter.
A different path is fine,
as long as we make sure it leads to a bright future.
Man, you guys sure are close!
Good luck, giant!
Hagita-kun, can you actually run?
You know I can't—
He can do anything when
he really puts his mind to it!
Seriously, stop.
Thanks, Naho.
I hope I'll be a good stand-in for you.
It'll be fine! Just fine!
I figured you'd end up volunteering, too.
Thanks.
Now I'm looking forward to the relay even more.
I'm really glad.
I'm starting to think we can really win this!
I'm happy it turned out this way, too.
This time, we made a different choice
than what the letter suggested.
But if it ends in us saving Kakeru,
then I think it's the right one.
Yeah.
You're right.
Thanks, Suwa.
Nah, I didn't do anything.
It was the others who made it possible.
Yeah.
Well, I think I'm gonna hit the sack.
Is that Naho-chan?
I bet it is!
For now, I'm going to stop relying on the letter.
I'm going to try thinking about what
would make Kakeru the happiest,
and then act on that.
Yeah.
It's gotta be Naho-chan.
Huh? Did you say something?
I've always carried this letter around with me.
October 1st
During P.E., everyone's times are recorded
in the 100-meter dash.
Runners for the relay race in the athle
tic meet are chosen.
Six people from our class, both boys and
girls, are going to do it.
Kakeru is the fastest runner, so he's g
oing to be the anchor.
During P.E., everyone's times are recorded
in the 100-meter dash.
Runners for the relay race in the athle
tic meet are chosen.
Six people from our class, both boys and
girls, are going to do it.
Kakeru is the fastest runner, so he's g
oing to be the anchor.
Takamiya Naho
Time to put it away.
And... goal.
Man, you're slow!
I told you... I can't do it!
Also, doesn't he run weird?
I'm the slowest kid in the class.
I'm going to humiliate myself.
I think you're actually the
slowest in the whole grade.
Seriously?
Who cares if we come in last?
The point is for Kakeru to enjoy the athletic meet.
And would you enjoy coming in last, Kakeru?
I want to run with you too, Hagita-kun.
If the six of us can run together,
I'll be happy, no matter how we place.
Besides, running in the relay
will make you popular, Hagita-kun.
Sheesh... I don't have a choice, do I?
If I must.
Let's go back in.
What's next, again?
Math.
Hey.
Hm?
On the way home today,
I want you to hang out with me for a bit.
Huh?
Uh, sure.
Naho.
Want to walk together to the school doors?
Yeah, sure.
I'll see you at practice.
Okay.
Tell them I've got cleaning duty.
Hey.
You walk slowly, don't you, Naho?
Huh?
It's like you're always a pace
behind whoever you're with.
R-Really?
That's just like you.
Kakeru's noticing even
the smallest details about me.
The wind's gotten cooler, huh?
Yeah.
Are you okay?
S-Sorry!
What?
Nothing, really.
Well, I'm off to practice.
Bye-bye.
Oh!
Hey! I got faster, right?
I was faster that time, right?
Wow! You're getting slower and slower!
Seriously? Awesome!
I mean, how do I make myself run faster?!
You tell me.
Hagita, you don't need to practice anymore.
And why did you want me
out here with you, anyway?
The others are faster,
so you should have them coach you.
I thought you could use the practice, too.
What?
It doesn't have to be just the two of us.
What's going on?
What is it?
There's something...
There's something I want to talk to you about.
Was Kakeru...
trying to tell me something back then?
Kakeru!
Hm?
Want to walk together to the school doors?
Sure.
I didn't think you'd be the one asking me, Naho.
There's something I wanted to talk about.
Me, too.
What's wrong, Kakeru?
Nothing.
Sorry.
Bye-bye.
See you tomorrow.
What's wrong?
Suwa...
Did your letter say anything about Kakeru today?
Nope. Nothing.
I see.
Didn't you say you weren't gonna
rely on the letter from now on?
But I'm worried about Kakeru.
Naho.
Don't put all your hopes on the letter.
Rely on us, too.
You've got these guys behind you, too.
Guys...
What's wrong?
Is something about Kakeru troubling you?
Why not try talking to them?
Yeah.
Well...
Yeah?
Kakeru's been acting a little weird.
How so?
He holds out his hand like this
but doesn't say a word.
When I ask him what it's for, he won't answer.
He had a sad expression on his face,
so I thought maybe something had happened.
I'm pretty sure Kakeru just wanted
to hold hands with you.
Of course he'd look sad!
Hold hands with the poor guy!
Not very manly of Kakeru, though.
I would've just straight up said,
"Hey, let's hold hands."
Me, too.
Would you now?
Naho, you overthink things.
That's right.
Talk to us more.
We told you, you don't have
to hide things from us.
Why not tell them everything?
I got a letter.
From my future self.
It said, "I want you to save Kakeru."
So...
I want all of you to help me.
Sure.
Of course.
You finally asked us for help.
There's something we want to show you.
Murasaka Azusa
Chino Takako
Sorry we didn't tell you before.
We got letters, too. From the future.
They asked me about it the other day.
Are you hiding something from us?
About Kakeru.
Suwa.
I'm not really trying to hide it or anything...
But I figured you'd never believe me,
even if I told you.
We'll believe you, so tell us.
Put simply, I got a letter.
From myself, ten years in the future.
What... kind of reaction is that?
Come on, Hagita, you too.
Yesterday, he said out of nowhere
that he wanted to tell me something.
Yesterday?
What, were you two on a date?
You kidding me?!
Who'd go on a date with this moron?
Come on. Just show it to them.
Hagita Saku
He said he got one, too.
All of us have the same goal.
Let's save Kakeru.
Together.
I have friends who'll never change,
even ten years from now.
Let's save Kakeru.
Together.
If my love for you could stay as it is
I'm fine with these feelings never reaching you
Not truly tied, yet never fully detached
Deep within my heart, tears are shed
At the end of this thin, delicate branch
Your future is being born
Don't prune back those as-of-yet undiscovered days
I want to protect you so that one day, you'll look back and smile
Deep within my heart, tears are shed
But I cherish them
Because I want to be by your side