Angelica, is that all he ordered?
Hugo.
Assuming his letter is right,
then this is everything, yeah.
Is all that stuff for his disciple?
Seems that way.
I guess you could call it
a basic learning materials kit.
Really, though, a disciple? For that man-child?
Hugo!
Behave yourself.
All right, let's get started.
Righto.
Ready when you are, Angelica.
All right.
O droplet, bore ever deeper.
O steel, forged by earth and fire.
Gold be parted and mortar be cut.
With those...
Angelica!
What are you doing?!
It should be around here somewhere...
Found it!
The Lonely Little Star
This is my gift to her.
I hope she likes it.
That's why I asked you if you
had everything he ordered.
I'd forgotten about this.
A book from the land of disciples?
I stumbled upon it at the used book store.
Now, from the top, Hugo!
Got it!
O droplet, bore ever deeper.
O steel, forged by earth and fire.
Gold be parted and mortar be cut.
With those hands,
turn the waterwheel shrouded
in the darkness of night.
Dispatch unto its rightful home
that which must be received.
Now, deliver that to Ainsworth
and his disciple, Chise, if you would.
Those Awaiting a Star
Part 1
Morning, Ruth.
Morning, Chise.
Yes?
Is the medicine I requested ready?
The cough medicine, correct?
Elias.
Would you like Darjeeling?
Yes.
Please.
We're having a lot of tomato dishes as of late.
It's summer, so we harvested a lot.
I see.
Ruth, you're having breakfast, right?
Yeah, Chise.
Was that a gremlin?
I was making him clean up after himself.
Time to eat.
Are you not eating?
Oh, it's not that.
Seems like he's in a bad mood.
Oh, I'll start eating.
You're making a mess, Ruth.
Chise.
Yes?
What are your plans for today?
I'll be checking on the field in the back,
to pick whatever is ready.
The herbs are maturing, too,
so I'm thinking of drying all of them.
Once I'm done with my morning tasks,
I'll be studying magic as usual.
What will you be doing?
There's a book I haven't finished,
so I'll read the rest of that.
Is it the one I gave you the other day?
It is.
Chise,
acquiring knowledge is fine,
but you need to gain experience, too.
It seems kind of dangerous, though.
I felt I should understand it thoroughly first.
That's important, too,
but do remember that I'm your teacher.
You can always ask me if you ever
want to do some experiments.
I'll keep that in mind.
I can pick something easy to read for you,
so just tell me if you'd like that.
Coming.
I-I'm sorry.
All this stuff came crashing down on me.
I couldn't do anything about it.
it's fine, you did nothing wrong.
Angie really stuffed it full, though.
Angelica?
I ordered some learning materials for you.
This is all for me?
Yes.
The books are still too advanced for you,
but I'll make sure you can use the tools right away.
Is something the matter?
No, not at all.
Okay.
Use this when you go into the forest.
Use this when you're gathering fairies.
This book's very easy to read.
This one's...
Now, Chise, let's carry this to the study.
The study?
Oh, have I not told you yet?
You haven't.
May I finish breakfast first?
That may be wise.
Aren't you going in?
I-I am.
What's wrong?
Elias, um...
May I tidy up this room?
I have a feeling that it'll be difficult
to find things in here.
Well, I suppose that would be fine.
Ruth.
On it.
I never even thought of sorting things on the bookshelves.
Whenever I did put the books on the shelves,
they usually ended up elsewhere on their own.
Eventually I got too frustrated with it.
I told Silky that she doesn't need
to concern herself with it, either.
B-But, maybe with enough diligence,
we can maintain some order.
If you say so, it must be true.
Chise, why don't we go for a walk?
Um...
Thank you very much,
for all the new learning materials, that is.
I'm your magic teacher.
I'm just doing what anyone would.
I know,
but why so many?
I simply thought you'd need them soon.
What is it?
Nothing. Never mind.
The Lonely Little Star
This book...
What's the matter?
Angelica sent this.
A gift?
A Japanese book.
How unusual.
Looks like it's special.
Is it?
I guess.
E-Elias?
Um...
Tell me.
In what way is that book special to you?
But, uh, we aren't done tidying up the books yet.
We can do that at any time.
I'm your magic teacher,
but in turn, you're my human teacher, are you not?
I think it's important to answer your
student's questions as much as you can.
I know, but...
Tell me
about that book.
Please?
All right.
Our sleigh beggy is telling a story.
The beloved child's telling a story?
I want to hear it!
I read this book when I was still alone.
The Lonely Little Star
You shouldn't have been born.
Mom.
Mom!
She's far too much of a burden to take in.
And I hear she's rather odd,
talking to herself and behaving
in all kinds of strange ways.
Hey, I heard your parents abandoned you.
Nah, you've got it wrong! Her mom killed herself!
What's the difference? She's still an orphan.
It just means no one needs you, right?
Give it back!
No way!
Please!
Wait until I'm done.
No way!
Please stop making a mess this early.
Take it if you can!
That's quite enough!
Okay.
Time to eat!
Thanks for the food!
Put your dishes away first!
Wait, I'm coming too.
Hold on!
Daiki, wear your hat,
and take your water bottle with you!
See you.
Take care.
Again?
I'm cleaning it up if you won't eat it.
Hey.
Say something, honey.
That girl won't warm up to us.
She wouldn't even touch the food I made her.
What? I gave her the same thing
I gave the other two.
Come on, what do you mean
you're in the middle of work?
You were the one who said you'd take her in!
I really shouldn't have accepted her!
Are you okay?
Wait, are you hurt?
Just one second.
Here.
Th-Thanks.
Are you okay?
What did you do that for?
Where are your parents?
You're bleeding.
I'm sorry...
Hey, wait a minute!
I'm sorry... I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
I'm sorry!
Is someone there?
Are you okay?
I-I'm sorry.
I'll leave right away.
Don't worry.
Those horrible creatures can't reach you here.
You can see them?
Who exactly are you, mister?
I am the magician of the forest.
Welcome...
To the library of the forest.
The young man stood amidst
an infinite collection of books.
What does the girl see in this dream-like library?
Maybe I should just take her away.