Myne's first step toward
making books was to make paper.
However, her attempts at making
faux-papyrus ended in failure.
And so, once Spring came, Myne planned
to head into the forest to make clay tablets.
She was filled with renewed determination.
I have a wish, just one simple wish
Ascendance of a Bookworm
LOREM IPSUM DOLOR SIT AMET CONSECTETUR ADIPISCING ELIT FUSCE EFFICITUR LECTUS ID NISI RHONCUS PHARETRA NULLA QUAM VELIT TEMPUS QUIS ACCUMSAN EFFICITUR TEMPUS EU ANTE DONEC ULTRICES MOLESTIE MAXIMUS DONEC NON LOREM VITAE ANTE PRETIUM VESTIBULUM IN IN MAGNA MAURIS PHARETRA PLACERAT URNA AC FEUGIAT TORTOR AUCTOR EGET MAECENAS SIT AMET EROS FELIS ETIAM SAPIEN PURUS MALESUADA FERMENTUM VIVERRA VEL PORTA SIT AMET LECTUS CLASS APTENT TACITI SOCIOSQU AD LITORA TORQUENT PER CONUBIA NOSTRA PER INCEPTOS HIMENAEOS MAURIS VEHICULA DAPIBUS INTERDUM FUSCE SIT AMET NISI VENENATIS PLACERAT LIGULA ID CONDIMENTUM ODIO DUIS URNA JUSTO IMPERDIET UT COMMODO ID ULTRICES IN ELIT SED EGESTAS FACILISIS EX IN HENDRERIT IPSUM EGESTAS IMPERDIET
I hold it dearly in my heart and hope
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
It'll come true someday soon
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to
I don't have anything, nothing at all
But if I could have this one wish granted
It would fill the void inside my heart
I can feel the warm breeze blowing
And see shooting stars filling the sky
They make me feel as if
I can do anything, y'know?
In this wonderful world
Where knowledge shines bright like the sun
Nothing is set in stone
Who knows what the future holds?
I want to take hold of my future
With my own two hands
And write pages filled with hope
Into the book of my life
Chapter 4
First Time in the Forest and Clay Tablets
Wow, everything looks amazing!
Myne really made all this?
Course I did!
It was my turn to cook today, after all.
Now, eat up before it gets cold.
The cooking itself was pretty odd though.
Myne, what are you doing with the
water you boiled the vegetables in?
Trust me, it'll be fine!
Thanks for the meal.
This is great!
This pome soup is super tasty!
Pomes look like paprikas but taste like tomatoes.
Oh why, yes.
This is quite good!
People in this world haven't thought to use
vegetable broth in their cooking just yet.
The vegetable broth really does
make it taste great, huh?
This alcohol and chicken dish is pretty good too.
Those parue pancakes were great as well.
You have a real gift for cooking!
You could even become a chef, you know.
We should find somewhere
that'd take you on as an apprentice!
Huh?
Book
making
-
Apprentice
Chef
Book
making
-
Apprentice
Chef
Not good.
If I'm not careful, I'll end up
too busy to work on making books.
I have to get to the forest and start
making clay tablets as soon as possible!
A-Actually, there's something I want to do.
Hm?
What is it, Myne?
I want to go to the forest!
"Go to the forest" she says!
Myne, we're talking about your future right now.
I'm serious about this.
I wanna make clay tablets.
That's why I want to go to the forest.
Clay tablets?
Yeah! And then I'll write on them
and make books using them!
Write?
Myne, you can't go to the forest yet.
Yes, I can!
I've hardly gotten sick lately, either.
But you still can't walk as far as the rest of us.
I can make it to the well without
running out of breath now!
I'll be okay.
And what if you start having
trouble while you're out there?
That'd make things hard for all of us.
But...
Tuuli goes to the forest all the time, so if that's
what she thinks, it's best you give up, Myne.
When can I go to the forest then?
You need to build up your strength first.
Until then, we can't let you go.
Okay...
With going to the forest completely out of the question,
I longed for books more and more.
Until... One day...
Wha—?
Me? Mr. Otto's assistant?
He's looking for someone to help him out
with paperwork. Calculations, especially.
And he wants Myne as his assistant?
Apparently Myne helped
him out with his work before.
He said she was a real lifesaver.
Wait, really?
However, legally speaking,
you can't employ children before their baptisms.
So, officially, he'll be teaching you the alphabet.
The alphabet?
Yeah. He'll be teaching you alongside his soldier apprentices.
I'm okay with you being taught
how to read and write at the gate.
Your body may be weak,
but Otto tells me you're incredibly smart.
You could become a scribe or something like that.
A scribe?
Someone that writes
documents for nobles or officials.
It pays well, and it's easy on your body too.
Dad...
Otto used to be a traveling merchant
before he became a soldier.
He's still got connections to other merchants.
The kind of work your mother and I can
get you would probably be unhealthy for you.
So, cherish your relationship with Otto.
Thank you, Dad.
Oh, almost forgot. The terms of your employment.
The pay is in slate pens. If you feel ill, you don't go.
He made it clear that he wouldn't be able
to find a better fit than you for the pay.
How can he be so stingy with a child?
Maximizing profit while minimizing his investment.
You can tell he was a former merchant, huh?
You'll be commuting to the gate.
Once you can do that without weighing
anyone down, you can go to the forest.
Is that okay, Myne?
Yeah, I'll do my best!
Myne, don't push yourself and walk slowly.
Yeah, I know.
In the end, I was carried
the rest of the way to the gate.
This is the captain's daughter, Myne.
She'll be joining our reading classes.
Take good care of her, you hear?
Yes sir!
Okay, let's get started.
There's a total 35 of basic letters.
Let's start out with practicing how to write them.
You're really picking this up quickly, Myne.
It's because I prefer this sorta
thing over physical activity.
That being said, don't you think we should probably
stop with the alphabet for today, Mr. Otto?
Huh? Already?
Everyone's started fidgeting in their seats, right?
It's a sign that they can't focus anymore.
It's probably best to move on to something else.
Well, but...
That's all for the alphabet today!
Wha—
Next up is calculations!
And that's it for today.
Make sure to memorize the letters and
numbers we studied today for next time!
If you don't remember them by then,
you'll have to stay here until you do.
Yes ma'am!
Finally! We're done!
They really took off. Guess that's boys for you.
Myne, if you go too soft on them,
nothing's gonna stick.
It's not actually that soft.
If they slack off and don't practice what
they've learned, they'll be stuck here next time.
Yes, but...
Mr. Otto, you can't compare them to me.
Well, I guess that's true.
Then I'll see how your teaching
methods work out for now.
Thank you very much.
Okay, up next are your personal lessons, Myne.
Let's put today's new material
into practice with some hands-on work.
Hell yeah!
This rules!
I'm learning so many new words!
New words! Wahoo!
When Tuuli and the rest return from the forest,
I join them on their way home.
What are you coming to the gate for?
I was wor—I mean,
I was learning how to read and write.
Huh? You can write?
I can really only write my name so far.
What? That's awesome!
Being able to write your name is impressive!
Really?
Being able to write at all
is considered incredible in this world.
I can see why Mr. Otto wanted me as his assistant.
Everyone's...
so fast.
You can slow down if you'd like, Myne.
But...
Your Dad told me to take care of you and Tuuli.
I'll make sure you get home safely.
Thank you.
I've barely gotten anywhere...
I'll be your escort!
Lutz...
Do your best, Myne.
Okay.
And so began my gate commutes.
At first, I'd go once, then rest for three days.
As time went on, I was able to go three
days in a row, then take a single rest day.
And then finally...
I managed to make it to
the gate every day this week!
So can I go to the forest now?
Yeah.
Yay, I did it!
You're really happy aren't you, Myne?
Well, she has worked a lot for it.
Oh, there's some here as well!
Here, too.
Where, where?
We got a whole bunch today.
I w-want to go to the forest.
You won't get better if you don't sleep.
Let me tell you a bedtime story, Myne.
Once upon a time, in a distant land,
there lived a group of star children.
And the star children all lived...
Mom would tell this story
right after I became Myne as well.
They really loved coming down to the earth.
You see, all kinds of different
people lived down there.
I got strong enough to go to
the forest around the end of spring.
It was around three months
after I started going to the gate.
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
The forest! Finally!
We're gonna go pick up firewood,
so you just rest here, Myne.
Okay!
At long last, I made it.
Clay       Tablet
Now I can finally start making my clay tablets!
Yay!
Heh, I'm not just gonna leave the forest
without getting my hands dirty.
Come to me, clay soil!
Oh man, that's hard!
I ain't done just yet!
I'm getting nowhere...
What are you doing, Myne?!
Did you forget the promise you made your Dad?
Just go to forest and back for today.
The goal is for you to walk to the forest, rest,
and then return together with the others.
Got it!
Yes, the goal today is to walk to the forest,
rest, and then return together with the others.
I do remember but, um...
Considering you brought that shovel,
it's clear you never meant to keep that promise.
Uh, I...
I was finally able to go to the forest
after all this time so I just kinda...
You just kinda what?
...it was premeditated.
So you basically lied, didn't you?
Uncle Günther was really worried
about your health, you know.
And yet...
I didn't think I'd have to keep
my eye on you constantly.
I'm sorry...
So, what are you trying to do?
After I told him I wanted sticky clay,
Lutz brought me to a place with no stones
or grass, where the water drains slower.
Why are you helping me, Lutz?
When I was really hungry, you went ahead
and made those parue pancakes for me.
That's when I decided I'd help you out.
Huh? That was it?
Yeah, I told you I'd help you out next time, right?
So in return, explain to me exactly
what it is you want to do here.
You can rely on me.
Thank you.
Here, this is what you wanted, right?
Yes! This is perfect!
That's amazing, Lutz!
It would probably have
taken me days to get it myself.
There are no boys that are weaker than you, Myne.
So, what are you going to do with it now?
I'm gonna make books.
Books?
Here, look.
These are letters?
That's right.
If you write things down like this,
it prevents them from slowly fading away,
which'd end up happening if you tried
to preserve them through word of mouth alone.
You can preserve thoughts, ideas, and events,
so you can read them however many times you like.
Huh...
Books are a collection of these writings,
preserved for all eternity.
Books...
Yup.
With books, we can learn the
thoughts of people long passed,
or of worlds far away, and surpass what
any of us can experience in our single lives.
Books are amazing, aren't they?
I'll get back to getting firewood, then.
Okay! Thanks a lot, Lutz!
No problem!
And done!
Long live, Mesopotamian culture!
I ended up making quite a few.
I wonder if they've dried yet.
Come on, quick.
Wait up!
Whoa, what's this?
Ah, these are...
And hop!
Me too!
Stop it!
Please!
What's wrong, Myne?
My clay tablets...
Fey and the other guy...
W-Were those things important?
Hey, something's wrong with her.
Do you have any idea what
I went through to get this far?
I had to commute to the gate for months.
Lutz and Tuuli helped me out so much as well.
And yet... That was just evil, Fey!
I-I'm sorry, really!
I didn't know...
I will never forgive you!
Calm down, Myne.
I'm sure they didn't mean anything bad by it.
Okay?
I understand your frustration, Myne.
You worked real hard for this.
Myne...
Come help, you guys.
Let's make new ones.
O-Okay...
Let's continue tomorrow and finish them.
Yeah.
And of course, I ended up with
another fever and had to stay in bed.
The rain didn't let up for the next few days, either.
Th-This is the rain's fault, not ours!
I know...
If you have enough time to cry,
we can spend it making new ones instead.
Everyone left to gather firewood, but Lutz
stayed behind to help until the very end.
Hey Myne, so is this what you wanted to do?
Well, what I really want to do
is live a life surrounded by books.
You want to be surrounded by this stuff?
No, no. Real books are too expensive
for me to buy, so these are my replacements.
What do you want to do, Lutz?
Me?
Yeah. You must have some sort of dream too, right?
I...
I want...
to go to other cities.
Other cities?
I want to become a traveling merchant
and see different places with my own eyes.
Traveling sounds nice.
What?
You really think so?
I'd be leaving this city.
Yeah, that sounds nice.
You know, I had a dream of traveling
to libraries all over the world once.
Libraries?
Yeah.
They're places packed full of books.
But that dream won't come true anymore.
Man...
Myne, I bet whatever happens,
you're gonna make your dream happen.
You should as well, Lutz.
It's done...
A book...
"With no books to read,
this wouldn't be a world I could live in."
I've always thought that.
However, despite that, I was able
to find something important to me.
As long as I have books, I'll be okay.
It feels like I've finally found
a path for myself in this world.
Myne, what's written on these?
It's the story of the star-children.
It's the story Mom told me that first night.
"First night"?
Yeah, it's the first story I remember.
When I wasn't able to accept becoming Myne,
Mom's love felt painful to me.
And yet, the first thing I wrote
down ended up being this story.
I don't ever want to forget the story Mom told me.
I want to preserve it in a book.
That way, I'll be able to read it whenever I want.
This was probably the first time I was able
to smile naturally since I'd become Myne.
Now I've just gotta heat them up
to harden them, and they'll be done!
Clay Tablet Explosion
Myne!
No way!
tell me, oh my angel
oh my lovely, let me dream again
I gently brush my hair
And put a hairpin through it
In the sea of green
A flower ornament blooms
It is a gift from my angel
It touches my forehead
Oh so gently
And it reminds me
Of the warm light that gathered
To bring my angel into this world
This fever is making me delirious
Ah, these times are so dear to me
There must have been something more
Some greater force that led me to you
Our fates tangle and unravel as we become family
I have been always living
Inside a book
But then my heart melted
And now I have experienced
The real world
Next Chapter
Baptism and the Mysterious Fever
The clay tablets may have failed too,
but I'm still not giving up!
So what will you try next?
Huh? Well, uh, next up is...
Next, I'll..
N-Next up is your baptism, right?
Speaking of baptisms...
It's finally time for me to shine!
Sorry, High Priest. No screen time for you just yet.
Myne! You shouldn't talk to weird strangers!
Illustration:     Iida Seriko