Having succeeded in her negotiations,
Myne obtains the rights to make and sell paper.
During that process, however,
Lutz begins noticing strange things about her.
Though his doubts linger,
their work toward making paper finally begins.
I have a wish, just one simple wish
Ascendance of a Bookworm
LOREM IPSUM DOLOR SIT AMET CONSECTETUR ADIPISCING ELIT FUSCE EFFICITUR LECTUS ID NISI RHONCUS PHARETRA NULLA QUAM VELIT TEMPUS QUIS ACCUMSAN EFFICITUR TEMPUS EU ANTE DONEC ULTRICES MOLESTIE MAXIMUS DONEC NON LOREM VITAE ANTE PRETIUM VESTIBULUM IN IN MAGNA MAURIS PHARETRA PLACERAT URNA AC FEUGIAT TORTOR AUCTOR EGET MAECENAS SIT AMET EROS FELIS ETIAM SAPIEN PURUS MALESUADA FERMENTUM VIVERRA VEL PORTA SIT AMET LECTUS CLASS APTENT TACITI SOCIOSQU AD LITORA TORQUENT PER CONUBIA NOSTRA PER INCEPTOS HIMENAEOS MAURIS VEHICULA DAPIBUS INTERDUM FUSCE SIT AMET NISI VENENATIS PLACERAT LIGULA ID CONDIMENTUM ODIO DUIS URNA JUSTO IMPERDIET UT COMMODO ID ULTRICES IN ELIT SED EGESTAS FACILISIS EX IN HENDRERIT IPSUM EGESTAS IMPERDIET
I hold it dearly in my heart and hope
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
It'll come true someday soon
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to
I don't have anything, nothing at all
But if I could have this one wish granted
It would fill the void inside my heart
I can feel the warm breeze blowing
And see shooting stars filling the sky
They make me feel as if
I can do anything, y'know?
In this wonderful world
Nothing is set in stone
The as-yet untold future
Shines brighter than the sun
I want to take hold of my future
With my own two hands
And write pages filled with hope
Into the book of my life
Chapter 8
Lutz's Myne
This is the workspace you requested.
I had some cleaning work done ahead of your arrival.
The pot and ash you require are right over there.
If more materials are delivered,
I'll have them brought here from the store.
Thank you, Mark.
Let's get the stuff we brought
from home moved in here.
Sure!
Lutz is still treating me the same as he always has.
At first, I thought he had realized
I wasn't actually Myne...
I'm glad we were able to make up.
If you'll excuse me, I shall return to the store.
I will leave the key in your care.
Please make sure to return it
to the store after you lock up.
Understood. Thanks for your help.
So, what are we going to do today?
Well, we need to figure out the size of the
steamer so we can note it in the supply order...
Oh, we need to get some
thin bamboo strips made, too.
Bamboo strips?
For what?
Bamboo
Screen
We'll bundle them all together
and make a screen out of them.
It's a part of the mold that we'll use
to spread the paper into slices.
Papermaking
Mold
Ah, it snapped again.
Making these is pretty hard.
Maybe we should just decide on the length
and have someone else make them for us?
We're going to the lumber dealer tomorrow
to order the steamer and other stuff.
Maybe we should ask them about it then?
Yeah.
Whaddya say?!
Ya want what wood?
W-Well...
We want wood to make a steamer...
That's why I'm askin' what sorta wood ya want!
I-I want dry, hard wood that
won't warp if it's heated up.
Oh, I think I'm startin' to get you.
Maybe somethin' like
schwalnuss, trocknen, or pedibay.
Which one you after?
I don't think I can answer that...
Lutz, do you know?
Schwalnuss should be easiest to handle, I think.
Ya know what dimensions ya want it?
Yes, it's written on the supply order.
Oh, and a squared piece of timber
to beat the tree fibers with.
Something in a size that Lutz can carry and use.
Ya wanna beat tree fibers?
The hell you doin'?
I can't tell you that.
I guess a balance between hardness
and weight is important then.
It'd depend on what surface
you're gonna be beatin' them on.
The surface?
I hadn't thought about that at all yet.
Could you make me a set of each?
I'll write a supply order right now.
If we make sets, it should be fine, but...
You're gonna write it yourself, girlie?
Yes.
Would this be okay?
No problems.
You're pretty impressive.
Oh and one more thing.
I'd like bamboo strips similar to this.
Could you make them for me?
Hmm...
Somethin' this detailed is work for an artisan.
You should try speakin' to one of them.
I see.
Thanks for your help.
Sure thing. Come by again if you need anythin' else.
Bamboo strips, huh?
You need them all in this size?
They were supposed to be
perfectly straight as well...
You were right to come to me with this.
Is that everything you need?
I'd like to make them into a screen.
Do you think you can do it?
Can you have them line up like this
and connect them with thread?
It sounds like it could be a tedious job,
but it's not impossible.
It's gonna require very sturdy thread though.
Sturdy thread?
Something like Spinne thread.
If we can go to a fabric store right now,
I can help you choose it.
Yes, let's go!
Hey, don't push yourself.
You'd be the first one to collapse.
I'll be fine! I'm not pushing myself at all.
I shall carry you to the fabric store.
It would seem that Ms. Myne
requires my services today, too.
I'm sorry to burden you once again.
It is nothing to be concerned about.
Over the next month and a half,
we finished up our papermaking preparations.
Blue sky!
White clouds!
It's the perfect weather for papermaking, Lutz!
Lutz?
Are you okay?
At least let me help carry the steamer.
No, it's fine.
You can't do this.
Maybe you should rest for a bit.
It's fine, once we start steaming,
we'll have to watch it for around a bell, right?
I'll rest then.
I'm gonna go chop some wood.
You take a break and watch the pot, okay?
Shouldn't you be taking a break instead?
We can't have you risking your health
before we finish making paper.
You can pick up branches near here,
but don't wander too far.
Also, make sure to scream as loud
as you can if anything happens. Got it?
Okay...
I'm running out of wood.
I guess I'll go pick some more branches up.
Huh?
What's that?
A red fruit...
Is it edible?
Ow! It's hot!
Wh-What?
What on earth is this?
They just keep sprouting!
Lutz.
Lutz!
What's wrong?
What is that?
A trombe!
A trombe? What's that?
I'll explain later!
Lutz!
What happened?
It's a trombe!
Hey, get away from it!
O-Okay.
Are any of them still growing?
I think we got all of them.
Th-That's some weird tree...
Are you okay?
Hey, Lutz, what was that just now?
It's a trombe.
If you don't cut it down when it starts sprouting,
it'll eat up the entire area's nutrients in no time.
So that's why it grew so fast...
Yeah.
It can turn into a real nightmare if it grows too big.
Only the Knight's Order
can deal with it at that point.
So there's a Knight's Order, huh?
This really is a fantasy world after all.
It's pretty odd though.
Trombes don't usually grow during this season.
Not only that, that one grew super fast.
The ground around it isn't
even that badly affected, either.
What's wrong? Don't you think it's weird?
Well... This is the first time I've seen one.
Oh, right.
You did only start going to the forest this spring.
Oh, wait!
Since we have it here, why don't we try
making paper out of trombe wood as well?
We have a whole lot here,
and since it was cut while it was still growing,
the fibers should be soft too.
And so, we tried making paper out of trombe wood.
Does this seem right for steaming wood?
I think so.
We should try peeling the bark off.
Amazing!
It came right off!
This could work for papermaking.
You know this stuff pretty well.
So, what do we do now?
Once we've peeled them like this,
we leave them to dry.
When they finish drying,
we soak the bark once again.
Hey...
What is it?
Never mind.
We'll talk once we're done with the paper.
We don't know when trombes will be growing
so we should try other types of wood as well.
Lutz...
Do you still suspect me?
After that, our papermaking
continued advancing smoothly,
but I still had no idea what
was going on in Lutz's mind.
All we need to do today is boil the white bark.
We just need to leave it for one bell, right?
Yeah.
Gotta make sure we don't forget to stir it...
No way! I forgot something else!
What is it?
Lutz, can you make me two
long sticks that I can use to stir?
Basically...
If possible, I'd like you to use bamboo.
Chopsticks
Something like that?
Yeah, thanks Lutz!
You're pretty good at stirring things like that, huh?
Huh?
Uh, yeah, I guess...
I'm pretty skilled, r-right?
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Today's work involves removing the knots
and other defects from the fibers.
Lutz, meanwhile, is beating the ones I've cleaned up.
Instead of the water and plant mixture
I'd normally use, I'm using edile for its stickiness.
After getting that ready, I mix in the beaten fibers.
And with that, the pulp mixture is ready.
Finally, a part I'm familiar with!
I'm glad I made paper from milk
cartons back in my Urano days.
You really know what you're doing?
Yeah, don't worry. I've done this before.
When? Where?
W-Well...
A lady has her secrets! Don't go prying!
Why are you moving it like that?
If I do it like this, the paper's thickness
should be much more even.
I see...
And you know this 'cause you've done it before?
Lutz...
Please, don't look at me like that...
Over the next few days,
we continued working,
and finally finished our first batch of paper.
It's paper.
It's real, proper paper.
I really did it.
It'll be totally dry by the evening.
We'll have to peel it off carefully to make sure
it doesn't break, and then it'll be done.
This is close enough to being done, right?
I said I'd have something to talk about
when we were done, remember?
Do you want to talk out here?
Or should we go inside?
Here's fine.
So...
What do you want to talk about?
You...
Who are you?
You said you know how to make paper.
You even said you've made it before, right?
Myne wouldn't know any of that.
Yeah.
So, are you actually saying that you're not...
Where is the real Myne?!
Give her back already!
Okay.
I'm fine with giving her back,
but I think it'd be better if I went home first.
Huh?
Why?!
If I disappear, there'd probably only be a corpse left.
Y-Y-You...
What the hell are you saying?
Are you saying that Myne's already gone?
That she won't come back?!
Probably.
Just answer this.
When Myne had a fever...
Did you consume her then?
That's half right.
And half wrong.
I also think that the real Myne
was consumed by her fever.
But I'm not that fever.
Rather, the same fever seems to
be trying to consume me, too.
What are you saying?
This is your fault, right?
It's your fault that Myne disappeared, right?!
Admit it!
It's not...
It's not like I wanted to become Myne!
I was originally in another world
and was supposed to have died there.
When I finally came to, I was in the body of a child!
Huh?
If I was given a choice,
I'd never have picked such a frail body.
You...
...didn't want to become Myne?
Would you want to, Lutz?
This body gets terribly sick
from merely walking a little too far.
Are you gonna get consumed
by fever just like Myne did?
Yeah.
Most probably.
That's why you should just
tell me if you want me gone.
I'll leave whenever you want me to.
How could I ever make that choice?!
If it hadn't been for you,
I'd have disappeared long ago.
When my Mom burned the wooden slips
I ended up collapsing, remember?
At that point, I figured that I wouldn't
mind letting the fever consume me.
Because no matter how hard I tried,
I was never gonna be able to make books.
"I've had enough", I thought.
But when I looked at your face and remembered
our promise, I felt myself coming back.
Our promise?
My promise to introduce you to Mr. Otto.
Th-That was just...
I fulfilled my promise and introduced
you to Mr. Otto and Mr. Benno.
I even managed to make paper.
If possible, I'd have liked to make books as well, but...
If you want me gone, I'm okay with it.
That's so selfish.
Since when have you been Myne?
Since when, indeed?
Since when do you think I stopped
being the Myne you knew?
You...
Around the time you started wearing that.
Yeah.
That's right.
That's almost an entire year.
Has your family not noticed?
They've noticed that I'm weird,
but I don't think they've considered that I'm not Myne.
And Dad said that he was happy
just to see me healthy.
I see.
Lutz?
I think this decision should be
left to her family, not to me.
What?
Are you saying you're okay with it for now?
Are you sure?
I'm saying it's not my decision to make.
Are you okay with me not disappearing, Lutz?
Despite not being the real Myne?
Yeah.
Even if you did disappear,
that wouldn't bring back the real Myne.
And...
If you've been her for almost a year,
then the Myne I know has been mostly you.
So, I'm fine with you being my Myne.
Lutz's words made something
click deep inside my heart.
It was a small change, invisible to any onlooker.
But to me, it was something very important.
As the river's water cooled,
making paper became more difficult.
Mr. Benno, we've brought the sample paper.
I see.
We've made it with two types of wood,
and in three different grammages.
I see. Let's take a look...
You can write on it.
It's easier to write on than parchment,
though there are some points where the ink runs.
Those are minor issues, though.
So, uh, is it passable?
Will you take Lutz as your apprentice?
Yup, you've passed.
We did it!
We did it, Lutz!
Yeah!
This one is of higher quality.
That's the one made from trombe wood.
What?!
Trombe, you say?
I wonder if we can use trombes for mass production.
There's no way we can use
something that dangerous!
Are you trying to kill the entire forest?!
So...
That's a no?
tell me, oh my angel
oh my lovely, let me dream again
I gently brush my hair
And put a hairpin through it
In the sea of green
A flower ornament blooms
It is a gift from my angel
It touches my forehead
Oh so gently
And it reminds me
Of the warm light that gathered
To bring my angel into this world
This fever is making me delirious
Ah, these times are so dear to me
There must have been something more
Some greater force that led me to you
Our fates tangle and unravel as we become family
I have been always living
Inside a book
But then my heart melted
And now I have experienced
The real world
Next Chapter
The Guildmaster's Granddaughter
How was that, High Priest?
I've finally made paper!
I see.
So you've finally gotten ready to make books then.
Ah, no. There's still a lot that needs to be done first.
For one, it seems like there's some
formalities to deal with to sell the paper.
Even then, the steps after that
require a whole lot of money...
It would appear that the path
ahead of you is still rather long.
Illustration:     Hachikawa Kyuu