Myne collapses from the stress of repeated failure.
It feels like my fever's suddenly fading...
Though her strange fever remains a mystery,
Myne opens up a new path to her goal.
I have a wish, just one simple wish
Ascendance of a Bookworm
LOREM IPSUM DOLOR SIT AMET CONSECTETUR ADIPISCING ELIT FUSCE EFFICITUR LECTUS ID NISI RHONCUS PHARETRA NULLA QUAM VELIT TEMPUS QUIS ACCUMSAN EFFICITUR TEMPUS EU ANTE DONEC ULTRICES MOLESTIE MAXIMUS DONEC NON LOREM VITAE ANTE PRETIUM VESTIBULUM IN IN MAGNA MAURIS PHARETRA PLACERAT URNA AC FEUGIAT TORTOR AUCTOR EGET MAECENAS SIT AMET EROS FELIS ETIAM SAPIEN PURUS MALESUADA FERMENTUM VIVERRA VEL PORTA SIT AMET LECTUS CLASS APTENT TACITI SOCIOSQU AD LITORA TORQUENT PER CONUBIA NOSTRA PER INCEPTOS HIMENAEOS MAURIS VEHICULA DAPIBUS INTERDUM FUSCE SIT AMET NISI VENENATIS PLACERAT LIGULA ID CONDIMENTUM ODIO DUIS URNA JUSTO IMPERDIET UT COMMODO ID ULTRICES IN ELIT SED EGESTAS FACILISIS EX IN HENDRERIT IPSUM EGESTAS IMPERDIET
I hold it dearly in my heart and hope
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
It'll come true someday soon
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to
I don't have anything, nothing at all
But if I could have this one wish granted
It would fill the void inside my heart
I can feel the warm breeze blowing
And see shooting stars filling the sky
They make me feel as if
I can do anything, y'know?
In this wonderful world
Nothing is set in stone
The as-yet untold future
Shines brighter than the sun
I want to take hold of my future
With my own two hands
And write pages filled with hope
Into the book of my life
Chapter 6
Meeting
Lutz.
Be quiet and do exactly as I say.
Wh-What's this about, Myne?
No, wait! Stop!
If all you were gonna do was wash my hair,
then you shoulda said so.
If I had, you'd have just said no and ran off.
Actually,
why is this necessary?
First impressions are key.
Make sure to wear your
best clothes tomorrow as well.
I don't really think it's gonna make a difference.
I want to make sure we've done everything we can.
Ah, that felt refreshing.
Hey, what do you want to do once
you become a traveling merchant?
Where'd that come from?
You need to really think about that.
You don't have a reference
from your parents, after all.
If you can't tell him what you want to do,
Mr. Otto won't introduce you to anyone.
Would you be able to answer immediately?
I mean, you want to become a merchant too, right?
Well, it's my second choice.
But I've thought about what I'd want to do
if I became an apprentice merchant.
And what's that?
I want to sell paper.
Paper?
Not books?
Being honest, I don't think books would sell here.
But paper should do well.
Hey,
it was at third bell, right?
Aren't we super early?
Better than being late, right?
Oh, he's here.
First off, the greeting, remember?
Y-Yeah.
Huh?
It's not just Mr. Otto?
Hey, Myne.
Good morning, Mr. Otto.
Thank you for taking the time to meet us today.
This is my good friend Lutz.
Good day!
My name is Lutz!
It's a pleasure to meet you!
This is Myne, my assistant
and the captain's daughter.
Your assistant is a girl who
has yet to be baptized, huh?
I'm teaching her to read and write so
that she can work for me in the future.
I see...
This is Benno. He's an old acquaintance
from my traveling merchant days.
He can seem kind of abrasive,
but he's a nice guy really.
It's nice to meet you. I'm Myne.
I hope we will have a productive day.
My, how polite.
I am Benno.
The pleasure is all mine.
Before we start, might I ask about
the stick you have in your hair?
This is a hair stick.
You use it to tie your hair up.
It really is just a stick.
Yes, it's a stick carved from wood.
Amazing...
Say, what are you putting
in your hair to make it like this?
It's a mixture of a variety of common
things, but the details are secret.
The boy's hair is impressive as well.
Yes, Myne washed it for me.
Tch. I see.
Too bad.
I'm not letting go of such a lucrative card so easily.
Well, then.
Lutz, you wanted to become a traveling merchant.
Y-Yes.
I...
Just forget about it.
Huh?
Only an idiot would void their city citizenship.
"City citizenship"?
It gives you your rights to live here in this city.
So, if you didn't have that...
Without city citizenship,
you wouldn't be able to confirm your identity.
Getting a job, renting a home,
or even marriage, would all be off the table.
You're baptized at the age of seven, correct?
Yeah.
That's when you're granted your city citizenship.
If an outsider wants to get their hands on one,
it'll cost them a great fortune.
But...
Not only that...
Living as a traveler is very different
from staying rooted in the city.
For example, what do you do when you need water?
I draw some from the well.
That's right.
But you can't assume you'll find one
reliably when you're out on the road.
You have to search out sources of water.
You could head for a river—
You might not always know
where to find the nearest one.
There's no guarantee you'll always be traveling close to rivers either.
Yes, Myne's right.
That's why a family's routes are passed
down through generations in this trade.
Those routes are too valuable
to share with outsiders.
And finally, the most important part
is a traveling merchant's goal.
Do you know what the long-term
goal for any traveling merchant is?
Um...
City citizenship.
Huh?
They all dream of one day
gathering enough money to bid farewell to the
tough life outside and live in safety within city walls.
That's all most traveling merchants ever want.
I had no idea...
Do you think those merchants
working hard to earn their citizenships
would ever accept someone
like you throwing away his?
This is the reality of it.
Give up on becoming a traveling merchant.
And, well, this is Myne's suggestion, but...
how about becoming an
apprentice merchant instead?
Myne?
I figured you should hear all this traveling
merchant stuff from someone who has lived it.
But after hearing everything he just talked about,
I really do think it'd be better
for you to give up on it.
I see.
So you've been looking out for me, huh?
Apparently regular merchants
leave the city as well to stock up.
An apprentice merchant, huh?
Do you want to become a merchant?
I do!
In that case, what do you plan to sell?
Once you become a merchant, what will you sell?
Uh...
Well...
If you have no answer, then we're done here.
Lutz, will you make my paper for me?
Huh?
I know just the thing!
I want to make all the things Myne thinks up!
So she'll invent new products,
and you'll make and sell them?
Do you plan on becoming a merchant as well, girl?
It's my second choice.
And your first choice
is doing paperwork at the gate?
My first choice is owning a book store.
Or rather, becoming a librarian.
Pardon? What's a librarian?
Um, someone that takes care of books.
That sounds like work for a noble.
Damn it! Those nobles are so lucky!
So, did you have a product in mind?
Yes.
I want to make and sell paper
that's not made from animal skin.
Paper not made from animal skin?
Yes.
I'll make paper using plants.
Out of plants, you say?
Yes, it should be more efficient
to make than parchment
so I think it will be profitable merchandise.
Makes sense.
So, how do you plan on making it?
The details are secret.
I'd like to see it.
Do you have any made?
None as of yet.
We'll have some prototypes made
by the time of our baptisms next summer.
You can decide then whether they'll be of use.
Very interesting.
Well, why not.
We did it.
We sure did, Lutz!
Let's do our best!
Yeah!
Mr. Otto, thank you for today.
It ended up being a pretty interesting day off.
Her appearance, her manner of speaking...
No matter how you look at it, they're not
those of an unbaptized commoner daughter.
The rest of her family is pretty normal.
Myne's the only one that stands out.
Plant-based paper, huh?
If she can make it, it'll turn the market upside down.
Hold on a second. Are you planning on hiring her?
Naturally.
She's already thought of hair sticks,
a way to make hair shine...
Not to mention, paper made from plants?
She must be a veritable font of crafting knowledge.
I wholeheartedly wish to take
both of them under my wing.
Not happening. She's my assistant.
It's nice to see that you're in a good mood,
but make sure you don't get too excited, Myne.
You'll come down with another fever.
But we're gonna be making paper!
If we make paper, then we can make books too!
Yahoo!
I mean, making it will be great, sure,
but how are we gonna go about it?
Oh, that's right...
We have no tools.
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
So, how'd it go, Myne?
Apparently she was accepted
as an apprentice merchant, together with Lutz.
What, really?
I didn't actually expect that to work out.
There are some conditions, though.
A steamer... and a papermaking mold...
There are two steps to papermaking:
extracting the fiber, and molding it.
First, you chop wood,
then steam it,
and peel the bark off after.
Then!
TH
THE
THEN!
Bathe it in an ash mixture
to remove any excess material,
and beat the resulting fibers to untangle them.
After that!
AFTER
THAT!
Mix those fibers in a special water and plant
mixture and spread it evenly into slices.
Place weights on the slices to squeeze the water out.
Once they're done drying, you're finished!
If I lack the tools, I'll just have to make them!
I should ask Lutz tomorrow whether
we can make all of these things.
I'm back!
Welcome home, Dad!
I'm home.
Oh, welcome home, Dad.
Myne, don't let it bring you down.
You'll just have to find somewhere
else to become an apprentice.
Why are you, Mom and Tuuli
all so certain I was gonna fail?
I'll have you know I was accepted!
Huh, what?
With some conditions though.
A tree that'd give us good base material?
Yeah, I want you to look for young trees
with long, durable, and soft fibers.
I can try asking someone
with a better head for trees.
That'd help.
Oh and...
Could you make these, Lutz?
Do we have nails?
Nails?
Yeah. Without nails, I won't be able to.
So, I'm now missing the tools to make the tools.
I guess you've gotta make some nails then.
This isn't funny, you know...
By the way, Mr. Otto, why did you become a soldier?
You said city citizenships are expensive, right?
To marry Corinna.
It was just as I had turned fifteen,
when I was taking my first steps into adulthood.
I had a fated encounter when I came to this city.
She stole my heart the moment I first saw her.
In short: It was apparently love at first sight,
so he bought his citizenship and became a soldier.
Oh, Myne. Shall we cut a deal?
A deal?
If you teach me how you get your hair
shiny like that, I'll finance your nails.
Really?
But why would Mr. Otto want to know
how to make all-in-one shampoo?
What he really cares about is... his wife?
It's for his wife, isn't it?
I can't show you how it's made,
but I can exchange some for the nails.
An exchange of goods, huh?
Sure, why not.
We have a deal.
I was invited to visit
Mr. Otto's house on my next day off.
This is amazing. It's all part of
the same city, but it looks so different.
Is this your first time visiting
the north part of the city?
It is. Us commoners don't really have
much money, so we live in the south.
How come you're living here, Mr. Otto?
Someone couldn't let go of his cute little sister
and had his brother-in-law live above his place.
Oh?
We're here.
Wait, this?
It's on the third floor.
It's impressive that he was allowed to marry
someone that can afford to live somewhere so fancy.
Please, come in.
I'm glad to see you've made it.
I'm Corinna.
Otto's wife.
It's nice to meet you, Mrs. Corinna, I'm Myne.
I've been looking forward to meeting you.
You really are a well-mannered little girl.
And, my, what beautiful hair.
Ah, pardon me, let me show you in.
Mrs. Corinna might still be young,
but she's apparently famous in the sewing world.
Tuuli got jealous that I was
getting to meet her seamstress idol.
I've prepared everything you asked for, Myne.
Thank you!
It's turned so wonderfully silky...
Has it been to your liking?
Yes, quite.
Thank you, Myne.
Say, Myne, would you mind me asking something?
Yes?
What's Otto like at the gate?
He gave up his merchant life for me so
I can't help worrying about him sometimes.
There's nothing to worry about.
He's still acting like a merchant even at the gate.
When a merchant comes by and
he strikes up a bargain for supplies
he gets all excited just like a merchant would.
I see. Just like a merchant, huh?
It feels like a weight has been lifted off my shoulders.
How does it look, Otto?
M-Myne, didn't you have something
important to be doing right now?
If you give me all the nails I want,
I might remember what it was...
Got 'em!
Having finally gotten the nails,
we started work on the molds immediately.
Can you make them to exact measure to
avoid any gaps when they're stacked?
Exact measure?
I'd have to ask my Dad or brothers
for the tools to be able to do that.
Do you think they'll lend you them?
Well...
I'm not sure.
Those merchants only think 'bout money.
Cold-blooded, barely human, I tell ya.
Rather than an apprentice merchant,
can't you just become a craftsman
like your father and brothers, Lutz?
Lutz, are you okay?
Nothing to fret about.
I'll figure something out.
Oh, yeah, I went around and asked
some lumber dealers about the wood.
Really?
Yeah, so the soft trees are...
Myne, Lutz.
Here you go.
It's an invitation.
What's it say?
To the two of us...
Oh, it's a summons from Mr. Benno.
Huh?
I wholeheartedly wish to take
both of them under my wing.
Not happening. She's my assistant.
Mr. Otto!
What's wrong, Myne?
I have a question.
Have you ever heard of an illness where
your fever suddenly rises, but then falls again?
It kinda feels like I'm being eaten up by the fever...
I... can't say I have.
No idea.
I see.
Thank you anyway.
Myne is sickly to the point of worry.
There's no way she can work for you.
Perhaps she suffers from the Devouring.
What?
If it is the Devouring,
then she doesn't have long left.
tell me, oh my angel
oh my lovely, let me dream again
I gently brush my hair
And put a hairpin through it
In the sea of green
A flower ornament blooms
It is a gift from my angel
It touches my forehead
Oh so gently
And it reminds me
Of the warm light that gathered
To bring my angel into this world
This fever is making me delirious
Ah, these times are so dear to me
There must have been something more
Some greater force that led me to you
Our fates tangle and unravel as we become family
I have been always living
Inside a book
But then my heart melted
And now I have experienced
The real world
Next Chapter
Seeds of Suspicion
Well, it seems you've gotten one step
closer to making plant-based paper.
Yeah!
More importantly, Head Priest.
What'd they mean by "if it is the Devouring,
then she doesn't have long left"?
It's exactly as it sounds.
Would you like to know more?
The way the Devouring takes you, perchance?
Being taken by the Devouring
is a truly terrifying experience.
No! Please stop!
I hate scary and painful things!
Then I suppose I shall stop.
Illustration:     Kitora Con