Myne was reborn as a commoner's
daughter in a world without books.
Wishing to read books more than anything else,
Myne sets out to create
books through trial and error.
However, Myne has a
terrible hurdle to overcome...
If it is the Devouring,
then she doesn't have long left.
I have a wish, just one simple wish
Ascendance of a Bookworm
LOREM IPSUM DOLOR SIT AMET CONSECTETUR ADIPISCING ELIT FUSCE EFFICITUR LECTUS ID NISI RHONCUS PHARETRA NULLA QUAM VELIT TEMPUS QUIS ACCUMSAN EFFICITUR TEMPUS EU ANTE DONEC ULTRICES MOLESTIE MAXIMUS DONEC NON LOREM VITAE ANTE PRETIUM VESTIBULUM IN IN MAGNA MAURIS PHARETRA PLACERAT URNA AC FEUGIAT TORTOR AUCTOR EGET MAECENAS SIT AMET EROS FELIS ETIAM SAPIEN PURUS MALESUADA FERMENTUM VIVERRA VEL PORTA SIT AMET LECTUS CLASS APTENT TACITI SOCIOSQU AD LITORA TORQUENT PER CONUBIA NOSTRA PER INCEPTOS HIMENAEOS MAURIS VEHICULA DAPIBUS INTERDUM FUSCE SIT AMET NISI VENENATIS PLACERAT LIGULA ID CONDIMENTUM ODIO DUIS URNA JUSTO IMPERDIET UT COMMODO ID ULTRICES IN ELIT SED EGESTAS FACILISIS EX IN HENDRERIT IPSUM EGESTAS IMPERDIET
I hold it dearly in my heart and hope
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
It'll come true someday soon
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to
I don't have anything, nothing at all
But if I could have this one wish granted
It would fill the void inside my heart
I can feel the warm breeze blowing
And see shooting stars filling the sky
They make me feel as if
I can do anything, y'know?
In this wonderful world
Nothing is set in stone
The as-yet untold future
Shines brighter than the sun
I want to take hold of my future
With my own two hands
And write pages filled with hope
Into the book of my life
Chapter 7
Seeds of Suspicion
Whoa!
It looks completely different
despite being the same city, right?
I bet the food will be super fancy too.
That's right,
that invitation Mr. Benno sent
spoke of eating lunch together.
Fourth bell, at the Gilberta Company.
Where is the Gilberta Company this speaks of?
It's the first floor of the building I live in.
Wait, it's there?
So the brother that wouldn't
let his little sister move out...
Was Mr. Benno all along?
And that would mean that...
Mr. Benno is your brother-in-law?!
Spot on.
He totally played me for a fool there.
Hey, Lutz, let's make sure
nobody manages to fool us today.
Huh?
Aren't we just having lunch?
We're here!
I'm super nervous...
Someone went in.
There's not a lot of customers, huh.
Not much for sale either.
Maybe most of it's sold already?
Yeah, I think that's it.
The store presents itself very well,
and the clerks seem to be very polite
and highly trained in customer service.
I wouldn't be surprised if most of their
customers were rich people or nobles.
Sorry for summoning you here out of the blue.
Go ahead and eat.
Thanks for the meal.
Blegh. Throwing the broth away, are we?
Our soup is much better in comparison.
Is he angry?
Did I do something wrong?
And now, to the reason I invited you.
He's gonna shout at me!
Why did you rely on Otto?
Huh?
I heard from Otto that he financed your nails.
From what he told me, you traded some of that
fluid that makes your hair shine for them.
You mean the all-in-one shampoo?
I did, yes.
Is there a problem with that?
Yes, a big one.
You should have come and spoken with me first.
Well, since we're only partnering
right now under certain conditions,
that doesn't make us your apprentices, so...
Yeah.
Not true.
Listen, if this plant-based paper that you're
trying to create does in fact come to exist,
then you will both be accepted as apprentices here.
From there, your paper will become a product
of this business, the Gilberta Company.
Which is why the first person
you should come to for help...
should be me.
We're sorry. We've probably made
you look bad as our employer.
We'll be more careful from now on.
Wh-What are you doing?
Oh. Right.
I forgot that they don't bow here.
I mean... I understand.
As long as you get it.
It's about time we talked business, then.
I will supply you with the necessary
materials to create your paper.
Making paper is our test
to become apprentices, right?
Is it really okay for you to supply us?
I won't be able to judge you properly
if you aren't working with the correct tools.
A new business cannot be
started without prior investment.
Well, that much is true.
Of course, I'm not saying it will be free.
In exchange for my assistance, you shall share
the method used to create that hair-glistening fluid.
I see, so you're basically asking for something
that can be used in place of collateral.
Huh? Where did you learn the word collateral?
What's collateral?
It's something you offer up when borrowing money.
Otherwise the lender would be in a
tight spot if they weren't paid back, right?
Huh.
That said, supplying the method used
to make it wouldn't work as collateral.
I'd like to buy the rights to it
in exchange for the tools.
It certainly isn't a bad deal.
Are you just supplying the tools as part of this deal?
Will the raw materials required also be included?
That can be done.
I've heard Lutz has been asking around about wood.
You want soft wood, right?
Merchant connections sure run deep, huh.
How long would you be supporting us for?
Baptism
Apprenticeship
7 Years Old
6 Years Old
Gilberta Company
Wage
Paper
Sale
Money
10 Percent
Apprenticeship
Until your baptism.
After which, the company will
purchase your entire paper stock.
Apprenticeship
Your cut will have the costs for raw materials,
plus a handling fee, subtracted.
Apprenticeship
And once we've been baptized?
The Gilberta Company will take
over sales of this paper.
Ten percent of the paper's net profits
will be added to your wages.
Rather than giving us a ten percent cut,
can you grant manufacturing rights of the paper to me,
and on top of that, all rights to sell it, to Lutz?
To what end?
You can promise to raise our wages, but you have
no reason to keep us once you can make it yourself.
We'd be in a pretty unfavorable position if you
threw us out once you got your hands on it.
So rather than potential profits, you'd prefer a deal
in which your job security is protected, huh?
Exactly. Is that a problem?
Your focus on self-preservation belies your age.
We've talked at length
about the rights to your paper,
but what of the hair fluid—
the "all-in-one shampoo", was it?
Do you not wish to retain any rights to it?
No, I don't.
I'm granting you the rights to sell it as you see fit.
Very well then.
That should be just about everything.
Write your supply order.
Oh, uh, how exactly do I...
Excuse me.
My name is Mark.
Master Benno has informed me of today's business.
After that, Mark taught me how to write supply
orders correctly while Lutz practiced writing.
Calculation without using a calculator, I see.
Truly remarkable.
To be totally honest,
I don't actually know how to use a calculator.
Hey, is everything okay, Lutz?
Yeah.
Supply orders, done!
Very good. Mark, get the contract magic ready.
Right away.
Huh? Contract magic?
H-He said magic right?
Was this a fantasy world all along?
Maybe I'll be able to use magic as well!
As you surely know,
magic is something only nobles are able to use.
Huh?
Not just books,
they even have my magic held hostage.
Those damn nobles.
Contract magic was originally conceived as
a means to hold unsavory nobles to their word.
With it in place,
it becomes impossible to break the terms
of a contract without both parties' consent.
This is special paper and ink
that is used for contract magic.
They're magical tools bestowed only
to merchants that deal with nobles directly.
That's a mysterious ink bottle,
and the ink inside it is blue.
Since they're expensive, they're only used for
contracts which involve large sums and profits.
Then the all-in-one shampoo is...
Damn it, I sold it off too cheap.
Myne holds the rights to manufacture paper
as well as to deciding who to partner with for its
manufacture, while Lutz holds the rights to sell it.
Both of them are forgoing all rights relating
to pricing and profiting from the paper.
Are there any problems with it?
No, it looks good.
I also think this is okay.
Then please sign here.
Mark.
The color of the ink changed from blue to black.
Right, it's your turns now.
Huh?
No way, I can't do this!
Myne?
We're signing the contract, right?
Give me your hand, I'll do it for you.
With that, the contract is in effect.
That ended up taking longer than I'd thought.
I'm surprised you managed
to write your own name already.
It's 'cause you taught me to before.
Good job remembering it.
Now all we have to do is make the paper, right?
Yeah.
Hey, Lutz, what's wrong?
Lutz!
Wait, Lutz!
Hey...
You are Myne, right?
What?
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
If you're really Myne,
then why are you able to talk like that?
Like what?
I'm talking about the conversation
we had with the adults.
I barely understood even half of it.
Seeing you talk on equal footing with
adults about things I don't understand...
It's just strange.
You...
definitely are Myne, right?
Who else could I be besides Myne?
Huh?
Ah, sorry. I got weird for a second there.
Hearing you talk about all that
complicated stuff kinda surprised me.
I messed up.
I got too excited about a lot of things today.
But as I get closer to actually making paper,
Lutz will realize that I'm not Myne.
When that happens, what will Lutz do about me?
Lutz...
I'm home!
Welcome back.
It's pretty late.
Yeah, I filled out supply orders at Mr. Benno's store.
I have to prepare for tomorrow.
Sorry to ask this right as you get back,
but could you draw some water?
Oh. Sure.
Hey,
who the hell are you?
Where's Myne?
Give Myne back!
Someone, please help me!
Who are you?
Who are you? Who are you?
Who are you? Who are you? Who are you?
Myne?
Did you have a bad dream?
I'm okay now.
Then get some more rest.
If people find out that I'm not Myne...
I'll just let whatever this heat
inside me is swallow me up
so I'll fade away into nothingness
and disappear for good.
I have to put my all into making paper now
so I won't feel any regret when the time comes.
Meeting Lutz feels a little awkward.
Good morning.
I'm going to the forest today,
so I can't go to Mr. Benno's store.
Okay.
I'll get all the business talk sorted while Lutz is gone.
That way I won't seem so suspicious anymore.
Perfect!
Then let us be on our way to order materials.
Yes, please!
Would it be possible to provide a workspace
of some kind to leave the tools in, Mark?
A workspace, you say?
I shall bring it up to Master Benno.
Do you have any special requirements?
We'll be going to the forest a lot,
so something close to the south gate would be ideal.
Understood.
I'll look into it.
Ah, we're almost at the lumber dealer.
Oh, this right here...
Ms. Myne!
Huh?
Where am I?
I'm glad to see you're awake, Myne.
You're finally up! I felt like I'd aged
a few years when I'd heard you collapsed.
Huh?
I am terribly sorry for inconveniencing you!
What... is that?
I'm prostrating myself!
Oh, well, uh...
It's something you do to
apologize and show remorse.
I see.
I heard from Otto that you had a frail body
but I didn't think it was quite this bad.
I'm fine now.
Your fever has already broken.
Yes, I feel much better now!
Go home for today.
But I still have to—
Now listen here!
I told you to go home, didn't I?
Ouch!
You're forbidden from coming
here by yourself from now on.
Make sure you come with that boy, you hear?
If you've got a good memory
then make sure you don't forget!
I won't.
I won't forget! Ah, that hurts!
And so, I was carried back home against my will,
given a long lecture by Mom,
and came down with another fever.
That girl...
She might really have the Devouring.
You talked about it before,
but what exactly is this "Devouring" anyway?
It's when a commoner is born with magical aptitude.
Isn't magic something only nobles can use?
I've never heard of that happening.
Most of them don't even make it to their
baptisms so it doesn't get talked about much.
They don't make it to their baptisms?
Indeed. Their mana continues
to accumulate as they grow.
However, it can spiral out of control and,
in the worst cases, kill them.
The stronger their aptitude, the earlier they die.
Is there no way to prevent it?
If they had a magic tool that could release
the mana trapped within them, it would save them.
So if Myne doesn't get one...
We can't be certain just yet.
But if it really is the Devouring,
then she's gonna die pretty soon.
Ah.
If the captain knew about this...
You hear me, Myne?
Keep pushing yourself too hard
and I won't let you leave the house.
I-I get it, Dad.
Lutz, I'm counting on you.
Got it, Uncle Günther.
Also, make sure you go together
with her if she goes to the store.
Mr. Benno told me that the place was
a no-go zone unless you were with me.
A "no-go zone"?
I'm counting on you, Lutz!
Um...
I got pretty frustrated.
You were able to do calculations,
and talk to adults about things I didn't understand.
I felt like I wasn't even needed in the first place.
Lutz...
So I said something mean.
I'm sorry.
So you were just frustrated, huh...
I thought you'd started hating me, Lutz.
I feel much better now.
Ah.
I-I don't hate you.
Come on, let's go.
Boy, keeping the girl healthy is your
top priority and most important task.
Think of it as the one central thing only you can do.
Got that?
Something only I can do?
Yeah.
Do you think there's anyone else,
apart from her family,
that'd go through the trouble of
looking after such a reckless girl?
Nope.
Do you think anyone in this store would?
Not likely.
Then, boy, I ask you:
Do you think the girl can walk
to the south gate today?
If she paces herself then I think she'll be okay.
Good to hear.
I'm lending you a building close to the south gate.
Mark will guide you there.
Thank you so much.
We can go and get everything
moved in as well and...
Huh?
Don't do anything unnecessary!
Just behave yourself, okay?
I'll handle all the physical stuff,
so don't do anything that'll cause you to collapse!
Please keep your frail physiology in mind.
Okay.
I know that face.
It's your "I'm totally gonna ignore
what I was just told" face.
You can tell?
Oh, come on!
I didn't realize it then,
but from that day on,
Lutz never called me Myne anymore.
tell me, oh my angel
oh my lovely, let me dream again
I gently brush my hair
And put a hairpin through it
In the sea of green
A flower ornament blooms
It is a gift from my angel
It touches my forehead
Oh so gently
And it reminds me
Of the warm light that gathered
To bring my angel into this world
This fever is making me delirious
Ah, these times are so dear to me
There must have been something more
Some greater force that led me to you
Our fates tangle and unravel as we become family
I have been always living
Inside a book
But then my heart melted
And now I have experienced
The real world
Next Chapter
Lutz's Myne
From then on, Lutz was assigned
the duty of watching after my well-being.
I see. Anyone would be concerned, I believe.
What do you mean?
Do you realize how shocking it is
to see someone faint right in front of you?
I harbor great sympathy
towards Benno and the others.
Oh, right, High Priest.
Next time, we're actually gonna make
paper out of plants, so look forward to it!
Illustration:     Chima