Academy City, the town of science
with a total population of 2,300,000.
I, Kamijou Touma, am a student here.
I'm a Level 0, meaning I have no abilities.
Or at least that's what people thought,
but my right hand seems to have a mysterious
power that eliminates any supernatural ability.
Thanks to that, my life is devoid of happiness,
fortune, and the protection of God.
FRIED NOODLE SANDWICH
Did I lose a bet or something?!
Isn't that way too unfair?!
One day, a weird white-clad nun called Index,
who has 103,000 books
in her head, fell from the sky.
And then it all started.
First I got attacked by a sorcerer
who tosses flames around like crazy.
Then I got chased around by a lady with a sword.
Then I had to fight the strongest esper,
who manipulates vectors.
And I also had to hang around by
the sparky Level 5, Misaka Mikoto.
And then crowds of girls
who look just like her showed up.
And just when I thought I'd gotten away
from the whole mess of magic and science,
the whole world was suddenly on edge.
Geez, gimme a break already!
There are foreign groups like the
Roman Catholic Church, or God's Right Seat.
What the hell's going on?
Hey, Tsuchimikado,
you're supposed to know about this stuff!
What's happening in the world?
What's everyone after?
C'mon, fill me in!
A Certain Magical Index
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
Carrying a ticking time bomb
The Earth keeps on turning, so hurry up!
No one can pretend it's not their business anymore
Suddenly common sense is out the door
Opposing fates fail to reach each other
Drenched in the rain of resentment
But why? Fear and doubt keep building up heavy in my heart
My racing heart is flooded with ambition
Ready!
Everyone that's drawn to this place
Has gone beyond the meaning and color of desire
My heart wants to stay strong
I feel it deep inside me
With all my soul, this one thing
Dive into a heart
Disturbance
Takin' a! Takin' a! Takin' a bath!
Foamy, foamy! Rinsey, then we take a bath!
No running away, Sphynx!
Touma's going to bring us some
yummy lunch soon, you know.
Wow, drying stuff without using magic.
Academy City's science is amazing.
Welcome back, Touma!
Geez, you were so late, I was starting
to think you'd never come back!
I was worried.
Sorry about that.
So, Touma, what's for lunch?
Well, you see,
I must have dropped my wallet somewhere,
so I couldn't buy anything.
So what about lunch?
Well, come on now,
you won't starve from missing one meal.
And the longer you wait for it,
the tastier the food is.
And...
Touma!
Such misfortune!
Come on!
I promise I won't get mad,
so explain to me why you did such a thing.
Can't you explain your actions?
You see...
You see, Aogami Pierce and I
were minding our own business debating whether
red or black bunny-girl suits are the best,
when Tsuchimikado butted in with
"white bunny-girl suits are the best, of course",
which we just couldn't let stand.
Fukiyose, don't tell me you were part of that.
Of course not!
I was just trying to get these idiots to shut up!
Even so,
don't you think you took things a bit too far?
And we couldn't even conclude our debate either.
I'll still stand firmly behind my position!
Flat-chested white bunnies for the win!
You're still saying that?!
Anything flat does it for this pedo!
Geez, just stop that already!
The four of you are going to pull
the weeds behind the gym after school!
Did you hear me?
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, man.
Now I won't be able to get to the
time-limited sale at the supermarket.
It's all Tsuchimikado's fault.
I know, right?
And I got dragged into it too.
Wait, where is he?
Tsuchimikado?
Got it.
No, I'll take care of it.
Yeah.
I'll leave the cleanup to you.
Oh dear, those children never change.
You said it.
By the way, Miss Oyafune,
are you knitting those gloves
as a present for someone?
I-It's not like that.
It's not like I'm starting now because
otherwise I won't finish in time for Christmas.
Late last night, large-scale
protests by a religious group
began in the industrial area
of Toulouse in southern France.
Toulouse, Southern France:  Religious Group Protests
Large-scale protest in Southern France
Transportation and other infrastructure
have been impacted severely.
Toulouse, Southern France:  Religious Group Protests
Large-scale protest in Southern France
Many fear that these protests against Academy City
and counter-movements opposing them
are going to increase tensions between
the Roman Catholic Church and Academy City.
It's hot in this thing!
Thank you for your efforts.
How come so many people are gathering to watch an
interception weapons exhibition event during work hours?
And this is just industry employees.
Tomorrow we open to the public,
and all hell's breaking loose.
Look at that, Shirai!
It's a fifth-generation tank!
And that's an autonomous
portable air-defense system!
Oh, they also have a cutting-edge powered suit!
This is just unbelievable!
You're unbelievable, Uiharu!
Man,
why doesn't he ever message me?
Darling!
What ails you, my darling?
You have been acting restless.
It's just that there are so many people here.
Indeed there are.
The event is more pompous and gaudy than usual.
And they've never brought Judgment
in to help with security before.
It's probably because of those protests.
They've all been looking for an excuse anyway.
Excuse?
You're overthinking it.
Although it's true that tensions
are rising around the world.
We have to get into position soon.
Let's go, Uiharu.
Y-Yes.
Farewell, darling.
Excuse us.
Yeah, keep up the good work.
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Inbox
Bargain Sale Goods Info
A very special deal just for you!
Super famous brand sunglasses
REPLY
Damned spam!
Damn it!
I knew those two would pull a disappearing act.
Such good friends.
Say, Fukiyose,
why do you still study so hard in your free time
even though the October midterms got canceled?
With no midterms,
the only thing that decides our grades
for the second school term are the finals.
Falling behind could be fatal.
Oh, I didn't think about that.
Also I'm not showing you my notes.
Huh? Well, school grades aren't everything.
You're making it sound like
all I can do is study for school.
So, can you do anything else?
I may not look it, but I throw a mean forkball.
Though I'm not really interested in baseball.
Oh?
Want me to show you what I've got?
Get ready to catch.
Are you serious?
Of course I am.
When am I not serious?
O-Okay.
Go ahead, I'm ready.
All right!
Don't lose your wits when you feel
my 150km/h super-speed ball!
H-Hold on, Fukiyose!
What?
Your skirt!
A-Are you all right, Kamijou?
Th-That was just a fastball.
Come on,
let it go already, Sphynx.
I told you, I'm sorry for forcing you into the shower.
Oh, it's Maika!
I'm going to be your neighbor again,
so I came over to say hi.
And I also plan to make lots of food,
so you can come over for meals.
Really?!
Oh, Sphynx! Wait!
Hey!
Watch the place while I'm gone!
Wait!
Wait, Sphynx!
Oh, my, what have we here?
Are you lost?
Come to granny.
Good kitty. There, there.
Sphynx!
Is this your cat?
His name is Sphynx.
Let's go back home, Sphynx.
Oh, my.
We had a bit of a fight.
Then he ran away.
I see.
We didn't have any lunch, so I'm so hungry.
Oh, my, we can't have that.
Food!
Yummy!
You want some too, Sphynx?
Looks like you two made up.
Yeah, thank you!
That scarf looks really warm.
Yes, it is.
You see, my daughter made it for me!
And then the next row is two fewer stitches.
Oh man, gloves are harder than I thought.
Let's see...
Oh, no!
Excuse me!
Can we go home...
now?
I'm sorry!
I-I thought she was gonna kill me.
A Certain Magical Index
Man, I really thought I was a goner.
And I guess Index is waiting hungry at home.
I should stop by the supermarket on my...
Huh?
Chaser!
What?
It doesn't work on this one?
A wise man stays away from danger.
Let sleeping sparkies lie.
Hey!
Don't ignore me and try to run away!
Please let me off this time!
Poor Kamijou is currently exhausted from
weeding the yard and getting hit-by-pitch.
I'd love to avoid any further problems today.
Hold on right there!
You never answered the message I sent you!
Message?
Did I get one?
Let me see that!
Hey! Don't snoop on my phone!
That's personal information!
What?
W-Wait a minute!
Why do you have a selfie with my mom?!
U-Umm...
What? You also have her in your contacts!
I-I didn't add that!
What?
I can see it right here!
I really don't know how that got there.
Misuzu was really drunk at the time.
You're on a first name basis?!
It's bad enough that you went and met her...
Misaka, i-it's not like that...
You scoundrel!
Tsk!
You're as vexing as always!
She was just drunk and fooling around!
Index was with us too.
If you have any doubts, just ask her yourself!
It's almost sundown.
Don't you still have that curfew?
Hmph, I can deal with that.
But lately the checks have gotten more rigorous.
Tensions are running high.
Well, you should watch out too.
O-Okay.
What's going on?
I don't know what happened on September 30th,
but you got in a fight, got hurt,
and whoever was behind it hasn't shown their face!
How did you...
That guy!
I see.
So that boy makes meals for you every day?
Yeah!
The food Touma makes is always super yummy!
Touma?
Yeah!
Is this Touma a kind person?
I'm not sure.
What do you think, Sphynx?
He says Touma's probably a kind person.
I see. That's good.
Excuse me for a moment.
Hello?
Ongoing Call
Yes.
All right.
Thank you.
Ongoing Call
I need to go now.
Thank you for keeping me company.
Thank you for treating me to all the yummy food.
You too, Sphynx.
Bye-bye then!
I'm sorry.
Toulouse, Southern France
Roman Catholic protests against Academy City intensify
Now that I think of it, after the Kazakiri incident,
Toulouse, Southern France
Roman Catholic protests against Academy City intensify
tensions are really running high in lots of places.
Toulouse, Southern France
Roman Catholic protests against Academy City intensify
Maybe I should visit
Tsuchimikado after I get home.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
No, I was the one that bumped into you.
That's not what I meant.
I was apologizing for the trouble
I'm about to cause for you.
Let's talk.
About the major disturbances happening
around the world at the moment.
You may want to discuss things,
but I have nothing to say.
I need your input in order to solve this problem.
Who in the world are you?
I'm Oyafune Monaka.
I'm a member of the
Academy City Board of Directors.
Does that answer your question?
You're a member of the Board?!
You don't believe me?
I'd imagine a board member
would be wearing a nicer scarf.
My daughter hand-made this scarf for me!
I won't allow you to speak ill of it!
I-I understand! I won't mention it again!
You mentioned solving the problem,
but I imagine no one can do anything because
the reasons and causes behind it are too complex.
True.
But what if there was a simple reason behind it?
That's why I wanted to speak with you.
My hopes lie with something you have
and even heads of state or the UN don't.
What are you talking about?
Your right hand.
Really?
Yes.
My Imagine Breaker.
So you're saying that a supernatural
ability is behind it all?
Yes.
What's happening at the moment isn't
the result of the events of September 30.
It's an ongoing problem.
Regardless of whether the recent protests
were instigated by the Roman Catholic Church,
it's true that they're using those disturbances
as a weapon to attack the stable
world order built around Academy City.
Even if the church has made a move,
my power doesn't help discover where
they are or what tricks they're using.
In order to try anything,
I need to know at least that.
Indeed.
I trust he can explain that part to you.
Tsuchimikado!
Done with your chat?
Not really, but it's fine.
I'll leave the rest to you.
I see.
Tsuchimikado!
Tsuchimikado! What are you doing?!
You bastard!
Tsuchimikado! You scumbag!
Don't...
Don't blame him.
What I just did goes against the plans
of the entire Board of Directors.
What?
They wish to aggravate the confrontation
and eliminate the Roman Catholic Church,
and the religious science faction they represent.
Such foolishness needs to be stopped.
That's why I needed to contact you,
a person who can resolve the entire situation.
I knew they'd found out what I had done.
And if I were to escape,
they'd probably go after my family.
That's why I asked him to exact
punishment on me directly.
Don't speak any more.
I'll deal with the rest.
You fulfilled your role perfectly.
So keep that in mind
and be at peace.
Can you get on it right away, Kamiyan?
All right.
First we head to District 23.
Then we fly to France.
Our target is a Roman Catholic mystic artifact,
the Document of Constantine, or C-Document.
It's the key to resolving this entire mess.
When I least expect it, you're gone
And loneliness hits me hard in the chest
In the night filled with signs I look up at the stars
I bite my lip and pray
Every time the dawn comes I run to you
You try to hide behind a smile that you're covered in wounds
But I notice, because I'm not a child
I'll protect you even if I have to make an enemy of the entire world
This strength comes from the light you've given me
I don't want to just wait for a miracle
I want to start a revolution that changes who the two of us are
And this is the night before it starts
Let's go, Kamiyan!
A-Are you serious?!
Next Time
I reunite with Itsuwa in the
foreign town I was dropped into.
Mystic artifacts? Ley lines?
Did you guys even need my right hand?
Next time: "God's Right Seat".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.