Come on,
tell me what I need to know,
Biagio Busoni and Lidvia Lorenzetti.
If you want a sermon from
the Roman Catholic Church,
we do those on Sundays.
Acting tough won't help you.
I'll drag the information out of
your heads by any means necessary.
Don't underestimate Necessarius.
Tell me what you know about God's Right Seat.
Could you first answer one question?
What is the present situation outside?
You can probably imagine.
It's that, or maybe even worse.
Saint Peter slips through the clutches
of the emperor and his sorcerer.
No!
Lidvia!
Let's hear her out.
Oriana Thomson.
I demand that you release her
so she can guide the weak who
have been engulfed in this chaos.
I see.
Even now you still concentrate on saving the weak.
But are you really in a position
to make that demand?
Oriana has agreed to a temporary
cooperation pact with the Anglican Church.
Her condition was for Lidvia Lorenzetti
to continue protecting the weak.
I doubt she would agree
to be released from that pact.
Don't make her hardship be in vain!
If this situation is caused by the Catholic Church—
no, by God's Right Seat,
then the key to resolving it lies in defeating them.
Don't you agree?
What are you people fighting for?
Our purpose is clear:
to save the stray sheep who have been engulfed
by the overwhelming power of magic.
That's how it's always been.
I've never met them in person,
but I've come by bits of information about them.
From what I hear, God's Right Seat is...
A Certain Magical Index
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
Carrying a ticking time bomb
The Earth keeps on turning, so hurry up!
No one can pretend it's not their business anymore
Suddenly common sense is out the door
Opposing fates fail to reach each other
Drenched in the rain of resentment
But why? Fear and doubt keep building up heavy in my heart
My racing heart is flooded with ambition
Ready!
Everyone that's drawn to this place
Has gone beyond the meaning and color of desire
My heart wants to stay strong
I feel it deep inside me
With all my soul, this one thing
Dive into a heart
God's Right Seat
M-My throat!
Strangl—
Are you all right?
Y-Yeah.
You're from the Amakusa Church.
Itsuwa, right?
Yes.
Long time, no see.
Did Tsuchimikado get you to come here?
Where is he, anyway?
Huh?
You know, that C-Document thing
that's causing protests everywhere.
H-How do you know about that?!
Listen closely, Kamiyan.
The C-Document is like a deed that gives the Pope
rights over all the lands of Europe
that were ruled by Constantine the Great.
It's said that the C-Document
can be used to make a sign appear over the land,
asserting that it belongs to the Pope.
However, the C-Document has
an even more preposterous power.
It can make anything that
the Pope says become the truth.
So the Pope can say something,
and to all Catholics,
that becomes the truth with
no other justification needed.
Th-That's...
Way too overpowered?
Well, all it actually does
is make people believe things.
It can't break the laws of physics.
And also it only works while
it sits in the heart of the Vatican.
So the Catholic Church is currently
using that C-Document
to make people believe that Academy City is evil.
You're saying that's what's causing the protests?
Possibly.
Didn't anyone contact you about this?
No.
We of the Amakusa Christian Church
are in France evaluating the magical properties
of the local terrain and ley lines on
a commission from the Anglican Church.
France?!
Yes.
This is Avignon, a city in southern France.
I thought he said that the C-Document
could only be used if it's in the Vatican.
Sorry,
do you mind if I fetch my bag?
I left it up on the bridge.
You jumped down from there to save me?
I panicked a bit.
I see.
I would've been in trouble if it weren't for your help.
Thank you.
Oh, no, don't worry about it!
By the way, do you happen to have
a change of clothes in your bag?
Yes. I have another set to use as a disguise.
Okay. That's good.
I-I apologize for my unsightliness.
It would've felt less awkward
if you'd just screamed at me.
Tsuchimikado
Motoharu
OPTIONS
It doesn't seem like it's broken.
Tsuchimikado
Motoharu
OPTIONS
Tsuchimikado
Motoharu
OPTIONS
I-I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Uhm, Itsuwa...
Th-This was supposed to go over the tank top.
It's supposed to make me look like someone else.
Don't say anything!
I-It's fine,
Kanzaki wears something similar.
The priestess doesn't wear anything so disheveled!
What? Really?
So, umm,
if you're also after the C-Document,
would you like to travel together
until you meet up with Tsuchimikado?
That would be really helpful for me,
if you're fine with it.
Of course!
A popular chain that's also in Japan.
Shouldn't we go to a place
that's more out of the way?
We'd stand out too much in such a place.
I guess you're right.
Come on, let's go inside.
Wait up!
Let me just tell Tsuchimikado where I am.
Tsuchimikado Motoharu
No Subject
drawly coffee
Inbox
Sending Mail...
That guy...
Think so?
Are those protesters?
Yes.
So, why Avignon and not the Vatican?
Are you familiar with the period
known as the Avignon Papacy,
beginning near the end of the 13th century?
There was a conflict between
the Pope and the king of France.
The king ordered the Pope arrested,
and brought here to Avignon.
During the following 68 years,
all functions of the Vatican took place
in the Palais des Papes in Avignon.
However...
Hold on! I'll get you a towel!
Thank you!
I mean, merci!
Sorry I interrupted you.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
So, can the Pope do his work from anywhere,
not just from the Vatican?
Not really.
There are things he can only do at his seat of power.
Most importantly, he can't use the
mystic artifacts that are in Rome.
That's why he used the ley lines between Avignon
and the Vatican to create a magical pipeline.
That allowed him to remotely control
the equipment in the Papal State.
I see.
So that means those mystic artifacts
can be used here in Avignon.
Exactly.
But that seems way more effort than it's worth.
Why not just use them at the Vatican directly?
Apparently, doing it from here lets him ignore
the procedures required to use them at the Vatican.
All you need here is the Pope's decision.
However, the drawback is that
it takes time for the artifact to activate.
So we might still be able to prevent
the C-Document from exercising its full power.
We might be, huh?
I'm sorry! All I have is speculation.
Say, Itsuwa, can I help in any—
There! That's him!
Hey, what are you people doing?!
There's a guy from Academy City over there!
Academy City?
This guy?
This way!
Damn! Get them!
Wait! That child!
It's fine. They didn't look like they were out to kill.
Let's go, quickly!
Damn it!
It's always the innocent bystanders
who get caught up that suffer the most!
I have to put an end to this as soon as possible!
It's true.
Damn Academy City wretch!
Itsuwa, have you gotten dragged
into these riots before?
No.
I've been trying to distance myself
from them the moment I sense something.
I knew it.
Their timing was too perfect.
This riot might be an interception
move from the other side.
Really?
Looks like I don't have time to wait
for Tsuchimikado to contact me.
Let's head to the Palais des Papes without him.
We don't want them to take
the C-Document back to the Vatican.
That's why I have to destroy it here and now.
Bend down a bit and run in.
All right! Let's run!
A Certain Magical Index
I've been told that God's Right Seat
is an organization whose purpose
is to overcome the original sin.
The sin Adam and Eve committed
when they ate the fruit of knowledge.
It's said that as their descendants,
all mankind shares in that sin.
However, there is an exception to that.
The Holy Mother, Mary.
The Immaculate Conception.
The Holy Mother was born without sin
to bring the Son of God into the world.
That demonstrates that it's possible
to be cleansed of the original sin
other than by leading a life devoted
to belief in the Son of God.
And you're saying that they
figured out a way to do this?
I was told that they succeeded in diluting
theirs to the greatest extent possible.
Even if it isn't completely gone,
the minimization of the sin allows them
to use the powers of God and the angels
that are far out of the reach of normal humans.
If they did that,
they'd become closer to angels than to humans.
Does that mean that the
ultimate goal of God's Right Seat
is to eliminate the final traces
of the original sin from their bodies?
That's just a means to their end.
They never really tried to hide their true goal.
Which is?
To literally sit on the right side of God.
They want nothing less.
I thought it might be like this.
Indeed, we need to go through this crowd
to get to the Palais des Papes.
Well, we have no choice.
Hey, Kamiyan! You okay?
Tsuchimikado! Where the hell have you been?!
I'm heading for the Palais des Papes.
I thought as much.
I don't remember telling you about that.
Itsuwa from the Amakusa Church told me.
But we're having trouble
getting close because of the riots.
Are these also caused by the C-Document?
Bingo!
Very perceptive.
But knowing that doesn't help you much, does it?
Isn't there anything we can do?
There is.
Question:
why is the Avignon Palais des Papes important?
Because you can remotely control
equipment in the Papal State from there.
Bingo!
Oh right! The ley line pipeline!
Bingo! Bingo!
Exactly! We can sever the ley line
connecting it to the Vatican.
It might be difficult to get close
to the Palais des Papes,
but we can definitely get to
somewhere along the pipeline.
And then I just have to destroy
it with my right hand!
It's probably safer if you don't do that.
But ley lines are magical, right?
So I can...
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
We still don't really understand
the power of your right hand.
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
Ongoing Call
Motoharu
Tsuchimikado
It might be able to erase
all magic and esper powers,
but there are probably exceptions.
It's Itsuwa, right?
Do you know how you can destroy the pipeline?
Y-Yes.
If you think the Amakusa Church ways would do.
Should be fine.
I'll go looking myself too,
but if you two find it first, take care of it.
Closed
A museum, huh?
They probably closed early because
they were worried about the riots.
I guess we can check inside, but how do we get in?
Come on! Quickly!
O-Okay.
Hey, wait!
Yes, it's here.
Power processed by Catholic Church techniques.
It has the distinct characteristics
of western Christianity.
I don't really see anything special.
It's concealed quite ingeniously.
Let's do it before the enemy notices us.
Oh yeah, the Amakusa Church uses mundane
objects for its magic rituals, doesn't it?
That's right.
A pamphlet, mineral water, white pant—
What's wrong, Itsuwa?
...the ritual.
I really need to use them for this ritual.
I can't completely sever the ley line.
But I can make it so the pipeline can't be used.
Here I go.
Get back, Itsuwa!
Itsuwa!
No! Get outside!
Quickly! Get out!
My, my!
Apparently shooting at such close range
really does reduce the accuracy.
Magic?
The Roman Catholics!
You're not wrong, but I prefer you think
of me as being with God's Right Seat.
I am Terra of the Left.
I finally have something to do.
After all, we can't use
regular magic that humans use.
We have to leave the operation
of the C-Document to others.
So I decided to come over
and kill some time with you.
I would be grateful if you would
provide some entertainment for me.
Those are rather powerful.
But my right hand can handle it.
Normally that last hit would've killed you.
I see. So that's the Imagine Breaker.
I heard you defeated Vento of the Front.
Itsuwa.
I'm really sorry.
Seven Blades of the Seven Teachings!
Change precedence.
The body before the wall.
The blade's movement before the wall.
Itsuwa!
The stories I'd heard about the Imagine Breaker
had me somewhat hopeful.
But to be honest, I'm very disappointed.
If Vento had been in good shape,
I'm sure defeating the likes of you
would've been child's play for her.
So, this is...
This is the power of God's Right Seat!
When I least expect it, you're gone
And loneliness hits me hard in the chest
In the night filled with signs I look up at the stars
I bite my lip and pray
Every time the dawn comes I run to you
You try to hide behind a smile that you're covered in wounds
But I notice, because I'm not a child
I'll protect you even if I have to make an enemy of the entire world
This strength comes from the light you've given me
I don't want to just wait for a miracle
I want to start a revolution that changes who the two of us are
And this is the night before it starts
Next Time
Mixing chaos with more chaos,
the city is covered by the fire of science.
What is the secret of my right hand
that Terra speaks about?!
Next time: "C-Document".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.