This girl's supposed to be Iwasawa's replacement?!
No way!
My name's Yui!  Let's all get along!
Who's this girl?
Didn't you hear?
She's a candidate for GirlDeMo's new vocalist.
Are you sure about this?
Girls Dead Monster is a rock band.
Are we trying to turn it into an idol band now?
No, I really can sing!
Please listen and then judge for yourselves!
Well, at least she looks the part.
Yeaaaaaah!
Thank you all so much for coming today!
Yea-heah-
Was that part of the performance?
Death metal, maybe?
Ohh, my! She's a crazy baby.
I... I'm dying.
No, I think it was an accident.
She's quite the lively young girl, huh?
She's like the reverse of Iwasawa's cool beauty.
I'm don't know how she'll fare as the lead vocalist of Girls Dead Monster.
Should we look for someone better?
Yeah, let's.
Hey!
My singing was fine, wasn't it?!
As Iwasawa's huge fan, I can sing all her songs!
There was nothing that appealed to the heart.
None.
Nope.
Hey!
Don't use such vague reasons to prune a budding flower like me!
What kind of Senpai are you guys?!
She sure is noisy.
She's wrapped up in her own motives.
What should we do?
She at least seems like she really wants to do it.
She's just being trendy.
Let's just leave it up to the band members to decide.
Really?!
Hooray!
I'm gonna be with Hisako-san, the guitarist!
I can't get enough of Hisako-san's murderous riffs!
It makes me wonder what she's thinking!
You're fired.
What?!
Definitely fired.
Whaaa!  Did I say something wrong?
If the band is like this, we won't be able to pull off large-scale ops during the ball game.
Ball game?  You guys do stuff like that?
Of course we do.  This is a normal school, after all.
Are we just gonna observe?
We'll be competing, of course.
Won't we disappear if we start participating in events?
We'll be competing unofficially.
Got that, everyone?  Start putting together a good team.
If your team performs worse than the regular students...
You'll have to face a penalty worse than death!
Stop ignoring me!
Is she getting desperate because we can't do anything right now?
Daily training is part of our job.  This is just a check-up on that.
Otonashi.
I need you.
You coming on to me?
NO!  I mean for my team!
Let's make a team!
If we lose, we're in for it.  Yurippe's serious about that.
Huh?  What about the other members?
Leave it to me.
I pretty much live by my popularity.
I'll put together the strongest team ever!
What?!  You joined Takamatsu's team?
Yeah.
Why would you do that?!  You should have waited to join mine!
Why should I sit around waiting for you to invite me?
Besides, Takamatsu's team is bound to be better than yours.
Man, and she's really athletic, too.
That hurts.
Yeah, you sure are popular...
Fine.
I didn't want to do this, but let's go ask
the charismatic Matsushita-godan to join us.
I'm sure he's already taken.
He'll be waiting for me.
How should I put this... he's a true friend.
I'm kinda embarrassed.
Ahh, I already joined up with Takeyama.
I had no reason to refuse.
Wait a second!
Why?!  I believed in you!
Well, he said from now on he'd hand over any Meat Udon tickets he gets...
Meat?
A minute ago this guy was like;
"He's a true friend.  I'm kinda embarrassed, haha."
Don't laugh!
Damn it!
We'll ask TK next.
TK, I'm counting on you.
By the way, why does everyone call him TK?
It's what he calls himself.
Nobody knows his real name.  He's a mysterious guy.
But I believe in him.
GOD DAMN!
Now you're starting to sound like TK.
Hey by the way, what kind of ball game are we playing, anyway?
Baseball.
Which means we'll need 7 more members...
Probably not happening.
You look troubled.
Well, if it isn't Miss Choked-Herself-In-Her-Death-Metal-Performance.
Do I look like the type to put on a performance like that?!
You do, totally.
So?  What do you want?
You don't have enough members, right?
I'll be an asset to your team!
Asset?
Wait a sec.  If she gets hit by a wild pitch,
that'll take out the opponent's pitcher.
If she gets hit!  Alright, sign on!
I can see what you're thinking, your brain tissue is melting and leaking from your nose!
Hey!  I'm your Senpai, you know!
Oh, my apologies.
Honorable Senpai, your honorable brain tissue is melting, and leaking from your honorable nose, is it not?
As if!
Senpai, it hurts!
I'm hurting, too!
Well, she at least seems athletic.
What are you talking about, Otonashi?
I don't even want to think about having a girl as brainless as her for a teammate!
It hurts!
Even if you say that, everyone from the main squad's been turning us down left and right.
That's right!  I saw it all.
So Yui-nyan thought she'd come and join your team.
Huh?  Try saying that again.
Yui-nyan~
That pisses me off worst of all!
I give! I give! I give!
Let's get going.
Shiina-cchi.
Where are you?  Come out!
Shiina-cchi!
What do you want?
I've been looking for you.
You've got good reflexes, right?
I've never measured them.
I know you'll do fine!
Baseball!  Let's play some baseball!
Ever since that day...
I've been in here pondering how it is that I fell behind a newcomer.
You're talking about Operation Drop Into the Guild?
It's true that Otonashi being the only one to survive is almost a legend.
I was just lucky...
In terms of power and skill, I should have far surpassed you.
Agreed.
Except in one area: concentration.
No, you're way past me in that area too.
Ever since that day, I've been balancing this broom on my finger.
She's an idiot.
That stupidity gives her strength.
This is a good opportunity.
Let's fight, kid.
What kind of fight involves holding a broom?
Baseball, of course.
If you're gonna fight, let your scores do the fighting.
Don't fight one-on-one!
I accept.
I don't have to hold a broom too, do I?
Of course.
I'll show you just how strong my concentration is.
Alright!  It's decided!
We keep getting more idiots!
That brings us to 4.
I guess we have to.  Let's let him in.
Nobody's gonna invite him.
He's blunt and doesn't listen to anybody but Yurippe.
In other words, he's an idiot as well, right?
But we can still use an idiot.
And look!  Nobody's better than him at swinging a stick around.
Hmph.  You've finally come, huh?
It's time to settle things!
Ahh, but first let's have a preliminary.
Let's compete in the ball game to see whose reflexes are the best.
Why?
Strength alone isn't gonna impress Yurippe.
I accept!
What a moron.
He doesn't realize he's just being used.
Sorry.
It looks like most of the SSS members are on other teams by now, huh?
We still only have 5 people.  What do you plan to do?
Can't you drop that broom?
Even when you're being serious all that you say comes off as a joke.
It will drop when my concentration is interrupted.
Then how about this ?!
Whaaaa?
What are you doing?
Hey hey, quit messing around.
Hinata, do something about...
Hinata?
Hinata!
What's wrong?
Ahh... nothing.
I was just spacing out a little.
Alright, I guess it's come to this.
Let's recruit from the regular students.
Ooh! Ooh!
I'll go bring some of my awesome friends!
Huh?  Friends?
Um... we're...
Yui-nyan-san's fans.
We're like her groupies.
Yui-nyan isn't the type to be stuck-up with her skills.
I've been accumulating live street performance experience!
Nothing but trendy girls.
How are they gonna help our playing ability?
Well?  If we let them in that'll make 8 members...
We don't have much choice.
With this many, we should be set.
We're unofficial competitors, anyway.
We'll just forgo having a center, and have the right and left cover the middle.
You really think that'll work?
UTW Presents:
Home Run!
Wow!
I knew you'd pull through, TK!
Even though nobody knows what the hell you were doing when you died!
Don't stop dancing!
Woah, he hit it!
Hmm.  Our guerrilla operations are going well.
I wonder how our dear Tenshi-san is feeling right about now...
Ohh, looks like all the Warfront teams are advancing.
Alright.  Let's go win one, too.
Not again...
The team that progresses will have to beat our team.
You wanna decide who's first with Rock Paper Scissors?
There sure seems to be a lot of teams, all of a sudden.
Yeah well, we're all students here too, aren't we?
Hey, say something...
Give us what'cha got!
What if they really do give it to us?!
You're breaking my joints!
I won't be able to hit a home run!
Nobody expected you to in the first place!
If we lose here we're gonna be punished.
We've gotta give it our all.
You're up first!
Me?
I'm first!
Now now, hold up.
I'll be up second.
Shiina's third.
And number four, is you.
If we don't do it like that, it'll be your loss.
Hmph.  Fine.
That's easy enough.
We've gotta win it within 7 innings.
Let's get out of here before Tenshi shows up.
Okay, let's do it!
Fight-O!!
Um... ohhh.
Ohhh...
Your lack of unity is shocking.
Play ball!
We're going for a called game, huh?
Which means I've got to bring it home as the lead-off man.
Yeah!
Yay!
Is that what you call a hit ?!
What'd you say ?!
Here I come again!
That's not how this game works!
You're out!
What a moron.
Hmph.  Honestly...
A good place to play.
You sure you're ready?
For what?
Come on!
Home run!
No way!
So...
Why am I the pitcher?
Because Noda hit a home run.
So now, you've gotta keep them from scoring to stay in the game!
Just who are we fighting here?
Bring it!
Strike!
Is that all you've got?!
Damn you!
Not good enough!
Oh yeah?!
Like I said, don't just play around together!
It seems that stupidity transcends even death.
Ball 4!
Out!
Wow.  An idiot.
Team Hinata.
Third inning.  Proceeding towards called game.
Excellent.
The Warfront teams are all advancing well.
Everyone's so terrified of the "punishment worse than death" that they're trying their best.
How amusing.
It's well known within the Warfront that anyone subjected to your penalty games
have been so scarred that their personalities changed, Yurippe-san.
That's right.
Wait, what penalty games are you talking about?!
I don't know, I've never taken the punishment.
I've never done anything like that- Whoa.
We've successfully lured her out.
We don't have any weapons today.  All we've got is bats and gloves.
What kind of peaceful solution will you ask for?
This'll be good.
Your team is not registered to participate.
What's the problem?  It's a good thing to participate.
I'm the Student Council Vice President, Naoi.
We've formed a Student Council team.
We'll take out all of your teams legitimately.
What?  Your team has everyone from the real Baseball club, right?
Then there's no way we can win.
Hey! You better keep your head clean for when we chop it off !
That's strike two!
The saying is to clean your neck !  A clean head is just basic hygiene!
It hurts!
They're advancing past Takeyama's team.
Takamatsu's team was a called game.
Gahh.  This is definitely foul play.
We've only got one team left, huh?
Where are they?
It's Hinata's team.
I wanted to defeat Tenshi fair and square, but...
I can't count on these guys at all!
So, you've finally come.
The final match will now begin!
She's not cute at all!  At least say something to provoke us...
Play ball!
Home run!
Yeah!
Time out!
This is pretty bad.
It's no surprise that it's hard to hold off the Baseball club regulars.
Especially with our outfielder shortage.
Huuuuuuuh?
Oh.  I still had lunch tickets left over, so I treated him.
You did it?!
Nice one!  That man never forgets a food-debt!
Now our outfield is totally covered!
Give! I give!
Uh... yeah...
Let me go I'll kill you!
Nice work, Matsushita-godan!
We're looking more like a circus troupe than a baseball team.
Out!
3 outs!  Change!
Yes!
Pitcher change.
If we keep this up, we can win it!
Those guys are better than expected.
We're playing nice and fair.
I don't think we've ever messed up Tenshi's plans this badly!
Serves her right!
Yurippe-san.  You sound like the villain.
We might be able to win this.
The last inning.
One point difference.
Two outs.
Runners on second and third.
Time out!
This is tough.
I'm not sure we can hold them off.
Hey, let's change the pitcher...?
What's wrong, Hinata?
Huh?  Oh, sorry.
In the past...
When I was alive, I was in a situation like this one.
It was a really important game.
You...
You're shaking.
Huh?  I am?
How strange.
What happened?
I'm not sure.
I can't really remember.
I was on the Baseball team.
We were going for the High School Nationals.
It was so hot you could die.
My mouth tasted like dirt.
Those are the things I can remember.
It was the last inning of the match.
There were two outs...
Runners on second and third.
There was an easy fly ball to second.
I was right under it.
But...
Did I catch it?
Did I drop it?
That's what I can't remember.
Well, if I caught it there's no way I'd forget that, right?
I'm sure I missed it.
I can't even talk to him.
All the hard work over the past 3 years wasted because of one guy.
He's a huge plague on our team.
Hey, take it easy on him.
He hasn't even moved for a while.
I guess he can't man up.
I'm worried.  I'm gonna go discuss this with Senpai.
Yo.
I heard what happened.
That must've been rough.  Torturous.
What you need right now is...
Something like this.
Don't worry.
Well, don't worry too much, and try it just once.
You'll feel much better.
Are you...
gonna disappear?
Huh?
If we win this match...
Are you gonna disappear?
I won't disappear.
Why...
would I disappear...
from something like this?
Let's end it!  Otonashi!
No way...
A fly ball to second?
This is just like...
... that time.
Hinata!
If I catch this... will it all be over?
That would feel incredible.
Don't catch it!  Hinata!
I...
I don't want you to disappear!
You're wide open!
You've placed me in one too many manji holds, damn you!
Home!
You bitch!
What do you think you're doing at a time like this?!
I'm sorry!
I know I was wrong!  I was wrong!
Like I care!
Home!  Game set!
Damn you.  I won't forgive you for this!
That hurts, that hurts!
Die!  Die!
Both of you...just disappear.
Testing is about to start.
I knew this was coming!
What did you guys do?
I refuse!
The operation was nearly perfect.
W-What is that ?!
Kyaa!  I'm number 1!
That's the last piece Iwasawa left behind.
Who exactly are we fighting with?
But it's a Physics test...
I only fall in love for real!
What a joke.
I took that simple happiness away from her.