Behind me stands a shutter.
My fingers smell of steel.
Moving on, strumming on, the streets are all packed.
Find a way from here.
I found out an answer.
Play your rock.
Gaze into the distance.
In this town where nobody can take a breather.
The starry sky makes for the greatest stage.
The crows are cawing along.
I've always wondered when they even sleep.
I'll find a way too.
I'll sing a song to do it.
Let my rock ring out.
I'll sing with the crows.
"How much time are you gonna waste here?"
I get the feeling I've been asked that before.
If that's all you've got to say,
may you get carried away by their jet-black wings.
Disappear.
I've played so hard I think I'm gonna faint.
And my finger hurts from getting cut on the strings.
But you know, I won't stop. Tonight's another big story.
Find a way from here.
I found out an answer.
Play your rock.
Sing of your luck.
I'm always going to be standing here.
Right in the midst of all the passerbys.
On this stage enveloped in darkness,
I'll sing a song of rising hope.
You're tired too, aren't you?
I wish this could reach you wherever you are.
In the midst of this darkness,
a song of illuminating hope is born.
I'll sing this song.