Excellent.
No hemorrhaging or ischemia found.
No major change in red blood cells,
white blood cells, or hematocrit.
But your pulse is a bit on the rapid side.
Are you under any stress, Minnie C. Tachibana?
Not especially.
Tired of all these physical exams?
Not at all.
My husband enjoyed physical exams, too.
He said it was like being in an amusement park.
Glad to hear it.
Okay, next is...
Just a moment.
Let's finish another time.
Kitou wants to see you.
All right.
Mirror, mirror, on the wall
I want to change this world
The streetlight brightens up the night
And brings forth a sea of light
That reaches far into the distance
I dream upon a restless star
As I wait for the night to end
So I can continue searching for the future
The curtains covering a new stage
slowly part
as I wake up
Wonder drive! Let's start running now!
Wonder drive! To the world ahead of us!
Uncertainty, hesitation, and confusion
Just throw it all away!
Wonder drive! Keep charging along this path
Replace that clock's rhythm with your own
We are walking along a road
No one has yet dreamed of
Mirror, mirror, on the wall
I want to change this world
Cards
Is something wrong?
No.
Doesn't Mount Fuji look beautiful today?
Ah, yes. It certainly does.
It's just like the day I first came here.
You know, to tell the truth, I was quite worried.
When I heard a former US Marine Corps
second lieutenant was coming,
I expected someone scary...
I'm glad it ended up being
someone like you, Tachibana.
Please feel free to call me "Minnie C."
That's how my husband introduced
me to his friends and family.
I'll do that, then.
You look wonderful in a kimono, Minnie C.
Do you often visit Japan?
No,
I first saw Mount Fuji when
I flew over it on my honeymoon.
My husband was so excited!
Oh?
He loved Japanese culture more than anything,
so when I wear a kimono, I feel as if he's near me.
Do you see it, darling?
Isn't it beautiful?
Here you go.
This is good.
I want more.
I'll go buy some more.
So your name is Sana?
Are you the lady who talked
to me at the research facility?
No,
but we have met recently.
You don't remember?
Pardon me.
I was asked to handle the pigs.
Right, over here.
What will they do with them?
They'll be cared for at a special facility.
The people there will probably do a few tests,
but they won't harm the pigs at all.
Tests?
Yes.
They're very special pigs
created by your power, after all.
You know about me?
Yes.
Where did this pig come from?
Huh?
Well, it's alive, right?
What would happen if I used
my power to get rid of it?
Do you want to do that?
Huh?
Yeah.
You know those long cylinders we always use, right?
Right, I'd like nine, if possible.
Can we do that?
Great, I'll send someone to get them now.
Thanks.
Cylinders? For the flowers?
The things like vases?
Yeah.
Hey, Chinatsu! Ichirou!
Yes?
I never knew those were provided by the florist.
I'm no expert, but can't you use something else?
Everything's decided through prior discussion.
I can't just change things like that.
What's up?
I need you to go to Sakaki's place
in Kokubunji and pick up the stuff listed.
Got it.
Take care of them, okay?
Just leave them to us.
How's it going on your end?
Sorry, I'm still analyzing.
This ability-user has a complex signal.
Sana.
Hm?
Her name is Sana.
Roger that.
I'll keep analyzing Sana's pattern!
When I see them like this, pigs are pretty adorable.
Huh?
What's wrong?
Didn't you see one that looked a bit different?
Was there one like that?
Wasn't there?
I believe you have something to say to me.
Well?
Let's apologize together.
Okay, Sana?
It wasn't on purpose.
I didn't ask if it was on purpose!
Shouldn't a simple apology come first? Well?!
L-Listen, Grandpa...
Sana really didn't do it deliberately.
I realize that!
But whether she meant any harm,
the fact is that she did this.
I told you not to use those
weird powers anymore, right?
One wrong move, and "sorry"
isn't gonna cut it anymore!
Bu—
Can't you even keep a promise?
Well?
B-B-But...
But it wasn't on purpose!
I wanna go to the research facility for my...
Hey, don't cry!
C'mon, take it easy, old man!
Don't be so touchy all the time.
And toward a little girl, at your age.
Huh?
Little girl, my name's Naitou Ryu.
I'm this scary old man's friend.
Know what "Ryu" means?
It means "dragon" in Japanese.
Pretty cool, huh?
Hey, I'm not done—
Just hold up a moment.
You know, I'm one of the guys who've been
chasing the baddies who held you prisoner.
I'm on your side!
So it's also our job to make
sure that you're kept safe.
And on that note, I have a favor to ask.
What's that?
We can't know when those guys
will try to take you away again.
So, to be sure we always know where you are,
I'd like you to wear a homing device.
This thing.
Don't like it?
Then, how about this one?
You don't seem like a bad person, so...
I'll do it.
I'll put it on for you.
Hear that?
I'm not a bad guy.
She said the same about me.
What, really?
I guess she likes it.
Yeah.
It looks good on you.
Sanae, I'm hungry!
What?
Already?
Shall I send someone to buy something?
Really?
I want that juice from before.
Very well.
Good for you, Sana!
Yeah.
You want some, too?
Can I? Yay!
Just a little bit, though.
Okay!
Oh, you're already there?
Thank you for moving so fast.
I'll transfer to the mission vehicle and stand by.
Ready for your order anytime.
Roger that.
Wait just a little bit longer.
I'll talk to you soon.
Oh? What's this?
Is that lady coming here?
You mean Minnie C?
She'll be nearby, but I don't think she'll join us.
Okay.
I don't like her.
But I think she's very nice.
She's always smiling.
Isn't smiling all the time
the same as never smiling?
You're rather perceptive, Kureo.
Ah, in Iraq?
Yes, while defusing a bomb.
And after her husband died,
she suffered from insomnia and was
on the verge of being discharged.
But then, after dreaming that her
husband's arms were embracing her,
her condition immediately stabilized.
And that's when she became a Dream of Alice?
Precisely.
In any case, she's an intriguing sample.
There have been very few cases
of a living being turning into a card.
Even if it's only one part of that being.
Listen, Minnie C.
Yes? What is it?
Don't laugh, okay?
I wouldn't do that.
I think I'm happier now
than I've ever been in my life.
Yes, I am, too.
No way.
This will sound silly.
But I never feared death until I met you,
Minnie C.
Darling...
Yummy!
You have some on you.
Watching you is making me hungry, Sana!
Thank you! Are these for me?
Yeah.
You want any?
I'm fine, thank you.
Sana?
Are you interested in becoming
a member of Zouroku's family?
Excuse me?
What the hell are you saying?!
Chill out, buddy.
I get it.
You'd have to make arrangements!
Like tableware and futons—
That's not what I'm talking about!
The agreement was to take her to
a safe place, where she'd be cared for!
Yeah, but just think about it...
This is a kid who gets into car races
with supernatural powers in town.
Who else is gonna take her in?
Just what do you think I am?!
Listen, I just want to leave her in
the hands of a good, responsible guardian.
I'll personally arrange bodyguards
and everything, of course.
You'd damn well better!
What I'm saying is—
Besides, old man,
what this girl needs is a family.
A warm home where she can
eat good food and sleep safely.
She's never known that kind of ordinary happiness.
"Ordinary happiness"?
That doesn't sound like you.
When you talk about stuff like that,
there's always an ulterior motive!
I've gotta hand it to you.
You know me well.
Still, just do this for me...
They want her to experience
a normal lifestyle as soon as possible.
Who does?
Weren't you sort of considering this, anyway?
That's how you are. I know you.
Sana...
If you ended up living with us, what would you do?
I don't know.
What about you?
Let's see...
I think I'd be kind of happy!
And you, Zouroku?
Do you not want me in your house?
Look, before we get to that,
you still haven't said something important to me.
You know there's something you have to say first.
B-Bathroom!
Huh?
No, really. I gotta pee!
You did drink a lot of juice.
It's this way.
Oh, wait, Sana...
Your hair will get in the way like that.
Can you use the bathroom by yourself?
Don't mock me!
I can do anything.
Okay, you're all set.
If you would, Minnie C.
Right.
A member of Zouroku's family, huh?
I'd live in that house, huh?
What should I do?
Oh, yeah.
I'll apologize to Zouroku after this.
Guess I have no choice!
I guess I have no choice!
Sana, are you okay?
Sana?
Sana!
Ma'am!
The transmitter's moving!
Yamada, where is she?
Make a right 300 meters ahead,
and then go straight for 500 more.
What is this?
Naitou!
Did you find her?
They got us!
They rewrote the toilet's location!
When she's like this, she looks like an ordinary child.
Well done, darling.
Thanks for always being there.
I have Sana's signal, ma'am!
You're sure?
Yes.
It's really weak, but the pattern is a match.
Where?
I'm sorry.
The system is still unstable, so I can't pinpoint it.
The GPS was for this, but now...
Ma'am! Her signal's gone!
Contact Naitou.
Check all area surveillance cameras at once!
Roger that!
What is this?
What's going on?
Oh? You've already perked up,
Red Queen?
I'm shocked.
We gave you enough to knock
out an adult for half a day.
Just what kind of monster are you?
Do you know who I am?
I am Minnie C. Tachibana.
I've come from the research facility to collect you.
What is this?
What's happening?
I can't move!
Being restrained by so much strength
that you cannot move at all
is rather alarming, isn't it?
In the military, I had that experience.
That won't work.
Don't worry.
If you just stay quiet, we will arrive soon.
Let's go home together.
Wonderland?
Yes.
I want to show it to you.
Just what are the Dreams of Alice?
Perhaps, rather than a gift from the heavens,
they're actually an illness,
or a bug in the workings of this world.
That's what some people say.
What do you think?
Who knows?
To be honest, I don't think it matters.
Even if they're demons,
if they can be used for a purpose,
then it's human nature to do so.
That is why I've come here.
That's great to hear.
I feel the same.
What I'm about to show you may
shed some light on those demons.
Ten years ago,
part of the facility underground
was rewritten into a mess,
and an impossibly huge space appeared.
Is that a relay antenna?
We tried releasing drones
to observe the space inside.
But it didn't work.
Anything in here that she dislikes is destroyed.
"She"?
It seems that she won't harm humans, but...
Hey!
Where are you?
I've brought a visitor.
Turn on the light.
I need your data in order to learn
what she really is, Minnie C.
We call her
the Red Queen.
This ridiculous spectacle
is an inexhaustible collection of cards
she's created from her Mirror Gate.
But for Dreams of Alice, cards are...
Yes, each only has one.
And getting the power they want isn't guaranteed.
But she is extraordinary.
In this Wonderland,
everything she wishes for becomes reality.
Anything she can imagine
can come true.
If you could obtain this power for yourself,
what would you wish for?
I...
I shall explain what's happening now.
Currently,
you're in a vehicle moving at 100 kph,
on a road you don't know.
If you were thrown outside right now,
you would either crash into the ground
or into another vehicle, and you'd die.
And if I apply just a little more strength,
your neck will break, and you'll die.
Do you understand?
Did you just imagine it now?
If you struggle or disobey me,
you will die.
Do you understand?
Until I met you, I'd never feared death,
Minnie C.
I would do absolutely anything
to see him again,
Red Queen.
Hidden beneath this scab
Are a great many things all working in unison
So please hold on just a little bit longer
Because I'll change myself starting from there
When do I start
To truly become myself?
Let's go meet the people who deserve my affection
We'll find them scattered across the world
I want to learn so much about them
One person, another person, more and more people
Three, four, five, six, the number rises and rises
Finding out the truth
Can sometimes be painful, but...
The world will keep moving
On and on, forever and ever
Even far into the future
Remaining unchanged
Next Episode
Something Not Human
Something Not Human.