The Magic Words
Long ago, in a faraway land,
lived an unfortunate little girl.
The Magic Words
The little girl was very, very unfortunate.
I'm very sorry...
At this point in March, these are all we have.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, Hatori.
You'll have to choose one of these.
Okay.
CLOSEOUT SALE
Mom, I want this one.
Oh?
CLOSEOUT SALE
Normally, the school insignia would go right here.
I'm sorry.
Mirror, mirror, on the wall
I want to change this world
The streetlight brightens up the night
And brings forth a sea of light
That reaches far into the distance
I dream upon a restless star
As I wait for the night to end
So I can continue searching for the future
The curtains covering a new stage
slowly part
as I wake up
Wonder drive! Let's start running now!
Wonder drive! To the world ahead of us!
Uncertainty, hesitation, and confusion
Just throw it all away!
Wonder drive! Keep charging along this path
Replace that clock's rhythm with your own
We are walking along a road
No one has yet dreamed of
Mirror, mirror, on the wall
I want to change this world
The Evil Witch
You're bringing that up again?
It happened over two years ago.
Hatori is a smart girl.
There are always middle school
entrance exams, if it comes to it.
You always do that.
You're always trying to put the issue off.
Sending her to public school for three more years...
It's your fault for not having her take
the entrance exams for other schools!
I thought not narrowing the options
would restrict her potential!
Get over yourself!
What's your problem?
What about you, then?
What have you done to help?
From the start, you've never cared
about her entrance exams!
You wouldn't listen to any of my concerns!
I took her to cram school, picked her up,
and researched schools, all on my own!
God...
Because I'm such a useless daughter,
my mom and dad don't get along anymore.
I don't need presents for my birthday or Christmas.
I'll study hard.
I'll do anything!
So please, God...
Make my mom and dad be nice and get along again!
Let's eat!
Ayumu...
Don't gulp your food down.
Daiki is copying you.
Sure.
Later, we'll come cheer at your match, okay?
Got it.
I'm heading out!
Good luck!
See you later!
Ayumu
I'll do my best at the match.
Come cheer me on, okay?
Close
View
Ayumu!
Good... morning...
I'm hungry...
S-So...
Ayumu has a match today.
Want to go cheer for her, like we used to?
All three of us...
That's a good idea!
Who's Ayumu?
Hatori's friend. The really lively girl.
Oh, the one who's a bit tomboyish?
We should all go. It's been a long time.
I'll have to make lunches for us, then!
It's fine. We'll get food somewhere.
One day, a good witch appeared
before the girl and asked her,
"What is your wish?"
And the little girl said,
"I wish everyone would be nice
to each other all the time."
And then, the witch said,
"Very well.
I will teach you some magic words."
But the little girl didn't know
how to use the magic words.
You're supposed to obey the traffic signals.
Hey! Hurry it up!
I hope the basketball court is open!
The guys from the class
next door might have taken it!
You aren't supposed to run.
What is this thing?
What happened?
Come on, let's go!
I wonder what that thing was.
It was kind of weird.
Do you think it might be magic?
Huh?
It must be.
Remember that guy from this morning?
I bet that was your power, too.
You can use magic, Hatori!
I don't...
Hey, try it again.
Huh?
Your magic.
But...
I know you can do it.
It worked on that guy and those boys!
You really think so?
Stop.
I did it, Ayumu!
Ayumu?
Ayumu! Ayumu!
What's wrong, Hatori?
Wow! You really can use magic!
You think so?
Yeah!
That has to be it!
I turned into a witch...
You're a good witch, Hatori!
What?
Hey, Hatori...
Try it again.
Walk.
Everyone, dance.
Wow.
They do what I say, too.
Okay, next...
Stop!
Ayumu...
You aren't afraid of me?
I'd never be afraid of you.
I'll always be with you, okay?
"I will teach you some magic words.
Use these, and you can grant yourself any wish.
Everyone will do as you say.
However, you must only use them for good.
Do that, and you can be a good witch.
But if you use them for evil,
you will become an evil witch."
But the little girl didn't follow
the good witch's orders.
Your mom is so great, Hatori.
She's so pretty, and she looks nice!
I wish my mom looked that stylish!
But she seems a little different now.
Back at the entrance ceremony, she seemed...
I don't know...
kind of scary.
She's totally different now, huh?
Mom?
Dad?
Ayumu
Hatori, what's wrong?
Hatori?
Hatori!
Ayumu...
"If you use them for evil,
you will become an evil witch."
I knew...
I knew it didn't make sense that Mom
and Dad were suddenly getting along.
I knew it must have been the magic...
But I was so scared about finding out for sure...
God is really mean, isn't he?
To give me a magic power like this...
What do I do, Ayumu?
As long as I'm here,
this house is full of nothing but lies.
Hatori...
I'll go far away.
Okay. I'll go with you.
What? But...
After all, I used your magic
to tease a lot of people, too.
We're the same.
Hey, what time is it?
It's 10:46.
It hasn't been two minutes since you last asked.
Oh, really?
You're really looking forward
to your friends coming over, huh?
"Hinagiri," right?
Yeah! Asahi and Yonaga!
Sana...
Would you throw out the,
um... you know, that stuff?
You know, uh, the green stuff.
Green stuff?
Oh, the squishy things?
Yeah, those.
Leave it to me! I'll take care of anything!
These are next!
The green things you stick flowers in.
I'll wring them out and toss them!
Squish!
It feels so gross, but so cool!
They're gonna be so surprised.
Since I left the research lab,
I've learned all kinds of things.
Because I'm amazing!
W-Wait up, Sis!
Don't go so far ahead alone!
You'll get lost aga—
No need to worry!
I have the map that Sana e-mailed me!
Here
Station
Omotesando
H-Hey, Sis, I don't think that...
Y-You see?
W-Well, everyone makes mistakes.
Um...
Th-This is...
Takeshita Street?
W-We haven't been here before.
S-Sis?
Yonaga...
Yes?
Which way do you think Ura-Hara is?
F-Forget it! We're already later than we should be!
Sana is waiting for us!
I-I know that! Of course I know that!
But still, I mean...
You know?
Y-You should probably ask Sana.
Y-You're right!
We've been looking forward
to playing with Sana again, for so long!
All right! Let's go see Sana, Yonaga!
Yes!
This is an order.
Stop.
Zouroku, I'm done.
What's the next...
What are you doing?
Hey, what's the matter, Zouroku?
Come on, what is this? Are you playing around?
Zouroku? Zouroku?
Zouroku!
Your arm will tire in that position.
Put it down.
And don't make such a racket,
while blocking the street.
You're grown-ups.
This is an order.
Everyone, out of my way.
What would you like?
Well...
Okay, I'll have the strawberry-strawberry.
That, and one kiwi with whipped cream.
So, what should we do now?
Well...
We'll do as we like, until we're out of money.
When we are, we'll get a job.
With magic, even an elementary
schooler can get a part-time job.
Yeah...
We'll live in an unfamiliar town,
find work, and when we have enough money,
we'll move to the next one.
It'll be lovely.
Hey, why don't we look from up there?
Yeah.
It's smaller than I thought.
It is.
But the view is nice.
Normally, we couldn't get into places like this.
It's so quiet.
As if everyone in the world disappeared,
and we're the only ones.
Yeah.
Are you sure about this?
Huh?
You don't have to come, Ayumu.
Why? You don't want me with you?
No, I didn't mean it like that.
I only meant that this is all my fault.
I can't even undo the magic myself.
That's why Mom and Dad...
I couldn't stay at home,
so I decided that I'd go on alone.
But that isn't the case for you, is it?
Didn't I promise I'd always stay with you?
Even if you're a witch, you're still Hatori to me!
Ayumu...
Ayumu, I love you.
You're such a good friend!
I'm a good friend, all right.
There, there.
What's that about?
The magic hasn't even worn off.
Wh-What's wrong with you? Stop this!
Are you joking around? Say something!
Over there!
Something.
No, no!
That isn't what I meant!
This isn't right.
What's going on?
What happened to Zouroku and everyone else?
E-Everyone outside is like this...
Who are you?
Are you okay?
I... I can't...
I've never run this much before...
How are you unaffected by the magic?
Huh? M-Magic?
What do you mean?
More importantly, what's going on?
And just who are you?
Are they... okay?
Zouroku and the others.
Everyone's acting weird....
Just...
What's going on?
I really don't like this.
I don't like this frazzled feeling.
What's with you?
What happened?
Does my magic not work on her?
It seems that way.
How can that be?
This has never...
Hey, where did you come from?
Huh?
If you know something, tell us!
Why doesn't Hatori's magic affect you?
What?
Did you do something special? Or have something?
Just tell us anything you know.
We're looking for a way to undo this magic!
Ayumu, what are you saying?
Please!
W-Wait a second.
What are you talking about?
I... I'm Miho Ayumu.
This is my friend, Hatori.
Stop!
If there's a way to stay unaffected by the magic,
Hatori won't have to leave home!
Not that...
What's going on?
Wait, did you two do this, then?
Then...
Then, wait a minute.
You're saying you two did all this?
To Zouroku and everyone?
It was all you?!
That's...
Why did it suddenly—
Hatori?
Whoops, careful.
Sorry.
Man, what're you doing?
It wasn't my fault.
No way.
The town
is back to normal.
Isn't this exciting?
Y-Yes! Sana is waiting for us!
You two...
I won't let you get away with that.
I won't!
What the heck is that?
Whoa, what's that?
Wow!
A promotion?
Why Santa?
What was that?
You also saw Santa Claus, right?
Wh-What is this? What's happening?
This is an order. You are to...
Did you just see a light?
Huh? Really?
What are you?
Ow!
H-Hey...
That hurts... Hey.
Just calm down! Stop it, okay?
Shut up! What's wrong is wrong!
Ow... Come on!
Was it you? Were you two the ones?
Let me go!
Hey, wait up!
W-Wait... You...
O-Oh...
Out of energy...
What happened?
Hang in there!
Hatori?
Hey, Hatori?
Even if the magic works on them,
they forget about it afterward,
so I thought I could get away with anything.
But everyone around her...
Probably her family, friends, and everyone else
ended up like soulless zombies.
And she was all alone, in the middle of them.
She must have felt so scared and nervous.
It must have been so confusing and terrifying.
Hatori?
Ayumu, I...
I really did turn into an evil witch.
Hidden beneath this scab
Are a great many things all working in unison
So please hold on just a little bit longer
Because I'll change myself starting from there
When do I start
To truly become myself?
Let's go meet the people who deserve my affection
We'll find them scattered across the world
I want to learn so much about them
One person, another person, more and more people
Three, four, five, six, the number rises and rises
Finding out the truth
Can sometimes be painful, but...
The world will keep moving
On and on, forever and ever
Even far into the future
Remaining unchanged
Next Episode
Where the Cheshire Cat Smiles
Where the Cheshire Cat Smiles.