The fire burned the housing complex's
twenty-square-meter third floor,
but no one was injured.
Currently, the fire department is
investigating the cause of the fire.
TOKYO
That concludes the news for this hour.
Next, the traffic report—
So, today, from the new drama
that premieres tonight—
...about an unusual dog.
This is Pan, and he lives
in America, in Wisconsin!
He can pull things much heavier than his own body.
Nope, it isn't on TV anywhere.
Hi, this is Sanae.
I'm on my way home.
Huh?
Sana?
Mirror, mirror, on the wall
I want to change this world
The streetlight brightens up the night
And brings forth a sea of light
That reaches far into the distance
I dream upon a restless star
As I wait for the night to end
So I can continue searching for the future
The curtains covering a new stage
slowly part
as I wake up
Wonder drive! Let's start running now!
Wonder drive! To the world ahead of us!
Uncertainty, hesitation, and confusion
Just throw it all away!
Wonder drive! Keep charging along this path
Replace that clock's rhythm with your own
We are walking along a road
No one has yet dreamed of
Mirror, mirror, on the wall
I want to change this world
Dreams of Alice
Laundry (Fold)
Meal (Morning)
Meal (Night)
Take Out Trash
Laundry (Dry)
Sanae
Grandpa
I'm home...
What a pretty little girl.
Huh? What's this?
What're you making?
They're graves.
Whose graves?
This one's for the bug.
This one's for the goldfish.
And these are for Mommy and Daddy.
Is that Grandpa and me?
Who are you?
You're flying!
Wow!
You really do have a mysterious power, don't you?
You know, Grandpa asked me
to make you some food.
Oh, I'm Kashimura Zouroku's
granddaughter, Sanae.
Nice to meet you.
Zou... Granddaughter? Food?
That's right.
I've come here to give you
a delicious meal and some snacks...
Because I'm a food alien!
And pose!
Just kidding.
Wha... F-Foo...
What? Huh?
Uh, no, I didn't mean it!
I'm sorry.
So your name's Sana, huh?
My grandpa told me all about you.
He said you lived in a really scary place
and went through some awful things.
It's okay if you're scared of me, too.
But if you're hungry,
you should come down, even if it's not right away.
Oink, oink.
I'm not a mean pig, oink.
I'm a food alien, oink!
What are these? Pigs?
Hey...
No! Stop!
Hmph. You're weird.
Darn...
Gotcha!
Now we're buried in pigs together! Take that!
S-Stop that!
I'm not stopping! Take that!
No!
This is gonna tickle!
Anyway, where did these little guys come from?
You received a new
message from Sanae
Ignore
Open
The heck is this?
Hello?
Hello, Grandpa?
Did you see my message?
That's right! They're pigs!
It's true, you know.
No!
They're live pigs.
Don't come out! Stay in there!
She is strange, just like you said.
I said no!
I mean, these are pigs... Pigs!
And you stay in there, too! I said stay!
She did something again?
No, it wasn't her fault.
Stop! Stop!
I just scared her a little. That's all.
What was that? Did something happen?
That tickles!
No, everything is fine.
Stop it!
Yep, I think she's warmed up to me a little.
Stop!
She's so adorable.
Okay, then.
Call me if anything comes up. Bye.
Was that Sanae?
Yeah.
Did something happen?
Nah, nothing important.
It's been a while.
Why don't you head home early today?
Suzuki Kennosuke
Kandou Gouzou
Kasuya Koushou
Suzuki Kennosuke
Kandou Gouzou
Kasuya Koushou
Takiguchi Kouichirou
Kandou Gouzou
Kasuya Koushou
Takiguchi Kouichirou
Takeda Shouzou
Kasuya Koushou
Takiguchi Kouichirou
Takeda Shouzou
Ken Ryoutarou
Takiguchi Kouichirou
Takeda Shouzou
Ken Ryoutarou
Takiguchi Kouichirou
Takeda Shouzou
Ken Ryoutarou
Takiguchi Kouichirou
Takeda Shouzou
Ken Ryoutarou
Tegoshi Eiichi
Takiguchi Kouichirou
Takeda Shouzou
Ken Ryoutarou
Tegoshi Eiichi
Takeda Shouzou
Ken Ryoutarou
Tegoshi Eiichi
Takeda Shouzou
Ken Ryoutarou
Tegoshi Eiichi
Tendou Takeshi
Takeda Shouzou
Ken Ryoutarou
Tegoshi Eiichi
Tendou Takeshi
Takeda Shouzou
Ken Ryoutarou
Tegoshi Eiichi
Tendou Takeshi
Ken Ryoutarou
Tegoshi Eiichi
Tendou Takeshi
Ken Ryoutarou
Tegoshi Eiichi
Tendou Takeshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Ken Ryoutarou
Tegoshi Eiichi
Tendou Takeshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Ken Ryoutarou
Tegoshi Eiichi
Tendou Takeshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Tegoshi Eiichi
Tendou Takeshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Tegoshi Eiichi
Tendou Takeshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Tegoshi Eiichi
Tendou Takeshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Tegoshi Eiichi
Tendou Takeshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Naitou Ryu
Tendou Takeshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Naitou Ryu
Tendou Takeshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Naitou Ryu
Tendou Takeshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Naitou Ryu
Tendou Takeshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Naitou Ryu
Tendou Takeshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Naitou Ryu
Nama Hiroshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Naitou Ryu
Nama Hiroshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Naitou Ryu
Nama Hiroshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Naitou Ryu
Nama Hiroshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Naitou Ryu
Nama Hiroshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Naitou Ryu
Nama Hiroshi
Toudou Yuuichi
Naitou Ryu
Nama Hiroshi
Yeah, it's me.
Been a while.
Actually, I have a favor to ask.
Was he mad?
It was fine.
He was a little surprised, though.
He said to be careful.
I was surprised, too!
Sana?
No, "Sa-na-e."
But it does sound similar to your name, right?
Sanae...
I'm sorry.
Well, let's take a little break for now.
Okay.
Do you want to change and take a bath first?
No.
My power keeps me from getting dirty, so I'm fine.
I hope Sana is eating well.
She won't die so easily.
Sorry, just a moment.
Harajuku...
Omotesando?
There. How's that?
Not too tight, is it?
No, they aren't too tight, I guess.
Oh, good.
Sorry, these old clothes are all I have for you.
I'll do your hair for you.
How do you usually wear it?
Usually...
I don't know.
I can do it myself,
but I don't pay attention since I use my power.
I see...
Okay, I'll make it cute for you, then!
There!
All done!
What do you think?
This is great!
Okay, next...
Eat up.
Wha... Thi... Bu...
What is this?!
They're pancakes.
Haven't you had them before?
No!
I'll cut them for you.
Wow.
Your tummy is growling while you eat!
Are you really his granddaughter?
I sure am.
You're nothing like him.
Oh, I'm not?
Then, let's see...
I hate crooked stuff!
Nothing like him.
Hey, Sanae, are there any more?
You finished them already?
Yep.
Shall I make some more?
Yeah! Yeah!
Okay, wait just a bit.
How long is "a bit"?
Well—
I waited a bit!
A bit longer.
I can't wait!
Wow! A pancake!
Laundry (Fold)
Meal (Morning)
Meal (Night)
Take Out Trash
Laundry (Dry)
Sanae
Grandpa
It's so big!
Sana?
Sana?!
Making food still doesn't work so well.
It's too inefficient...
I guess it's due to conservation of energy.
Pancake...
Don't eat it!
Shall I make some fresh ones?
Hey, Sanae!
Are they done yet?
Not yet.
How about now?
Sanae, are they done now?
Laundry (Fold)
Meal (Morning)
Meal (Night)
Laundry (Dry)
Take Out Trash
Sanae
Grandpa
Today's
Chores
Not yet.
Now?
No, not yet.
"Meal... Morning"?
Today's
Chores
Laundry (Fold)
Meal (Morning)
Meal (Night)
Take Out Trash
Laundry (Dry)
Sanae
Grandpa
You can read that properly?
Sure!
Meal (Night)
That one's "Night."
Grandpa makes the evening meal.
Today's
Chores
Meal (Morning)
Laundry (Fold)
Meal (Night)
Grandpa
Sanae
Laundry (Dry)
Meal (Night)
Grandpa
Sanae
Laundry (Dry)
Meal (Night)
Grandpa
Sanae
Laundry (Dry)
Meal (Morning)
Laundry (Fold)
Meal (Night)
Grandpa
Sanae
Take Out Trash
Meal (Night)
Sanae
Take Out Trash
He can make food?
Meal (Night)
Sanae
Take Out Trash
Meal (Morning)
Laundry (Fold)
Meal (Night)
Sanae
Take Out Trash
Yeah, it's really good.
Sanae, this won't open!
Maybe you should try pulling or sliding it sideways?
Oh!
Flowers!
Grandpa's growing them.
I water them, too.
One isn't blooming.
That one only blooms at night.
It's called "queen of the night."
I see...
This feels kind of weird.
It's cramped and dark,
and it isn't very clean.
It's nothing like that other place.
You really are Zouroku's granddaughter, huh?
Hm?
You're a good person, too.
Why are you so nice?
They were nice, too. But they were bad people.
"They"?
At the research facility.
My memories begin at the research facility.
I might have come from somewhere else,
but I don't remember.
One day, I realized I was there.
The first thing I knew was hunger.
They gave me food.
And they put all kinds of hard things on my body.
Now, face the other way.
I didn't understand language,
but I didn't need it.
I could merge into other people's
consciousness and become one with them.
The boundary between other
people and myself was vague.
But one day,
two people who looked identical appeared.
So I tried to become one with them, as usual.
You can't.
You and we are different beings.
I am me.
You are you.
That was when I learned what "language" was.
You are you?
Yes.
You will also learn to recognize
the boundary between others and yourself.
I am Hinagiri Yonaga.
The younger twin.
I'm Hinagiri Asahi, the older.
What's your name?
I don't know.
Then we'll give you a name.
We came up with one together.
The Red Queen loves fish.
So your name is Sana.
Sana...
That's how I became Sana.
The twins taught me many things.
They taught me all about cute
and girlish clothes, about language.
Poems and lots of songs, too,
and even how to count.
I was happy every day there.
But then I saw it.
Far beneath the research facility...
They did something to someone there.
It made them into something inhuman.
I was so scared...
And I ran from the facility!
But the outside world was scary, too...
I didn't know anything.
I was scared.
You know what?
I really think we're alike.
You and I.
Our names?
It's okay.
It'll all be okay.
You're making a mess, Naitou.
So what? I was starving!
Don't get the seat dirty.
I'm the one who'll get the heat from the director!
C'mon, don't be so touchy.
How old are you again, Ichijou?
I'm 26.
Wow! Really?
You're so young!
That's sexual harassment, you know.
Huh? Not at all...
Say, have you ever heard of
those old sidewalk dance groups?
Yeah, I've heard of them, and that's it.
Oh, you're a sharp one, all right.
Well, at the time, I was still
a subordinate at the main office.
Every weekend, they made me work
security at pedestrian-only zones.
And one time, I saw this grown man
fighting with some weird kids!
I thought, "He must be an idiot."
He was yelling, "I hate crooked stuff!"
Oh, really...
And for the thirty years since then,
we've been buddies, somehow.
But it's been five years since I last saw him.
This is the first time I've
heard you talk about a friend.
You two must be very close.
Nah, not at all.
He's a stubborn, old stick in the mud.
We're polar opposites.
Oh, look at this...
His company has a homepage.
It says he's a "flower coordinator."
Sounds to me like you really are close.
That was delicious...
Hey, Sanae... Let's go to the research facility.
Huh?
I had lots of good food, so I'm all better now!
This time, I'll crush it.
But...
Don't worry.
You can... Oh, I know!
Bring lots of snacks and come with me!
Oh, by the way, where did Zouroku go?
I think he's working right now.
Working? With flowers?
I know about that!
Wow...
He's a real jerk, leaving me alone!
After all that sleep and a snack,
you're much more energetic.
And he's supposed to be my servant!
What?
Nothing. But...
Just wait for a bit, okay? I need to clean up.
Okay, let's go get him!
We're falling! We're falling!
What the heck?
I didn't do this on purpose! I swear!
What's going on?
What the heck?!
Help! Save us!
What now?!
Help!
How cute! Penguins!
Huh?
These are penguins. Penguins.
Wow! It's so cold!
Is this the South Pole? I've never been here before.
I haven't, either.
Just like me.
This one's small.
It's a baby.
Isn't it cute?
It is cute!
So cute...
Calling
Kashimura Sanae
Boss, which cylinder is it again?
You're amazing, Sana.
Can you go anywhere?
Y-Yeah, I can.
Where to next?
Hm...
How about home?
If we suddenly disappear,
Grandpa will be really surprised.
Zouroku? Will he be angry?
No, but he'll be worried.
Really?
Yep, really.
So let's go home, okay?
Okay.
Crap! I forgot!
Huh?
Pigs! There are pigs in here!
Why are there pigs?
Because I had pork cutlets yesterday?
Hey, Roku, I'm here.
Crying won't tell me anything!
U-Um, Grandpa, this was...
Grandpa, I'm saying—
I'm asking what you're saying!
Right, we're outta here.
Keep it together, Naitou.
This is work, after all.
Hidden beneath this scab
Are a great many things all working in unison
So please hold on just a little bit longer
Because I'll change myself starting from there
When do I start
To truly become myself?
Let's go meet the people who deserve my affection
We'll find them scattered across the world
I want to learn so much about them
One person, another person, more and more people
Three, four, five, six, the number rises and rises
Finding out the truth
Can sometimes be painful, but...
The world will keep moving
On and on, forever and ever
Even far into the future
Remaining unchanged
So suddenly? But I can't just...
R-Right.
I'll make the arrangements at once.
Call Minnie C.
Next Episode
Cards
Cards.