What do you want?
I was in the area,
so I thought I'd pay you a friendly visit.
...Not falling for that one, huh.
What is that?
Info on the Dreams of Alice.
Fine, I'll take it. But it's too soon.
We can't cover it up any longer.
You came up with this yourself?
Let's just say I acted on my own authority.
How very valiant, for a lizard's tail.
If it becomes necessary, you'll be cut off.
Well, even tails have their own sense of pride.
Mirror, mirror, on the wall
I want to change this world
The streetlight brightens up the night
And brings forth a sea of light
That reaches far into the distance
I dream upon a restless star
As I wait for the night to end
So I can continue searching for the future
The curtains covering a new stage
slowly part
as I wake up
Wonder drive! Let's start running now!
Wonder drive! To the world ahead of us!
Uncertainty, hesitation, and confusion
Just throw it all away!
Wonder drive! Keep charging along this path
Replace that clock's rhythm with your own
We are walking along a road
No one has yet dreamed of
Mirror, mirror, on the wall
I want to change this world
I'm Home
MISSING GIRL
Name
Shikishima Hatori
Age
9 Years Old
Most Likely Wearing
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
It's been ten days since Hatori disappeared.
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspender Skirt
White Tights
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Most Likely Wearing
Shikishima Hatori
9 Years Old
MISSING GIRL
Name
Age
Shikishima Hatori
April is almost here.
Shoot!
Pass it back!
Nice, Ayumu.
Nice, Ayumu!
Shikishima Hatori
Pigtails with Red Hair-ties
Light Blue Blouse
Green Suspenders
White Tights
Shoes Unknown
Please contact us if spotted.
The police and all the adults
have been looking for her.
But...
I don't think she's coming back.
Hey, if you took a trip, where would you go?
I'm not sure.
Where would you go?
Off the top of my head, I don't know.
Anywhere in the whole world.
Oh.
Wait, I know! I'll try to guess.
Liverpool, right?
I knew it.
How did you know?
You told me before, remember?
Because you like soccer.
Did I say that?
You sure did.
Then where would you want to go?
Huh? What is it?
It's embarrassing...
Come on, no fair!
Well, um...
when spring comes,
I want to follow the cherry blossom front
from the south to all the way up north.
Yeah.
That sounds really cool!
Really co—
Jeez!
It sounds great! Let's go!
Let's definitely go! Together!
Yeah.
We'll go together.
No Response
Hatori!
Pick up!
Please!
Hatori...
Did you go without me?
Ayumu
Missed Call
If we ever get out of here,
will you forgive me?
Forgive you? For what?
I'm not mad about anything anymore.
In that case, will you be my friend?
I'll introduce you to my best friend, too.
Your best friend?
You mean Ayumu?
I already know her.
She said you're her most precious friend, too.
That's right... she's my very best friend.
So how do we find the exit?
Well,
if we had a clue about where to start...
Huh?
What's wrong?
I think I dropped my phone!
Huh?
I'll go back and...
Ayumu
My phone!
When did he—
Give that back!
You're not going anywhere!
Ayumu
Ayumu?
A minute ago it was out of range!
Is it broken?
A call?
I got a call from Ayumu.
It should connect...
Ayumu
Missed Call
The rabbit is connected to the outside!
What? This guy?
Hey, you!
Wait!
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Sana
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Sana
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Sana
Zouroku
Sanae
Sana
Please come out.
Sanae
Sana
Zouroku
Sanae
Sana
It's okay...
Zouroku
Sanae
Sana
Zouroku
Sanae
Sana
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Sana
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Sana
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Sana
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Sana
This is a mailbox.
They open from the ba—
Hatori, wait!
What?
Don't your feet hurt?
You should... put shoes on.
Lots of them... are growing right there...
Oh...
I wonder where the rabbit went.
He can't be far.
How do you know?
He's just... like me.
He was made in Wonderland.
He likes fun things and strange things.
So I'm sure he's teasing us for fun.
There he is!
You little...!
What are all these pancakes doing here?
Well, Sana loves pancakes.
I hope Sana's okay.
I'll bet she's getting hungry...
H-Hatori, wait...
Are you all right?
I'm done for!
Me too!
You fell for it!
You have one new message.
Read
Close
You have one new message.
Shikishima Hatori
Close
Read
You have one new message.
Shikishima Hatori
Close
Read
You have one new message.
Shikishima Hatori
Close
Read
You have one new message.
Shikishima Hatori
Close
Read
You have one new message.
Shikishima Hatori
Close
Read
You have one new message.
Shikishima Hatori
Close
Read
You have one new message.
Shikishima Hatori
Close
Read
You have one new message.
Shikishima Hatori
Close
Read
You have one new message.
Shikishima Hatori
Ha... Hatori!
Well? Did it send?
Wait a second. I'm not sure yet.
Give it here! I'll send a bunch of them!
Don't! You'll run the battery down.
Miura Ayumu
Hello, Ayumu? Can you hear me?
Listen, I'm sorry, but I need your help.
Give me that! I wanna talk to her!
Wait!
Hatori?
Is it really you, Hatori?
Yeah, it's me.
Thank goodness...
I thought I'd never see you again!
Huh?
I mean, everyone's been looking for you!
It's been more than ten days!
More than ten days? What's she talking about?
What do you mean? What day is it?
What day?!
Hatori, It's already March 29th!
Don't cry... I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
I thought I'd made you angry...
I thought you didn't like me anymore.
So, I'm sorry, but please don't come again.
No, not at all...
It's my fault.
I wasn't a good friend to you, Ayumu.
You've...
always been my best, most precious friend,
who I love most of all.
Yeah...
Same here, Hatori.
Wh-What's that?!
Low Battery
Close
Power Saving Mode
The battery...
Hey, Ayumu, I have to be fast.
I need you to look for a rabbit hole.
Let me!
A rabbit hole?
Hey, Ayumu!
Kashimura?
Listen, do you remember the rabbit
you saw when we talked before?
Rabbit?
Right now, Hatori and I can't use our powers.
We can't get out of here, and we're in trouble.
But that exit might still connect to the outside.
Wonderland is too big.
We can't find the exit from the inside.
But the outside world is smaller,
and there are lots of signs.
We want to get home as soon as we can!
Please, Ayumu.
Okay, I think I know where it is.
And if there's anything I'm sure of, it's my speed!
Wait for me!
Think she'll be okay?
Yeah.
Ayumu can handle it.
I know she'll save us.
Grandpa, what is this?
A lunch box, I guess?
I can see that, but...
The day I first met her,
she was in the convenience store,
staring at lunch boxes.
This "Wonderland" sure is a weird place.
So this is where Sana was born...
I suppose this is normal for her,
and the outside world seems strange.
Since she left this place,
everything Sana saw
has been confusing and strange.
To her, everything is a first.
And as she confronts each of those things,
she's learning how to associate with people.
Come to think of it,
that's how I've always lived, too.
I've made it this far with the help of others.
I guess that's true of me, too.
When you receive something,
you need to repay the favor in kind.
Yeah.
Ah, the pig!
It should be around here.
Come on, please.
My friend's waiting for me!
Come out.
STOP
H
X
Z
H
STOP
Please!
Take me there!
What is this?
Where did that door come from?
What the... it disappeared?
What's going on?
It's expanding even faster!
We're seeing effects to the surface
much earlier than we expected!
Is there no way to stop it?
Ma'am!
Hey, hasn't it been a while?
Does she really know where it is?
She does.
Ayumu definitely knows.
What makes you think that?
Huh? Well, I'm not sure.
Because she's my friend, I guess?
You guys say some similar things.
Listen...
What?
Ayumu is your best friend,
and you're Ayumu's best friend, right?
Yeah.
Th-Then am I...?
A-Ayumu!
Hatori!
Thank goodness!
Wait!
Huh?
I was expecting two of them, but I see three.
Sana... and a friend?
Sana!
You think we can cross this?
Whoa! What now?
Can we ride these?
How convenient!
H-Hey!
What's that?
Zouroku, hurry!
All staff, please begin evacuation.
Please begin evacuation.
Wonderland is coming to the surface!
Facility 3 is going to collapse!
Ma'am! Get out of there!
Yamada, what are you doing?
Didn't you hear the evacuation order?
But she's still in Wonderland—
You can't! We don't know what's going on inside!
Ma'am! Ichijou!
Zouroku!
What's happening?
I don't know, either.
Looks like something big is about to happen.
Zouroku!
You okay?
Yeah!
Good.
Cut it out already!
He really did give Wonderland a talking to.
He's getting away!
Aren't you forgetting about something?
You want us to push that?
Grandpa, maybe he's just teasing us again.
If so, he'll get another talking to.
I thought so...
Ichijou!
What in the world is going on?
Expansion of Wonderland has stopped!
Thank god!
We're going to be okay!
Why did it stop?
Huh?
Where are we?
It's my house! Yay!
It's my house!
Hey, Kashimura, your shoes...
Sana!
We take off our shoes first.
Ma'am!
Is Wonderland still expanding?
It's stopped!
I see...
That's good.
Where are Kashimura and the rest?
They all made it back home safely.
Now...
I'm going to sleep for a bit...
Wow!
It really has been ten days!
What's going on?
This is pretty screwed up.
But I only found the door about thirty minutes ago.
I'm so glad.
Now your parents won't worry.
Um, I'll... go home with Hatori.
I'll walk you there, then.
Is this your house?
Yes.
Thank you for seeing us off.
Hey, it was close by. Think nothing of it.
Um, I'm really sorry for all the trouble.
After I talk to my parents,
I'll take myself to the police.
I-I'll go too!
You two do have a lot to atone for.
That's the truth.
But you still have people on your side.
If you're ever in trouble again, call us.
Yeah! With Zouroku around, you'll be fine!
Hush up a minute.
Also, I know someone who makes his living
by helping troubled kids like you.
Thanks.
Hatori, listen...
When you disappeared,
your parents spent every day looking for you.
Sana...
I'd like to ask you a favor.
What is it?
Could you stay here, just for a little while?
When you're with me, I can't lie.
I know!
I promised, after all!
I'm your friend too!
I'm home.
Hatori!
I'm sorry.
So, to repeat,
The Dreams of Alice Response Office
is in its preparatory stages.
Furthermore, the Kyoto Ferris wheels
are the result of a Dream of Alice.
The important thing to remember
is that the phenomenon known as a "Dream of Alice"
can happen to anyone.
No one is special or more likely
to experience it than anyone else.
We're off!
So, to protect these people's rights,
the government will open a special response office—
Hey,
what Hatori has is a "Dream of Alice"
like they talked about on TV, right?
Will she be okay?
Oh, Hatori is a good girl.
The government finally made
an official announcement
about the existence of the Dreams of Alice.
The world is about to change, isn't it?
I do hope it will be for the better.
Well, I'm sure things will work out.
If the kids are happy and healthy,
that makes it a good world.
Hidden beneath this scab
In the future, what sort of adult will she become?
Are a great many things all working in unison
How will she retain the cuteness
and innocence of childhood?
So please hold on just a little bit longer
Sana
Because I'll change myself starting from there
These are the things that Alice's
older sister thought about.
Sana
Because I'll change myself starting from there
When Alice becomes an adult,
she will surely tell many strange, fanciful stories
When do I start
to many small children who look just like her.
To truly become myself?
Among those tales, perhaps,
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Sana
will be this one.
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Sana
To truly become myself?
The story of a wondrous land
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Sana
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Sana
Let's go meet the people who deserve my affection
Hatori, Ayumu, ...(3)
Shikishima Hatori
Miura Ayumu
Good morning
Today's the day.
You ready?
which she dreamed of, long ago.
We'll find them scattered across the world
Sana!
I want to learn so much about them
Morning!
Okay, I'm off!
Watch out for cars, you three.
One person, another person, more and more people
Three, four, five, six, the number rises and rises
Okay!
Finding out the truth
Can sometimes be painful, but...
This is...
The world will keep moving
the story of a girl
On and on, forever and ever
Even far into the future
who continues to search for "herself,"
so that she can find her purpose...
Even far into the future
who continues to search for "herself,"
so that she can find her purpose...
Remaining unchanged
who continues to search for "herself,"
so that she can find her purpose...
I'm all right now.
Thanks to you...
Zouroku.