Where am I?
I can't remember a thing.
Finally woken up?
Who are yo—
Welcome.
To the "To Hell With Dying" Warfront.
I know it's a little sudden,
but won't you enlist with us?
Huh? "Enlist"?
Your being here means that you've died.
What?
Um, I don't really understand what you—
This is the world after death.
If you don't do anything, you'll be erased.
Erased? By who?
By God, of course.
What do you mean by "enlist" then?
Enlist in the "To Hell With Dying" Warfront.
Well, the name of the unit tends to change.
Previously it was the "Afterlife" Warfront.
But if you call it "Afterlife..."
That makes it sound like you're
accepting death, don't you think?
We ended up scrapping that name,
and we're in the process
of coming up with a new one.
Right now, it's the
"To Hell With Dying" Warfront.
Before that, it was the
"Don't Feel Like I Was Ever Alive" Warfront.
That came off as a bit of a joke though,
so we changed it the next day.
So, uh...
Is that a real gun?
Everyone who ends up here asks me that...
You need to work on your adaptability.
React to things as they happen.
"As they happen..."
So what should I do?
You should fight.
Fight what, exactly?
That.
That thing is the enemy of the
"To Hell With Dying" Warfront.
Angel.
"To Hell With Dying" just doesn't
work for me. I expected as much.
Hey, you. Come up with something better.
Hang on a second... Angel's just a normal girl
no matter how you look at her, no?
What on earth is this girl on about?
Hey, do you mind if I go over there?
What?!
Why the heck would you do that?
What could possibly make
you think that's a good idea?
Are you completely crazy?
"Maybe I'll go see what dying's like?"
"You wanna die?"
is a common joke in this world.
What do you think? Hysterical, right?
Th-The joke's fine, but...
I imagine that she'll make for a better conversation
partner than the one pointing a gun around.
I'm on your side, you know.
If you tell me to lower my gun, then I'll do so.
Give me a little credit.
Hey! Yurippe!
How's the recruitment coming along?
We're crazy low on members.
We'll use whatever we can get!
Huh?
I'm going over there now.
Damn it! My invitation didn't work at all!
I have no idea what is happening...
What's with these people?
Excuse me...
Ah, good evening.
Well, uh, you just had a gun aimed at you.
They were saying you're an angel or something.
I'm not an angel.
As I thought. Then—
I'm the Student Council President.
I'm way too gullible.
That girl was just messing with me after all.
Damn it! I'm so confused right now...
I'll just go to the hospital or something.
There are no hospitals here.
Huh? Why not?
People never get sick.
Wait, never?
Because everyone's dead.
Oh, I get it! You're in on it too!
You're trying to trick me.
Is my amnesia down to you as well?
Many people lose their memories when they come here.
Maybe you were in an accident
and hurt your head.
Fine. Prove it to me!
I'm already dead, so I can't die, righ...
Hand Sonic!
Where am I?
I'm alive.
That was agonizing, though...
Damn it! I have no idea what's going on,
but I can't stay here!
What's with this guy?
So you're the guy who insulted Yurippe,
and spat on our warm welcome, huh?
H-Hey. Hang on a second.
Let's not do anything crazy.
You wanna die?
Ah, that.
What the heck?
Very funny. That's a joke here
in the afterlife, right? Good one.
One-Hundred Strikes!
Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die!
Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die! Die!
Insult Yurippe again, and we'll dance once more.
You're gonna kill me?
Talk about a sharp wit...
What kind of twisted world is this, anyway?
The pain makes you think you'll die,
but you won't! This sucks!
This is the world after death.
If you don't do anything, you'll be erased.
That's right! I can just get erased!
If I do that, I can say goodbye to this place.
What should I do though?
I'm on your side, you know.
Give me a little credit.
Is there anyone around here that I can trust?
I know! I'll look for an adult!
Where are all the adults? The teachers?
I guess I can ask the principal...
Huh?
Hm, let's see... How about this?
"You're The One Who's Gonna Die" Warfront?
That makes it sound like I'm gonna die!
Well, we're talking about her, of course.
Okay then. Look this way for a second.
Where am I?
"You're The One Who's Gonna Die" Warfront.
Oh crap. You're right.
It does sound like I'm gonna die.
Anyone else here have any good ideas?
How's this one? "Life Flashing Before Your Eyes" Warfront.
That's only the verge of death.
Well then how about this? "Suicide Corps" Warfront.
That sounds like you want to die.
"Stalemate" Warfront.
Uh huh, oh yeah, that's right, oh yeah, oh, nice.
It's not a stalemate!
How about, "Invincible Armada"?
Now it's not a warfront.
"Dying Without Surrender Squadron."
Don't think I won't punch you...
"The Wright Brothers!"
Mystic Chop!
It has to end with "Warfront."
I won't surrender that point.
We're the front line of this battefield.
Can't we think of something that actually works?
Hey, that guy's awake now.
Huh? Oh! You're up now?
That's right. I told him to think about it, too.
You've had plenty of time to think. Let's hear it.
Hear what?
A new name for the "To Hell
With Dying" Warfront, of course.
"Do Whatever The Hell You Want" Warfront.
Oh? You've got some guts to go against Yurippe.
I said, do whatever the hell you want!
What was that?!
What's with you guys?
Don't drag me into this!
I'm just gonna disappear soon!
You want to disappear?
Even though you're still here, existing?
Yeah, that's right!
I already explained it to him.
So you're gonna sit back and accept your erasure?
Damn right!
Just so you can end up turning into a water flea?
Totally!
Huh? Water flea?
What? You thought only humans had souls?
How foolish.
You could reincarnate as a corn barnacle.
Or maybe as a hermit crab.
You might even become a wharf roach.
What? There's no way!
You look so confused that you can't even joke about
why we're only concentrating on sea creatures.
Incidentally, there's no reason to it.
Did you plan on leaving us, sucking up to Angel,
and being sent to wherever you go from here?
Maybe you'll become a corn barnacle
and get eaten by a human.
Sounds great, right?
A corn barnacle?
Huh? You can eat those things?!
Yeah, they're edible.
Wow, I never knew that.
How foolish.
Take it easy, people.
Let's try not to run him out too quickly.
Poor thing.
Right now, we of the...
Wait, what are we right now?
Corn Barnacle Warfront.
Right! We of the Corn Barnacl-
We're changing back! Afterlife Warfront!
That was a pretty nice kick...
As long as you're here
in the Warfront's HQ, you'll be safe.
You knew that and made your way here, right?
Not really. I tried to enter,
but ended up going flying.
More importantly: In my next life,
I might not even be human?
That's a joke, right?
No, we're serious.
You say that, but how would you know?
Did someone come back and tell you?
Of course we can't check for ourselves.
But in Buddhism, there's no guarantee that one will be reincarnated.
No way... a corn barnacle...
Well, religious beliefs are just things that humans made up anyway.
But still, listen well. This is important.
In the world we used to live in, "Death"
was a random and indiscriminate visitor.
That's why we had no means to resist.
But this world is different.
Here, we can even go against
an angel, and continue to exist.
We can fight.
Hang on. What will happen after that?
What exactly is your goal?
Our goal is to erase Angel.
We do that, and this world will be ours!
You only got here a little while ago,
so it's no surprise that you're confused.
Work on your adaptability,
and then react to things as they happen.
And then I'll... fight an angel?
Exactly. We'll do it together.
Don't apologize. Yuripp—
What a moron.
He got caught in his own trap...
Is that what happened to me?
You need a password to enter this place safely.
This is the Anti-Angel
Operations Headquarters, after all.
There's no other place for us
to meet that is as safe as this.
Can I have some time?
As long as you leave here, sure!
Okay!
So what's the password?
"No Angels, Gods, or Buddhas."
I'm Yuri. The leader of this warfront.
And, he's Hinata.
As you can see, he's pretty useless,
but he has his moments.
What's that supposed to mean?!
That's Matsushita.
I'm being ignored?
He's a Fifth-rank in Judo, so he's well respected and we call him Fifth-Rank-Matsushita.
Nice to meetcha.
This is Ooyama.
His distinguishing trait is
his lack of distinguishing traits.
Welcome to the warfront.
Come on, let's dance!
Uh... I don't dance...
Oh yeah, don't be afraid.
That's just how he says hello.
Feel the groove man. Yeah. Look inside yourself.
Everyone calls him TK.
Nobody knows his real name.
He's a bit of a mystery.
Is it really okay to hang out
with a guy like that?
The guy always pushing up his glasses and trying to sound intellectual is Takamatsu.
He's actually a moron, though.
Huh?
My pleasure.
Yeah...
The last one is Fujimaki.
I'm Fujimaki, punk.
I'm not a punk, buddy.
The guy who went flying earlier is Noda.
The girl in the shadows constantly muttering "how foolish," is Shiina.
Sitting over here is Iwasawa.
She's the leader of the diversionary squad.
Uh huh, oh yeah. Hm, yeah. Where's the beat?
They're not here right now, but we have
dozens more members within the school.
Which reminds me, what's your name?
Huh?
Oh, uh, well... Oto... Otonashi.
First name?
I can't remember.
You're one of those anmesia types, huh?
Don't worry, it'll come back to you soon.
Hey, shouldn't we give him a uniform?
Ah, that's right. I'd forgotten.
Now that you mention it,
why do I have a different uniform?
It's not yours that's different, it's ours.
That uniform is the one
the "good" students wear.
This is the uniform of the Afterlife Warfront.
This campus is huge, isn't it?
There's over two thousand students enrolled here.
It's an enormous boarding school.
Who in the world came up with—
Hey. Is it safe for us to talk here?
Yeah, so long as we don't talk about our operations.
I feel duped.
What?
Nothing...
So what's that? Canned coffee?
It's called Key Coffee. It's great.
Was that your question?
Er... no. Who are they?
Club activities are going on right now.
You guys aren't gonna join in?
If we did that, we'd disappear.
Huh?
If we joined in with club activities and
attended classes, we humans would disappear.
"We humans?"
You make it sound like those guys aren't human.
Well, that's because they aren't.
Those guys are just NPCs.
NPCs?
You don't know the term? Non-Player Characters.
Is that a gaming term?
It's a metaphor.
It means those guys have been
in this world since the very beginning.
So they have no self-consciousness?
So if I tried to talk to them,
they'd repeat a scripted line?
Why don't you try it?
You're still new to this place,
so you can't tell what makes us different.
Can I converse with them?
Go down there and try "probing" one of the girls.
"Probing?"
They'll probably run off,
or kick you or something.
They're, uh, pretty well-designed.
The teachers, too?
Yep. Incidentally, the NPCs never age.
And neither do we.
Anything else?
What's with Angel's brutality?
She stabbed me right after I met her.
I was watching that. Wasn't that your own fault?
If you tell Angel to prove that you won't die,
she'll just stab you right in the heart.
The way she sees it, it was no different than
you asking where the teacher's lounge is.
So Angel is obedient to the rules of this world?
More like she's just awkward.
Is she self-conscious?
Who knows? It's a mystery.
Regarding her emotionlessness,
her bluntness, and her lack of vocabulary,
she's rather unique in comparison to the NPCs.
So, is she usually able to kill—
I mean, do things like that?
For those students who don't engage in "proper" activities at school...
First, she gives a warning.
If you run, she'll chase you,
then outrun you and block your path.
And use of force?
An eye for an eye!
At least, whenever we've challenged her.
So she's gotten you guys before too, I guess?
Of course.
And don't even try pretending
to be a good student.
Some people have disappeared doing that.
Got it.
Okay, last question.
It's about God.
Does God exist?
I believe so.
I've never seen him, though.
Haven't you ever asked Angel?
Any questions about this world
are met with "no comment."
That's all!
This little study session is over for now.
To be honest, I'm not really
planning on joining their fight.
Right now, I'm fighting for
something more important.
I'm just trying to buy enough time to safely recover my memories.
That's all there is to it.
After that,
After that...
I don't know.
Here, Otonashi.
You might be new, but give it a try.
Will it work?
Aim for her legs.
That should stop her chasing you for a while.
I'm fighting against that girl, right?
Won't her injuries heal right away?
You need to learn from experience.
That's how we've all made it this far.
Very well.
Good answer, Otonashi!
The first order of business is to get you acclimated.
For this, we'll be having you participate
in a nice and simple operation.
The operation will be called:
Operation Tornado.
Oh man, this sounds like a big one!
T...Tornado?!
We're going to steal lunch tickets from the students!
We're stealing what?!
That's not big at all! This is just petty bullying!
I'm at a loss here!
You've got all these members and weapons for this?!
You scum! Are you trying to insult Yurippe again?
Take it back.
Why should I?!
We of the "Corn Barnacle Extinction" Warfront would
never threaten students with power or superior numbers.
They're going extinct?
Someday, most likely.
But you said you were going to steal from them!
Well, maybe I should have said that we're "lifting" the tickets.
Listen up. You're part of the barricade group that that will be stopping Angel's advance.
You'll be surrounding the
area of operations, the cafeteria.
From there, you'll be on standby.
Don't worry, I'll put you somewhere easy.
Talk with Takamatsu or Ooyama
for the particulars of your role.
Iwasawa, I'm expecting another fine performance tonight.
Right.
If Angel appears, open fire.
That will be the signal for reinforcements.
If you hear any gunfire,
make sure you offer support, too.
This operation will commence at 18:30.
Operation... Start!
How the heck are we supposed to "lift"
their tickets peacefully with this plan?
This is Yusa.
Lighting and acoustic teams are on standby.
It's about time.
The fans have noticed and are gathered.
Okay, let's get started then.
Hey, GirlDeMo's playing!
The live show just started!
She showed up.
She's here, and she's headed right towards me.
Does that mean I'm the
weak point in this operation?
She's belittling me.
Damn it! I have to shoot!
But can I really put a bullet
into that delicate body?
If I don't shoot,
she's gonna get me,
and she'll give me no mercy.
It hit!
Wait... I wanted her legs.
Isn't this good enough?
Come on!
Guard Skill: Hand Sonic.
No way.
No way!
Why?
Why isn't she stopping?
Wh-What the hell was that?!
Damn it!
Ugh. I missed?
Sorry we're late.
Give you a little kiss!
Going for our weakest member, huh?
She's still only using Hand Sonic.
Get her into the open!
We'll attack in numbers as we pull back.
Understood.
Let's do it!
Guard Skill: Distortion.
Fire!
Crap! We're too late!
My god!
This is why guns are useless.
Damn it! What's the status on the lifting?
All we're doing is buying time...
I had no idea it would be this epic.
The show is at its apex.
Start it up.
Start it up, please.
You all good? Let's get going!
Here you are. One Meat Udon.
So delicious!
Is this really okay?
Relaxing here and eating like this?
Won't she come after us?
It's fine, all we're doing is eating.
Is that how it works?
With this kind of power and leadership,
she could do whatever she wanted to.
But she's just sitting here relaxing and eating.
I really have only one enemy.
That's Angel.
We're fighting against her.
But what we're doing...
Is it really right?
Wait.
Don't think about it right now.
After all...
I can't remember a thing.
D-Drop?
We call it the Guild.
You'll definitely be next.
It seems you still don't understand...
Run for it!
The traps aren't deactivated?!
I forgot about this one!
Because I was the first to resist.
I don't know. I don't know anything about that!
Angel's recovering!
Fire!
What am I doing?
Don't you find a life like that totally unforgivable?