You become friends with girls
before you realize, Kei.
It'd be good for you to make
some more friends, too.
Do you mean male friends?
It doesn't matter what gender,
but it'd be more fun to see you talking to girls.
Who do you recommend in that regard?
Nonoh, maybe?
I'll do what I can.
That's what happened.
I see.
I understand your situation.
So, could you be friends with me?
Let's see...
If you bring me some cream puffs from
Sangatsudou next time you come here.
I will.
Thank you.
I achieved my goal very quickly.
I had a feeling making friends would
be a more time-consuming activity.
I'd never guess it was so simple.
For now, sit here.
I will.
The
flow
of
time
makes
a
continuous
sound
(so
close
your
eyes
and
feel
it)
It's
a
melody
that
invites
the
coming
future
(which
begins
today)
What
kind
of
world
is
waiting
for
me?
(Who
is
calling
me?)
I
tried
asking
myself
for
an
answer
(in
my
heart)
Here,
in
the
middle
of
ideals
and
reality
(I'm
searching
for
them)
The
hands
of
the
clock
are
being
constantly
moved
(as
I
turn
them
back)
I'll
do
anything
to
erase
all
sadness
(over
and
over
again)
Even
if
it
means
going
back
down
the
passage
of
dark
stairs
(to
recreate
the
past)
There's
something
I
want
to
protect
no
matter
what
(I'll
protect
you)
I'll
say
that
out
loud
(and
try
resetting
again)
Believing
that
fate
will
bring
us
together
again
A Day in the Life of Haruki
Actually...
Yes?
What do you think being friends means?
I've researched that topic a lot.
Friends seem to study together, have fun,
text, and talk on the phone at length.
Texts and long phone calls?
I don't know your number.
What should we do, then?
Let me think...
Okay, put your number in my phone.
ADD NEW CONTACT
PHONE
Haruki
Misora
HARUKI
MISORA
PHONE NUMBER
MOBILE
EDIT CONTACT
Haruki... Misora.
So your given name is Misora.
Yes.
Now we can message and call each other.
What should we do next?
Should we study together?
I don't want to study.
It's too annoying.
Should we do something to have fun, then?
I like simply sitting and talking.
I understand.
What should we talk about, then?
What do you want to talk about?
Nothing in particular.
You're always so honest.
Is being honest a problem?
Generally, you'd call it a virtue.
But it can be problematic at times.
For example?
For example, let me ask you, do you like me?
No. I wouldn't say I do or do not like you.
That's very honest.
Such words could hurt a person
depending on the circumstances.
Though I prefer that honesty,
and not having to guess at people's feelings.
Everything should be that simple.
I guess we can talk about something trivial.
Something meaningless that would make us sleepy,
just a comfortable conversation.
For example?
Let's see...
We can try searching for
the kindest words in this world.
The kindest words?
It could be fun words or happy words.
It could be anything,
but I chose kind words this time.
What are the kindest words to you?
I don't know.
Let's think more specifically, then.
Let's say there's a starving cat sleeping
on chilling asphalt on a cold night,
very exhausted, and in need of food...
Are there any words that could save it?
I'm sure that cat would be suffering.
What it would need wouldn't be words.
It could be saved with some milk and a blanket.
Would it even be possible to save it with just words?
You don't need to think about it so seriously.
There's no answer to a meaningless question.
Just say whatever comes to mind.
Then, I'd say, "I'll bring you what you need".
For example, I'd promise that
I'd bring milk and a blanket to that cat.
I see.
A promise would give it hope.
Hope?
If there's help coming to it,
the cat might try to endure
a bit more cold and hunger.
What both people and cats
need to endure pain is hope.
Is hope a kind word?
I'm not sure.
Maybe it's just cruel.
Maybe the next day, the cat would
be freezing and hungry again.
But I think the feeling that you
want to give someone hope
is definitely kind.
I see.
What are the kindest words to you?
Well, if there were a cat suffering
from hunger and trembling from cold,
I'd say, "isn't it cold?".
I'd say, "it's cold, and I'm hungry".
Would that save the cat?
Of course not.
No matter what I'd say, nothing would change.
But at the very least,
I'd be able to convey to it that I feel the same.
And what comes from conveying that?
Depends on what it does.
If the cat said it'd try to find food,
I'd answer, "okay, let's go".
If it said that it wanted a warm place to sleep,
I'd go search for one with it.
What if the cat said nothing?
I'd also say nothing, and just sleep next to it.
What would Kei do?
I believe that's a sincere answer.
What do you mean?
You accept the reality the way it is.
Is that kind?
I wouldn't know.
But I believe the cat would be saved in some way.
I see. I'm glad.
Me too.
But you know,
I don't really trust what we call "words".
You can't trust words?
If I put what I'm thinking into words,
it makes me feel like my words belong to someone else.
It's a bit unpleasant.
For example, when I'm petting
a cat, it's a sign of love.
But how could I show that
amount of love using words?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I said something stupid.
No.
But that's exactly why I wanted
some trivial conversation.
There's no right answer, and no one will be troubled
if we don't manage to convey our meaning clearly.
I like this kind of simple, comfortable conversation.
I see.
Please tell me, then.
What?
How to hold trivial conversations that
would have no meaning and make you sleepy.
Simple, comfortable conversations.
What we just talked about
was exactly a trivial conversation.
Don't worry. You can do it just fine.
And then we talked about
everything that came to mind.
About a dream I had recently.
About the shapes of clouds.
About the cats' paws.
None of it had any meaning.
They were conversations for their own sake,
that we would forget the next day.
Have we managed to become friends?
I wonder.
Rather than friends,
we're still more like acquaintances.
I see...
Come here the next time you feel like it.
Will it make us friends?
I think that when you talk just once,
you're acquaintances,
but when you talk a lot, you're friends.
Is that how it works?
I don't really know, but I think so.
And I quite like you, actually.
We'll become friends eventually.
I was actually worried.
Until now, there was only
one person I could call a friend.
One?
Do you mean Asai?
No, someone else.
I see.
Yes.
I feel like Kei isn't in the "friends" category.
Next time, I'll bring cream puffs from Sangatsudou.
Okay, I'll be waiting.
Yes.
And so, my plan to make a friend began.
Though I don't know yet when I'll see the results of it.
Asai Kei caught a cold and didn't come to school.
It wasn't really unusual for him not to feel well.
It happens a few times a year.
There are three problems, though.
First, should I go visit him?
Second, if I do, what should I bring?
And third, should I help U-Research or not?
Hello!
Can I eat with you?
SOY MILK
You look kind of languid today.
What does that mean?
You know, just, Asai caught a cold and isn't
here today, so I figured you'd be languid.
I see.
You're going to visit him, right?
I'm considering it.
Why?
You should go!
Do you think it's the right thing to do?
Of course!
You can't waste such a great love event!
There's no connection between love and colds.
There is!
You should aim for him exactly
when he's sick and weak!
Misora, you know what's the quickest
and simplest way to cure a cold?
Taking medicine and sleeping a lot?
I'm not talking about realistic methods here,
more, you know, miracle-of-love methods!
First, when you kiss someone,
you catch the cold from them.
Second, when you give
someone your cold, it's cured.
And that means kissing cures colds!
So logical!
That's impossible.
The logic there isn't wrong,
but the basic premises are.
It's one of the things U-Research is researching.
"Are colds really cured when
someone catches them from you?"
What's U-Research?
It's exactly what the name suggests.
The "U" comes from "unidentified".
Basically, in U-Research we research
anything that is unidentified.
Let's say I catch a cold
from Kei and his cold is cured.
I don't think it can be proven just from that
situation that giving someone a cold cures it.
It could've just been cured afterwards.
That's why you check if the
cold was given to someone
between catching a cold and its curing
and look at statistics, that's the point!
I think infecting people with your cold
usually just happens without you noticing.
Yeah.
It's probably impossible to gather proper statistics.
Isn't it then pointless?
Exactly!
The true purpose of U-Research
is researching pointless things
and deciding on the results by ourselves!
I see.
So if you feel like it, try kissing Asai.
I was asked by Minami Mirai to help her research.
I would if there weren't any problems,
but Asai Kei is involved in this case.
Kei probably wouldn't want to give anyone his cold.
And that means I can't help U-Research with this.
What's more important, his stomach
might be weak because of the cold,
and I heard that a warm meal,
easily digestable and rich in carbohydrates,
increases body temperature
and immune response.
So I'll go with a well-known
comfort food: rice porridge.
Dried kelp, check.
Rice, check.
Pot, check.
Kei should have salt and other spices
in his house, so I'll just borrow them.
It's difficult to walk.
I always feel like this when I'm alone.
When Kei isn't next to me,
I feel like my balance is disrupted.
I wonder if my heavy bag is making it worse.
I know!
If I carry it on the side Kei walks on,
it might help with the balance a bit.
Nothing really changed.
There's nothing I can do. I should just hurry.
I should have everything necessary.
No, let's check it again.
Once I get to Kei's,
it'll be too late to go back for anything.
First, rice.
Dried kelp.
A pot.
I'll be borrowing spices, so I'm missing...
I know! Dried plums!
Dried plums are a staple of rice porridge.
I don't know the details, but I heard they're healthy.
I'm glad I rechecked everything.
I'll buy them on the way there.
Seems like the balance is still the same,
despite adding the plums.
Sangatsudou
Since 1947 - Sakurada
Sangatsudou...
They have sweets in there.
Sangatsudou
Since 1947 - Sakurada
Kei likes sweet things.
Sangatsudou
Since 1947 - Sakurada
Still, I don't think it's appropriate
for a sick person to eat sweets.
Sangatsudou
Since 1947 - Sakurada
Peaches! Right, peaches!
Summer
Peach Festival
Warabi
Mochi
Peaches are an obvious choice.
I don't know where I heard it, but I feel like
something like this was commonly known.
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Roll Cake
Fruit Tart
Mont Blanc
Castella
Welcome!
Two Peach Jellies please.
I'm terribly sorry, but we've sold out already today.
How about this Fruit Tart instead?
It's filled with peaches, too.
I'm sure Kei likes tarts.
But would he want to eat one when he has a cold?
I know!
HARUKI MISORA
That's a problem.
I don't know what to do
if I can't get advice from a specialist.
What will you do?
Right! I have a specialist right here too!
Someone working at Sangatsudou.
Who else would be a better person to ask?
Do you have something good for eating when you're sick?
Are you visiting someone?
Yes.
How about ice cream?
Ice cream...
It does seem to be nice to eat
something cold when you have a fever.
But that's not peaches.
Ice cream is great when you're sick.
Better than peaches?
Peaches are good, but ice cream is better.
Even though that's not peaches?
We don't have peach ice cream,
but I recommend apple ice cream.
Apple...
Apples might be nice for visiting someone.
I feel like they are.
Fruit Tart
Peaches, but in a tart...
Not peaches, but ice cream.
Apple Ice Cream
And they have apple!
Two tubs of apple ice cream, then.
Sure, just a moment.
The weight of the plums got
counterbalanced by the ice cream.
The balance is so bad I can't walk.
But now it's perfect.
Rice, dried kelp, a pot, dried plums, apple ice cream.
I hope Kei will be happy.
But...
To visit him, I need to ring the doorbell.
And he'd have to unlock the door for me.
I'd wake him up when he's resting in bed,
and make him walk to the door.
Is it worth it just for rice porridge and ice cream?
Maybe he already prepared dinner for himself.
I've never visited him before.
Asai Kei is excellent at everything,
so he can handle most things by himself.
It's not a problem for him that he's alone.
There's no reason to be worried about him.
I should go home...
Asai Kei
Text message
Received
From:          Asai Kei
To:               Haruki Misora
Subject:     Ice cream
For some reason, I really want
some ice cream. If you have time,
could you buy some for me?
For some reason, I really want some ice cream.
If you have time, could you buy some for me?
Like the specialist said!
Ice cream is better than peaches after all!
I should hurry to Kei's—
This is weird.
That's not the kind of message Kei would send.
There's no way he'd use people
to do something for him.
Minami, right?
Hi.
Were you following me the whole time?
Well, how should I put it...
I'm sorry!
Why did you do that?
I thought it'd be fun...
Was it fun?
In its own way!
The best part was how
you passed the confectionery,
changed your mind, and went back there!
I don't understand what's fun about it.
But you failed, Misora.
Why didn't you go to Asai's?
Because I realized there's no need to.
I don't think you need a reason to visit a sick friend.
I realized I actually could bother him if I went.
So I should just give up.
You wouldn't! He'd be happy!
Kei is the one to decide that.
That's not true!
Anyone would be happy, I'm sure!
And that's why you contacted Kei, right?
Yeah, I thought I couldn't let this chance slip by,
so I told him to contact you...
I see.
Yeah.
Thank you.
No problem.
I'll go eat ice cream with Kei, then.
You should.
Try feeding him.
I will.
What?! You really will?
Isn't that what you do when you visit a sick person?
Yeah, I think...
I think that's just how visits should go.
Well, good luck then!
Thank you.
So if you feel like it, try kissing Asai.
Apple
Next Episode
Welcome! To the world of dreams!
There's someone I want to meet.
I want to be like a god.
It's inverted...
Michiru is still Michiru.
I'm supposed to destroy this world.
Please wait!
We're always simply standing in a rain of eternal sadness
That is why I need that warmth of yours
Life is but a dream we never wake up from
We repeat it over and over, praying for salvation
I kept waiting endlessly for your signal
To make sure you wouldn't disappear all by yourself
Ah, it doesn't matter where I am or what I'm doing
My heart can't go against your will
So I'd follow you even to the ends of the world
I fell in love with you at the dawn of our new world
But we kept pushing the hand of the clock backwards
And lost not only time, but our smiles as well
You're the one who brought it back
And taught me that even lies can be meaningful