August 28th
Monday, 06:30 PM
Second Time
It's time.
Did you hear your voice?
Good question.
What do you want the answer to be?
I'm sure whichever one you choose is correct.
What are you planning to do now?
Everyone thinks you're dead.
You don't have to worry about me.
You can't just say that.
I was the one who revived you.
That's not true.
I used you, and was reborn of my own accord.
There's no reason for you to feel responsible.
If possible, I want you to live the life of a normal girl.
I want you to live with your parents,
and attend school again.
Impossible.
I don't want the Bureau to learn
about my existence yet.
Because they'd lock you up like the Witch?
Do you think it's possible for me to be a normal
girl while staying out of the Bureau's sight?
Can you make that happen?
Souma...
What if you and your family moved out of Sakurada?
If you leave this town, your death should be erased.
It should disappear even from your own memories.
Do you really believe in such miracles?
You should know that.
Tell me.
Would you become a normal girl
if you left Sakurada?
That's for me to know.
The
flow
of
time
makes
a
continuous
sound
(so
close
your
eyes
and
feel
it)
It's
a
melody
that
invites
the
coming
future
(which
begins
today)
What
kind
of
world
is
waiting
for
me?
(Who
is
calling
me?)
I
tried
asking
myself
for
an
answer
(in
my
heart)
Here,
in
the
middle
of
ideals
and
reality
(I'm
searching
for
them)
The
hands
of
the
clock
are
being
constantly
moved
(as
I
turn
them
back)
I'll
do
anything
to
erase
all
sadness
(over
and
over
again)
Even
if
it
means
going
back
down
the
passage
of
dark
stairs
(to
recreate
the
past)
There's
something
I
want
to
protect
no
matter
what
(I'll
protect
you)
I'll
say
that
out
loud
(and
try
resetting
again)
Believing
that
fate
will
bring
us
together
again
The Bureau has accepted your request.
As a member of the Service Club,
you are allowed to conduct an investigation
into Katagiri Honoka's ability.
Thank you for approving my selfish request.
The Bureau also wanted to
investigate her ability thoroughly.
Your ability is perfect for spotting inconsistencies.
Spotting inconsistencies?
Find out how closely the dream world
resembles the real world.
That's your task.
I understand.
I'm surprised.
About?
That I was able to meet you like this.
I didn't expect you to answer a simple message.
I need to ask you a personal question.
Why do you want to enter the dream world?
I'm curious.
It may be just a dream,
but the ability user is able to create a world.
Why?
Isn't that
like a god?
I'd like to be like a god.
I see. That'll be all, then.
Let me give you one final warning.
Warning?
You're drawing attention.
Do not do anything as reckless as two years ago.
Hoshina Memorial Hospital
Let's go, Kei.
We made plans to eat dinner together.
September 23rd
Saturday, 1
:
0 PM
What will happen if we take
Souma Sumire out of Sakurada?
If all goes well, she'll lose her
memories about her ability
September 23rd
Saturday, 03:00 PM
and even about her own death.
September 23rd
Saturday, 0
:00 PM
She'll become an ordinary middle school student.
But if something goes wrong...
We don't know what will happen.
That's why I needed a safe way to test that,
something I could accurately simulate it with.
What I found was a world created with an ability,
a dream world which was an exact copy of reality.
September 23rd
Saturday, 07:00 PM
Haruki.
It's time to reset.
September 2
2n
3r
d
Fri
Satur
day
Second Time
It's September 22nd, 12:47:08.
Looks like we've reset.
Thank you.
Everything went according to plan.
Tomorrow, on the 23rd,
we walked around the town,
ate dinner, and reset at 7 PM.
We'll go to the hospital tomorrow
and enter the dream world.
Thank you for the food.
Does it taste good?
It does, it really does.
I'm glad to hear that.
By the way, before the reset, we made a promise.
Do you know what it was about?
The school festival, maybe?
Exactly.
I don't mind if we're going to be
too busy to go there, though.
It's fine.
Okay then.
Kei.
Please be my lover.
Why don't you come to our school festival?
What for?
I'll buy you takoyaki.
Or a hot dog, doesn't matter.
Wouldn't professionally-made ones taste better?
What's your class doing?
A play.
Haruki's the lead.
I ended up being her lover.
For real?
Since there were probably others who
wanted this role, I'm feeling a bit guilty.
It's fine.
No one wants to take part in school festival plays.
Oh, did you just try to cheer me up?
No way!
A villain doesn't comfort people.
Instead, we hurt people with the cruel truth.
Anyway, come if you feel like it.
If I feel like it, yeah.
I probably won't.
Bye.
That's weird.
No one came at this time before the reset.
It's been a while, Asai.
I'm surprised you knew where I lived, Nonoh.
I got the address from a girl I met today.
What brings you here?
There's someone I want to meet.
That's unexpected. Who is it?
I don't know his name.
I used to call him "the old man
from the stray cat mansion".
Where is he now?
He's...
Apparently he's inside a dream.
How did you learn about me going inside a dream?
I was told that!
By the girl I met.
She told me that the old man from
the stray cat mansion is in a dream,
and that you'd take me there if I asked you to.
Was that girl about middle-school age?
Yeah.
A slender girl with short hair and big eyes?
Exactly. Your acquaintance?
Yes, she's my friend.
She was at the shrine.
Left a message for you.
A message?
"Read volume 407 of the Script very carefully."
Volume 407 of the Script...
Asai.
I want to meet the old man
from the stray cat mansion again.
Would you take me to the dream world?
September 23rd
Saturday
Second Time
How is Katagiri Honoka's condition?
Nothing has changed.
She's been asleep for almost nine years now.
Have you ever entered her dream?
No, we're not allowed to.
Is Katagiri Honoka's ability dangerous?
The Bureau concluded her ability
was a possible cause of great trouble.
One Hand Eden.
Yes, exactly.
A replica of happiness so small
that it fits into one hand.
A closed Eden.
Katagiri Honoka can do anything in her dream.
So in the dream world, she's omnipotent.
Humans shouldn't be allowed into a fake world
where the god can easily make them happy.
Based on this declaration,
the Bureau doesn't allow anyone near her.
What if it's real happiness? Is that still a problem?
Katagiri
Honoka
The Bureau concluded that such happiness is fake.
If you fall asleep near Katagiri Honoka,
you'll automatically enter her dream world.
Where is she?
Asleep in the next room.
I think I'll be a little late getting to the dream world.
Should we wait for you?
We have things to do.
You should go ahead and visit the old man
from the stray cat mansion, Nonoh.
Okay.
Well...
Good night then.
Good night.
Should I prepare a sweet cake, then?
I'll also make some nice tea.
You don't talk much, Misora.
Welcome to the dream world!
So you're Kei?
Yes.
Misora was just telling me about you.
You like sweets, right?
Yes, for the most part.
And you are?
I'm Mytyl.
Are you Katagiri Honoka?
You're so silly.
I'm Mytyl. Katagiri definitely isn't my name.
Do you know where Katagiri is, then?
Never even heard that name before.
I see.
What kind of place is this world?
Fairly normal!
There's stores, this hospital...
Almost the same as the outside world!
So it somehow differs from it?
There's only one big difference.
In this world, if you wish for something, it'll happen!
For example...
In the real world, I can't even stand up,
but here I can run around!
I think I could even fly!
Tell me, what do you wish for?
Shall I prepare a huge cake?
Or ice cream? Chocolate? Cookies?
Cookies are fine, thanks.
Okay. I'll ask Tyltyl, then.
Who is Tyltyl?
Tyltyl is my hero!
He's strong, smart, and can do anything, like a god!
And he always protects me!
He made me his little sister, so I'm Mytyl.
You're Mytyl, because you're Tyltyl's sister...
That's right!
Then what was your name before
you became his sister? Your real name?
My name is Mytyl.
It's my real name.
I'm sorry for asking.
It's fine!
Everyone who comes here is like that at first!
They have this misconception
that reality is important.
It's because they don't know
how it feels to escape from it.
They give in, they come to terms with it,
and believe that reality can't be changed.
A sweet lemon.
What's that?
The opposite of the sour
grapes from Aesop's Fables.
It's the concept that people convince
themselves that what they have is great.
Everyone knows that reality is stupid and boring,
but they're deluding themselves that it's sweet.
That's kinda sad.
If possible, I'd like to meet that Tyltyl person...
I'm the only one who can meet Tyltyl freely.
I'll ask about it, since I'm already asking for cookies,
but I don't think it'll be possible.
I feel like I was supposed
to tell you two something...
What is it?
I forgot.
Probably wasn't important anyway.
See ya!
Let's get going.
Sorry it took so long. Just like I thought,
took me a while to fall asleep.
It's fine.
Should I sing a lullaby next time?
That's... a charming idea.
Hoshina Memorial Hospital
This world...
It's amazing.
Hoshina Memorial Hospital
Everything is reversed.
Normally, when leaving the hospital,
I'd have the sea on the left and the town on the right.
But here we have a wall on the
right and the town on the left.
Seems like we can't get past this wall.
Does that mean there's nothing outside
of Sakurada in the dream world?
Might be, yes. In this case, we can't see
what happens if we take Souma outside.
What are we going to do then?
We'll do the job we were given in the Service Club.
Isn't it pointless if we can't do our experiment?
The person who told Nonoh that she can meet the old man
from the stray cat mansion was most likely Souma.
Souma led Nonoh to come to this world.
She should have had some purpose in that.
Let's go then, Kei.
We had plans to eat dinner together.
Shall I make the wind a bit stronger?
No, it's fine like this. Thanks.
It's been quite a while, Sumire.
I'm happy to see you again.
Hello, Tyltyl.
You're still playing god, I see.
What's wrong? You seem to be in a bad mood.
A certain boy is going to eat
dinner with a certain girl tonight.
A boy you like, and a girl who isn't you?
You didn't have to say it aloud.
She forgot the message, by the way.
That they shouldn't go out at night.
And you came all this way here
just to complain about that?
Of course not.
I'm here to take a look at your future.
I forget, can you see my future?
Of course. I'm seeing it right now.
My ability works while I'm talking to people, after all.
So how does our future look?
The same as always.
Mytyl is still the same Mytyl.
She'll never change.
Even despite all your effort?
No matter what I try to do,
I always end up thinking there might
be no point in doing anything.
That's not true.
Your effort will pay off.
Sumire, dear.
You're planning to save Mytyl, aren't you?
I'm not doing anything.
It's up to Kei to decide.
But even his actions are regulated by the Script.
I guess, yeah.
You shouldn't have died two years ago.
If you didn't like your life,
you should've escaped to this world.
I could've made everything
the way you wanted it to be.
In my case, that'd have been pointless.
What are you trying to achieve?
That's for me to know.
Reality and this dream world are similar
enough to say that they're mostly the same.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
You want some?
Yes, thank you.
What brings you here?
A part-time job. I got a request from the Bureau.
What is your job?
The same as it used to be.
Saving the world?
Yeah.
I don't mind you admiring me.
I've been keeping quiet about it,
but I've actually been admiring
you for quite some time, yes.
I guess we should get to the job.
Did you notice any differences
between this world and reality?
Apart from the white wall and the town
being flipped on the north-south axis,
everything is the same as the
reality I saw before the reset.
I see.
I guess I'll take a look around this world myself.
Ukawa.
What are you going to do
once you learn the differences?
Depending on the circumstances...
I'm supposed to destroy this world.
I wonder what Ukawa thinks about this world.
I don't quite understand what she considers right.
Tyltyl
Tyltyl...
Hello, I'm Tyltyl.
Nice to meet you. I'm Asai Kei.
I have a warning for you.
It's forbidden in this town to go out at night.
Will it be fine if we go back home now?
Hard to tell.
You might not make it in time.
We'll hurry.
It's my fault I didn't contact you earlier.
I'll send you home this time.
And there.
Connecting
Also, here's a present.
Bye. Make sure you don't go outside.
Wait, please!
I've just got two questions for you.
What is it?
Why is this town surrounded by a white wall?
That's just how it is.
If I had to say, it's because this place
is the blue bird's isolated cage.
And the other?
Tyltyl,
are you Katagiri Honoka?
I'm not.
Katagiri Honoka is Mytyl.
She doesn't remember that anymore, though.
Mytyl created you, didn't she?
Didn't you have only two questions? Bye.
Haruki...
If everything suddenly goes dark,
you should at least scream.
I see. I'll do that next time.
What happened?
A lot,
but to sum it up, I guess we dined and dashed.
What's that?
It seems like cookies.
It's the thing that fell down earlier.
That's sweet.
Did Mytyl create Tyltyl?
Most likely.
I'm pretty sure Katagiri Honoka
is almost omnipotent in this world.
If she's omnipotent, why would she create a god?
It's the same as getting
a birthday cake from someone
instead of making it yourself—
you feel happier that way.
Giving up your omnipotence,
forgetting about everything,
and creating a god devoted to you
makes your life a lot happier.
I understand.
There's a problem, though.
Ukawa would probably hate this situation.
So...
Ukawa will try to destroy this world?
That seems pretty likely.
Kei, isn't this weird?
I've never felt this sleepy before.
Yeah, me too.
I have an idea why.
It's been six hours or so since
we entered the dream world.
That means we've been asleep
for six hours in the real world.
And?
It's time for us to wake up.
The us in this world might fall asleep instead.
Don't force yourself.
Just use the bed.
What will you do, Kei?
I've never mentioned it before,
but I actually like sleeping on the floor.
You're lying.
It's the truth!
I'll sleep on the floor too, then.
Haruki...
Please, just sleep on the bed.
Do that for me.
Haru—
So this is what he meant
when he told us to stay inside.
What is that thing?
The monster.
Do you know what it is?
The monster is the monster.
Appears during nighttime and destroys the world.
Next Episode
I have to protect her.
A written copy of the Script...
Numbers are the only thing I don't forget.
I guess that means I was rejected.
Do you remember the day we first met?
If you push one small knife right into his heart...
We're always simply standing in a rain of eternal sadness
That is why I need that warmth of yours
Life is but a dream we never wake up from
We repeat it over and over, praying for salvation
I kept waiting endlessly for your signal
To make sure you wouldn't disappear all by yourself
Ah, it doesn't matter where I am or what I'm doing
My heart can't go against your will
So I'd follow you even to the ends of the world
I fell in love with you at the dawn of our new world
But we kept pushing the hand of the clock backwards
And lost not only time, but our smiles as well
You're the one who brought it back
And taught me that even lies can be meaningful