July 15th
Saturday
Good morning, Kei!
This time, I've got a message from Friday,
July 14th, which is yesterday for you.
I believe you made an important
appointment before yesterday.
You were going to drink tea with
some cutie on Saturday the 15th.
I'm giving you this wake-up call
so that you don't oversleep.
And now, it's time for our pop idol,
Haruki Misora, to take the stage!
Um, Kei, are you awake?
Please don't be late for tomorrow.
You heard her, Kei. Isn't it about time you wake up?
What do you want, Kei? It's so early...
Payback for disrupting my sleep.
The
flow
of
time
makes
a
continuous
sound
(so
close
your
eyes
and
feel
it)
It's
a
melody
that
invites
the
coming
future
(which
begins
today)
What
kind
of
world
is
waiting
for
me?
(Who
is
calling
me?)
I
tried
asking
myself
for
an
answer
(in
my
heart)
Here,
in
the
middle
of
ideals
and
reality
(I'm
searching
for
them)
The
hands
of
the
clock
are
being
constantly
moved
(as
I
turn
them
back)
I'll
do
anything
to
erase
all
sadness
(over
and
over
again)
Even
if
it
means
going
back
down
the
passage
of
dark
stairs
(to
recreate
the
past)
There's
something
I
want
to
protect
no
matter
what
(I'll
protect
you)
I'll
say
that
out
loud
(and
try
resetting
again)
Believing
that
fate
will
bring
us
together
again
Sorry about that. That must've been bothersome.
That's an annoying ability.
It's a pretty strong ability despite it
only being able to send voice messages.
I can't resist it no matter what.
Oh, I just remembered.
I added another cat to my collection.
A wind chime, huh?
I haven't seen one of those in a while.
Want me to lend it to you?
I like hearing wind chimes once
in a while when I least expect it.
Much like finding a rainbow.
Wouldn't it be wonderful if there was a tool that
could allow you to see a rainbow at any time?
Isn't there a bit of charm
in noticing them once in a while?
It's kind of sad for a wind chime to keep
ringing where no one will notice it.
For all you know, the wind chime might
enjoy its own gracefully lone sound.
Nice to meet you. I'm Asai Kei.
And she's Haruki Misora.
I'm Murase Youka.
I've come on a referral from Mr. Tsushima.
Asai, you're a high school student, right?
Yes, I'm a first-year.
Why are you doing the Bureau's work?
Because I'm in that kind of club.
It's called the Ashiharabashi Service Club.
"Service Club"?
We're being monitored by the Bureau.
Do you possess a dangerous ability?
My memory is kind of good, that's all.
Murase, I heard that your request
is to search for your lost cat, but...
I already found my cat.
He's been run over by a car.
My request is for you to revive my dead cat.
I see.
By the way, Murase,
are you prepared to kill three days'
worth of the world's time for your cat?
What do you mean by that?
The cat's name is Mike.
She's had him for six months.
Yesterday morning, on Friday the 14th,
he was run over by a car in front
of a bakery in the shopping district.
Doesn't that seem a little strange?
What about it is strange?
The Bureau doesn't get involved
in non-ability incidents, right?
Yeah.
The Bureau only acts in cases where
problems involving special abilities arise.
Also, there was too little time
between the accident and the request.
She found out about the accident yesterday morning,
and I heard about the request
yesterday during lunch break.
In just a few hours, we were given both the Bureau's
authorization and Tsushima's instructions.
That's way too quick.
What are we going to do?
We'll save the cat, of course.
Let's gather some information first.
I'll contact Hitsuuchi.
Could you go check out
the scene of the accident for me?
Sure.
The number you have reached
is no longer in service.
Please check the number and—
The number you have reached is no longer in—
The number you have reached is—
The number you have... reached is...
This is Asai. I'd like to ask you something.
...no longer in service.
Please check the number and...
It's been a while, Kei.
Would you quit with this system, Hitsuuchi?
No way.
What'll happen if my voice gives away my identity?
Are you looking for a cat today?
Yeah.
Let me introduce you to a cat expert.
Nonoh Seika, a first-year at Oomiya High School.
Her ability allows her to distribute information.
Our speciality !
Packed with cream:
Cream Bread
However, it works only on cats.
When it comes to cats, there's no one more knowledgeable and loving than she is.
On her days off, she naps with
the cats at the Kamisaki Shrine.
Got it. Thank you.
By the way, Kei, do you know what a MacGuffin is?
"MacGuffin"? I know the dictionary definition of it.
I see. Well, if you don't know, then it's fine. See ya.
Here, have one.
Thanks.
It seems the shop assistant didn't see it happen.
But he said he might've heard the sound of the
car braking sometime between 8 and 9 o'clock.
The time matches.
Also, Hitsuuchi asked me about a MacGuffin.
What's a "MacGuffin"?
It's a film and theater term.
It's an item that serves as a trigger
for the protagonist in the story.
If the protagonist is a thief,
then it's a precious stone he'd be after.
If he's in a gang, then it's wads of cash.
But you can switch the items around.
Basically, the possible objectives of a protagonist
are commonly known as a "MacGuffin."
Is it related to this incident?
Beats me.
We had plans to come to the festival at night...
Let's come here at night, too.
You saved three days ago at 12:59.
It's 12:40 right now.
We don't have much time left, huh?
I'd like to ask you about a cat
that was in an accident.
We might be able to save that cat.
Just 13 more minutes. We're cutting it close.
Are you Nonoh?
Morning.
You said someone was in an accident?
A cat with gray fur, blue eyes, and a crooked tail.
He belonged to a person named Murase.
How long did this Murase person have that cat?
About six months.
There isn't a cat like that in Sakurada.
This cat was run over in front
of a bakery yesterday morning.
I certainly haven't seen him around lately.
Something probably happened, then.
Even if he did get into an accident,
how can you save him?
We have an ability that allows
us to—or rather, she does.
Would you like some?
No thanks. I'm good.
If you happen to visit again, please bring
some cream puffs from Sangatsudou.
We're out of time.
Anyway, we'd like you to tell us about that cat.
I can't fall asleep immediately.
You can't use your ability when you're awake?
I need to be in a clear state of mind that is free
of any thought so that I can forget myself.
Sleeping is the quickest and easiest way to do that.
If you sleep, you'll know where the cat was, right?
Not if it's dead.
Let me try sleeping.
Sing me a lullaby.
Haruki?
Huh?
Should I sing?
It's time to reset.
July 1
th
Satur
day
Fri
Satur
Thurs
Fri
Wednes
Thurs
Second Time
It's 12:59 on a Wednesday. The date is July 12th.
It seems you did a reset.
Looks like we have to look for a cat.
Why did you reset?
Three days from now, on Saturday the 15th,
we went to meet a person named Murase
Youka under Mr. Tsushima's instructions.
And we accepted her request to save
her cat, which was run over by a car.
Got it.
Thanks.
Sure.
Searching for a cat, huh?
Well then, I'm counting on you.
That's it?
Is there a problem?
It's a request you'll give me two days later.
I'm busy with all sorts of things, too, you know.
I can't stand students who play hooky.
Since you've reset, I'll be doing the same work
I've already done for the next three days, right?
Yeah, pretty much.
That's depressing.
You don't even remember doing the work,
so in reality, this is your first time.
It's a matter of how I feel.
By the way, do you know what a MacGuffin is?
A "MacGuffin"?
Hitsuuchi asked me about it before the reset.
I see.
Well, it's not like I'd know
something that he doesn't know.
Hey, did you know?
I heard that a vampire appears
at the haunted mountain!
A vampire?
Wasn't that rumor popular a few years ago?
Wanna come with me to look for the vampire?
This must be Kei's second time
hearing this conversation.
But he faithfully recreates
the conversation from the first time.
He keeps acting like he's listening for the first time.
Go with the U-Research people for that.
"U-Research"?
It's a club that researches the unidentified.
I'm a member.
After what happened two years ago,
Kei hates changing the future unnecessarily.
Sangatsudou
What kind of person is that cat-lover Nonoh?
She's cat-like, but she doesn't end her
sentences with "meow" when she talks.
Do you like things like that?
Things like what?
Ending sentences with "meow."
Oh, yeah, I think it's cute.
Nice weather we're having today, meow.
Yeah... um...
What's wrong, meow?
Sorry, I lied.
Please speak normally.
Is that so? All right, then.
You should value yourself a little more.
If you say so, I'll try my best to.
For now, you should do something
about that thought process.
You sure say some complicated things.
Nonoh.
And you are?
We met in three days. My name's Kei Asai.
So basically, what you two are saying
is that you know the future.
Well, that's about right.
Whatever.
What's really important is that
you know what my favorite food is.
As things stand right now, a cat is going to die
in a car accident the day after tomorrow.
How long has this Murase person had that cat?
Next Saturday, you asked the same question.
I happen to know something about that cat.
But the cat I know of is a stray.
Do you know where that stray cat is now?
Let's try and find out.
Kei, are we still going to
go through with this request?
There's no reason for us to quit.
But Murase might be lying.
Did that cat really belong to her?
It being a stray or not makes no difference.
If it's going to get into an accident, let's save it.
Isn't there a possibility that
Murase is trying to use us?
Of course there is.
She might've wanted us to use your
reset ability for some other reason.
Is it okay to continue fulfilling this request?
We're talking about a possibility here.
We can't dismiss it just because of that.
It's no good.
What's no good?
It seems he's sleeping right now.
Is that a problem?
My ability is gaining access to a cat's senses.
So even if I share a cat's senses with it while
it's sleeping, I won't know what's going on.
I see.
If you want me to, I could try again later.
Please do.
Would you please call us
once you find out where it is?
Sure. I'll be more than happy
to do it if it saves the cat.
There's a festival on Saturday, right?
Would you like to go together?
That's right.
This request should wrap up before that time.
I need to get a yukata for it.
I was thinking of buying a new one.
Isn't last year's fine? It looked good on you.
No matter what I wear,
you always say it looks good on me.
You must not be into girl's clothing.
I like stuff like miniskirts.
Preferably, red plaid skirts.
But you'd hate it if I actually wore one.
That's because that'd be extreme for you to wear.
But you just said you like it.
I did say that, but...
Should I get a red plaid miniskirt, then?
You don't have to.
I only like it if some girl I passed
by happened to wear one.
Kei, that's—
This is Asai.
Hey, Kei. What do you need today?
We reset after I got information from you.
I was looking for the cat,
and I got introduced to Nonoh Seika.
I see.
So why did you go through
the trouble of calling me this time?
I've got something I want to ask.
Do you know Murase Youka?
Disclosing information about her is prohibited.
In other words, you do know her.
I already said I can't talk about that.
What's a MacGuffin?
Disclosing information on that is also prohibited.
Did the same person instruct you
to conceal information regarding those two?
That's a secret.
You seem to be doing well right now.
What makes you think that?
You're suspecting a relation between
the MacGuffin and Murase Youka.
Naturally, they shouldn't be related in any way.
Is it okay for you to be saying this to me?
I'm almost crossing the line.
Though I don't know anything
about the nature of the MacGuffin.
See ya.
How did it go?
We shouldn't be distrustful of people.
There's no point since our hands are tied.
Yes?
He had been abducted!
"He"? You mean the cat?
He was kidnapped.
He's been taken somewhere by a stranger.
Where is he now?
Sorry. I know nothing about the things
the cat personally doesn't understand.
I don't mind if it's just what you know.
He was abducted at around 3 p.m today.
It happened in front of Nishi Ward Park.
It's immediately after the reset.
Is the cat inside a room?
It seems like it.
I could see a bed and a desk.
There was a framed picture of
a young man on top of the desk.
Anyway, that means the cat is alive, right?
Yeah.
Please continue gathering information.
It'll be all right.
If he's still okay, I'm sure it means
the guy doesn't intend to hurt him.
That's true. I'll call you later.
Why was the cat abducted?
If her objective was to make us reset,
then she should've achieved her goal.
There's no need to do anything unnecessary.
So why?
July 13th
Thursday
Second Time
Do you know the story about the hole in the wall?
Hole?
It's not just any hole. It's shaped just
like a hand with five distinct fingers.
People say they saw it on the
residential street yesterday evening.
What's more, they said the hole suddenly
closed up right before their eyes.
What do you think, Asai?
I didn't hear about this before the reset.
Um... I'm sure an ability like that exists.
What?! It's a ghost-like story!
You sure are a spoilsport.
Ghosts, huh?
By the way, have you guys
ever heard of a MacGuffin?
"MacGuffin"? What's that?
A rumor or something.
I don't have the slightest idea.
Want me to ask my friends in U-Research?
They might know if it has
something to do with the occult.
That'd be great. I appreciate it.
Is there someone else who has the ability
to preserve their memory from a reset?
Hello?
It's no good. I can't use my ability.
You're unable to sleep?
Yeah. I've been using my ability
too much for the past day.
Is there anything I can help with?
Please talk to me about something.
Anything will do.
Let's talk about something trivial
that will make me sleepy.
Okay, then, what would you
want to be if you were reborn?
Well, a humongous tree would be good.
Why?
As a tree, cats would climb up on my body.
Then they could sit on my branches
and look at things in the distance.
Since I'd be a tall tree,
they'd be able to see everything far away.
The world is peaceful, and it often has clear skies.
So we'll look at that together.
Rain or shine, the cat will climb up on me,
and I'll just support it as it looks
at everything in the distance.
That's a great answer.
Asai, what would you want to be if you were reborn?
I'd want to be God.
I won't put each and every person through trials.
I'll be a God that isn't distrustful of humans.
Ham and Lettuce
Sakura
Milk
I'll give bread to the hungry,
and make sad people happy.
I could even put a rainbow up in the distant
sky for you, the tree, and the cat to see.
I could see just a little.
He ate high-grade cat food and is happy.
So the cat is safe, right?
Yeah, it might've just been picked up.
That's good to hear.
I'll call you later.
Kei, it's been 24 hours since we last did a reset.
Haruki, tell me the time.
59 minutes and 10 seconds. 11... 12...
Save.
It's Thursday, July 13th. The time is 12:59:15.
It seems you still haven't done the second reset.
Well, then, let's eat lunch.
Is the cat okay?
For now, yeah.
Tomorrow morning, let's go to the site
where the cat will get into an accident.
I'll bring black tea in a thermos.
July 14th
Friday
Second Time
Let's have some freshly baked bread together.
Do you think the cat will come?
It's touch and go.
A voice!
I hear a voice.
"Voice"? You mean the cat's?
There's no mistake. It's him!
Um... Nice to meet you, I guess?
Wait!
Upper body. Gravity.
She flew!
You rescued the cat, so isn't that a good thing?
It's a done deal.
What was Murase's objective?
Who cares what it was.
You fulfilled the request.
No one's unhappy.
What more are you asking for?
Then, I don't have to do anything anymore, right?
Just one thing.
When's the last time you saved?
Yesterday, during the day.
Sorry, but for the time being, don't reset.
Not until the very end of the three days, if you can.
Yes, sir.
Which means there might be something else, huh?
This time, we reset to save the cat.
But that reset made something unexpected happen.
What kind of objective did
she have to make that request?
Why did Mr. Tsushima approve of it?
July 15th
Saturday
Second Time
Good morning, Kei!
This time, I've got a message from Friday,
July 14th, which is yesterday for you.
I believe you made an important
appointment before yesterday.
That appointment was reset, you know.
You were going to drink tea with
some cutie on Saturday the 15th.
Um... Morning?
I'm giving you this wake-up call
so that you don't oversleep.
Morning...
And now, it's time for our pop idol,
Haruki Misora, to take the stage!
Next Episode
We found Minami's body.
She was alive before the reset.
He goes by "Hitsuuchi."
He was killed.
I still did something bad.
Do you know what a MacGuffin is?
I decided to kill you both.
We're always simply standing in a rain of eternal sadness
That is why I need that warmth of yours
Life is but a dream we never wake up from
We repeat it over and over, praying for salvation
I kept waiting endlessly for your signal
To make sure you wouldn't disappear all by yourself
Ah, it doesn't matter where I am or what I'm doing
My heart can't go against your will
So I'd follow you even to the ends of the world
I fell in love with you at the dawn of our new world
But we kept pushing the hand of the clock backwards
And lost not only time, but our smiles as well
You're the one who brought it back
And taught me that even lies can be meaningful