A series of events that started with the MacGuffin...
Everything that happened after
I met Souma Sumire two years ago...
Think, think, think.
The current ability rampage case...
That's part of Urachi Masamune's plan.
His goal is to force the Bureau
to play their trump card.
To get rid of all abilities in Sakurada.
What will he do next, then?
What does he need to do
for his plan to proceed smoothly?
I
used
to
say
there
was
a
novel
I
loved
That
I
kept
on
a
shelf
and
never
opened
up
"See,
this
is
how
you
stay
true
to
yourself"
Showing
off,
proud
of
just
being
me
People
around
me
Try
to
sound
mature
and
take
some
wise
words
They
use
them
as
if
those
words
belonged
to
them
Showing
off
the
fake
wisdom
they
had
stolen
So
I
laughed
at
them
But
actually
my
sense
of
self
that
I
kept
on
a
shelf
Was
no
different
from
what
I'd
been
laughing
at
And
the
truth
is
that
I
already
knew
But
no
more
lies,
it's
time
For
my
heart's
reset
I'll
myself
So
I
told
myself
somewhere
deep
down
in
my
heart
Even
if
they
might
talk
behind
my
back
Why
should
I
care
when
I
don't
turn
around?
You
can
choose
To
follow
the
path
someone's
already
walked
But
wouldn't
you
rather
leave
footprints
yourself?
You
believed
your
own
dreams
and
chose
a
path
So
it's
the
right
one,
just
trust
in
your
heart
It'll
all
be
fine
I don't mind you eating while I talk.
I will, thank you.
I wouldn't want the ice cream to melt.
I'd like you to do something for me.
I generally take any job if it's from the Bureau.
It's not a request from the Bureau, though.
It's something personal.
Personal? From you?
I'd like you to use your ability for me.
What would I do?
Doesn't matter.
Something big, but not too big.
Then I'd like you to tell the Bureau
that you used your ability subconsciously.
It's not possible to lie to the Bureau.
I'll take care of that.
I'm sorry, but I can't do that.
Why?
I don't know what you're planning,
and I don't want to lie.
Yesterday, two ability rampage cases took place.
Rampage?
It's very dangerous.
I'm really scared.
I believe you witnessed one of those cases.
Me?
You mean what happened in the supermarket?
That's right.
I'd never laughed so much in my life.
It didn't seem dangerous.
The other one was a traffic accident, though.
One of the drivers had some bad chest trauma.
Fortunately, he made it through with some cracked ribs,
but someone could've easily died.
And how is that related to your request?
The Bureau is currently shaken.
They have to make an important decision,
but they currently can't.
And that is?
This morning, a team that's supposed to deal
with the ability rampage cases had a meeting.
They decided that if a particularly
dangerous ability goes berserk,
they'll use their last resort.
If you say that you couldn't control your ability,
the Bureau will get rid of all abilities in Sakurada.
Let me think for a bit.
I'm not sure if getting rid of abilities is the
right thing to do, so I can't make a decision yet.
I understand that.
But there's not much time left.
Why?
Since multiple people's abilities have
gone berserk for no apparent reason,
it's only natural to restrain dangerous abilities.
Restrain?
We make people unable to use their abilities.
The Bureau is currently going around
town sealing dangerous abilities.
Which means I'll also lose my ability soon.
Actually, your ability is one
that should be sealed immediately.
No matter how much we try to delay it,
the Bureau people will surely
appear within a few hours.
Why do you think all abilities should disappear?
I'm scared of abilities.
I've always been scared of them.
Even though you work for the Bureau?
I started working there exactly because I'm scared.
I didn't want to avert my eyes from
something I know nothing about and fear.
Are you still afraid?
Of course.
I'm the advisor of the Service Club.
It's the club Asai Kei and Haruki Misora are in.
And?
Those two take too much
unnecessary weight on their shoulders.
Their abilities make them do that.
He can't stand being able to
do something and not doing it.
Even though there's no need to,
he ends up doing everything he can.
You should do everything you can, though.
Let's say you can save the world
by sacrificing your own life.
There's no need for you to die.
Just because you happen to have an ability like that
doesn't mean that you should throw
your life away like some hero, that's cruel.
Sakurada's abilities are over the top.
Powers that defy laws of nature
and let you do anything
are way more than humans can handle.
Putting your hope into such things,
and continuing to suffer because
you won't give up, is just too sad.
Even without abilities, people can be happy.
Will Ukawa Sasane help us?
She's trying to save the world,
which means that of course
she's on the side of the weak.
There's no way she could ignore
what someone without an ability says.
Is that why you used Tsushima Shintarou?
He's pretty bright.
He doesn't hesitate to tell convenient lies,
and he agrees with my plan with all his heart.
Is the restriction of abilities progressing?
Without problems, yes.
We still can't find the person
working with Asai Kei, though.
I see. That's fine.
Everything is progressing according to plan.
We'll probably be able to finish everything today.
Agasadai
10 | Sakurada Station
I'm sorry I'm late.
You're five minutes early.
10 | Sakurada Station
I'd like you to search for
a person called Ukawa Sasane.
Agasadai
10 | Sakurada Station
It feels like my ability's lately been
reduced to mere people-finding.
Agasadai
Whatever.
Let's go.
Good morning, Nonoh.
Morning.
I didn't expect to see you here today.
And yet you still came?
Yes.
Is it something related to Asai?
No. I just wanted to kill some time.
I see.
I'm here because I got a request from Asai.
"If you spot Ukawa, please tell me."
"There's a chance she might be a small child,"
"so tell me if you find a girl
that looks like her as well."
"Thank you."
What could it mean that she might be a small child?
Who knows... That's certainly strange.
Have you found her?
Just now, yeah.
Once you leave the shopping district,
there should be a small café.
In front of it, there's a black car parked,
with Ukawa Sasane inside.
Thank you.
Ukawa's been found.
I'm sorry, but I'm going to run there.
Where was she?
Close.
About ten minutes if I run.
You didn't want to tell him anything?
No.
Yes...
Which one is it?
I wanted to tell him something,
but didn't have any words to say.
What? I don't get it.
Something big happened two days ago.
What was it?
It was like happiness of all kinds
came to me in one big bundle.
Oh. So it wasn't anything bad.
The exact opposite.
Haruki...
Even if we didn't have our abilities,
I'd still want to spend time with you.
So, Haruki, I hope we'll spend
plenty of time together.
I'm truly happy.
That's good.
But there's still something I'm not happy about.
I met Kei this morning just for a bit.
I see.
When I parted with him,
I told him "I'll be waiting for you".
And?
And that's all.
I don't understand where the problem is.
I didn't say "goodbye", not even "see you again",
but "I'll be waiting for you".
It was as if I was claiming my right to him,
as if I wanted to tell him that I find
it obvious he'd come back to me.
I chose those words knowing that.
I've been so selfish recently.
I still don't really understand the problem.
Are you unhappy with yourself being selfish?
I...
I want to stay selfish.
Then there shouldn't be any problem.
But I don't want to cause
Kei problems by being selfish.
I see. That's complicated.
But I'm sure that you won't cause
him problems by being selfish.
I hope so.
But the truly selfish thing
about me lies somewhere else.
When I met Kei this morning, he was tired.
I'm sure he was very tired.
I actually wanted to stay with him.
I think I want to be able to naturally stay by his side.
And to be able to help him at any time,
I want to become much more useful.
I don't think it matters if you're
useful or not to stay near someone.
If you want to improve, though, I think you should.
There, I guess.
I can't let Ukawa focus!
Did you know this would happen?
I did.
Why didn't you prevent it?
To show you, of course.
A young man pitied the roadside
trees whose branches were cut.
That was what caused this.
Do you think he used his ability on purpose?
Even if he was conscious of what he was doing,
it doesn't change the problem
happening in this town.
Ukawa.
You're free to judge what is right or wrong.
I understand.
It is indeed dangerous.
Let's eliminate abilities from Sakurada.
Mr. Tsushima! Why?
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE BICYCLES OR MOTORBIKES HERE
Did I make it in time?
You were late.
Please tell me,
is it wrong to drive if you're
going somewhere far away?
No, you can drive as much as you want.
Is it against some rule to use a mobile phone
to talk to your loved ones at any time?
You can use it as much as you want.
Is it wrong to be liked because you're pretty?
Is it wrong to live in luxury if you
were born to a wealthy family?
What's wrong with any of that?
There's nothing wrong about it.
So...
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE BICYCLES OR MOTORBIKES HERE
Why are only the abilities in Sakurada a problem?
Because I feel like they're unfair.
And that's enough to disapprove of something.
Kei.
Become an ordinary high schooler.
Focus on simple worries
like your future, dreams, love.
And one day, give those up and
live a peaceful, happy life as an adult.
That's exactly what I don't want.
Children are always selfish like that.
And adults are always under the impression
that whatever they think is common sense.
Of course.
Life is full of false impressions.
Such nice weather.
Look, when the sky is clear,
even small puddles look beautiful.
Ukawa Sasane used her ability, didn't she?
Yeah, and in a wonderful way.
It was beautiful and blessed and
very problematic for the Bureau.
will be Ukawa  Sasane
Send Tsushima  Shintarou to do the persuading
Make Ukawa  Sasane use her ability
Done
The most dangerous ability user used her ability.
It wasn't controlled.
This will be the end.
Are we doing the right thing?
Where do you see anything wrong?
I'm just pointing out a problem
that this town had from the start.
The Bureau will now finally face this problem,
and make the right decision.
I hate this town.
But I like the name.
This town's name?
"Sakurada."
It's similar to a Spanish word that means "holy".
Sagrada Familia?
That's "holy family".
It's Catalan, I think.
I'll right the holy town.
I'll rearrange it, removing the corrupted parts.
Don't you agree it's a beautiful thing to do?
That's all I wish for.
I want to like this town.
Good job, Kei.
Here's the last request.
Can I borrow your shower?
According to my clairvoyance, I'm apparently
supposed to take a shower in your apartment.
This will be the end.
I'll tell you everything I know, just like I promised.
I'll also make a really good
chicken curry while I'm at it.
We'll eat it together.
Hi, Asai! It's been a while.
Hello.
I have two matters to talk about.
One is related to my job at the Bureau.
The other is something personal.
Which one should I start with?
Doesn't matter.
Let's take care of my job quickly, then.
As a member of the Bureau,
I have to confiscate one of your belongings.
Do you know what it might be?
No, not really.
That's a lie.
It's not good to lie.
I just wasn't sure.
What do you think it is?
A picture, maybe?
Exactly.
It's about Sasano Hiroyuki's ability,
and being able to meet with
a future-seer for just ten minutes.
Could you hand it over?
I can't.
I burned Souma Sumire's picture yesterday.
He's telling the truth.
So you didn't want to give her picture away.
What about the other Witch, then?
The other Witch?
The nameless system.
The first Witch.
Don't you have a picture of her as well?
Yes, I do.
Give it to us, then.
I guess I don't have a choice.
Do you have any other pictures
taken by Sasano Hiroyuki?
I don't.
I only have that one picture.
Then once we collect it,
our job here will be done.
Please wait, I'll bring it.
Wait. Before that, I want to take care
of my personal matter as well.
This is just pure curiosity, you know.
How much did you understand
of what was happening?
I don't know anything.
I've just been guessing.
I'd love to hear your guesses.
You're the culprit.
The culprit?
What culprit?
In the case of four ability rampages
in Sakurada, beginning yesterday.
Those were simply accidents.
There's no culprit or anything.
If you cause an accident on purpose, you're a culprit.
You created an environment in which
an accident would happen with your ability.
Such an interesting story.
Continue.
Yesterday, this girl's ability went
out of control at an intersection.
I was there when it happened, and saw her.
But the girl I saw was around ten years old.
In this picture, she's at least in middle school.
You might be remembering wrong.
Please, it's impossible for me
to remember something wrong.
The same happened with
the boy in the supermarket.
I got a good score on my last test,
and you said you'd buy it then!
The test was last month!
Neither of them was wrong.
But the boy was talking from the
perspective of one month before that.
When people are unaware of their abilities,
they naturally go out of control.
Even if you were right about all that,
how can you blame my ability?
Because I know what it does.
Thank you very much for fixing my keychain.
I always felt bad about it.
I didn't thank you back then.
I told you to go home quickly.
You should've left this town just like I told you to.
So you remember.
Of course.
The nameless system phoned you,
which was enough
to become wary of you.
Back then, I wasn't even aware
of the existence of abilities.
I never thought much about your ability.
But now I understand.
You can rewind the time of an object.
You can recreate the past
of a keychain... or of a human.
Isn't that what your ability does?
It's true that I possess an ability like that.
But you see, you can't draw the conclusion that
I'm the culprit just because I'm able to do that.
That's true.
Asai.
Do you know how the Bureau
will deal with this case?
They'll erase all information
about abilities from Sakurada.
Huh... How do you know that?
I read the written copy of the Script.
I'm aware of what happened during the first year.
Anyone who crosses the border
will forget about abilities.
That's a rule that two ability users created.
And soon this town will become
just like the outside of the border.
It'll be a place where no one is aware of abilities.
With just one exception.
You, Asai.
In those forty years, you were the only exception.
I'd been wondering if you'd
appear here with a knife.
I don't need a knife to do this.
Should I rewind your time to before you were born?
That's impossible.
The most you can rewind with your ability
is most likely around two or three years.
Maybe five, at most.
What makes you think that?
There was only one exception
to the four ability rampage cases.
Ukawa used her ability out of her
own free will, not by losing control.
I heard it's about five years ago
that she acquired her ability.
You couldn't rewind her time that far back.
I see.
What about the two or three years estimate?
The keychain you fixed for me
broke again some time ago.
It was repaired, but there was still a small crack,
and from there, it broke in exactly the same way.
Considering when that crack appeared,
and when you repaired the keychain for me,
I realized you must have rewound
its time to less than three years back.
You figured it all out nicely.
My curiosity is satisfied.
One more thing.
What is it?
How can I turn you into an
ordinary person with no abilities?
If you don't want to use a knife,
even I can't think of any way
to rid me of my memories.
Those words...
are not a lie.
Next Episode
People become kinder to accept themselves.
I'm sure I can't save you.
It's time to wake up from your dream.
Could I borrow your shower?
You haven't told me anything.
Souma Sumire!
I can't help being the same as her.
You're such a fool.
On such a cold dark sky of grey
Rises the sun, which breathes life into it
A scenery so plain and so mundane
And yet it seems to break my heart, it's so dear to me
As the time never stops passing by
You get lost while searching for
Pure like the rays of a morning star
What we all yearn for the most
In what colors bliss is dyed
Struggling against all your past mistakes
At last from the answer you found kindness fills your heart
More beautiful than anything you know
And you find it behind a dark veil of sadness
If I closed my eyes and stopped my thoughts
If it were so simple to just
Lock your own heart
How lovely life would be
But I believe you have the key
To let my soul be free