October 23rd
Monday
Second Time
Hi, Oka Eri.
What a nice morning, don't you think?
Hey there.
It's a terrible morning, honestly.
The middle school is the other way.
Where are you going?
Nowhere.
A villain doesn't show up at school.
I don't think a villain would
cooperate with the government either.
You're on your way to help Urachi, aren't you?
None of your business.
Oka Eri.
I want you to side with me, not him.
You don't understand a thing, do you?
What I want to see is how you lose!
Do you know what Urachi is planning to do?
As long as I win, it doesn't matter at all.
Urachi is trying to rid Sakurada of all abilities.
Everyone will forget about them,
and Sakurada will become an ordinary peaceful town.
That's Urachi Masamune's plan.
I want to prevent that.
I want to protect the abilities.
That's why...
Let me ask you this.
Oka Eri, please help me.
I
used
to
say
there
was
a
novel
I
loved
That
I
kept
on
a
shelf
and
never
opened
up
"See,
this
is
how
you
stay
true
to
yourself"
Showing
off,
proud
of
just
being
me
People
around
me
Try
to
sound
mature
and
take
some
wise
words
They
use
them
as
if
those
words
belonged
to
them
Showing
off
the
fake
wisdom
they
had
stolen
So
I
laughed
at
them
But
actually
my
sense
of
self
that
I
kept
on
a
shelf
Was
no
different
from
what
I'd
been
laughing
at
And
the
truth
is
that
I
already
knew
But
no
more
lies,
it's
time
For
my
heart's
reset
I'll
myself
So
I
told
myself
somewhere
deep
down
in
my
heart
Even
if
they
might
talk
behind
my
back
Why
should
I
care
when
I
don't
turn
around?
You
can
choose
To
follow
the
path
someone's
already
walked
But
wouldn't
you
rather
leave
footprints
yourself?
You
believed
your
own
dreams
and
chose
a
path
So
it's
the
right
one,
just
trust
in
your
heart
It'll
all
be
fine
What?
Do you think I'll help you
just because you lowered your head?
Of course.
You will help me.
Why?
Silly question. Because that's your goal.
Oka Eri, you said you wanted to win.
You said you wanted to prove my weaknesses.
Of course! So—
So you will help me.
What?
Listen, I used a reset.
And?
I was completely cornered by you and Urachi.
I utterly lost, and ran away with a reset.
And now I've come to you for help.
You know what it means, Oka Eri?
What I'm saying is
"I give up, so help me."
What?
I've never seen such a proud surrender!
Okay, Oka Eri. Help me.
That'll be your victory.
You're doing all of this on purpose.
If you pretended to be the same
as two years ago, I'd help you.
Isn't that what you thought?
This is an honest surrender,
from the bottom of my heart.
The purest declaration of my defeat.
Even now,
I still believe what I did two years ago was wrong.
But I—
But for now, I'll accept defeat.
I'll admit that I've gotten weak in the
past two years, just like you're claiming.
So? What will you make me do?
Sorry for the wait.
Okay, let's start.
Start? Start what?
The meeting to decide Sakurada's future.
October 23rd
Monday, 9:30 AM
Second Time
Hm, so it is different.
Before the reset, today at 9:30 AM,
there was a traffic accident caused
by the first ability rampage case.
So we failed?
We did.
He must have done something.
Oka Eri didn't show up either.
That's another change after the reset.
I wonder what Asai is trying to do.
Doesn't he want to protect Sakurada's abilities?
Of course.
But you see...
How will he do it?
If he's not a complete fool,
he should be aware that it's impossible
to keep standing in my way.
I don't think he's a fool.
Then there's only one possibility.
If he's not a fool, he's a genius.
He must have found a way to win against me.
Some way...
That's all.
Any questions?
Ukawa,
I just want to talk with Urachi.
I want both of us to speak from our hearts.
In a way we can shake hands after.
I don't want to fight.
I want a discussion where
we can exchange opinions.
I know that you're both just and
level-headed in your world-saving.
So now that you've learned everything,
if you still want to side with Urachi,
I won't stop you.
But Urachi doesn't leave any room for negotiations,
he decides everything by himself.
So I want you to watch me closely, Ukawa.
I'm quite certain you'll deem my actions righteous.
Will you agree with that or not?
Please see for yourself.
Index
End Call
Hi.
It's been a while, Urachi.
Has it?
Didn't we meet a day or two ago?
I've used a reset, though.
The last time we met was last month.
I wonder, why have you reset?
That much should be obvious.
Something unpleasant happened, that's all.
I see. What exactly?
Index
End Call
There was a traffic accident, for instance.
And abilities disappeared from Sakurada.
So you reset and prevented
the accident from happening.
The cause of the accident
was a little girl using her ability without realizing it.
Urachi.
Do you know what kind of ability the girl had?
No.
End Call
Index
Isn't it written in your notebook?
The ability she used
made people unable to turn towards her.
As a result, a driver who couldn't
look forward caused an accident.
The user must've been really shy.
The girl tripped.
A sidewalk tile was cracked and her foot got stuck.
She must've used her ability because she was embarrassed about tripping in front of people.
I see.
So preventing the girl from tripping
also prevented the accident.
Yes.
I moved some flowers over the crack this morning.
The crack she was supposed to trip over later.
Index
End Call
Asai,
do you realize what you've done?
I prevented an unfortunate accident.
That's certainly admirable.
But you're smart enough
to understand that's not all, right?
End Call
Index
If there was a problem before your reset
big enough to warrant erasing all abilities,
you should've reported that to the Bureau.
That's true.
But instead, you erased the
Bureau's decision with a reset.
That's against the law.
It's a crime you can't talk your way out of.
Right back at you, Urachi.
You intentionally caused a problem.
You set everything up so the Bureau
would make the wrong decision.
That's also a crime you can't talk your way out of.
Isn't that just your guess?
What if I had an objective basis for that?
Then I'd love to hear it.
Index
End Call
There's a girl called Souma Sumire.
She died two years ago,
but came back to life this summer.
And?
She's a future-seer.
End Call
Index
I see. You're so mean.
Clairvoyance is the most highly
regarded ability in Sakurada.
If there's a girl possessing this ability,
even you shouldn't keep that information secret.
But you never told the Bureau.
Because if the Witch had a successor, it'd become
more difficult for you to confuse the Bureau.
You don't have any proof.
Now I do. Because I told you about her.
If you keep Souma's existence
secret from the Bureau,
it's a crime you can't talk your
way out of that I have proof of.
Index
End Call
Urachi, why don't we talk face to face?
Let's meet, then.
What do you want to talk about, though?
I think we're both misunderstanding each other.
I want to clear things up.
End Call
Index
I see.
Let's meet in one hour, then.
That soon?
Is that a problem?
He's making sure we can't prepare for it...
I'd rather meet tonight or tomorrow.
Do you not have time?
I don't. I'm a busy man.
If you can't meet me now,
I won't have time for a while.
Index
09:57
09:58
I see.
Let's meet in an hour, at eleven.
I'll send the location to Index.
Sure.
I'll be waiting.
Index
End Call
I'm going to meet Urachi.
It doesn't seem like it'll just be a simple nice chat,
and we can't save for another nine hours.
Haruki, I'm in a very bad situation right now.
Will you help me?
Yes, of course.
Thanks.
Everyone, please take a while to think.
I'll leave for around thirty minutes.
If you think abilities should exist in Sakurada,
please stay in this room.
I'll be back in thirty minutes, then.
Kei. Don't you want to convince them?
There's no need to.
When I used clairvoyance inside the picture,
I learned a bit about the future.
Does that mean...
I only pretended to give those five a choice.
I know what they're going to choose.
That's why I needed a break.
No matter how honest the words,
if you voice them only after
learning the answer, it's like a lie.
I'm glad.
You always seem to be forcing yourself.
I'm glad you took a break for once.
It's thanks to Souma that
I'm able to talk to Haruki again.
That's... That means the world to me.
The one message Souma risked her life to deliver
protected all I hold dear.
Is that the room?
It's nice to see you again, Urachi, Index.
Oh, and Kagaya.
You have guards outside of the room?
No, his only job is to open and close the door.
Would you like to sing?
We can't sing on duty in the Bureau.
Really?
Asai, let's keep this discussion efficient.
I'll get to the main topic, then.
I'm thinking about preserving
the abilities in this town.
It'd be a shame to throw away those prayers
that are answered with miracles.
I, on the other hand, think abilities
should all disappear from this world.
This fake hope they give only creates tragedies,
like a devil's power.
Our opinions are polar opposites.
That's true.
If there's no room for a compromise,
we can only do as we please now.
I wonder.
Urachi, don't you think erasing abilities
simply means you want to have
absolute control over all the abilities?
That's true.
I agree in that matter.
And?
I'm saying that we're quite similar.
I'm also planning to control all abilities.
I can prove it's possible to control all of this town's
abilities without making people forget about them.
A single human shouldn't have all that power.
I'm aware of that.
Right now, they're not being
controlled by the Bureau's staff,
but by the Bureau's system itself.
Yeah.
The Bureau doesn't allow dictatorship.
But, Urachi,
if the system of the Bureau is absolute,
and even the people there can't oppose it,
doesn't that make it the same as dictatorship?
You're absolutely right, Asai.
It's one of the main problems of the Bureau.
If there's an error in the system itself,
we can't deal with that in any way.
It remains an error for eternity.
I can see that.
Which means, if an ability user
is sacrificed to the system,
they cannot be saved in any way, can they?
In other words, the two ability
users that created the border
won't ever be saved due to how
the system of the Bureau works.
So you're saying, Asai,
that to resolve the problems created by
the Bureau being trapped in its own system,
you'll go as far as to become a dictator?
A ruler with a mind and a will
would create an environment free
of the errors of the current system.
That's more or less correct.
I'd like to add one more thing, though.
What is it?
Even I can't fully trust myself.
I make mistakes sometimes.
What I consider right
might become like one of
the system errors you speak of.
Yeah, it's perfectly normal to fear that.
That's where I want to ask you a favor, Urachi.
I need to be under someone's surveillance.
Not a system,
but a few people who do have emotions
should be watching over me.
I'm considering you to be one of them.
Please. I'd like you to work with me.
Sure. It's a brilliant idea.
I'll fully support you.
He's my most trusted colleague.
I'm sure he'll help you as well.
What's wrong, Asai?
You don't want to shake his hand?
It'll be a pleasure to work with you, Kagaya.
This is the end.
No. It's the beginning.
Director...
I can't remember how to use my ability.
Asai,
you seem to have a lot of amazing friends.
It's not a lot.
But you're right.
They're all such a great help.
It must feel great when everything
proceeds according to your plan, doesn't it?
It's not like that.
You never looked me in the eyes properly.
But of course.
I'd never do something that risky.
When did you realize?
When you set up our meeting at a karaoke place.
I pretended not to notice,
but you needed to prepare a private room.
Two adjacent rooms, in fact.
Yes.
You've gathered your friends in the other room.
Have I?
I sure hope they all consider me their friend.
One of them has an ability to manipulate memories.
What triggers the ability
is looking someone in the eyes
for five seconds, was it?
Exactly.
She's a girl called Oka Eri.
Another one can copy abilities.
Thanks to him, you temporarily gained
the ability to manipulate memories.
That's Sakagami.
But he can only copy an ability
for the time he's touching the target.
Isn't there also someone
who can open a hole in the wall?
There's a hole in the sofa you're sitting on,
and they're touching your back from the other room.
That's Murase.
She's able to erase any object
or phenomenon for five minutes.
Thanks to the efforts of your friends,
you temporarily gained the ability
to manipulate memories.
And so you made Kagaya
forget how to use his ability.
That's right.
You were planning to use it on me, weren't you?
You wanted to manipulate my memories
and force me to listen to you.
How uncivilized,
meddling with people's minds.
But it's all pointless.
Asai.
Your effort is all in vain.
With my ability I can rewind the time of any object.
Rewinding Kagaya to just ten minutes ago
will make him remember how to use his ability.
What just...
See, he's back to normal.
Let me repeat myself, Asai.
This is the end.
The end?
You don't understand a thing.
This is not even the beginning.
Why do you think I'm continuing
this pointless conversation?
Actually, why do you think I didn't warn
Kagaya despite realizing your trap?
It's because I suspected all of it.
The moment you used your abilities against us,
your defeat was assured.
Asai Kei,
you have used an ability against a Bureau
employee to interfere with their duties.
Under the law of the Bureau,
you will now be restrained.
Why do you think you were
the only one who was buying time?
You made such a silly mistake, I can't believe
Souma Sumire had such a hard time opposing you.
I made up my mind two years ago that I'd
oppose the Bureau with all my power, if necessary.
But I wouldn't want to win that way.
Urachi, now everything will begin.
Was that Ukawa Sasane?
That's right.
Within one minute,
she can create whatever she imagines.
I haven't been on a slide since elementary school.
Hey, Kei.
Who is that man in an expensive looking suit?
God,
I can't believe I'm helping
one of my students skip school.
It's unthinkable.
It's because we're in an unthinkable situation.
You, driver.
You're Tsushima Shintarou?
That's right.
This is crazy.
Why are you using someone
from the Bureau as your driver?
I don't know anyone else with a license.
Are you serious?
What in the world is happening?
This is Urachi Masamune.
He's the director of the Bureau's
countermeasures department.
What?!
Nice to meet you, Tsushima.
I've heard you're an excellent
member of the Bureau.
I'm surprised.
I am as well.
Kei, can you explain yourself?
I entrapped and kidnapped him.
Spare me the jokes, I want to hear the truth.
This is the truth.
I am currently being kidnapped by Asai.
And, Tsushima...
You're his accomplice.
Next Episode
Do you really think you can convince me?
Let's take a classic hostage.
He got rid of you.
You have to accept all the despair and trouble!
Stop! Stop, please!
and live without turning
your eyes away from reality!
You're the one turning your eyes away from reality.
On such a cold dark sky of grey
Rises the sun, which breathes life into it
A scenery so plain and so mundane
And yet it seems to break my heart, it's so dear to me
As the time never stops passing by
You get lost while searching for
Pure like the rays of a morning star
What we all yearn for the most
In what colors bliss is dyed
Struggling against all your past mistakes
At last from the answer you found kindness fills your heart
More beautiful than anything you know
And you find it behind a dark veil of sadness
If I closed my eyes and stopped my thoughts
If it were so simple to just
Lock your own heart
How lovely life would be
But I believe you have the key
To let my soul be free