October 24th
Tuesday
It's possible that Oka Eri will come to your place.
If you become unable to reset, please tell me.
Compose
To:
Haruki Misora
add more recipients
Subj:
Re:
It's possible that Oka Eri will
come to your place. If you
become unable to reset,
please tell me. Also, once you
read this message, delete it
immediately.
Send
Save Draft
Send Later
Also, once you read this message,
delete it immediately.
Inbox
Haruki Misora
Re:
Compose
Haruki Misora
Re:
Compose
Haruki Misora
Re:
Refresh
Compose
I understand.
Inbox
Subject:  Re:
I understand.
What are you doing now, Kei?
Reply
Reply to all
Forward
Delete
What are you doing now, Kei?
I was tidying up my room.
Inbox
Haruki Misora
Re:
Compose
Refresh
Haruki Misora
Re:
Subject:  Re:
Have you finished what you
had to do?
Reply
Reply to all
Forward
Delete
Have you finished what you had to do?
I'm done with most of it,
now I just have one more thing to do.
Will you be able to finish everything today?
Is it okay if I keep messaging you?
It's been a while, Kei.
Come in.
It really has been ages.
I wouldn't mind you coming more often.
I also wouldn't mind that,
but I have a lot going on, you see.
I
used
to
say
there
was
a
novel
I
loved
That
I
kept
on
a
shelf
and
never
opened
up
"See,
this
is
how
you
stay
true
to
yourself"
Showing
off,
proud
of
just
being
me
People
around
me
Try
to
sound
mature
and
take
some
wise
words
They
use
them
as
if
those
words
belonged
to
them
Showing
off
the
fake
wisdom
they
had
stolen
So
I
laughed
at
them
But
actually
my
sense
of
self
that
I
kept
on
a
shelf
Was
no
different
from
what
I'd
been
laughing
at
And
the
truth
is
that
I
already
knew
But
no
more
lies,
it's
time
For
my
heart's
reset
I'll
myself
So
I
told
myself
somewhere
deep
down
in
my
heart
Even
if
they
might
talk
behind
my
back
Why
should
I
care
when
I
don't
turn
around?
You
can
choose
To
follow
the
path
someone's
already
walked
But
wouldn't
you
rather
leave
footprints
yourself?
You
believed
your
own
dreams
and
chose
a
path
So
it's
the
right
one,
just
trust
in
your
heart
It'll
all
be
fine
It's really nice and tidy here.
Because I don't have much stuff.
Also, I did some quick vacuuming earlier.
I could have cleaned your room for you.
That would be kinda awkward.
Want a coffee or something?
Coffee does sound nice,
but I'd like to make some chicken curry first.
I bought this just for that purpose.
What is it?
Something you can't cook without.
How is it?
Looks like something you'd wear in home ec class.
I can imagine handing out
cookies you made looking like that.
What's that supposed to mean?
Does that mean I don't really look housewife-y?
It means you look like a normal girl.
It suits you well.
Sure, if you say so.
Okay, let's make that chicken curry.
CURRY ROUX
MILD
RICH TASTE
yogurt
I think I'll tell you a story.
What kind of story will it be?
First, let's see...
A story of a certain ability user and his child.
I hope abilities disappear soon.
They won't.
Because we're here, you see.
Don't you want them to disappear, Dad?
Of course not.
Our goal is to create a town where
abilities can exist without any issues.
Why?
I used to hate abilities.
They're useful, but there's
too many problems involved.
I used to think it'd be wiser to get rid of them.
Yeah.
But I realized something when you were born.
There's something to gain from our abilities.
I want to make this town a place
where wonderful miracles happen.
That's my goal.
Miracles shouldn't happen!
People should be happy with their own power!
You're a very strong child.
But I believe that a world
that allows people to be weak
is more rightful than a world
where everyone is strong.
A place where weak people
are saved by handy miracles
couldn't be wrong, don't you think?
I'm sorry.
I'm making you go through something sad.
I don't really care.
I can't allow anyone to become
a sacrifice to abilities, though.
Masamune...
I'm sure I can't save you, Dad.
But I want to make sure
no one like you is ever born again.
You have a very strong sense of rightfulness.
But I want you to listen and understand.
I really love you.
You're my pride and my hope.
But I'm sometimes scared.
Why?
Because you're a very strong child.
You right everything that is wrong.
What's scary about it?
We're way weaker than you might think.
We're weak, and so we make mistakes.
But there's some happiness to gain from that.
I'm sure you'd right even that, though.
You're very strong.
Now you need to learn how it is to be weak.
What's there to gain from being weak?
Once you learn how it is to be weak,
you become more forgiving.
There's no need to allow people to make mistakes.
It's not about people. It's about yourself.
People become kinder to accept themselves.
Urachi... am I correct?
Who are you?
I've practically turned your father into stone...
I'm sorry.
There's no need to apologize.
What you did was right.
Take pride in it.
There was a need for my father
to continue using his ability forever.
It's like you saved the world.
If my father really believed that abilities are rightful,
he should have exposed them to the whole world.
The reason he hid them from the world
is probably that he was aware of their dangers.
We can't pretend that wasn't it.
Abilities won't save weak people.
It's the opposite.
If we want to protect the weak,
we should get rid of abilities.
RICH TASTE
yogurt
yogurt
That's Urachi Masamune's story.
Now I understand.
Urachi hates abilities with every fiber of his being.
Are you okay with that?
No, I'm not.
I love Sakurada's abilities.
Yeah, seems good.
We should move onto the main topic now.
That sounds as if this story
wasn't related to it at all.
Of course it wasn't.
I couldn't care less about Urachi.
It was just a way to kill time
while making the chicken curry.
That's mean.
Could I borrow your shower?
So you really were planning to take a shower?
That's why I'm here.
Inbox
Subject:  Re:
Could we have dinner
together tomorrow?
Reply
Reply to all
Forward
Delete
Could we have dinner together tomorrow?
Of course.
I'll look for a good restaurant.
Thinking of anything particular?
Come here. To the door.
Why?
Didn't I promise you?
That I'd tell you everything I was keeping secret.
I can hear it later.
You should take your time washing yourself.
There's nothing to wash.
I took a bath right before coming here.
Why would you take a bath before taking a shower?
It's very simple.
I couldn't go meet with the person I love being all sweaty, could I?
What are you going to tell me?
What do you want to know?
I'll answer any question.
Say, Souma.
Why did you die?
Haven't I answered that already before?
I didn't want to become like the Witch.
Trapped by the Bureau forever, you know.
You could have just left Sakurada two years ago.
I had to stay in Sakurada
to execute my plan, you see.
That doesn't change anything.
You could have left and come back two years later.
The reason...
The real reason you died was to stop
being Souma Sumire, wasn't it?
I've been thinking about it all night.
I'm still thinking about it.
But I can't see any other reason you could have had.
That's why the instructions I've been getting
were from the Souma Sumire who died two years ago.
And that's not you.
Because you don't consider yourself Souma Sumire.
You haven't told me anything.
That's correct, Kei.
Urachi asked me this question:
"Will you try to foil my plan?"
I had to answer that I wouldn't.
In front of Index, you see.
I had to say "No, I won't do anything",
and it had to be the truth.
So you died as a preparation for that.
Yeah.
The one opposing Urachi's plan is Souma Sumire.
The one giving you instructions
was also Souma Sumire.
I don't consider myself Souma Sumire, though.
I'm her swampman.
Just a system without a name or identity.
That's why I could honestly say
that I wouldn't do anything.
Urachi is certainly something,
but he missed this one little thing.
If he'd used "Souma Sumire"
instead of "you" in his question,
I would have had to tell him everything.
I had to bet on that.
But I made sure that he wouldn't be able
to call me by my name before that.
I helped him on the condition he
wouldn't investigate into my identity.
How can you talk about it like that?
That's because, you see...
You're the only one who understands me, Kei.
I managed to deceive Urachi,
but I'd never be able to deceive you.
You think a lot about Misora,
but I know that you thought even more about me.
Souma Sumire!
You're such a fool.
I'm not Souma Sumire anymore.
I'm just an android without a name
that resembles a human.
It must be from Haruki.
Inbox
Subject:  Re:
You don't have to look for a
restaurant. I'll make some chicken
curry at your place.
Inbox
Subject:  Re:
Sorry, on second thought, I'd rather
eat out.
You can reply, you know.
I'm talking with you right now.
Haruki can wait.
Is that so?
Such trust.
Souma.
What are you trying to achieve?
You're asking now?
Don't you already know the answer well?
My goal is to foil Urachi Masamune's plan.
No, not mine.
It's the goal of Souma Sumire,
who died two years ago.
You're lying.
You were cooperating with Urachi.
It was Souma Sumire's choice
whose time to rewind when
to make accidents happen.
You had to accelerate Urachi's plan.
A reset can only erase three days worth of time.
If his plan didn't fit within that time,
we wouldn't be able to resolve it.
You gave me a chance.
I was only after efficiency.
It was the most efficient to use you
to foil Urachi Masamune's plan.
Efficient? No way.
Your actions are far from being efficient.
If foiling Urachi's plan was your sole goal,
you could have told me everything
at the very beginning.
That way, I could have acted way more accurately.
It was to deal with Index's ability...
Didn't you already die two years ago for that?
Even if you couldn't tell me now,
your self two years ago shouldn't
have had any restrictions.
There wouldn't be any problems
even if you had told me sooner.
You had an entirely different reason
to keep all of this secret.
Two days ago, I was truly happy.
I was able to talk with Haruki about something
really important on the school roof.
I'm sure we still have a long way to go.
But something had definitely changed.
I think I hadn't ever been
that happy in my life before.
And yesterday too,
when I picked up trash with Haruki,
when we ate crepes together,
went shopping together at that supermarket,
it was so fun, I couldn't have been happier.
Thank you, Souma.
You protected my happiness.
I mean... I didn't have any other choice.
I'm stupid, aren't I?
Don't you think I'm a fool?
The reason I didn't say anything for so long
was to wait for the person I love
to tell another girl how much he loves her.
I never understood Souma's intentions.
I've always known that.
But only now, I understand.
She had to take a shower.
Because she knew she'd cry.
You know, Kei. There's someone I absolutely hate.
She's so unfair.
She's the only one who doesn't suffer.
Pretending it's for your sake, she escapes
into a position where she doesn't get hurt.
All the pain is forced onto me.
She's the only one who has it easy.
Do you know who I'm talking about?
She was so stupid, so selfish, and extremely weak.
Please... I want you to...
I want you to forgive Souma Sumire.
You really are the only one who understands me.
I can't forgive her for creating me.
But you know, Kei...
I can't help being the same as her.
I'll always wish for your happiness alone.
How is it?
It's very good.
It's also somehow nostalgic.
A lot of tomatoes,
and just a little bit of yogurt was the key.
My mother used to add yogurt to make sure
it wouldn't be too spicy when I was young.
She kept reducing the amount,
but there was always a little bit of it in our curry.
But it's a bit different, isn't it?
That's true. Any particular reason?
No, there isn't.
I just couldn't recreate it.
I used my ability many, many
times to make this curry.
But no matter how hard I tried,
I couldn't find a future where
you'd say it tastes the same.
That's so strange. I wonder why?
Who knows.
Even clairvoyance can't
compete with motherly love.
I'm sure that's the only reason.
Thank you.
It was really good.
But of course.
I made it with lots of love.
I've decided to protect abilities.
To borrow your words,
I'm planning to rule over all abilities in Sakurada.
Like the MacGuffin was supposed to allow.
I'll rule over them, use them all as I please,
and proceed towards the goal
of making Sakurada's abilities
a miracle that brings happiness.
I'm sure you'll do well.
You're my protagonist, after all.
Can I leave the dishes to you?
Of course.
I'll be leaving, then.
It'll start raining soon.
Could I borrow an umbrella, maybe?
When will it rain?
In about ten minutes.
I see.
Should I go with you?
No, I'm fine.
It's dangerous for a girl
to walk outside at night alone.
Only if it's a normal girl who doesn't see the future.
Well, goodbye.
That won't do.
Huh?
You've only said "goodbye" to me once before.
Two years ago, at the bus stop in the rain.
See you again then, Kei.
Come in.
We're from the Bureau.
What about my mother?
Another member of the Bureau
is explaining the matter to her.
What is it?
It's a bit difficult to explain.
It won't take long, though.
If you don't move, there won't be any problems.
Look...
We're done already.
She still alive?
Of course.
She was just sleeping during
the time I rewound her to.
Two years and seven months ago.
What are you doing now?
Oh, it's nothing.
Okay, I need to be going now.
I need you to do me a favor.
Well, of course you do.
An ambulance will come here soon.
They'll quarantine her in the hospital.
And?
I want you to accompany them.
Once she wakes up,
could you make her forget how to use her ability?
And will this really be a win against Asai?
Of course.
He'd hate that more than anything else.
I'm counting on you.
Rewinding Haruki Misora to before
she met Asai Kei for the first time...
I wonder how much of this
Asai was expecting to happen.
Oka Eri.
You're cooperating with Urachi, aren't you?
Asai's voice?
I'm sure you don't know their goal, though.
Listen, what they're planning to do
is to erase all the abilities from Sakurada.
You don't have to believe me.
If you doubt them even the slightest, please.
Just don't take away Haruki Misora's reset ability.
Please, Oka Eri.
I've been driven into a corner.
I need you to help me.
He's so unfair.
"I need you to help me" is against the rules.
Would there be any better way
of winning than helping him?
Is it painful to look at them?
Yes, of course.
You shouldn't care this much.
You did the right thing.
Take pride in it.
Yes, I'm aware.
Is it not painful for you to meet them?
Of course it is.
But I'm meeting my mother for
the first time in ages, so I'm also happy.
My mother turned into stone
eight years after my father...
The day I turned twenty,
you stopped her time with your ability.
Today, she will live again.
She'll be human again.
It's a happy event.
Please.
It's time to wake up from your long dream.
I'll reset Sakurada.
Next Episode
I don't remember you.
Seems like today is the beginning of a new world.
Is it like the hypothesis that
the world began five minutes ago?
I've done a terrible thing to my mother and father.
I want you to remember everything.
Please, remember!
I can't.
Haruki!
I can't remember you!
It's time to reset!
On such a cold dark sky of grey
Rises the sun, which breathes life into it
A scenery so plain and so mundane
And yet it seems to break my heart, it's so dear to me
As the time never stops passing by
You get lost while searching for
Pure like the rays of a morning star
What we all yearn for the most
In what colors bliss is dyed
Struggling against all your past mistakes
At last from the answer you found kindness fills your heart
More beautiful than anything you know
And you find it behind a dark veil of sadness
If I closed my eyes and stopped my thoughts
If it were so simple to just
Lock your own heart
How lovely life would be
But I believe you have the key
To let my soul be free