This is Mr. Sasano's ability...
The world within photographs...
It was torn from outside of the angle of view, huh?
The
flow
of
time
makes
a
continuous
sound
(so
close
your
eyes
and
feel
it)
It's
a
melody
that
invites
the
coming
future
(which
begins
today)
What
kind
of
world
is
waiting
for
me?
(Who
is
calling
me?)
I
tried
asking
myself
for
an
answer
(in
my
heart)
Here,
in
the
middle
of
ideals
and
reality
(I'm
searching
for
them)
The
hands
of
the
clock
are
being
constantly
moved
(as
I
turn
them
back)
I'll
do
anything
to
erase
all
sadness
(over
and
over
again)
Even
if
it
means
going
back
down
the
passage
of
dark
stairs
(to
recreate
the
past)
There's
something
I
want
to
protect
no
matter
what
(I'll
protect
you)
I'll
say
that
out
loud
(and
try
resetting
again)
Believing
that
fate
will
bring
us
together
again
This is no fun!
Don't you have anything to say?
You know, something like "Please give back Asai!",
while you're screaming and crying.
I don't need to worry about Kei.
I don't believe that Kei would ever lose to you.
Wake up and smell the coffee a bit more!
NO TRESSPASSING
So, where's Asai?
That's more than enough. It's been five seconds.
We're friends.
We've been the bestest of friends for a long time.
Hey there, Misora!
Good evening.
When did we first meet?
Well...
...earlier today.
Her memory hasn't changed!
We're friends, right?
A memory like that exists,
NO TRESSPASSING
but it's fake.
What makes you think that?
NO TRESSPASSING
Kei says so.
He predicted the pattern
in your memory manipulation
and pre-recorded his words to negate it.
I will keep listening to Kei's voice forever.
Between my memory and Kei's words,
it's clear which one I should believe.
What the hell? That's ridiculous!
NO TRESSPASSING
But it's the truth.
In that case, I'll take all of your memories!
Full body. Ability.
What?!
With that, I'm immune to all abilities.
Your memory manipulation included.
Why are you here?!
Asai asked me to.
He expected Haruki to get attacked,
so he wanted me to stage a dramatic rescue.
But that's just weird!
I've been watching my surroundings
from the top of this lighthouse!
I would have known if you came!
I had been sticking close behind you.
Before you reached the top of the lighthouse,
I was already hiding in here.
That's all. Any questions?
I'm good. I got it.
I'll take you down, too!
You used your ability again on Haruki earlier.
Since that erased the previous memory-altering effect,
Haruki regained her ability to reset.
He already accomplished his goal.
All that's left is for us to go straight home.
Everything went exactly as Asai planned,
from start to finish.
I'll say this again,
but Asai Kei is way stronger than you.
I don't like it.
What's that supposed to mean?
Exactly that.
I don't like Asai being stronger than me.
I'll deny it. I can't accept it!
That's the source of your downfall.
I'm speaking from experience, so I already
know it's pointless to go up against Asai.
You were outclassed before
the battle had even begun.
If we're not fighting yet, then I haven't lost.
NO TRESSPASSING
It's fine if that's the way you wanna think.
I've had enough. I'm going home.
I need power... something stronger!
Everything's done and over with.
Should we reset?
If you say you're fine with the way things
are now, then I don't want to reset.
I want to remember losing my ability
and your promise to get it back for me.
Okay. Let's save.
Thank you very much.
Save.
Save. It's August 8th, 9:28:55 p.m.
What are you doing?
I was looking at the cherry blossoms.
Cherry blossoms?
But you won't see them by looking at your feet.
That's true.
I saw the tree first.
When I saw the cherry tree covered in flower petals,
I thought it was so beautiful.
And then, the wind swept them away.
The petals were fluttering in the wind,
and I found that even more beautiful.
I was happy for some reason,
so I continued to watch them twirl in the sky.
As the petals landed on the ground,
I finally noticed something.
I wondered why they were still so beautiful,
despite stepping on them.
Were you sad about that?
I'm not really sure.
But I wanted to cry a little.
Say, do you think this is beautiful?
No, I don't.
Me neither.
I'm sure that's why I felt like crying.
It's okay to cry.
Yeah. Thank you.
Can you tell me a story?
What kind of story would you like?
I'd like a story about two people
who fulfill their promise to meet again.
Let's see...
There was once a witch in a faraway land.
Is she good or bad?
She's a good witch.
But everyone thought she was evil.
The witch flies through the sky on a broom
to see her beloved who
she promised to reunite with.
It's been 50 years since then, huh?
August 9th
Wednesday
Second Time
In the previous timeline,
there were two things that happened today.
The first was that Mr. Sasano said
he wanted me to give him the MacGuffin,
so I accepted his request to restore the ability he lost.
And the other thing was being
summoned by the Witch.
Those two are hiding something.
At the very least, Mr. Sasano is lying.
It's possible to enter his photos
without the use of any ability.
He doesn't need the MacGuffin.
Come see me right away.
The other two are presents.
"Come see me right away.
The other two are presents."
Come see me right away.
The other two are presents.
This is it.
Are you... Asai Kei?
Yes. I came here through Mr. Sasano's ability.
Why?
I was under the impression that you summoned me.
This is a future I didn't see.
That means I betrayed myself, huh?
What do you mean?
I believe the me in some other photo
made arrangements for you to come here.
I'm sure it was to make my plan fail.
Your plan?
Yes. I'm currently working toward one plan.
I will be confined by the Bureau
for the next 28 years.
And those years represent
how much time I have left.
I accepted that I would die while
being confined by the Bureau.
But...
I decided to escape from the Bureau and reunite
with my beloved just for the final week of my life.
However, the Bureau won't allow
me to be free for even a week.
That's why...
Sorry. I decided to use you both.
Me and who?
A girl named Oka Eri.
She wanted an ability far greater
than the ones you two possess.
She has her eyes dead set
on the ability to know the future,
which is why I decided to escape
that building with Oka Eri's help.
Is that even possible?
When I'm closer to death,
my security will become lax.
That means, with Oka Eri's memory manipulation,
your security will fall apart.
But if I wait for her to come, I won't make it in time.
By then, I'll already be on the verge
of death and be unable to walk.
That's why I needed to speed things up.
By losing to you,
she'll be determined to take me away.
On August 9th at 9:18 p.m,
Oka Eri will appear before me.
And by telling me about that,
you're betraying yourself.
When I'm abducted, she'll confront the Bureau.
In Sakurada, there is only tragedy
for those who oppose the Bureau.
Thank you for telling me.
I told you because it has nothing to do with me.
After all, the one who will
reunite with him is not me.
I'm not the real one.
I couldn't stand the guilt of doing
it for the other me, that's all.
Farewell.
If things continue this way,
the Witch will be able to escape,
but Oka Eri will become an enemy of the Bureau.
If I stop Oka Eri, the Witch will remain
confined and pass away in a week.
I need to find a way to save the Witch
without anyone turning against the Bureau
and let her reunite with Mr. Sasano.
This is Sasano.
Nice to meet you. I am Asai Kei.
You've heard about me from the Witch, right?
Sorry. I did something bad to you.
Sorry.
Thank you for sending me the photos.
What's your situation?
The red-eyed girl came by again
and manipulated my memories.
She made me send her all the pictures
I took with my ability.
But I didn't have any photos left at home.
I see.
But that means you remembered how
to use your ability in exchange, right?
Yes, most likely.
What are you going to do now, Mr. Sasano?
I'll try asking the Bureau to let me see her.
I can't think of anything else.
I see. Please let me help you out, then.
I heard from the Witch within the picture.
Oka Eri successfully infiltrates the building and
will come in contact with the Witch at 9:18 p.m.
So basically, if we follow right behind her,
we'll be able to go in, too.
It's 9:10 p.m.
She's here.
Let's go.
Please take a picture of this corridor.
We won't have guns pointed at us
the instant the door opens, will we?
I really don't think they would have guns.
If the Bureau seriously prepared security guards,
we wouldn't be able to come this far.
It's 9:18 p.m.
Is this okay?
No. A Bureau staff member is photographed.
He'll be a nuisance within the photo.
One, two, three...
Hold it right there, Oka Eri.
Asai?!
Oka Eri, I've come to stop you.
That's unnecessary. We'll handle everything here.
Hurry up, hurry up!
That's not going to work. Please let us talk to her.
Stop right there.
Full body. Ability.
Do you understand what it means
to use an ability against us?
Of course. But we couldn't think of another way.
The Bureau won't forgive you.
Would you be able to forget
everything for us, if possible?
That's impossible.
I see.
Upper body. Gravity.
Reset.
August
th
Wednes
day
Tues
Wednes
Third Time
It's August 8th, 9:28:55 p.m.
Looks like we've reset.
Murase disappeared.
Let's go meet up with her. I know where she is.
What are you thinking?
So this means these photos
didn't get reset, just like me.
August 9th
Wednesday
Third Time
You will escape from here in a different way.
Please call me as quickly as possible.
I'll bring these photos with me.
We reset.
The things you planned for tonight will fail.
I knew you'd reset, and I knew
you'd come to my rescue for sure.
But that's no good.
Why?
You're too weak. Eventually,
even I will become your weakness.
You can't be weak.
When did you come back from a reset?
Yesterday night.
It still hasn't been 24 hours!
You're not supposed to see me at this time.
Save properly and take various precautions.
You have to appear composed
enough to piss me off.
It's true that I'm currently defenseless,
but there's no danger.
You won't do anything to me when I'm defenseless.
You're so unfair.
No matter how hard I try to fight
and beat you, you won't fight back.
That's just how it is.
You know, I tried really hard for two years.
I changed the way I talked, changed my wardrobe,
and even bought colored contacts.
I thought I'd see everything around me
in a different color if I wore them.
Did your view change?
Not in the slightest.
There's no color on the colored
contacts where your pupils are.
But I like them.
When I look at the mirror,
I feel like the reflection isn't me.
I see. I'm glad that you like it.
Tsushima Shintarou
Talking
There's someone who wants to see you.
I believe a Bureau staff member
will be picking you up today at 4 p.m.
Understood.
Talking
Sooner or later, I'm going to find
an extravagant way to beat you.
Okay. I'll be waiting.
Don't!
Be afraid instead.
I'm from the Bureau.
I've come to pick you up.
It's been a long time.
Or should I say, nice to meet you?
May I ask what your name is?
I'm sorry. I don't have one.
I'm not sure how I should address you, then.
I'm an entity that essentially needs no name.
Call me "Witch," if you must.
Yes, ma'am.
Come a bit closer.
Bend down a little.
I wanted to see you, Asai Kei.
I had always wanted to apologize to you.
Would you be able to fall in love with a stone?
No, I probably can't.
Try thinking about the person you love, then.
Let's imagine that girl as a pebble—
one that neither speaks nor moves.
Imagine that she's a cold pebble that can only think.
Could you fall in love with it?
My first answer was wrong.
I'm sure I can fall in love even with a stone.
What would you love about the stone?
Well, our past and our lifetime of memories.
I think the same goes for me, too.
What I love might be an ordinary stone.
Is that a sad thing?
Yes, very sad.
I don't know if I actually love a person.
Maybe I just want to believe
that I still love that someone.
All I have is the past,
so I might just be in love with that past.
Your beloved can't be an ordinary stone.
If I still do love a person,
I want to make sure of it, if possible.
Looks like time's up.
Is there anything you'd
like to ask me before you go?
Why are you a witch?
It was something I heard a long time ago.
A story of a witch who rode on a broom,
flying through the sky to knock
on the window of her beloved's room.
I've been longing to do that.
What are you going to do now?
I'll leave Sakurada, forget about my ability,
and live out the rest of my life.
It'll just be a week, though.
Do you want to know your own future?
Yes.
Even if it's something painful?
Yes, please.
The witch, riding a broom,
knocks on the window of her beloved's room.
What happens next?
He hastily opens the window.
And then...
the two of them find happiness.
You're going to be involved in something big...
Something involving my successor.
Does such a person exist?
The Bureau has been looking
for one for a long time now.
But no matter how much they looked,
they couldn't find anyone with the ability to see the future.
However,
you know someone who does possess it.
You've met that person a little over two years ago.
Is your successor...
Is the future-seeing ability user a girl?
Yes.
A slender girl with short hair, big eyes,
and about the age of a middle schooler.
Yes.
Is it the girl who died two years ago?
Correct. And you will run into her again.
Next Episode
I can't use my reset ability.
I avoided Haruki.
Reset.
Want some Kit Kats?
You can at least check and see if what
I'm saying is true or false, right?
I can make a hole in the Moon.
She won't be coming to the rooftop anymore.
I'm afraid of being hated by Kei.
We're always simply standing in a rain of eternal sadness
That is why I need that warmth of yours
Life is but a dream we never wake up from
We repeat it over and over, praying for salvation
I kept waiting endlessly for your signal
To make sure you wouldn't disappear all by yourself
Ah, it doesn't matter where I am or what I'm doing
My heart can't go against your will
So I'd follow you even to the ends of the world
I fell in love with you at the dawn of our new world
But we kept pushing the hand of the clock backwards
And lost not only time, but our smiles as well
You're the one who brought it back
And taught me that even lies can be meaningful