Kurakawa Mari died seven years ago.
She died?
When the doctor performed a C-section on Mari's
mother, Mari had already stopped breathing.
Mari, if Kurakawa Mari died,
then who might you be?
I'm Kurakawa Mari...
What is the meaning of this, Kei?
Mari, you were created
with someone's ability, right?
The flow of time makes a continuous sound
I'm pretty sure your mother gained
the ability when her real daughter died.
The ability to create a clone of her dead daughter.
It's a melody that invites the coming future
You're the clone, right?
What kind of world is waiting for me?
Tsushima...
I work for the Bureau.
I came to pick up Kurakawa Mari.
Now, let's go.
I tried asking myself for an answer
Go where?
Where she needs to be.
Will Mari's mother be there?
She won't be coming back anymore.
Here, in the middle of ideals and reality
She left Mari in the Bureau's care and left this town.
Was it to forget Mari's existence?
Yes.
I see. That's terrible to hear.
The hands of the clock are being constantly moved
What is that supposed to mean?
Somewhere along the line, Mari's mother stopped
being able to believe that Mari was her own child.
I'll do anything to erase all sadness
"Somewhere along the line," meaning what?
Mari's father could never accept
Mari as his own daughter.
He took off after putting up with it for three years.
Even if it means going back down the passage of dark stairs
It was around that time.
It was the Bureau that suggested
she should leave Sakurada, right?
The ability to create lives is something
that must be kept under wraps.
There's something I want to protect no matter what
If she leaves Sakurada, then her memories
about her ability will disappear.
What are you planning to do with Mari?
She'll grow up as a normal child.
I'll say that out loud
The Bureau decided it was best
to keep a problematic ability secret.
Believing that fate will bring us together again
To achieve that, they took away the mother's memories
of Mari, and turned a little girl into a victim.
That means you chose to look at the bigger picture.
That's the Bureau.
Do you really think that's right?
There's nothing right about a child crying.
Was it something you had
to choose despite it being wrong?
It's not like that.
It isn't something we should have chosen,
and that's why it's wrong.
You're contradicting yourself.
What do you want to do?
I don't want to do anything.
I don't even want to get involved in this mess.
But you are involved.
My job means doing things I don't want to do.
We're done here.
I'm taking Mari with me.
You're not the one who gets to choose that.
You choose, Haruki.
Are you going to hand Mari over to the Bureau?
Asai Kei, please let go of him.
And you're okay with that?
Yes.
Based on the circumstances, I've determined
that Mari has to be taken care of by the Bureau.
But Haruki isn't able to help anyone.
Haruki Misora, can you really be that indifferent?
Of course not.
Then choose.
Choose with your own feelings.
Not on a passing whim, but as a necessity.
Have your own, clear will.
You have to choose a side.
I want to help Mari, but...
If that's what you want, then let's help her.
Is it possible?
With our abilities, yeah.
With the memories we gained today,
we'll aim for a happier ending.
We can redo this.
Haruki, it's time to reset.
August 1
th
Satur
day, 03:15 PM
Reset.
Fri
Satur
Thurs
Fri
Second Time
Haruki, you need to remember your feelings.
Is that so?
Yeah, so let's begin.
Okay.
I'm starting now.
Let's go.
I remembered all of the sadness
I was supposed to feel soon.
Let's go erase the girl's tears.
We'll rid this world of such things.
That's the plan that I came up with.
Would you help us out, too, Sakagami?
Uh, no... I can't.
It will be in defiance of the Bureau, wouldn't it?
It'll be okay if you get permission, right?
As things stand, Mari's mother will be leaving
Sakurada on Saturday, which is in two days.
We need to solve everything before then.
But still... I can't defy the Bureau, sorry.
Do we need him no matter what?
Yeah. I want his ability at all costs.
Sakagami Yousuke won't use his ability for us
unless he has the Bureau's permission, right?
That's his rule.
You use the word "rule" often.
Would you tell me what your rules are?
Among my rules are three big ones.
I basically decide on things
according to these three rules.
What's the first rule?
If something has a probability of causing a strongly
negative effect on my surroundings, I refuse.
Which means you won't cause trouble for anyone.
How about the second?
I'll agree to a proposition so long
as it doesn't violate the first rule.
In other words, you'll follow someone's instructions.
And the third rule?
When I come across someone crying,
I use my reset ability.
Haruki, do you know the Three Laws of Robotics?
No.
The First Law states that a robot
may not harm a human being.
The Second Law states that a robot must
obey orders given to it by a human being.
And the Third Law states that a robot
must protect its own existence.
The first and second laws are exactly like your rules.
But the third one is different.
That's what's wonderful.
What does that mean?
It means you're a human being.
I don't really follow.
Well, it's fine if you don't.
There's a Zeroth Law in the three laws for androids.
There wasn't one at first, but it was
added later when it was deemed necessary.
Can you guess what it is?
No, I have no idea.
Try thinking about it.
If you were to make a Zeroth rule for yourself,
what kind of rule would it be?
What do you want to do with Haruki Misora?
What do you mean?
You've become interested in Haruki Misora.
You thought her personality was the ideal good.
She doesn't care about protecting herself,
her image, or her ego,
and she doesn't even want to be loved by others.
She's pure like purity itself.
She's so purely good that she
doesn't even realize it herself.
She's the most beautiful being.
And yet, you're trying to give her feelings.
That's right.
You're contradicting yourself.
You yourself are trying to destroy the very
thing you believe is the most beautiful.
You may be right.
So why?
I don't know why. It's just a whim.
You're a liar.
You won't believe me?
I believe you from the bottom of my heart.
You wish for Haruki to become a normal
girl who can laugh and cry, don't you?
Even as far as putting her own
happiness above being your ideal.
It's just more convenient that way.
For getting my hands on her reset ability, I mean.
You really are such a liar.
Are you okay? Are you feeling sick?
I wonder...
I might not be okay.
Haruki, it's time to save.
August 13th
Friday, 08:15 PM
Second Time
Save.
Will everything really be all right?
That guy is kind.
And a kind adult will listen
to a child's selfish demands.
I received a message in my mind.
It told me to come here.
That's his ability.
He can make his voice reach whoever
he wants, whenever he wants.
What a self-serving ability.
There's something I'd like to ask of you.
We want to help Kurakawa Mari.
Would you give us permission to do so?
I can't.
The decision was already made.
Sakurada's abilities can't be manifested
unless you truly desire to use them.
There's no way a mother's
love for her child is wrong.
Are you trying to threaten me?
Quite the opposite.
What are you doing?!
Please give us permission to use
an ability on Mari's mother.
I don't have that kind of authority.
It's okay even if you lie.
I won't stop until you give us permission.
What are you thinking?!
You'll die!
That's true.
I implore you. It's okay if it's just lip service.
Please say that you'll give us permission.
All right.
Please say it again, so that it's crystal clear.
All right, I'll give you permission.
It's okay for us to use Sakagami's
ability on Mari's mother, correct?
Yeah, I don't mind.
Thank you very much.
You're crazy.
No matter what I say,
the Bureau won't give permission!
I know that.
Haruki, would you please reset?
Reset.
August 13th
Friday, 08:15 PM
Third Time
Let's get out of here. She reset just now.
Wait, seriously?
Tomoki, cancel that message to Tsushima.
A prank call?! You're terrible.
What did you do?
Before the reset,
Tomoki sent a message to Sakagami
saying he had permission to use his ability.
We've already tested earlier if Tomoki's
ability would work even after a reset.
August 14th
Saturday
Hoshina Memorial Hospital
Mari's mother just left the hospital at 10:36 a.m.
She's in a black car. We're moving out now.
Good luck.
That's a handy ability.
And there's no calling fee.
It's a one-way call, though.
Haruki!
Are you sick?
No, I came to see you.
Hello.
Pardon me, but who are you?
I'm Mari's friend.
Do you need something?
I'm here to stop you.
Are you really fine with forgetting all about Mari?
She'd be better off without me.
A mother who can't even love her own child...
All I can give her is unhappiness.
Mari loves you.
But I hurt Mari.
You not being around hurts her even more.
There's a way for everyone to be happy.
Will you work with us?
What does that mean?
All you need to do is love her back.
I can't do that.
Why not?
Are you that repulsed by what
you've created with your ability?
How do you know about that?
Haruki Misora is Mari's friend.
She also learned about her true identity,
yet she still remains her friend.
You wouldn't understand.
The real Mari died.
My child wasn't even allowed to be born.
There's no way I can forget about her
and smile with the Mari I created.
Please imagine yourself in her shoes.
Suppose you were the one who died,
and the real Mari created an exact clone of you.
Would you be sad if Mari loved your clone?
That's not what this is about!
But it is.
Mari will be sad, and she won't
have anyone to be happy with.
I'm sure your mother will come back.
She won't.
What makes you think that?
Because she hates me.
She'll love you soon enough—
no, she'll remember how much she loved you.
Mari, wishes are something
you need to say out loud.
Put all your heart into it,
so that everyone can hear you.
Go on. Say what you wish to happen.
We'll now help you remember the time
when you gave birth to Mari seven years ago.
Please decide if you really should leave
Sakurada after you remember everything.
What's going on?
She's under the influence of the most
selfish and beautiful ability I know of.
It's time.
Go on. Say what you wish to happen.
I love my mom!
I want to stay with her forever!
I'm sorry...
I'm so sorry!
Would you happen to be free?
I'm going to the mountains after this.
In this rain?
So, who do you think is the android?
There isn't an android.
No matter how much I racked my brain
over it, everyone was human.
Even so, you're supposed to assume
that there's an android among us!
In that case, everyone's an android.
Every single person is influenced and
molded by somebody else, after all.
There's no such thing as a human
who isn't created by humans.
That's true. I'm pretty sure it is.
Hey, Kei. Why did you ditch your parents
and decide to stay in town?
I was interested in special abilities.
That's all?
I used to be like Haruki.
I used to think this world was
made of only very sad rules.
But this town was different.
All the rules that I was forced to accept
fell apart before my very eyes.
You stayed in Sakurada to erase the sadness
that you were forced to accept.
Just like her,
you wanted the power to erase sadness,
so you desired Haruki's reset ability.
It's very convenient.
Kei, I think you should allow people
to help you a bit more.
Help?
You'll feel better if you're helped.
I'll give you an excuse for that.
The truth is, you're a foolish person who wants
to keep talking honestly about what is right.
And yet, your reason can't apply the
"righteous person" definition to yourself.
You wanted to help Mari from the start, didn't you?
But since you cut yourself off
from your own parents,
you felt it wouldn't be right to condemn
a mother trying to cut off her child, right?
That's why you used Haruki as an excuse.
You're weak, cunning, and the truth
is that you want to be a good person,
but in your eyes you're a villain
you can't forgive because of that.
That's why I'll give you an excuse.
Haruki is changing.
She'll be feeling a lot of things from now on.
She'll learn them from you.
You need to become a good person
for Haruki Misora's sake.
Make teaching Haruki Misora
the correct feelings your excuse,
and continue being righteous.
I'll do what I can.
When I'm with you,
we always end up talking about Haruki.
Yeah, you're right. I wonder why.
Isn't it obvious?
It's because you love Haruki Misora.
That makes sense.
Ah, that's a shame.
I thought you would deny it.
Do you want to come see the
sunset after it stops raining?
I've got a novel to finish reading.
Really? Well then, goodbye.
September 1st
Wednesday
First Time
You cut your hair.
I followed your suggestion.
It looks good on you, Haruki.
Thank you.
I saw Mari the day before yesterday.
Really? What did you talk about?
We didn't talk.
Why not?
She was with her mother, so I thought
it'd be okay to not start a conversation.
Well, that's good to hear.
It really is.
You weren't sad?
No, why do you ask?
I thought about the zeroth rule.
Your rule?
Yes. I found the zeroth rule:
I will follow your lead.
I'll trust in all your actions and words.
I think if you hadn't been around,
Mari would still be sad.
I don't know about that.
Mari smiled.
Just like you said, one girl's tears vanished.
I think that was the right decision.
What I wanted to erase were your tears.
You ended up erasing both of our tears, then.
I couldn't do it with my rules.
I've finally found my feelings.
I'm pretty sure I love you.
I understand that you trust me,
but that isn't love that you're feeling.
Why do you think that?
I've always been thinking about you.
I'd at least know that about you...
You're not used to having feelings,
so you're confusing the two with one another.
I think it'd be wrong to fall
in love with you as you are now.
I don't understand.
Yeah, I didn't think you would.
Would it be okay for me to try this out?
Yes.
Are you happy?
I don't know.
I'm not happy at all.
If we put our abilities together,
we can erase the tears.
We can overcome most obstacles.
Doing that much is enough for now.
Let's make that our reason for being together.
Do you have a save?
Yes.
September 1
st
Wednes
day, 02:45 PM
August 31
September 1
Tues
Wednes
Second Time
It's possible that might have been a happy event.
But it was something I couldn't accept.
I kissed her only to prove that she doesn't love me,
so I wanted to erase that.
If I'm not mistaken,
Souma should've come here at this time...
September 1st
Wednesday
Second Time
Today at dawn, Sumire Souma,
a second-year at Nanasaka Middle School,
was found dead in the river.
Sumire did not return home last night.
Local middle schooler dead
Police received a missing persons report.
However, local residents discovered her body
drifting around the mouth of the river.
Local middle schooler dead
She was transported to the hospital
where she was confirmed dead.
There were no signs of foul play.
It appears she may have lost her footing
as she was hiking up the mountain in the rain.
I was looking for you.
I have a request.
Please give me orders to reset.
We can't reset.
We already used your ability.
We weren't able to avoid her death
even though we did a reset?
That's not it.
Are you... crying?
Yeah,
I'm crying right now.
Are you sad?
I'm not the one who's sad.
You are.
I'm crying because you're sad.
Summer ended that day.
Two years later
A service club at Ashiharabashi High School?
Yeah. I'll be the club advisor
and you guys will be the members.
So we're being monitored?
Don't you two want to help others
with your combined abilities?
What are you going to do, Haruki?
I'll follow your lead, Kei.
Next Episode
We're always simply standing in a rain of eternal sadness
That is why I need that warmth of yours
Life is but a dream we never wake up from
We repeat it over and over, praying for salvation
I kept waiting endlessly for your signal
To make sure you wouldn't disappear all by yourself
Ah, it doesn't matter where I am or what I'm doing
My heart can't go against your will
So I'd follow you even to the ends of the world
I fell in love with you at the dawn of our new world
But we kept pushing the hand of the clock backwards
And lost not only time, but our smiles as well
You're the one who brought it back
And taught me that even lies can be meaningful