First, you put everything
you can think of into box A.
Then, you look and think about what is in there
and if you find any problems with something,
you move it into box B.
What are you talking about?
It's a way to figure out what you
find "right" that a friend taught me.
There's something wrong about every single thing.
You have to notice that first.
After you learn both the good and bad sides,
you can decide on what you find truly right.
Does that mean Kei isn't perfect either?
I think so. Of course not.
Do you think he never makes mistakes?
If so, that seems a bit like a tragedy.
If he never makes mistakes,
the moment he makes one,
he'll stop being Asai Kei to you,
which I find tragic.
I wouldn't be able to live knowing that
I'm not allowed to make any mistakes.
You look like you're about to cry, Haruki.
I think I need to think more about certain things.
I don't know the bad sides of Asai Kei yet.
Me neither.
Let's think about it for a bit.
You know, even I understand this.
I'm human too, after all.
Sacrificing a cat to save a human
must be the right thing to do.
I think I'll be going home.
I'll stay here for a bit longer.
I'll be back.
Sure.
Nonoh.
It's not like we're stopping
the cat's time for eternity.
Kei will eventually find a way to save
everyone without sacrificing a cat.
Yeah, I know.
Incoming Call
Asai Kei
Slide to answer
Decline
Quick Reply
Yes?
Are you with Nonoh?
Yes.
I was just about to go home.
Good job.
By the way, I want to ask you one thing.
What is it?
Souma Sumire collapsed.
I want to help her.
What's Souma Sumire's condition?
She's still asleep.
I don't know anything more.
Was she carried here at your request?
I asked Urachi to do that, yes.
You're quick to act.
Did you know this would happen?
No.
But...
I had my suspicions.
What are you going to do?
I'll help her, just as planned.
I expected her to get hurt.
That's why I have to save her, just as planned.
Asai Kei, you're not that righteous.
You're neither good nor pure.
But I'm sure you are a hero.
You may not be omnipotent like you wish to be.
You may be weak and reality might be cruel,
but you are truly a hero
even if you don't seem like one.
I'm just doing as I please.
Asai.
Putting in an effort for others
sure seems to please you.
Where's Haruki?
Heading this way as we speak.
She really will do anything for you.
This time she's helping me on one condition.
She's really kind.
Demanding something in exchange means she
understands the responsibility you're giving her.
It's always been like that—
I owe everything to her help.
Eat some chocolate once
you're done with everything.
Chocolate works wonders when you're tired.
CRISPY!
Hi, Haruki.
Good evening, Kei.
I think Sakagami will be here any minute now.
I'm sorry for asking this of you.
I don't think the condition you
gave me will be difficult with his help.
Why do you want this, though?
Because I want to understand you.
If you really aren't perfect,
I want to learn about it and try to understand.
I'm not perfect at all.
But I don't know your bad sides.
I think that until now,
I've never really tried to understand you.
Somewhere deep in my heart,
I've been wishing for you to never change.
Kei, I've been afraid that my love for you
was blinding me to who you really are.
What's wrong, Kei?
This is the second time you've said you loved me.
When was the first?
You're going to remember that day in a moment.
Are you ready?
Yes, please.
Let's start, then.
So these are Kei's memories...
How kind yet cruel they are...
How clever yet foolish he is...
How bold yet sensitive he is...
Asai Kei is very special to me.
This equilibrium he maintains is perfect.
It's so beautiful and peaceful.
I'm pretty sure I love you.
Are you happy?
I don't know.
How was it?
I found one of the mistakes you made.
Two years ago, when you kissed me
on the rooftop of the south school building,
I was actually happy.
If that's the case,
I sure took the long, cowardly way around.
I did the same.
What's wrong, Sumire, dear?
You look awfully sad.
Say, Tyltyl.
Will you listen to my request?
Of course. Whatever it may be.
Then make me the same as you, Tyltyl.
Make me able to do anything, like you can.
Good morning, Kei.
Morning.
It's been a while.
Yes, it certainly has.
I thought you'd be visiting me more.
It takes a lot of effort to get here.
I'll try to keep that in mind, though.
I don't mind!
But please do try to visit more.
Sure.
By the way, have you seen Souma Sumire?
Me? No.
Tyltyl met with her, though.
Are you saving her this time?
Yeah.
What are you, some kind of a hero?
No, I'm Souma Sumire's friend.
Souma is the second most important person to me.
In such a ranking, only first place matters.
She's sitting alone in a corner precisely
because second place means nothing.
That might be true.
Are you going to make her first?
I'm going to get her to make do with being second.
You're so cruel.
I am.
I am cruel and selfish.
She's here?
The rooftop of the south school
building, the tetrapods...
Both are important places,
but to the Souma from two years ago.
Not the current one.
Once we're done with everything,
let's have a Kit Kat together.
Take a break with some chocolate
and plan to make some curry together.
We'll make the best curry in the world.
Yeah.
_________________
October 23 (Mon)
Haruki, save.
Save.
It's 7:15:20 PM.
Let's go.
Why are you here?
This is my apartment. Of course I'd come back.
You didn't have to come all the way
to the dream world for that.
I will be the one to define your happiness.
I don't think I can save you.
But you can save me.
You can make me happy.
Impossible.
I've hurt you.
That's only what you think.
You've been a greater help to me than anyone else.
I'm sure of it.
The happiness you ensured for me is true happiness.
I really am happy.
Thank you.
So please, keep helping me.
I can keep being happy thanks to you.
It's too bright.
Kei.
You're always the same.
And that's so unbearably painful for me.
I knew it. You're crying.
Look at my future.
In one month, in half a year, in a year...
Whenever I see you, you're smiling.
Look at that future.
Kei.
If that's what you wish for,
I'm sure that's how it'll be.
But I'm scared of such a future.
Knowing that I can't have you for myself
and I keep smiling despite that
is such a scary thought.
You know?
But fine.
If you accept my one condition,
I'll do whatever you say.
What is it?
Play a game with me.
If you win, I'll do what you say.
And if you win?
If I win, let me decide your future for you.
You'll become mine.
And you'll live here in this dream world.
We'll live here together
like two pebbles, never causing any trouble for anyone.
Sure. What kind of game will we play?
You haven't said my name even once since entering this room.
I'm sure you're being considerate.
But...
Please, Kei. Say my name.
If you say it right, you win.
Good evening, Haruki.
Took you a while.
October 23 — (Mon)
Thirty minutes have passed...
Have you met with Kei?
Yeah, we talked.
Where is he now?
In my hands.
What is that supposed to mean?
Kei made a promise with me.
We played a game, and he'd become mine if he lost.
And he did lose.
That's why he's like this now.
That's impossible.
Why?
I'm practically the same as Tyltyl now.
Turning him into a pebble is no big deal for me.
Souma Sumire.
There is no way you'd wish for such a thing.
If I really were Souma Sumire, no.
That's so stupid!
If that pebble isn't Asai Kei,
there's no need to be panicking that much, is there?
Haruki Misora, that really is him.
He can't see or hear anything,
but keeps thinking inside there.
It's a pebble which possesses his consciousness.
I'm telling you, give up.
He's already mine.
Souma Sumire.
Please forgive me for not mincing words.
To think Haruki Misora has become so human...
Two years is quite a long time.
Whatever,
there's no need to be considerate of me.
Then...
This is absolutely ridiculous.
You can't claim Asai Kei as yours
just because you've done this.
You let me into this room exactly
because you're perfectly aware of that!
You're like a child throwing a tantrum.
You cannot be satisfied with such an outcome,
so you're trying to truly claim
Asai Kei for yourself now, aren't you?
Basically, you've been waiting for me
to come and let you have him, no?
I see, that's such an effective method.
I was always on his side,
I even threw my life away for him,
so if I got depressed after all that,
he wouldn't be himself if he left me alone.
And if I turned him into a pebble,
there was no way you wouldn't
come to save him, Haruki Misora.
You put him way above yourself,
so you're even able to leave
his side if it's for his sake.
And if that's the case...
Give Asai Kei to me.
Souma Sumire.
Did you know?
I used to be able to use my ability by myself.
I could until the summer two years ago.
But after one of my resets
Souma Sumire died, even though she didn't before.
And so Asai Kei was hurt.
That's when I became unable
to use my ability on my own.
I didn't want the same thing to happen again.
He's the only one.
He's the only person who remembers what happens
before resets, and I didn't want him to get hurt.
No, I was scared that if I used my ability
on my own and failed, he'd hate me.
Can you use your reset without him now?
I can.
Rese—
I'm so sorry.
You really do care only about him, don't you?
There's no way I could've
missed that future, could I?
There's no way you'd just give him to me
after spending two years with him, right?
There's no way Kei wouldn't
see through such a plan, right?
It's not like I can calculate
every single thing to go my way.
It's not like I can help having
feelings like everyone else!
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
There's no point if you can't be fooled.
So I was right that you
wouldn't turn Kei into a pebble.
You did this for me.
You did this so that I could
use my ability by myself again.
That's the only reason you lied.
It wasn't for you.
Kei is trying to shoulder the responsibility
for all the abilities in Sakurada.
You can't stay in his care forever.
You, if no one else,
have to be his savior while he tries
to save everyone and everything.
If you can't take responsibility for your own ability,
I don't want you to stay by his side.
I'm sorry, Souma Sumire.
I'm jealous of you.
I could say exactly the same.
Do you know what my dream is?
To be by Kei's side.
Not exactly.
He's smart, he has an excellent ability,
so I want to be able to be useful to him.
That's my dream.
Souma Sumire,
I want to be like you.
Haruki Misora,
I wanted to be like you.
Someday, I'll become able to stay
useful by his side, just like you.
And when I can fulfill both my and your role,
my selfish self will be satisfied.
What a cheap provocation.
True.
He actually asked me just a moment ago.
He wants me to keep helping him, you see.
And when it comes to working together
for him, I'm the more capable one,
so I don't think I should let you
take this role from me as well.
Where's Kei?
Already awake.
Let's go back too, then.
Please, Kei. Say my name.
If you say it right, you win.
Say it.
Souma Sumire.
You were Souma Sumire the whole time.
The message sent by Tomoki's ability
reached you too, didn't it?
On such a cold dark sky of grey
How were you able to believe that?
I just had to think about you.
Rises the sun, which breathes life into it
If the message didn't reach you, you would've been
too kind to say that whichever I chose was true.
A scenery so plain and so mundane
But Kei,
I wasn't able to believe anything
until you decided for me.
And yet it seems to break my heart, it's so dear to me
I knew that even if I heard my message,
I wouldn't be able to believe that I'm Souma Sumire.
As the time never stops passing by
The reason I was able to plan everything
You get lost while searching for
was because I knew my own weaknesses.
Pure like the rays of a morning star
I tried to make you decide
my own name, my own identity.
What we all yearn for the most
In what colors bliss is dyed
I'm sorry, Kei.
I made you carry another burden.
Struggling against all your past mistakes
At last from the answer you found kindness fills your heart
Souma.
You might not know about this,
but I'm actually very stubborn.
More beautiful than anything you know
And you find it behind a dark veil of sadness
Two years ago,
I decided that I'd bring you back to life,
If I closed my eyes and stopped my thoughts
and since then I've been prepared
to carry all kinds of burdens.
If it were so simple to just
I know.
Lock your own heart
But there's times when it's too heavy,
and you just want to run away from it all, right?
How lovely life would be
But I believe you have the key
If it's too heavy, that's perfect.
I have my ability so that
I wouldn't just abandon all of it.
To let my soul be free
What I wished for was to move forward
without throwing burdens away.
Morning, Souma.
Did you look at my face while I was asleep?
Is that bad? You looked pretty.
I don't really care,
but even I haven't seen it.
Why were you with me, not Haruki?
There's two reasons.
One is that I felt like you'd be the first to wake up.
And the other one?
The moon is beautiful.
Huh?
You were sleeping by the window, and Haruki wasn't.
Oh, right.
I've lied to you once.
What was it about?
I actually hate messages.
Please listen to my voice in person from now on, Kei.
I definitely will.
I should get going.
Where?
It'd be kind of awkward to see Haruki Misora now.
If I wander around,
I'm sure Urachi will come to pick me up.
I'll be counting on your help again, Souma.
Always, Kei.
Has she left?
Yeah.
Why were you hiding?
It'd be kind of embarrassing to see Souma Sumire.
Do you want me to be friends with her?
It's not like you wish for her to be unhappy, do you?
No.
You'd help her if she was in need.
If I could.
Then that's fine.
I'm glad.
I wouldn't know what to do if
you told me to be friends with her.
You dislike her that much?
I'm fine with me and Souma
competing properly as rivals.
I'd say that's... more natural.
Is it?
Yes.
I'm sure you wouldn't understand.
Kei, does this mean everything's over now?
For now, yes.
Let's make dinner together, then.
Sure.
We'll go shopping tomorrow.
I also have an idea.
What is it?
I used to say there was a novel I loved
I'm thinking of growing my hair out a bit.
That's great, but why?
That I kept on a shelf and never opened up
I remembered today.
"See, this is how you stay true to yourself"
You told me a long time ago
that my hair was pretty.
Showing off, proud of just being me
Do you remember that?
People around me
Of course I do.
Try to sound mature and take some wise words
My memory is pretty good.
They use them as if those words belonged to them
Showing off the fake wisdom they had stolen
So I laughed at them
But actually my sense of self that I kept on a shelf
Was no different from what I'd been laughing at
And the truth is that I already knew
But no more lies, it's time
For my heart's reset
I'll be the one to let go of myself
So I told myself somewhere deep down in my heart
Even if they might talk behind my back
Why should I care when I don't turn around?
You can choose
To follow the path someone's already walked
But wouldn't you rather leave footprints yourself?
You believed your own dreams and chose a path
So it's the right one, just trust in your heart
It'll all be fine
Sakurada Reset
SAGRADA RESET
Holy Rebirth