Is that...
...what Felia was talking about?
The ring of light?
Felia's powers surged out and unleashed it.
Unleashed?
The Altar of Abyss is definitely there!
Felia!
Sogo...
Felia, take a look.
That's the...
Let's go to the Altar of Abyss.
Yeah.
A warm light shines upon the ground
With it, that seed can sprout from the earth
There's a magic that can overcome
cold rain, heavy winds, and anything else
So why does it push our backs?
You know we've all had days where we almost gave up
But then a strange power surges from within us,
and we forge ahead like a boy chasing the sun
At the end of the long winter,
spring's warm breath embraces us with the good news
I've been searching for you,
having waited the entire time for this day
Never be afraid of the trust held in your heart
It'll surely come to ease the loneliness one day
So even if you do return to the stars,
let's plant more seeds
Path
How do we get all the way over there?
If only there were an easy way...
We might be able to use the waterway.
Look! This river seems
to flow all the way there.
But how?
Due to the volume of its cockpit,
the R7 can float on water, so if we make a raft...
Then we all can go!
All right!
Let's split up and get
everything we need for a raft!
Otto.
Over here, next!
Okay.
This should be enough to get by...
No!
You need to eat.
P-Please no mushrooms!
Don't worry. I checked,
and they're perfectly edible.
See?
No means no!
This rich, spicy aroma...
It's a p-pot!
Why is there a pot of curry
in the middle of the forest?
It smells great!
Is this edible?
It's way too suspicious.
But this aroma's sort of familiar.
Yeah, because I made that curry.
No way!
Why?
I figured I'd give you kids a surprise.
Do Mon!
You must all be starving, right?
The flight-attachment came
sooner than expected.
It's too late!
If we'd had these in the last battle,
we could've finished them off!
Al, have we received any updates?
About that.
I've been trying to contact Honeybee, but...
This smells like a ripe palymia fruit...
Might be edible when it's cooked.
Professor Amagi?
Yes.
Your mission will be to guard and observe her.
I heard from the brass.
She's important enough
to mobilize the army for, huh?
She came up with the Lima Theory.
The theory that says that matter from outer space
may produce more energy than Giftdium.
I can't believe you'd dedicate so many
resources to a fairy tale like that.
You're a weird one.
Perhaps.
But be it a fairy tale or a heretical fantasy,
that matters not to me.
So long as it elevates
this planet to greater heights.
Well, I'm not fussed.
I'll just do as ordered, and eliminate
the enemies standing in your way.
Please stay still...
At least while I'm looking
through the microscope.
Come in!
If you're busy, we can come back later.
Oh!
You're the one who read my paper, right?
I'm Ena Amagi. It's a pleasure!
I'm Gulf Zoneboyle.
I've assigned one of my men to guard you.
I'm Hajime Do Mon.
Please let me aid your efforts
to bring more prosperity to this planet!
We will be departing for
Berberine resort momentarily.
Please make sure your
seatbelts are fastened.
I sent word that you'd leave for the meeting
as soon as your work is done,
maybe even tomorrow.
But I believe the elders of the Council
will soon be taking their leave...
Permanently.
They disappoint me.
How could they not sympathize with your
desire to bring this planet greater glory?
I daresay no one will be left
to stand in your way now.
The time has finally come, huh?
Do Mon.
Where have you been?
Oh, I was just looking for
anything that might be edible.
The raft's almost complete.
Let's leave first thing tomorrow.
Sogo...
What?
Stop what you're doing.
Don't go any farther.
What are you talking about?
Go down the eastern branch of this river.
It will take you back to Garden Indigo.
Why would you say that?
The people you're going
up against are soldiers.
If you keep going, you'll die.
You think I don't know?
But I have to go!
I want to protect Felia!
And if I die trying,
who's to blame but me?
This is none of your business.
Protecting someone isn't as easy as you think!
Sogo!
What's wrong?
You're willing to put
your friends in harm's way?
Do you want that red crystal so badly?!
That worthless piece of trash?
Do Mon?
Your mother lost her life because of it...
Because of that filth, of all things.
It takes nothing at all for a person to die.
You can spend your whole life grieving,
but it won't bring them back to life.
Don't let it get you down.
But that probably doesn't help, huh?
Do Mon loves Sogo.
That's right.
Sogo loves you all.
Yeah.
And I love you all very much, too.
And yet...
Much has happened today.
So just get some rest.
Okay.
I heard that some folks are
sniffing around this research...
You'd best be careful.
My calculations were correct.
There are signs that matter from
outer space landed in the Bolvia region.
The concentration also matches
the figures observed at Indigo.
My theory really was—
I'm sorry! Did you need something?
I'm telling you to be careful and
pay attention to your surroundings.
I'm not your butler, you know?
Well, I'm happy that I get to enjoy
your delicious coffee all the time.
The members of the Bureau
don't agree on everything.
Some don't want to see Giftdium
replaced as our primary energy source.
Right...
Anyway, if you ever need help,
call this number.
I'll rush to your aid at once.
Hey, Sogo!
At least say hello!
He's really grown.
All done!
This is Lucifer...
I need to hurry and tell
Do Mon and the rest!
All signals go.
I repeat, all signals go.
Quickly eliminate anything or anyone
that could be an impediment.
Once we have control of the facility, retrieve as
much information about its backers as possible.
Engaging target.
Do Mon?
You can't have that...
Let go of me!
Do Mon...
Please take care of Sogo...
Ena!
Stop right there!
Stay back!
Ena...
Ena!
They say there was nothing left of her.
At least her son wasn't
with her at the time, I guess.
Apparently, his father died in an
accident before he was born, too.
I hope someone will take him in...
The poor thing.
There you are.
Hey...
I really can't leave Felia alone.
I know that Do Mon's right, and it's only going
to get more dangerous from here on out.
It's not like I want to put
the others in harm's way.
So we'll head for the Altar
of Abyss as a group of three.
The two of us will keep Felia safe!
Sogo, you care so much for Felia...
You really are hopeless without me around!
I'm counting on you.
But of course!
A weird talking stone...
And a weird human,
who accepted it without batting an eye.
Man, we make one odd couple...
Maybe the time has finally come to tell you...
About Felia and me.
This universe is home to countless life forms.
Moura?
And all of them originate from the "Seeds of Life,"
which drift across space, like feathers on the wind.
"Seeds of Life"?
And when they descend upon
a planet fit to bear life,
they birth an angel that will
foster life, as the planet's avatar.
An angel?
Right.
And the angel born to planet Gift...
Is Felia...
In other words, Felia is the very
embodiment of this planet.
And I too was born from those seeds,
as the guardian to protect that angel.
I'm Felia's fated servant.
So every inhabitable planet
has its own Felia and Moura?
Now that Felia's out of the earth,
she needs to replenish her powers at the Altar.
If she doesn't, using them will
cause her to wither and fade away.
Does she know about this?
Because you vowed to protect her with me,
I wanted you to know.
Felia will...
Let's both protect Felia!
Yeah.
The two of us, together.
My keycard?
I'm borrowing it for a while.
I have some business with the Bureau.
Do Mon!
Your aim still skews to the right
when you shoot from the hip.
How many times have
I told you to correct that?
You've got some nerve,
showing your face to me!
You're...
To me...
To me, you were the greatest soldier I knew!
I don't belong in this world anymore.
Bullshit!
The Hajime Do Mon you knew
died in that operation.
As if I'd accept that load of crap!
I'm still fighting my own war,
Do Mon!
Sogo?
Early this morning, a flight chartered by
Administrative Bureau Council members
went missing en route to Berberine.
The passengers included all the Council
members except Secretary Gulf Zoneboyle.
No further details are available at this time.
You're gentle, Kaon.
You're reliable, Otto.
And you're cool, Roman.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah.
Let's go, Felia.
Waking up to a new morning every day,
The first thing I tell myself
Is that I love this world
I really, really do
When the light calls for me
I want to reach it even if it's on my bare feet
Don't stop me
I'll go further and further
One step at a time
To look for it
Let's go on an adventure
Past this door that our hearts dream of
Another fun day starts, so let's go
I want to chase those clouds I saw
I wonder where it went?
I want to catch it soon
Let's go as all this fun bursts out
I'll run after it no matter how far it is
I think I'll be able to do it if it's with you
Because with you by my side,
I won't be scared of anything
Close your eyes,
and you'll remember that familiar taste.
Open your eyes,
and you'll see that gentle taste.
Next time, on Comet Lucifer:
Feelings That Must Be Conveyed.
Feelings That
Must Be Conveyed
Grab a ticket and join us on this adventure!