The typhoon is predicted to hit
Garden Indigo within two or three days.
Oh, it's the costume
we bought the other day.
You look adorable.
The pinnacle of the Valov family's technology.
I present the Valov R7!
But your mouth...
What's this? All alone?
Sogo!
Felia...
What the hell happened here?
She was taken away by two men!
What?
Felia's... Felia's...
Calm down!
She might still be nearby.
We're going to save her!
A warm light shines upon the ground
With it, that seed can sprout from the earth
There's a magic that can overcome
cold rain, heavy winds, and anything else
So why does it push our backs?
You know we've all had days where we almost gave up
But then a strange power surges from within us,
and we forge ahead like a boy chasing the sun
At the end of the long winter,
spring's warm breath embraces us with the good news
I've been searching for you,
having waited the entire time for this day
Never be afraid of the trust held in your heart
It'll surely come to ease the loneliness one day
So even if you do return to the stars,
let's plant more seeds
Embracing Souls
Why hello there,
my darling mademoiselle.
How do you do?
Oh? You haven't taken a single bite.
Such a bad girl...
You're going to be
with me until the end of time.
So you'd better eat, okay?
Open that tiny mouth
of yours nice and wide.
Sogo...
Where's Sogo?
I'll never let you see
that damned brat again!
How dare he do this to me?!
You'll never see him again!
She's calling.
I can sense Felia's choker.
To the east!
Gotcha!
Well, we've captured Lima.
Let's just lighten the load and dump her
at the Administrative Bureau already.
Well, those are the terms...
Well then, what's the rendezvous time?
It appears their recovery
squad's headed our way.
Don't be in such a rush.
But...
He'll definitely come here.
What is this?
I had always thought you, the Administrative Council,
and we, the Eighth Division Special Corps,
were working toward a common goal.
That is correct.
Would you care to explain your recent,
arbitrary actions, then?
A little confrontational, aren't we?
We have confirmed you carried out operations
without consulting us beforehand.
Why did you use one
of my officers for them?
If you mean Captain Stewart,
then let me tell you it was his own decision.
Lima is considered a taboo.
But its powers can grant this planet
new and improved prosperity.
Beyond this lies an abandoned
Alizarin Mountain mine.
The signal's coming from deep inside!
Then we have no choice but to go.
Hang on tight, Moura!
Where'd you run off to?
Have you checked the rendezvous point?
A long time ago.
Quit nagging me over everything.
Huh?!
Thermal signatures
closing in from eight o'clock.
Sure took their sweet time...
It's not an official transport.
Did you check its ID code?
No matching results.
Zoom in.
It's that kid from before.
She's inside.
Where exactly could she be?
Sogo?
Felia!
Quit scurrying about.
What are you doing?
Shut your mouth—
Sogo!
Moura!
There he is...
Fire up my unit!
Come on, let's settle this!
Now, that's what I like to see!
You'd better not use
that missing arm as an excuse!
What exactly do you
think you're doing?
Hey now, what's the matter?
Do you really think...
this is enough...
...to satisfy me?
What?
He disappeared?
Don't you dare wimp out on me!
Snow?
Shall we head home?
Unfortunately, I only have this one umbrella.
Guess it's all yours then.
Felia!
Where's Felia?
Shut up!
Felia...
Shut your trap or I'll kill you.
Cuculus to Lanius. Cuculus to Lanius.
Currently November Whiskey 980
from Lima handover point.
Cuculus to Lanius. Cuculus to Lanius.
Currently November Whiskey 980
from Lima handover point.
You heard him, great leader.
Make preparations to hand over Lima.
Be gentle.
Copy that.
Felia!
Where are you?
Sogo?
Sogo!
Sogo! Sogo!
Felia?
Felia!
Honestly, is there anything
you can do without me?
Moura!
Now, let's find Felia!
Okay!
We're getting closer to the signal.
Let's hurry!
Sogo?
Come.
Felia!
She's close.
Very close, but...
Sogo! Sogo!
Shut up already...
Sogo!
Hey, isn't Cuculus here yet?
They say they can't approach
due to lack of visibility.
Sogo!
Damn it... They're useless.
Felia!
Sogo—
Damn you!
Stop right there.
Want me to cut off her head?
What?
You wanna die?
Eat this!
Sogo!
You little bitch!
Crap.
Felia!
A new enemy?
Is my unit repaired yet?
Prepped and ready to go.
What about the drive?
Currently operating at eighty percent.
You have five seconds to get it to max!
Turbine pressure will be optimal soon.
Systems check.
All clear.
Releasing safety.
Opening hatch!
Moving out!
Cease fire!
Damn, I'm in luck...
I don't care who you are,
as long as you get my blood boiling.
That's more like it!
My head's pounding!
Pounding like crazy!
What?
Assault rifle!
Come on!
Where's Felia?
You're pushing your luck, buddy.
Hell yeah...
I'm getting goosebumps!
All right.
Make me climax!
Come on, make me!
Just die!
Sogo!
Together
We walk through life
Sogo...
Straight forwards
Sogo?
We just keep moving on
Throughout our lives
Thank goodness...
Listen to the hope
Everything is all right now.
Of your life
Slowly, we're becoming adults
In this radiant world
Even if I'm at the end of the world
But it looks like I used my powers too much.
That I know nothing about
Moura's going to yell at me again.
As long as you're here with me
I'm not afraid
People are weak and lonely things
Are you...
But if they can channel their warmth into strength, then maybe...
Felia?
Thanks for coming to save me.
At the place where hearts are bound,
the girls' feelings sway.
Next time, on Comet Lucifer:
Flower Boy.
Flower Boy
Grab a ticket and join us on this adventure!