Have as much as you like!
Did you make all this, Ans?
Indeed!
Also, the townspeople insisted on giving this to you.
A huge serving of rice to boot!
Yuna?
Ans!
You should come to Crimonia
and open a Sunrise-style restaurant.
I'll handle both the funds and the location!
I...
want you!
What?!
I-I-I appreciate the sentiment,
but Crimonia is so far away,
and I wouldn't be able to see my family much,
not to mention I wouldn't
be able to get fresh seafood...
In other words, you're on board
as long as the distance isn't an issue?
Great, I'll hold you to that!
What?!
Now I'll be able to eat this food in Crimonia too!
Now, as for shortening travel—
You look like you're having fun.
Huh?
Atla!
Let me thank you again for helping us, Yuna.
I just did what I felt like.
You're far too humble.
But that side of you is partly why
I'd like to ask for your help.
What is it?
Welcome back!
Yuna!
Fina!
I'm back!
Thanks for coming to greet me!
Of course!
I heard you were coming back today!
Welcome back, Kumayuru.
Yuna, you're free for the rest of the day, right?
You see, I—
Oh, uh...
I'm sorry, Fina.
I've got a pretty important errand to run.
Huh?
Oh, okay...
You're pretty busy for someone who just got back.
Yeah... I'm really sorry.
Don't worry.
Work is important too, and all.
Miss Yuna!
Noa!
What brings you here all of a sudden?
Oh, did you perhaps come to see me?
I was longing to see you t—
Lady Noa.
It's time for your studies.
Let's be on our way.
Lala, just a moment!
I want to talk to Yuna for just a moment!
Have fun with your studies...
Miss Yuna!
The port town of Millela
wants to be annexed into Crimonia
and receive the protection of the kingdom, correct?
Yeah. I was asked to act as a mediator
between Crimonia and Millela.
So, what do you think?
That'd be a tad difficult.
Why's that? The kingdom
gets to expand its borders.
Did you forget about the Elegent Mountains?
As long as they stand,
never mind oversight and protection,
it'd be hard to simply conduct negotiations.
Do you expect me to grow wings, or what?
If you can't fly, just dig a tunnel instead!
It's not quite that simple.
Just imagine the amount of time and money
needed for a tunnel through those mountains.
Well, you won't have to worry about that.
I already made one!
Just how did you...
I just used a bit of magic.
I dug and hardened, dug and hardened,
dug, hardened, rested,
dug, hardened, dug, hardened, dug, hardened...
Something like that.
I'll depart for Millela tomorrow for negotiations.
Wait, tomorrow?!
What?
So these are the cute bears I've been hearing about!
They're so fluffy!
What's Milaine doing here?
We'll need the commerce guild's help going forward.
That's why I'm bringing her.
And I'm also personally
interested in trade with Millela!
Your personal interest isn't relevant here.
I can't very well do this without the guild master.
Oh, I see.
Wait, the guild master?!
Oh? Did I not tell you?
Milaine, could it be that you're
actually older than you—
I'm in my twenties—just as old as I look.
R-Right.
"Twenties" doesn't say much when there's
a considerable difference between 20 and 29.
But I'll keep that to myself.
I'm the lord of Crimonia,
Cliff Fochrosé.
Delighted to make your acquaintance.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Milaine, the guild master
of the Crimonia commerce guild.
I-I'm Atla, the guild master of the adventurers' guild.
Thank you for coming all the way out
to our humble town on such short noti—
Hey, why did you bring the lord here
instead of just replying to the letter?!
Ask him, not me.
I'm sorry.
This sudden development
just had me a bit confused.
Not only did you defeat the bandits and the kraken,
you even dug a tunnel to connect the two towns.
I can't even begin to thank you.
Oh, about that...
I'm happy as long as you
don't tell anyone that I'm behind it.
You can rest easy.
We'll announce the tunnel as a joint effort
between Crimonia and Millela.
We won't mention you, Yuna.
That's a relief.
I mean, if word got out that I only
dug that tunnel out of self-interest
because I wanted rice,
fresh seafood, and skilled cooks,
that'd be pretty embarrassing.
Anyway, I'll leave the rest to the adults and...
Huh?
Yuna.
I can't just let you get away with changing the
country's territory for personal gain, now can I?
We can expect your full cooperation
with the construction of the tunnel, correct?
We'll be counting on you, Yuna.
Hey...
Wait, I just want to go back
to Crimonia and take it easy...
No!
Another great day!
I guess she's busy with work...
I-I'm back...
Fina...
Yuna!
It's been pretty rough,
but things have finally started to calm down.
So with that, let's get going!
Get going? Where?
And shouldn't you rest up a bit first?
I want to keep my promise.
We said we'd visit the sea once things
calmed down in Millela, remember?
If your parents are okay with it,
let's take Shuri with us too!
Y-Yeah, good idea!
We couldn't take her with us to the capital, after all.
The sea is on the other side of this tunnel?
That's right.
Now we can visit without
having to cross the mountains.
And you built all this, Yuna?
That's incredible!
Rather than the digging, it was the
outfitting of the tunnel I've been busy with.
A bear!
Fina, look!
It's a bear!
Yuna...
What's...
Please don't ask.
That's the sea?
It's so big!
Let me show you to the inn, then.
There's bear houses here too!
They're huge!
You don't get to visit the sea every day.
I'm planning on inviting the kids at the orphanage
and the Bear's Resting Shop staff at some point,
so I made them on the larger side.
Yuna...
I want to see the sea up close!
Let's go have a look, then!
Hooray!
Careful not to slip and fall.
I can't wait!
Fina, there's so many boats!
Look, a fish jumped!
Yeah...
She's taught me so much I never knew before,
and takes me to places I've never laid eyes on.
Thank you, Yu—
It's the bear lady!
Guys!
The bear lady came to visit!
You came by to visit again?
Here, have some freshly caught fish.
No need to hold back.
Have some fish I caught too!
It's been one big haul after the other
since the kraken went away!
I made some delicious dried fish too.
Yuna's really popular, huh?
Miss Yuna!
I've come to visit!
Coming!
Lady Noa?
Oh no...
And here I made sure to finish my studies
early just so I could visit Miss Yuna...
I can't believe she's out defeating monsters...
I-I'm terribly sorry...
You have nothing to apologize for!
I'm sorry for interrupting your butchering work.
No, don't worry about it! I'm not bothered one bit!
But it was unfair of you to have
Miss Yuna all to yourself in Millela!
I didn't have her all to myself...
My sister was with me, not to mention...
Yuna's popular wherever she goes.
That won't do, Fina!
As the vice president of the Bear Fan Club,
you need to be more aggressive!
Just like me, the president!
I could never be like you, Lady Noa...
Fina?
I'll take my leave for today.
Also...
Please give this to Miss Yuna.
I'm back!
Oh, it's from Ellelaura in the capital.
From Lady Ellelaura?
Yeah.
Apparently Princess Flora is crying
about wanting to see the bear.
Princess...
Oh...
Are you going to see her?
I can't just leave a girl crying, can I?
I'll take Kumayuru to go and see her.
You're not using that gate?
People will get suspicious
if I use the Warp Gate too much.
Oh yeah, why don't you come with me?
Kumakyu's back is still free.
Sur—
No, I'm good.
I have butchering to do, for one.
Huh?
You can take a break every now and then.
But it's my job.
Besides, I get nervous at the castle
with the king around.
Oh, okay, that's too bad.
I'll leave a few days' worth of
monsters in the butchery fridge.
Okay.
I'll work hard!
Hello?
Hey, it's me!
Yuna!
Sorry for calling so late.
I just got back.
Thanks for taking care of the
butchering while I've been gone.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
So starting tomorrow, will you—
By the way, I'm going to Millela tomorrow!
Do you remember Ans, that cook
who specializes in Sunrise cuisine?
We made plans to meet up tomorrow!
Oh, really...
So yeah, I'll probably end up leaving
some monsters before I go again.
Oh, I'll make sure to prepare some food and flan.
Okay. Can't wait.
Great! Good night!
Wait, Yuna!
Huh? What's up?
Tomorrow, I think I'd also like to—
I'd also like to do my best tomorrow.
Good night.
Yeah. Good night.
That's it for today, then.
Yuna...
Fina!
I did it, Fina!
Y-Y-Yuna?
Wh-What is it?
I managed to convince Ans to come to Crimonia!
Th-That's great...
Ans made this Sunrise food for us.
Come on, have some too.
O-Okay.
Thank you.
It's great!
I know, right?
That hits the spot!
I'll have to find a good place for the restaurant
before the tunnel is formally open.
You sound really excited, Yuna.
Of course! I'll get to eat this food
in Crimonia whenever I want!
I'm so glad both Morin
and Ans decided to come here.
Yuna!
What is it? Already full?
Would you mind if I took a break
from butchering for a while?
Do you have something to do, or what?
I want to get even better at butchering
by learning from my dad, Gentz.
I want to be of even more use to you, my employer!
You're plenty helpful already, you know.
Okay, sure.
If that's what you want to do,
sure, good luck!
Thanks.
I'll work hard.
Morning, Fina...
I'll get today's work ready in a minute.
Fina?
Oh yeah, I guess she was
taking a break starting today.
Maybe I should go look for
a location for the restaurant.
Milaine kind of looked like a zombie...
It wasn't because she's had so much
to do since I dug that tunnel, was it?
Anyway, I found a good place,
so what do I do now?
Just like that. Avoid cutting
the muscles as you insert the knife.
Perfect. You're doing great, Fina.
But I'm still nowhere near as good as you, Dad.
I'll work even harder.
Miss Yuna!
Fina?
Miss Yuna! I finally got to see you!
Noa...
What in the world are these?!
Miss Yuna, please let me have these two!
I can't just give them out...
Oh, I can't believe Fina didn't tell me about them.
She's failed as a Bear Fan Club member!
Bear Fan Club?
I-It's nothing!
Anyway, where is Fina today?
Oh, Fina is...
What do you think?
Hey, Fina.
How long are you planning on staying here?
W-Well, until I've become better at—
Is this about Yuna?
Honestly, Fina.
I told her to be more aggressive and everything...
I don't understand why.
I was used to being alone.
If anything that was easier for me.
But lately, it's like there's this hole in my chest.
I can eat delicious food whenever I want,
sleep, have fun...
My life has never been so fulfilling, yet...
How about this...
Huh?
Say one of your acquaintances began to avoid you
and left your side, what would you do?
Nothing in particular.
Well then,
what if it was Fina?
Surprisingly, it seems some
matters are beyond your grasp.
Well yeah, I'm just your average girl—
or bear, rather.
Sorry, something came up
that I need to take care of.
Thank you, Noa!
As the president of the Bear Fan Club,
it's my job to ensure the happiness of
Miss Yuna and the other members.
But I don't intend to lose here either,
Miss Yuna and Fina!
It might be a bit late, but I realized something.
Yuna is amazing, and everywhere she goes
she's relied upon by so many different people.
Yeah, if it weren't for her,
we probably wouldn't be together like this now.
So I couldn't tell her.
That I always want to be with her.
That would be too selfish of me.
I'm no princess,
and I can't cook delicious food either.
Butchering is about all I'm good for.
Oh, give me a break.
No matter how level-headed you are,
you're still just a ten year old kid.
It's fine!
Be as selfish as you want!
Huh?
If you want to be with Yuna, just tell her so!
You just need a bit of courage.
Courage...
Otherwise you'll end up like me, you know.
Yeah! Thank you, Dad!
Fina.
I have to tell her.
I have to find the courage.
I have somewhere I want to go with you.
Bare and Fina
Bear and Fina
Bear and Feena
Isn't this...
My home country is far, far from here.
So far away that I don't know
if I'll ever be able to go home again.
What?
I spent every day there just doing what I wanted.
All alone.
Alone?
What about your family and friends?
Well, I didn't really see any need for them.
Don't you miss it?
Don't you want to go home?
Even if I can't return, it doesn't really bother me.
I was never the type
to be attached to places or people.
I never planned to settle down in Crimonia...
...nor did I plan to enter
a contract with a girl I met here.
I never even dreamed of it.
Then, why?
Why do you concern yourself
with someone you just met?
"I couldn't butcher by myself."
"I was asked to by Gentz."
I can come up with a lot of reasons.
But to be honest, I still don't understand.
But you know...
In the time we've spent together,
Tell ya what, tell ya what
Have a small heads-up
being with you started to
feel natural and comforting.
Today's been utterly lovely, yes
And I know, yes I know
That's never happened before.
What I feel will grow
Come now hurry there's good times yet
I don't even need a reason anymore.
'Cause for me, can't you see
All the time that we share
There's no compare
I...
You're so special to me
want to be with you, Fina.
Yuna...
I...
Can't help but smile
I want to be together with you, Yuna!
For days gone by
I wanna cherish every moment
I want to be with you!
These charming memories
Like crystal clear melody
I'm a bear, you know.
Brightens up the time we've treasured, hand in hand
Are you...
Though I couldn't speak my mind,
...going to eat me?
With a little courage, I'll find
All the words I've longed to tell you every moment
Why would I eat you?
Welcome back and welcome home
I hope a smile will brighten your day
I can't wait to hear
The voice that greets me when I
Open up the door
Tell ya what, tell ya what
Have a small heads-up
Today's been better than anything
There'll be, there'll be
More for you and me
Come now hurry there's good times yet
Every day, every day
Will be just as swell
We'll spend our days in a safe and warm embrace
Treasure these feelings inside
Tell ya what, I love you!
Welcome home, Yuna!
I'm back, Fina!