What is this place?
Where am I?
What was that?
The goddess dances with the void,
death, the Emperor, and eternity...
Is it true, Aldea?
Did you really find Zeros on Lemuria?
Yes, I saw it with my own eyes.
Why didn't you report that to the brass?
Because I wanted you to get all the credit, Grabel.
You're a fool.
Oh, and one more thing...
That girl who was wearing
Zeros called herself Aine.
Then I suppose we'll just have to
take care of this ourselves.
My love for you is like a bucking colt
You act so innocent, but I know you're feeling it
I'm not a wizard anymore
The craziest things you can imagine all start from nothing
It's like we're in a fairy tale
But this is real life
My charm makes you swoon
Our hearts beat in unison
Just let your passion explode
My feelings won't reach you like this
I need to shoot them at you with everything I've got
They're on a direct course to your heart
My spirit is on fire
I'll expose your true nature
Don't worry, I'll be gentle
I'll take you to a secret paradise
And offer you a grand feast
When the two of us become one
An innocent flower blooms
Episode 7
Imperial Hero -Grabel-
Initiating sealing.
Entrance Magitech signal is rapidly falling.
Ninety, seventy, fifty, thirty...
The Magitech particles have dropped by 99.999%.
The sealing is complete.
So the data was real?
If we can seal the entrances,
we'll drastically alter the course of this war.
We finally have a means to make the joint
US-Japan operation to retake Okinawa a reality.
But who sent this data to us?
I can't believe that my first time is with you.
This should be fun!
I just brought you to the cafeteria 'cause
you said you wanted to try it out.
Don't make it sound like something else.
May we sit across from you, leader?
You're...
I'm never going to forgive you.
The leader of the Masters, Scarlet Fairchild.
Nice to meet you.
Gertrude Baird.
Nice seeing you, asshole.
Sharon Cunningham.
Wh-What are you doing here?
We've joined the academy.
Well, for the joint operation, anyway.
Hey, Kizuna, I hear you have
some kinda special power.
N-No, it's no big deal.
Now I'm even more interested.
Hey, Kizuna, wanna show me around Ataraxia?
Since we're both the leaders of our teams,
we should get to know each other.
Enough!
Kizuna has a lunch meeting with me.
Don't interrupt us.
G-Give me a break...
Aine?
Let's go, Kizuna!
Hey, wait!
Okay, Kizuna, we can't let this
valuable afternoon go to waste.
Only thing going to waste
is all that fat in your boobs!
Uh...
We'll just have to...
...fight for him!
It's on!
Champion!
You guys are ballers!
I'm not done yet!
We're just getting started!
So, why are you having a swimsuit contest, exactly?
Wait, am I even allowed back here?
Ki-zu-na!
Here we are!
They're wearing the same swimsuit?
Why are you copying me?
It's the other way around!
H-Hey!
Come with me, Kizuna!
Wait!
Well?
My breasts may not be as big,
but my proportions are way better, right?
Why are you so obsessed with me?
I told you, I'm interested.
Interested?
Like, the whole Heart Hybrid thing...
What's it like?
Wanna try it with me?
Ow...
Don't move!
I'm sorry!
Don't talk!
Is this a Heart Hybrid?
What are you doing?
Listen, Yurishia, that was an accident...
It's fine.
It was silly of me to take
a child's game so seriously.
Where are you going?
Don't make me say it.
Hey...
Hey, Scarlet.
What?
You and Yurishia are actually friends, aren't you?
Huh?
You were in perfect sync when you were dancing.
And you had basically the same taste in swimsuits.
No!
That's not true!
Scarlet...
You don't know what a horrible person Yurishia is!
She...
She used us as pawns to be sacrificed!
Sacrificed?
It was our first time fighting a Dragorie,
a Category-A Magitech weapon.
W-We can't fight this thing!
Save m—
Yurishia deliberately sent us
on ahead to soften it up.
And after we wore it down,
she came and stole all the credit.
I'm never going to forgive her!
I'll never forgive Yurishia!
I can't believe Yurishia would do that.
She's not that type of person.
Forget it!
I'm going home!
You heard that?
Yes.
Is what she said true?
If that's what she said, it probably is.
Yurishia...
See you tomorrow.
All hail the General!
All hail the Empire!
How dare she act like she's more
important than the Royal Guard?
We should just let her do what she wants for now.
I'm sure she'll trip up eventually.
I know that!
Cheers!
You're getting too excited.
What's wrong with that? We're celebrating.
I'm so hot.
On days like this, it starts to throb.
This scar you gave me...
The same goes for me.
A fragment of your spear is still within me.
Did it hurt? I'm sorry.
Hey!
Grabel...
Stop it...
No.
Aldea...
I know.
I'll go get a battleship ready.
One with long range capabilities, right?
Th-That's right.
Then let's get back to it.
No.
N-Now's not the time...
Don't say that.
It's okay, right?
N-No...
You're so mean, Grabel.
Captain, I made these in Home Ec!
Please share them with everyone!
Thanks!
Tastes great.
I'm sure you'll make a good wife someday, Sylvia.
A-A wife?
N-No, it's too sudden!
I'm still not old enough to marry,
but if it's with you...
Did you say something?
Bye!
Why?!
Why can't I find anything?
It's me I'm looking up!
The goddess dances with the void,
death, the Emperor, and eternity...
What am I?
There you are, Aine.
What are you doing in here?
I'm free to go wherever I want.
What are you doing here?
Sylvia made us some cookies.
Want some?
Don't need any.
But...
I said no!
You do need some.
Why aren't you saying anything?
About what?
Don't play dumb.
There's something you want to ask me, right?
I don't want to ask about something
you don't want to talk about.
So if you ever do want to talk about it,
come straight to me.
Kizuna.
Kizuna...
I...
Give me a sitrep!
How many enemies?
It's...
It's a woman!
It's a single, unarmed woman!
You, from the other dimension!
Surrender, bitch.
I'm impressed you were willing to come alone,
but that was a dumb decision.
Bored now.
Can I shoot her?
Not yet, whore.
I am General Grabel,
Commander of the Batlantis Empire's
Lemuria Theater 6th Expeditionary Force.
I demand you hand over Zeros
and its Magitech knight.
Immediately.
Otherwise I cannot guarantee your safety.
What? Are you crazy, slut?
You're surrounded by the enemy.
Bite it, alien.
Negotiations failed, then?
A-All units, engage!
Zoros.
Hurry!
What happened?
Gertrude? Sharon?!
Come in!
That's...
Gertrude!
Sharon!
Deploy!
Wait! You can't just attack without a plan!
Shut up!
What is this?!
It's so powerful!
Kizuna...
It's my fault this happened to you...
Forget about me.
Where's everyone else?
Himekawa... Aine...
Both of you get back!
I can't let you handle this!
Fuck off!
Are you planning to fight with no ammo?
Blades!
You're mine!
Gunblade...
Raver.
You may be proud, Knight of Lemuria.
You made me use my Gunblade.
I'm going to hit you hard.
The Kuros, huh?
Go!
Bullet!
No way... She managed to stop
a full-power burst from the Kuros?
No!
Everyone...
How dare you?!
Stop it!
Come.
I'll take out a wimp like you in one hit.
Take this!
Wait!
I won't let you touch Aine.
You're...
...a man?
Wiped out...
Amaterasu has been wiped out!
Kizuna...
I see.
Do you know who you are?
If you want to know, come with me.
Don't touch her.
We'll meet again, male Magitech knight.
Get the recovery teams out there!
Hurry! No wasting time!
She let them go?
Welcome back.
I'm almost out of magic too.
Being on Lemuria uses more
of my magic than anticipated.
But...
Next time, I will succeed.
What was that...
Kizuna!
How about an apple, Snow White? Relax, it's safe
You know, that shit-eating grin really pisses me off
I'm gonna punch you
Forgive me for being cold to you
It's just that there was this girl looking at you in the cafe
I'm gonna kill her
She'd probably leave you before the night is over
Let me show you the storm of emotions trapped beneath the surface
Go beyond your dreams, love's waiting for you there
What do you want so badly that you'd cry for it?
All I want is your heart's warmth
There's no escape from the love that's seeping through your veins
Hold me, hold your breath
You're my prince
Just kidding
Illustration
Yoshihiro Watanabe
I swear by the honor of Batlantis,
and my pride as a soldier, I shall claim victory!
Come on, Grabel, let's start up where we left off...
And that Zeros...
Oh, you're so silly, Grabel.
NEXT TIME
S-Stop it, Aldea!