My love for you is like a bucking colt
You act so innocent, but I know you're feeling it
I'm not a wizard anymore
The craziest things you can imagine all start from nothing
It's like we're in a fairy tale
But this is real life
My charm makes you swoon
Our hearts beat in unison
Just let your passion explode
My feelings won't reach you like this
I need to shoot them at you with everything I've got
They're on a direct course to your heart
My spirit is on fire
I'll expose your true nature
Don't worry, I'll be gentle
I'll take you to a secret paradise
And offer you a grand feast
When the two of us become one
An innocent flower blooms
Episode 6
World-Splitter Gladius
This is the first person from the other
dimension we've encountered so far.
Her identifier is Aldea.
The name of her Magitech armor is Zeeru.
It appears similar to a Heart Hybrid Gear,
but its special ability allows it to warp space.
So this is what reflected the Pulverizer?
And it's also what trapped us before, right?
She said the Batlantis Empire
lies beyond the Entrances.
Is that the enemy that's sending
in the Magitech weapons?
We don't know yet.
We've named the three-headed dragon Tri-Head.
Since its power far exceeds that
of a Category-A weapon,
we've designated a new Super-Category Class.
Commander!
We should head back there right away!
No.
This mission is complete.
Why?!
That Magitech weapon is dangerous!
We can't just let it sit out there!
We infiltrated enemy-occupied
territory for the first time,
found a new type of Magitech weapon,
and discovered and made contact
with otherworldly beings.
That's more than enough for one mission.
I can't accept that!
We should wipe them out with everything we have!
What's gotten into you, Himekawa?
Nothing!
I'm just suggesting the obvious!
Besides, if we capture that person from the other
dimension, we can get even more information!
Calm down, Hayuru.
If we go in without a plan, we'll just lose again.
Getting cold feet, are we?
After all that bragging about being
the American ace and the strongest?
What'd you say?
Hida, you understand, right?
Well...
I'm disappointed in you!
Okay.
Himekawa?
No, she wouldn't...
Oh my.
You came back by yourself?
Where is that Magitech weapon?
You're not interested in me at all? How rude.
Well, not like you're the one I'm after, either.
Zeeru.
I've got questions for you too!
I'll play with you.
Come on.
Blades!
That strange technique again...
I'll show you something even more fun.
Labyrinth Cube!
Wh-What's this?
The Labyrinth Cube, an inescapable
prison made by warping space.
I control everything that happens inside.
I know, I can slice the space inside into
itsy-bitsy pieces and rearrange them.
It will rip your body apart.
You'd better let our little kitty-cat go
or you're going to have a big problem!
Himekawa!
You idiot! That was crazy!
H-Hida...
But why?
I can't let you fight alone!
We're on the same team!
You need to die too.
You really are amazing.
Hey, would you tell me your name?
You should be grateful that I'm telling you.
Chidorigafuchi Aine.
A-Aine?
Would you tell me the name
of that Magitech armor too?
Magitech armor?
What's that?
This is a Heart Hybrid Gear.
Zeros.
The goddess dances with the void,
death, the Emperor, and eternity...
Are those your last words?
They don't make any sense to me!
H-Hey!
Jeez...
You guys can play with him.
There it is.
If your Magitech armor really is Zeros,
then show me your true power.
How dare you?!
Hey!
Don't push yourself too hard.
Your Hybrid Count!
You idiot!
What kind of fool leaves without permission?!
Sis!
Kurumizawa.
Roger.
Kizuna, Climax Hybrid!
The love room!
Let's go, Himekawa.
Himekawa...
I'm a terrible person!
I try to correct everyone else's behavior,
but I cause more trouble than anyone else.
My selfishness put my team in danger!
In the end, I'm no better than this.
Himekawa, what happened with you
and that Magitech weapon?
It's not my first time...
...fighting that Magitech weapon.
During the second world collision, my mission was
to escort the evacuees aboard the Megafloat.
That's when that Magitech weapon appeared.
I couldn't do anything.
I couldn't do anything!
If I had more power...
If I was just a bit stronger...
I could've protected them!
I was just acting arrogant because
everyone said I was Japan's ace.
I did so many interviews, went to so many parties,
and never trained as much as I should have.
If I'd trained harder and gotten stronger,
I could've saved so many lives!
I don't want to make that mistake ever again!
I control myself, discipline myself,
live an ordered life,
abandon my worldly desires,
and train every day so that I can give
everything I have to my mission.
That was how I decided I'd live.
But...
But you shouldn't just focus on
the lives you couldn't save.
I mean, there were a lot of people you did save.
You don't know what you're talking about.
Where can I find someone like that?
Right in front of you.
When I first came to Ataraxia,
you saved me from an attack by that Viking, right?
B-But even if I hadn't saved you—
I couldn't fight back then.
You saved me, which is why I was able
to save Yurishia and Aine later.
You've saved a lot of people.
You just don't realize it.
That's not...
I know how you feel.
What could you possibly know?
I had a Heart Hybrid Gear, but I couldn't fight.
I wanted to protect other people,
but in reality, I couldn't even protect myself.
But now, if the two of us
work together, we can fight.
If we Climax Hybrid and bring out the
Immoral Weapon lying dormant within you,
we can defeat Tri-Head.
We can defeat Tri-Head?
Yeah.
If we work... together?
Will you do it?
No...
Your breasts are so great.
Can you show them to me?
I don't know how you can say something
so indecent with a straight face.
You think my breasts are small, don't you?
That's not true.
You're lying.
I know you're comparing them
to Aine's and Yurishia's!
N-No! Not there!
N-No, I can't!
You're sensitive, aren't you?
N-No, th-this is...
Your breasts are just as good
as Aine's and Yurishia's.
R-Really?
Yeah.
I'm glad.
N-No!
N-No! This is too embarrassing!
So this is a Heart Hybrid...
It's like the whole world's changed.
We're just getting started.
Hida, what is this?
I prepared a situation I thought you'd like.
Th-This is...
I don't like this!
No!
Himekawa, are you okay?
Yes, but...
Don't touch me there too much!
I-I told you not to do that!
Himekawa, this isn't...
I-I don't meow!
Don't ask!
It's nothing! It's nothing!
Don't pull it!
Got it.
Are you okay, Himekawa?
I'm fine.
Just don't touch my tail anymore.
I'm sorry, Himekawa.
We have to make our Climax Hybrid a success.
So this is a Climax Hybrid...
What is that?
Neros!
Gladius!
Himekawa Hayuru! Here I come!
I'll never forget how I failed to protect Japan,
or all the people I couldn't save,
or that girl's smile.
But I won't let it stop me anymore!
Begone.
In one hit?
What the hell is that?
I could tell you,
but there are things we want
to learn from you first!
I just saw how you move, so I think it'll be difficult!
Eros has no weapons.
Is there no point in doing a Climax Hybrid with it?
If I had Neros' weapon...
Is this...?
What?
Neros' blade?
It's probably an effect of his
Climax Hybrid with Himekawa.
But... does this mean Eros is also
capable of creating matter?
That's an interesting power you've got.
Blades!
There's nowhere left to run.
I didn't expect this to be so much fun.
I'm glad I came to Lemuria after all.
Enemy battleship incoming!
500-meter class!
Three more of them!
And four 1000-meter classes!
So many—
2000-meter class, incoming!
Well, I'll get serious now.
Time for you to die.
Is that...?
What's that?
Is that from the other dimension?
Nope.
They're allies.
That light...
America's Heart Hybrid Gear unit.
The Masters.
This is getting even more fun.
Now, let's dance—
Aldea.
You're satisfied, right?
Come back.
Grabel.
What are you doing here?
I came to capture an idiot who
disobeyed orders and broke regulations.
Don't be such a wet blanket.
Things are just about to get good.
Aldea!
Fine.
The enemy fleet is retreating into the Entrance!
It's a message from Megafloat West USA.
"Hi, girls. The cavalry's here.
Now that we're here, you're safe.
Start picking out your dresses
for the victory party."
Ask them what they're doing here.
Um, what are you doing here?
Huh?
You're tracing a mysterious radio signal?
So the same thing as us?
Did that fleet come just to get Aldea?
I'm curious about the other dimension...
But I'm a lot more interested in Hayuru right now.
Wh-What?
You clearly did a Climax Hybrid, didn't you?
No way.
Hayuru never shuts up about how
much she hates indecent things.
No, it's impossible.
I can't believe anybody but me could
do a Climax Hybrid with Kizuna.
I did!
Kizuna and I, together!
But I didn't have a choice because
it was for my mission!
I won't let you do anything
indecent that's not necessary.
What?
Now there's nothing for us to do.
Well, I guess they must have
gotten scared of us and ran.
Scarlet?
It's been a long time.
You seem to be doing well.
Stay away!
I'm never going to forgive you.
How about an apple, Snow White? Relax, it's safe
You know, that shit-eating grin really pisses me off
I'm gonna punch you
Forgive me for being cold to you
It's just that there was this girl looking at you in the cafe
I'm gonna kill her
She'd probably leave you before the night is over
Let me show you the storm of emotions trapped beneath the surface
Go beyond your dreams, love's waiting for you there
What do you want so badly that you'd cry for it?
All I want is your heart's warmth
There's no escape from the love that's seeping through your veins
Hold me, hold your breath
You're my prince
Just kidding
Illustration
Shonan Ruizu
Hi, everybody!
It's Scarlet, from the Masters!
Now that we're here, everything will be okay!
No matter what enemy may come,
I'll send them to hell with a single shot!
NEXT TIME
IMPERIAL HERO -GRABEL-
Yurishia, I'll never let you beat me!