We'll have to swap out 10,000
square meters of ground surface unit.
ONE WEEK LATER
Fourteen commercial buildings were
either partially or completely destroyed.
Damage to six other sectors has been reported.
The underground lifelines were affected
as well, but they will be repaired soon.
We were lucky the enemy
landed in a commercial area.
Not many people were out since it was a weekday
afternoon, which kept casualties to a minimum.
Kizuna.
Kizuna!
I'm back, everyone.
Are your injuries all right now?
Yeah.
I can't stay in bed any longer.
She was far stronger than Aldea,
the one you fought in Guam.
I want to wait for further analysis on the
Magitech armor and combat capabilities
of the woman from the other dimension
who attacked Ataraxia, Grabel.
What's most important now is that the
enemy's target was Zeros, as well as Aine.
Why would they be after Zeros and Aine?
Aine, you have any idea?
No.
I'd like to know myself.
Aine...
To take back Japan, we need to close
the Tokyo and Okinawa entrances.
We've headed north from Guam,
and we are presently 500km southeast of Okinawa.
We'll start by sealing the Okinawa entrance.
But Grabel is there.
We'll have to defeat her
if we wish to take back Japan.
She's strong.
We'll need a new Hybrid to defeat her:
the Connective Hybrid.
Connective Hybrid?
A Connective Hybrid is when Eros and two other
units engage in a simultaneous Hybrid Heart.
Wow!
In other words...
The energy created is overwhelming.
It allows for a far more powerful offensive
energy charge than the normal Heart Hybrid.
Sounds fun!
It's the same as a Climax Hybrid.
You'll be able to acquire a more powerful
Immoral Weapon through the Connective Hybrid.
We'll have to go that hard?
What in the world are you trying to make us do?!
Doing it with another girl...
That's so indecent! I just can't!
The Heart Hybrid and Climax Hybrid unite two
hearts and bodies to share both love and pleasure.
But if you simply want to power up,
a new form of stimulation and a greater feeling
of depravity would prove most effective.
The Connective Hybrid
makes both of them possible.
Th-That's so indecent! It's immoral!
That's not all.
The Connective Hybrid uses a new kind of
emotional energy that the previous ones haven't.
The love Kizuna feels for each of them,
and the friendship and trust between the girls.
The result of these emotions and their combination,
which is impossible with a Heart Hybrid,
allows for far greater power
than you would ever attain alone.
Then I suggest Yurishia and Scarlet.
My love for you is like a bucking colt
You act so innocent, but I know you're feeling it
I'm not a wizard anymore
The craziest things you can imagine all start from nothing
It's like we're in a fairy tale
But this is real life
My charm makes you swoon
Our hearts beat in unison
Just let your passion explode
My feelings won't reach you like this
I need to shoot them at you with everything I've got
They're on a direct course to your heart
My spirit is on fire
I'll expose your true nature
Don't worry, I'll be gentle
I'll take you to a secret paradise
And offer you a grand feast
When the two of us become one
An innocent flower blooms
Episode 8
If only I were stronger...
Scarlet, I'm sorry to call you out of the blue,
but can you join me for a while?
We have a new training facility
that'll help you power up in a flash.
Power up in a flash?
How is this a training facility
that helps you power up?!
Mobile
Mobile Hybrid Special Bath Mk. 2
And you didn't say anything
about Yurishia being here!
If you're going to power up,
it's better that I do both of you at once, right?
I-Is this what a H-Heart Hybrid is like?
If this is enough make you embarrassed,
you're still a kid.
I'm so happy I get to take a bath with Kizuna.
But, Yurishia, it's kind of bad
if you get that close to me.
Get off each other, you two!
You okay, Scarlet?
Y-Yurishia?
I wanna hear the sound of Kizuna's heartbeat.
S-So soft...
Your back's pretty sensitive, isn't it?
It's ticklish, but it kinda feels good...
Kizuna!
I don't think I can do this!
I'm also kind of...
No, I can't!
No!
What is this?
Something's happening inside me...
It's so gentle and warm.
Okay, we're moving to the next stage.
My whole body feels warm...
Take yours off too, Scarlet.
K-Kizuna, you too.
O-Okay...
What's wrong?
Do you want to play with them?
I-I just l-lost my balance...
Oh my...
You always used to follow me around, right?
I figured that's what you used to be like.
Wh-What is this?
I asked Shikina to get me old footage of you two.
Why'd you do that?
Oh, Kizuna...
That's when I first started
fighting together with Yurishia.
We trained together.
We laughed together.
We cried together.
Yurishia...
You weren't the kind of person who'd do that.
You wouldn't betray us.
You wouldn't use us as pawns.
So why?
Yurishia.
You actually didn't know the Dragorie
was going to appear, did you?
Yurishia...
The enemy had attacked an urban area.
There was a risk that Scarlet's missiles
might miss and hit the town and civilians.
If any innocents died because of that,
I didn't think she'd ever recover.
So...
I lied to get her and the others away.
You lied?
I hear there's an enemy attack from a new Entrance!
I'll stay here to fight the enemy.
So you...
Okay!
I'll head there now!
I didn't think the enemy would actually appear.
But it's a fact that I ended up
taking all the credit for myself.
So in a way, I really did use you
to become a super ace.
That's right.
She never even got hit by the Dragorie.
She was hurt 'cause she'd been
fighting other enemies on her own...
And she still came for us anyway!
Now, how about we attack Kizuna together?
Okay, Kizuna.
Grab both of us tight!
Okay!
Does that feel good?
Yeah...
Of course it does.
Kizuna, don't forget about me, okay?
I need to make them feel good too.
W-Wow!
No... No more!
Okay!
The Connective Hybrid's almost complete!
Kizuna, I feel weird!
I don't know what's going on!
There's an ache inside my body...
I want to feel you closer to me...
Which will you choose?
We recommend both.
Who do I pick? Yurishia? Scarlet?
Don't panic. Think calmly.
This is a Connective Hybrid.
You can't just choose one!
What is this?
Feels like I'm being filled with power...
This is a Climax Hybrid.
No, a Connective Hybrid, isn't it?
Looks like it worked out, Kizuna.
Yeah.
Today, we'll split into two teams for the operation.
We'll attack Grabel and seal
the Entrance all at once.
Roger!
Let's go! Eros!
Kuros!
Ares!
H-Hey, Yurishia...
What?
If you really want, I can let you
be leader of the Masters.
Nuh-uh.
You're the leader of the Masters,
aren't you, Scarlet?
And, right now,
I'm Yurishia Farandole of Amaterasu.
We're ready to go whenever.
No, this time they'll come to us.
They'll come. I know it.
They're here?
I've been waiting!
I'll take good care of you.
You're Grabel, right?
I want to ask you something.
Ask me what?
Why are you trying to take me with you?
Silver hair, red eyes.
And the Zeros you wield.
You're—
Aine, are you okay?
Let us handle those two!
We'll pay them back for last time!
You defend the Entrance sealing system!
There are too many enemies for Kizuna and the others to handle.
Fine!
I won't let you go.
Scarlet!
Roger!
Shoot!
So many!
My, not bad!
Now, Yurishia! Go ahead!
Leave it to me.
Cross Head.
That's...
...Yurishia's...
...Immoral Weapon!
Aldea!
Drive!
You did it! You did it, Yurishia!
I'm not the type who likes to stay on the losing end.
You're so amazing, Yurishia!
No...
She survived that?
I will bring my full powers to bear against you.
This is my real weapon, the Gatlingblade.
Kizuna!
Are you two okay?
You're the man from before?
Why are you trying to take Aine with you?
I see no reason to answer that.
Kuros Mode!
Come, Grabel!
Very well!
What I need is enough firepower
to defeat her weapon.
A gun,
a rifle,
a cannon,
a machine gun,
a rail gun,
a particle gun,
the Differential Flame...
I want them!
Wh-What?
Is he carrying an entire military arsenal on his back?
Go, Gatlingblade!
I'm coming too!
Kuros's light...
So I can't overwhelm him with this?
That's not nearly enough!
More!
I need more!
I need more firepower...
Like Scarlet's...
Hybrid Mode!
Ares's missiles...
How could I... lose...?
Kizuna!
Aldea...
I'll back off for now.
Next time, you will be mine.
All Entrances on Okinawa have been sealed.
All enemy unit signals have disappeared as well.
Amaterasu, and Scarlet of the Masters, are all safe.
We won!
We did it, Kizuna!
You were so cool!
Hey!
Get away from him!
Yeah, it's thanks to all of you.
You actually did it with two girls at once...
How perverted!
N-No, it wasn't...
Oh, then what was it?
Just get away from him!
Next time, you will be mine.
Just who am I?
How about an apple, Snow White? Relax, it's safe
You know, that shit-eating grin really pisses me off
I'm gonna punch you
Forgive me for being cold to you
It's just that there was this girl looking at you in the cafe
I'm gonna kill her
She'd probably leave you before the night is over
Let me show you the storm of emotions trapped beneath the surface
Go beyond your dreams, love's waiting for you there
What do you want so badly that you'd cry for it?
All I want is your heart's warmth
There's no escape from the love that's seeping through your veins
Hold me, hold your breath
You're my prince
Just kidding
Illustration
Kenichiro Kasutani
An important mission is about to begin!
I just wish I could be a little more useful...
What? You want me to go in Aine's place?
That's your order as captain?
NEXT TIME
Academy Festa -First Live-
What do I do?
It's my first time, and I'm so excited!