I wanna be like her someday.
You're always so amazing, Chidorigafuchi.
I'm tired of trite compliments like "amazing."
Of course, with your intellect,
I'm sure that's the best you're capable of.
Well, excuse me.
And I was only up against a dummy Magitech built by
the Engineering Division, so of course it was easy.
Well, excuse us!
After all, I'm here to kill the enemy.
Cut them to pieces! Blade!
Fire!
Himekawa's the best!
OMG, Julicia!
The destructive powers of Neros and Kuros
really are on another level, huh?
We need to develop weapons
that are as good as Amaterasu's!
Chidorigafuchi?
My love for you is like a bucking colt
You act so innocent, but I know you're feeling it
I'm not a wizard anymore
I have no idea how things ended up this way
It's like we're in a fairy tale
But this is real life
My charm makes you swoon
Our hearts beat in unison
Just let your passion explode
My feelings won't reach you like this
I need to shoot them at you with everything I've got
I can feel victory with all my heart
My spirit is on fire
I'll expose your true nature
Don't worry, I'll be gentle
I'll take you to a secret paradise
I'll make your mind go blank
When the two of us become one
An innocent flower blooms
Episode 3
Gentle Days - Memories
So that data was accurate after all.
Like Aine, Julicia was also able to
successfully perform a Heart Hybrid.
Now we can proceed as planned.
However...
The genius scientist, Dr. Hida Nayuta,
developed our strongest weapons, the only ones
that can take on Magitechs: the Heart Hybrid Gears.
But...
Great power always comes
at an even greater price, huh?
I wonder what expression
she's got on her face now...
That woman.
Kizuna!
J-Julicia?
So, what did you think when you
saw me doing the training exercise?
You fell in love a little, didn't you?
U-Um...
No wonder you're the American ace.
I was impressed. Really.
Do you really mean that?
Then give me a reward.
Wow! Fantastic!
Why'd you want to go to the
Kyoto float for your reward?
Well, I've always wanted to go sightseeing.
Hey, Kizuna, is this temple the real deal?
It's a replica.
There wasn't enough time to get all our
cultural assets onto the megafloats.
I see.
I want to see the real one someday.
You will.
Once we all go back to Japan.
That's why we're fighting.
Okay, Kizuna.
Let's head to the next one!
Next?
Didn't expect to spend the
entire day touring the megafloat.
It's not all that big, but it still feels
like we've traveled all over Japan.
Sorry for dragging you along.
But it was so much fun!
You're really proactive, Julicia.
Not many people would act on a crazy idea
like this, even if they did think of it.
You're right.
I think I've changed.
Changed?
When we were attacked by that Magitech
weapon on the uninhabited island,
I thought I might die,
for the first time in my life.
But when you saved me, this is what I felt:
I want to live my life to the fullest.
Julicia.
I want to have more fun.
I want to do plenty more things,
like fall in love with a boy.
No, I...
It's thanks to you that I can feel this way.
Thank you.
I don't mind her saying thanks,
but I'm not so sure about this...
Hey, is that you, Himekawa?
Hida?
Do you always stay at school this late?
The disciplinary committee sure has it rough.
There's no end to students causing problems.
Especially indecent boys.
But I like this school.
I want to make the lives of my
fellow students as fun as possible.
That is my desire, as well as my duty.
You're really dedicated, huh?
I like that.
L-Like?
Wh-What are you saying?
That's indecent!
Himekawa...
H-Hida...
A Heart Hybrid?
In an instant?
Why?
How could I be so indecent?
Chidorigafuchi?
Aine's always like that.
She always trains by herself.
I wanted to spar with her,
but she just ignored me when I asked.
At this point, everyone keeps
their distance from her.
She has a strange obsession with fighting.
Julicia and I don't know
what she's thinking, either.
Even though we're all part of Amaterasu.
After all, I'm here to fight.
So he managed to do it with Himekawa?
Guess I can't run away now.
Chidorigafuchi?
She only joined us in high school,
so I don't know any details.
Come to think of it, I've never seen her smile.
I see...
U-Um...
Can I go?
Y-Yeah...
So, why exactly are you talking about me?
Well, this sucks.
This is a good chance to learn about
Chidorigafuchi, but what do I say?
Hey.
Have you eaten yet?
No, not yet.
I see.
I guess I'll give you this, then.
Be grateful.
That looks good.
Are these handmade?
Yes.
I bought them at a convenience store,
cut them in half, and put them in a lunchbox.
I don't think that qualifies as handmade.
I see.
How would you define "handmade," then?
Huh?
How strict is the definition?
If I can't use something that's already been made,
I'd have to grow my own wheat for the bread, right?
Oh, I'd have to go catch the tuna, too.
I'll be right back. Can you wait here?
I'm sorry!
I'm really grateful!
As long as you understand.
What am I doing here again?
Thank you.
Wait.
There's one other thing I want you to eat.
Dessert or something?
H-Hey, you can't mean—?!
Wh-Wh-What are you doing?
We're in broad daylight!
I read in a book that if you do it in a place like this,
the immorality of it turns the guy on more.
What kind of book did you read?
I-It doesn't matter!
Come, Hybrid Heart with me right now!
Are you...?
Wh-What are you talking about, you worm?
Do you think that I, of all people,
would be scared of something like this?
But you're shaking.
I'm about to get my Immoral Weapon.
I'm so happy, I'm shaking.
Immoral Weapon?
What's that... Wait!
Is this still not good enough?
Why am I getting excited?
Bet she's wearing a pilot suit underneath like before—
Or not!
Go ahead. You can touch them.
But...
Hurry up.
W-Wait!
They're so soft...
Th-This is weird!
You can't force it...
And, I mean, you have to think about
how the other person feels.
I don't care.
I can't lose.
I can't let Julicia and Hayuru beat me forever.
You...
I want power.
If I can get some...
I don't care what happens to me!
Fine.
Hey...
We're doing a Heart Hybrid, right?
I can't do it.
Not when you've got that look on your face.
You don't know anything about me, right?
And I don't know anything about you.
So, like, we should spend some time
getting to know each other.
That's impossible.
Impossible?
H-Hey!
Sis?
Hello?
Kizuna, it's Reiri.
I need to talk to you.
Can we meet?
Y-Yeah.
Here.
Do you remember this room, Kizuna?
Yeah.
I could never forget it.
This is...
This is the place...
...where it all began.
I underwent the Core Install surgery
for the Heart Hybrid Gear.
Right here.
I was scared.
But I still did it for Mom.
I wanted Mom's approval,
so I tried to help with the Gear experiment.
But Mom...
I'll never forget.
That's right.
Kizuna, actually...
Oh, right, there was something I wanted to ask you.
Ask me?
I want you to tell me what
you know about Chidorigafuchi.
Aine?
Why?
Because I have to know about her, I think.
What she's like, where she came from,
why she's here...
I want to know.
There are no records of her early life.
Seven years ago, in Chidorigafuchi, Tokyo,
a girl with no known identity was found.
She had no memories and couldn't
even remember her name or identity.
Was that...
Yes, that was Aine.
In order to help identify her,
she was given a physical.
That's when the researchers found
she had a high Gear compatibility.
So the lab took her in as
a test subject for that woman.
Hello, Chidorigafuchi Aine.
Aine...
Then...
Chidorigafuchi Aine is the name
that woman gave her.
After she took her in, her life at the lab began.
All she ever did was take part in experiments.
But they suddenly came to an end
when Hida Nayuta disappeared.
That woman disappeared one day,
and we still don't know why.
Or, of course, where she went.
That's all I know.
I see.
She's...
She's always been alone, huh?
It might take time, but I'm sure
we'll come to understand each other.
Sorry, but our time is limited.
What do you mean?
The archive you're about to see
was only recently discovered.
No one but Reiri and I know about it.
Be careful.
It will link with your vision.
Linkage.
It hurts...
I can't take any more....
Continue, please.
But my Hybrid Count...
All right.
We'll take control of the Gear from here, then.
Dr. Nayuta?
No... Doctor... Stop!
Output increasing.
Someone, stop!
Count has entered the danger zone.
Stop it! No! I don't want to die!
Subject's vitals are yellow.
Count remaining:
I'm going to die!
7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
No!
Count zero.
Vitals lost.
Increasing maximum output value by 5.0.
Thank you.
This is useful data.
What the hell was that?
As you just saw, the Hybrid Count is the
energy source of the Heart Hybrid Gear.
At the same time, it is the life energy of the pilot.
The Eros, Zeros, Neros, and Kuros
are all entries in the Ros series.
If their count drops to zero, then...
The pilot dies.
No one else knows this.
Not even the members of Amaterasu.
But Kizuna, as the unit commander,
I wanted you to know.
You're kidding.
Then everyone...
had those cores installed
without knowing anything,
and they're risking their lives
each time they fight?
You knew that, and you
made them fight anyway?!
This fact only came to light very recently.
And besides, don't you think Reiri
suffered when she found out?
That's just another reason to find a different way!
We don't...
We don't have a choice.
This is all we have to fight the enemy.
What else can I do?
I have to order them to fight, right?
Sis...
That's my responsibility.
I'm going to hell for this, I'm sure.
But even so...
You're our one hope, Kizuna.
The Heart Hybrid...
You're the only one who can save their lives.
That is the special feature of Eros,
the Gear that was installed in you, a boy.
I'm the only one who can save them?
Welcome back, Captain!
Sylvia...
Did you make all this?
Yes!
It's my job to take care of you, Captain!
I see.
Looks good.
But are you okay?
You look tired.
No, that's not true.
I see.
If you need anything, just let me know.
I want to help you!
Thanks, Sylvia.
Captain, huh?
Hey, baby, don't be scared, just do it
You know, that shit-eating grin really pisses me off
I'm gonna punch you
Forgive me for being cold to you
It's just that there was this girl looking at you in the cafe
I'm gonna kill her
Your only future is with me
Give me your grief, your pleasure, your everything
Go beyond your dreams, love's waiting for you there
What do you want so badly that you'd cry for it?
All I want is your heart's warmth
No matter how much your head spins, my love will never disappear
Hold me, hold your breath
You're my prince
Just kidding
An enemy fleet has appeared!
Illustration
Keita Hagio
I want my Immoral Weapon.
Because fighting is the only reason
I'm allowed to be here.
That's not true!
Tell me who you really are, Aine.
NEXT TIME
D-Don't call me by my first name...
Dummy.