No... Not there...
Jeez, hurry up and climax already.
N-No, Kizuna, that's my...
I guess this is the right spot.
I'm surprised you're so sensitive, Himekawa.
Th-That's not true!
I-I'm just doing this 'cause it's part of our mission!
I'll finish it now!
Take this!
No!
Yes!
Heart Hybrid successful!
Charging is complete, Himekawa!
You're finally done.
Julicia!
Your Heart Hybrid always takes so long, Hayuru.
Well, you were having a good time, I suppose.
Th-That's crass slander!
I would never do something
so indecent for such a reason!
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
Anyway, now that you've recharged, get to work.
Of course!
Neros!
See you.
Aine!
Aine?
A-Aine? What do you think you're doing?
It's supposed to be my turn now! No fair!
Talk about an annoying crowd.
Wha—
Aine?
Kizuna, do me right now.
Huh? But your Hybrid Count is still high.
I want to use the forbidden weapon
to change the course of this battle.
But that's...
Don't worry, Kizuna.
I'm me.
No matter what happens, that won't change.
So just do me...
Let's Climax Hybrid.
My love for you is like a bucking colt
You act so innocent, but I know you're feeling it
I'm not a wizard anymore
The craziest things you can imagine all start from nothing
It's like we're in a fairy tale
But this is real life
My charm makes you swoon
Our hearts beat in unison
Just let your passion explode
My feelings won't reach you like this
I need to shoot them at you with everything I've got
They're on a direct course to your heart
My spirit is on fire
I'll expose your true nature
Don't worry, I'll be gentle
I'll take you to a secret paradise
And offer you a grand feast
When the two of us become one
An innocent flower blooms
EPISODE 1
STRATEGIC DEFENSE ACADEMY ATARAXIA
W-Wait up, Mom!
Goodbye, Kizuna.
You're not needed anymore.
I must be really nervous if
I'm having dreams like that.
Seriously, what's Sis planning?
Dear Kizuna,
I filled out all the paperwork for you to attend Ataraxia.
Go there immediately.
Report to HQ at noon tomorrow.
I filled out all the paperwork for you to attend Ataraxia.
Go there immediately.
Report to HQ at noon tomorrow.
I filled out all the paperwork for you to attend Ataraxia.
Go there immediately.
Report to HQ at noon tomorrow.
I filled out all the paperwork for you to attend Ataraxia.
Go there immediately.
Report to HQ at noon tomorrow.
Reiri
I filled out all the paperwork for you to attend Ataraxia.
Go there immediately.
Report to HQ at noon tomorrow.
Reiri
I filled out all the paperwork for you to attend Ataraxia.
Go there immediately.
Report to HQ at noon tomorrow.
Reiri
I filled out all the paperwork for you to attend Ataraxia.
Go there immediately.
Report to HQ at noon tomorrow.
Reiri
I filled out all the paperwork for you to attend Ataraxia.
Go there immediately.
Report to HQ at noon tomorrow.
Reiri
I filled out all the paperwork for you to attend Ataraxia.
Go there immediately.
Report to HQ at noon tomorrow.
Reiri
I filled out all the paperwork for you to attend Ataraxia.
Go there immediately.
Report to HQ at noon tomorrow.
I filled out all the paperwork for you to attend Ataraxia.
Go there immediately.
Report to HQ at noon tomorrow.
I filled out all the paperwork for you to attend Ataraxia.
Go there immediately.
Report to HQ at noon tomorrow.
Dear Kizuna, I filled out all the paperwork
for you to attend Ataraxia.
Go there immediately.
Report to HQ at noon tomorrow.
Reiri.
I hear from her after ages, and that's all she says?
Though I came anyway, so I'm one to talk.
Arriving at Ataraxia now.
Please have your ID ready for the border crossing.
Welcome to Ataraxia.
So this is the research facility that's been training
people to fight against the otherworld invasion—
the Strategic Defense Academy Ataraxia.
Are you a transfer student?
Hello there!
That's Julicia for you.
You can say that again.
Hey!
Wait!
I can't ignore something so indecent!
So I'm going to be living here now?
It feels so surreal.
That guy must've dropped this.
H-Hello?
Kizuna, did you make it here okay?
Sis!
Yeah, just now.
But is it really okay for me to be here?
My grades aren't all that great,
and I was already kicked out of here once.
I don't want to hear your excuses!
I need you and your Heart Hybrid Gear.
What are you talking about?
It's not gonna be useful for anything now.
Shut up and get your ass to HQ, Hida Kizuna!
I always get what I want!
I want that thing that was
installed in you, the Er—
I-I'm coming!
I'm coming right now,
so please don't say another word!
I'm lost...
Wh-Where's HQ?
Who are you?
U-Um...
Do you lack the intelligence required
to understand language?
I've never met a creature like you before.
Uh, I'm Hida Kizuna.
From now on, I'll be going to school here.
You're a student here, right?
What else could I be?
Do you think I'm a weirdo who got
a uniform and snuck through security
just so I could take a look at the scenery?
You don't need to be so touchy.
Touchy?
Why would I waste my time being touchy with you?
It would make more sense for you
to get on your knees and beg me.
Beg to kiss my feet.
I'm not gonna beg for that!
You're lying, you inferior creature.
What's with this girl?
She's hot as hell, but her personality's not so swell.
I'm Chidorigafuchi Aine, from Class 2-A.
Now worship me!
Hell no!
Sheesh...
An air raid siren?
An air raid?
This place is supposed to be in the safe zone.
Their ships shouldn't be able to reach this far.
This is Ataraxia.
There'd never be a false alarm here.
The enemy really has appeared.
The enemy...
You need to run.
W-Wait!
What are you doing?
What if someone sees you?
The only one watching is you!
I told you to run, you lecher.
Y-You're the one who started
stripping, you exhibitionist.
Just look away.
That way, there won't be a problem.
Right now, I'm a poor victim,
and you're a perverted Peeping Tom.
Who are you calling a pervert?
A pilot suit?
You can't be...
Zeros!
A Heart Hybrid Gear!
She has a core installed, too?
Chidorigafuchi Aine, your Heart Hybrid
Gear has little charge left.
You can't fight for long.
You don't have to spell out the obvious.
A Magitech weapon?!
I should go, too.
What's all that stuff doing here?
I guess normal weapons won't work after all.
Sh-She hit it?
What an absurd fighting style.
There's an interception system here, too?
Wow! You just defeated a Magitech
with a normal gun and your bare hands.
Are there weapons hidden everywhere?
Of course.
We never know when the enemy will attack.
And fighting Magitech weapons
is Amaterasu's mission.
Amaterasu...
They never learn.
Evacuate quickly.
If you don't, you'll die.
Shouldn't I fight, too?
You're not needed anymore.
Hard work means nothing
without the talent to back it up.
Talent can be honed, but if there's none
to work with in the first place...
There's nothing that can be done.
Sure, my Heart Hybrid Gear has very little power.
But if I equip it, maybe I can do something.
Er... Er... Er...
I can't do it! I can't say its name!
Blade!
What's an off-campus student doing here?!
This is an emergency!
You have a Hybrid Gear, too?
Hey!
We'll be in trouble if all of us aren't fighting,
so could you please not slack off?
Oh, is that your boyfriend?
H-H-He couldn't possibly be my boyfriend!
How indecent!
We have a more important, more noble goal!
Okay, okay.
Let's go take out the descending
Magitech weapons, then.
If we don't hurry, Ataraxia will be wiped out.
I know that!
You get to a shelter immediately!
Understood?
Those girls are fighting, and I'm just...
I can handle this, too.
My Hybrid Count...
Is something wrong with her?
A-Are you serious?
What do I do?
What do I do? What do I do?
Listen, Kizuna.
A person's value isn't decided by their abilities.
It's decided by how they live.
Sis!
Eros!
Make it in time!
Ow...
Seriously, how is it so freaking weak?
Hey, Chidorigafuchi! Pull yourself together!
Are you okay?
Damn it! What the hell do I do?
Kizuna, can you hear me?
Sis! Is that you?
Good, I'm in a bad—
Shut up!
I know the situation.
If you want to save Aine, do exactly as I say.
Fine. What should I do?
First, fondle Aine's breasts.
Okay.
What are you making me do?
Be gentler.
Fondle them like crazy, but gently.
No, I mean, why am I fondling a girl I just met?
Don't think! Feel!
Feel her heart and body.
Her heart and body?
If you can't do that, both of you will die.
If you want to get out of this situation
and save Aine, it's the only way!
Only you can do this, Kizuna!
O-Only me?
Just think of it this way:
You're checking her body for wounds.
Check every nook and cranny.
O-Okay. I can do that.
Chidorigafuchi?
Just keep going!
O-Okay. Got it.
I-I didn't know a girl's body was so soft.
Now spread her legs.
Get in between them and look. Carefully.
Okay.
It really just seems like I'm feeling this girl up...
And...
No!
I-It's digging in so deep.
What was that shaking?
Did a cannon hit?
Hurry! You're running out of time!
I thought I was going to... suffocate...
Is this the light of her Heart Hybrid Gear?
She's so cute...
Now, Kizuna! Feel up her breasts!
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm doing what you said...
Harder!
But that's not...
Do it now, and do it hard!
Success!
Well done, Kizuna!
S-Success?
The Heart Hybrid was a success!
Heart Hybrid?
A mixing of heart and love.
That is the true power of the Heart Hybrid Gear!
Are you okay?
Hey, Chidorigafuchi!
What did you do while I was unconscious?
I feel so light.
No way. My Hybrid Count...
It was almost zero.
Aine!
Commander! What is this?
I'll explain later. Can you fight?
Yes!
Zeros!
This power...
I can do it!
Chidorigafuchi?
She's crazy.
Wow!
That's amazing, Aine!
You defeated that huge army.
Julicia! Hayuru!
Where's the enemy carrier?
Retreating...
Yes.
But we destroyed most of the enemy's
Magitech weapons, so let's be happy with that.
But what happened?
Aine was like a totally different person just now.
Oh?
Is that...
Who...
...are you?
What was that?
For now,
we've made it through the first stage.
The mission has only just begun, but the Hybrid
Heart is the key to the success of this mission!
The key to retaking the mainland...
Retaking the world we lost!
How about an apple, Snow White? Relax, it's safe
You know, that shit-eating grin really pisses me off
I'm gonna punch you
Forgive me for being cold to you
It's just that there was this girl looking at you in the cafe
I'm gonna kill her
She'd probably leave you before the night is over
Let me show you the storm of emotions trapped beneath the surface
Go beyond your dreams, love's waiting for you there
What do you want so badly that you'd cry for it?
All I want is your heart's warmth
There's no escape from the love that's seeping through your veins
Hold me, hold your breath
You're my prince
Just kidding
Illustration
Kana Miyai
What's with him?
How he could do that, or that, to me of all people?
You'll pay for this, Hida Kizuna!
But if I can gain power that way, I...
NEXT TIME