Chapter 5
Yumemi's Wish
My pre-emptive strike failed.
That makes things difficult.
I've got two grenades left.
I need to get as close as possible, take out its legs.
Then aim for the topside armor
and knock it out of commission.
Doesn't waste ammo, I see.
Standard operating protocol when faced
with an enemy of unknown firepower.
Then resumes suppressive fire...
Knew it!
One... two... three!
Shit... my ears...
Need to assess the situation!
It takes thirty seconds to reload.
Won't be long before it fires again!
A fracture?
An eye for an eye, a leg for a leg, is it?
Why did you do such a stupid thing?!
Welcome back, Mr. Customer.
Are you hurt?
I told you to stay put until I got back!
The unregistered machine appeared
to be in a rampant state.
A force-stop signal was sent, but was ignored.
The receiver may have been out of order,
so an emergency physical shutdown
was attempted, and failed.
The rampant machine appears
to have ceased functioning.
Please step away from the rampant machine
and report this incident to a nearby
police station or support center.
My sincerest apologies for
violating a critical directive.
However, there was an older promise I had to keep.
I must not knowingly allow
any human being to come to harm.
Keeping this promise is the pride of us robots.
Mr. Customer,
are you injured?
No,
I'm fine.
That is most relieving to hear.
I apologize on his behalf.
I believe he may have malfunctioned, too.
We robots were created
for the happiness of humans.
I'm sure he never wanted to act with such violence.
I know...
Because I, too, am slightly malfunctional.
The emergency batteries will deplete
in approximately 600 seconds.
Because the backup batteries are depleted,
I will be unable to boot after this.
I am sending a maintenance call,
but it is not being acknowledged.
I feel somewhat abandoned.
You don't need to call anyone!
I'll save you.
But...
I'll fix you.
My sincerest apologies for my disorderly state.
Please do not worry.
Since I am a robot,
I do not feel pain.
I can be repaired,
or transferred to a whole new body.
There are no longer any engineers
that can repair you...
Any bodies to replace yours...
Or any humans that need you...
Not in this world...
Please, if you maintain that facial expression,
I will be most worried.
I am a robot.
My customers' smiles are most important to me.
I remember every single one of them.
As a robot, I am good at remembering things.
I am Hoshino Yumemi.
Thank you for this wonderful name.
I will be sure to do my best.
Thank you very much.
Here you go, Yumemi!
Yumemi, thank you for the pretty stars.
I'll bring all of my friends next time,
so stay well!
Next time, I'll visit with my wife on our anniversary.
The starry sky was as beautiful
as it was when I was younger.
I hope to visit you again next year.
I learned a lot about the stars,
and I had a lot of fun!
For my summer science project,
I'll write about you, Yumemi.
Um, it was super pretty, and really moving!
I'm so gonna come again!
I love you, Yumemi!
Thank you very much.
We eagerly await your return.
Yumemi, we um...
need to go on a trip for a while.
A trip? That sounds wonderful.
Yumemi...
Could you please wait for us here until we return?
Yes, understood. When will you be returning?
That's...
W-We're not really sure yet.
But we'll be back for sure.
When that happens,
let's work together again, okay?
Do you understand, Yumemi?
Yes, Mr. Manager.
I'm so sorry, Yumemi...
To leave you out here, all alone...
Please do not worry about me.
I will be waiting here for you with
Miss Jena for as long as you need.
Please leave matters in my hands,
and enjoy your trip.
That was from 29 years and 71 days ago.
44 years and 138 days have passed since
our first projection at the planetarium.
Until you came, Mr. Customer,
time after time I wondered...
When would Mr. Manager and
the other staff members return?
When would our next customer arrive?
I always found myself reaching
the same conclusion—
that the humans would never return again.
But that was impossible.
That is why I thought I must
have been malfunctioning.
I ran my self-diagnostic program to locate the error.
However, no error could be found.
Therefore, I concluded that there must be an
unknown bug within the self-diagnostic program.
When you arrived, Mr. Customer,
I was overjoyed.
It seemed I was wrong after all.
The customers had not forgotten about me.
That is what I thought, and it made me very happy.
But again, I was wrong about that.
There was nothing wrong with me.
What's wrong was...
Why is the world all wrong...?
The emergency batteries will deplete
in approximately 150 seconds.
Because the backup batteries are depleted,
I will be unable to boot after this.
I can record one more message.
Mr. Customer,
to commemorate your visit to our planetarium,
please record a message with me.
Listen closely.
Yes, sir.
To tell you the truth,
I came to get you.
Could you clarify?
On the other side of that wall
is a new workplace for you.
Your projector partner, your coworkers,
they're all waiting for you there.
There's also a venue full of customers,
all waiting for you too.
Everyone's eagerly waiting for your commentary.
That's your new workplace, starting today.
You can work there
for as long as you want.
That's just like Heaven, is it not?
Yeah...
Yeah, it is.
I finally understood who you are, Mr. Customer.
Mr. Customer, will you hear my wish?
Sure, what is it?
Behind my ear receiver
is a memory card slot.
All of my memories are stored there.
Each and every one is precious to me.
Could I ask you to deliver it to my new workplace?
If you can provide me with a new body,
I can start working on that very day.
I can continue working for people
for as long as I am allowed.
So, to tell you the truth,
I do not need a heaven.
However, if I must go to Heaven,
please, God,
do not divide Heaven in two.
Please do not divide robots and humans.
I would very much like to work
for humans... forever and ever...
I understand. I will do as you wish.
Yes. Thank you... very much...
I am overjoyed.
Mr. Customer?
Where did you go?
Are you there?
I wonder...
It seems I am indeed
malfunctioning slightly, after all.
I am an Economy Edition model,
I lack the capability to shed tears.
However, if I did have that functionality,
I believe I would most likely be crying now.
I believe the tears would never stop.
But I am very happy.
I am filled with a joyous feeling.
So... why?
I wonder what my new workplace will be like?
I must be in top condition,
so that I can welcome my guests
whenever they arrive.
Why don't you come to the planetarium?
The beautiful twinkling
of eternity...
I'd better get going...
The scorpion, eyes stained in deepest red
The soaring eagle, wings spread wide
The puppy, eyes of piercing blue
The coiled serpent, forged of brilliant light
From above, Orion sings tearfully
Crystallizing into dew and frost, they fall
Stare at the cloud of Andromeda
And a fish's mouth stares back
If the big bear journeys north
Taking five full steps
Above the forehead of the little bear
Do the heavens revolve
The scorpion, eyes stained in deepest red
The soaring eagle, wings spread wide
The puppy, eyes of piercing blue
The coiled serpent, forged of brilliant light
From above, Orion sings tearfully
Crystallizing into dew and frost, they fall
Stare at the cloud of Andromeda
And a fish's mouth stares back
If the big bear journeys north
Taking five full steps
Above the forehead of the little bear
Do the heavens revolve
Hey, you alive?
Probably.
You a Junker too?
No... I'm...
a starteller.