One day in September
School District 7, Bridge 3
Patient is a 16-year-old female, Hitokawa Hasami.
Fell from Bridge 3 in School District 7 into the river.
Pocket contained what appears to be a suicide note.
H-Huh? I'm still alive...
No pulse. Currently attempting resuscitation.
Aww, I can't even die right.
Damn. I'm a failure at everything I do.
She appears to have regained consciousness.
That explains it. She's a Level 2 pyrokinesist.
Not a bad category.
Her ability is suited for combat.
Best of all, attempting suicide was an act of evil.
Huh?
Good. Let's go ahead and dispose of her.
Acknowledged. So then, following
Hitokawa Hasami's plunge into the river,
attempts to resuscitate her
proved ineffective, and she drowned.
Are you sure about the liquid?
They won't figure it out at the autopsy?
We're making sure to use water from the river.
Rest easy. We will use your body
to serve the cause of justice.
By DA's dogma.
Everything reflects the darkness
A Certain Scientific Accelerator
The pitch-black town is coated
In light from countless windows
It shines across the barren streets
I sneer at all the shadows
As I remain constricted
By the chain wrapped around my neck
Everything reflects the darkness
When it's inside of my hand
Shadow is the light
I will bear the burden
Of the hell that's in my past
These bloodstained memories I bear
Though they haunt my mind
Fighting dark with darkness
I will still destroy all of
These shadows cast in days gone by
I'll never change
Everything reflects the darkness
When it's inside of my hand
Three days later
Raiser of the Dead
Necromancer
They're reanimating even dog corpses!
Nobody told me about this!
Here.
Antibiotics.
Once the infection takes hold,
it'll be too late. Inject yourself.
HQ calling Alpha. Report your status.
This is Alpha. One injured.
Bravo is currently pursuing target.
We've located the facility she broke into,
but it's been designated off-limits.
If it's off-limits in that area,
you must mean the hospital.
Requesting confirmation of our next action.
Do we proceed or withdraw?
If we're proceeding, will we need revised orders?
No need. Carry out your mission.
Just make sure to avoid any collateral damage.
Yeah, be sure you're careful.
The target you're after is a unique esper
who can control the corpses of dead creatures.
Morgue
Underestimate her,
and you'll suffer even more casualties.
Copy that.
Not here.
To reiterate, once you locate the target,
secure them immediately.
Avoid any collateral damage
to the patients and staff.
Roger.
Why, you!
Target spotted! Near the second floor
west staircase, fleeing east!
CONFIDENTIAL
The target of the investigation request (henceforth
referred to as A) is currently located in the hospital facility
in School District 7 (see map provided on separate sheet).
According to our information, A is in building 2, room 203.
A's identity is still under investigation.
Furthermore, A seems to have subordinates on the premises
Experimental data shows that
This doesn't match my intel.
This is an emergency. Please listen to me.
Where is this girl?
Her life...
Anti-Skill. We've caught a criminal
that snuck into the hospital.
We appreciate your cooperation.
Hmph, he's feigning indifference
to avoid any trouble.
Huh?
You apprehended her?
Of course.
HQ, HQ, this is Alpha. Target secured.
Encountered a patient in the process,
but avoided contact.
This is HQ. Good work.
Mm-hmm, so it sounds like you
didn't have to use the "coffin".
You must be the guest. No, we didn't.
Good.
They're still difficult to control,
so I was hoping you wouldn't have to use them.
If things went wrong,
you all would have been killed, too.
We wouldn't screw up like that.
Are you sure?
Well, Esther has been secured,
and after a little research,
the coffins' performance will improve.
Mm-hmm, I think they'll be
weapons that even you can use.
Tch.
Some punk kid who's never
been in the field. We're pulling out.
You really did a number on us earlier.
Ordinarily, I'd see to it that you got some
serious payback, but you're staying alive.
You can still be of use to justice, after all.
We were told not to kill you,
but if we want to correct a foolish child,
we do need to administer
some kind of punishment, don't we?
Don't overdo it.
This isn't like last time.
We're moving out.
Copy.
What?
What is it?
Somebody's blocking our way.
Hey, move it!
Is the girl inside there?
You're the one from earlier.
There's something I wanna ask her. Leave her here.
The girl in our custody is a criminal.
This is no business of a civilian such as yourself.
Hurry on back to your bed in the hospital.
You guys aren't Anti-Skill, are you?
What are you talking about?
We keep the peace in this city—
Those guys are so damn serious it's laughable.
They would never suddenly aim
their guns at an unarmed civilian.
Hmph. Anti-Skill?
Those guys are the fakes.
We, DA, are the real justice!
We are Academy City's hunting dogs of justice,
and with our fangs, we flush out evil,
chew it up, and destroy it!
DA?
Move! Or do you want to be
chewed up by the fangs of justice?!
Go ahead and try.
What?
Don't. Our orders are to do no harm to the patients.
Patients? I don't see any patients.
This guy is just vermin,
standing in the way of our justice.
And vermin should be exterminated
by the fangs of justice!
By DA's dogma.
This is your last warning. Get lost, vermin!
Justice? You call that justice?
You're an esper?
The hell with it! Run him over!
Roger.
Don't get too full of yourself, vermin!
Disciplining monster children
like yourself is part of our mission!
Hey!
Beat it, while I'm still just
handing out gentle love taps.
Otherwise, I'll crush you!
Y-You little...
We don't put up with vermin!
Let me show you what absolute justice looks like!
What's this? Did you beg Santa Claus to bring this?
A coffin?
Hishigata, you succeeded in affixing the soul?
That's the guy from earlier!
Pyrokinesis? Is there someone inside there?
Hmph, well deflected, vermin. But how about this?
Your kind, who only use your
abilities for yourselves, are evil!
You can't protect anything!
You can't save anyone!
Evil is to be chewed up by the fangs of justice!
I can't save anyone?
A Certain Scientific Accelerator
You really like playing at being a force for right?
Then go ahead and try chewing up
this evil standing before you!
And if you can't,
go ahead and give yourselves a bite!
It's all the same flavor anyway,
though compared to mine,
yours is a whole lot more plain!
Screw that! Don't you compare us
to a villain like yourself!
Limiter released!
Incredible.
I realize this is your prize toy,
but it's time to turn it into scrap!
You think you can get away?!
What's the meaning of this—
sticking a dead body inside there?
It's necromancy, all right.
Don't move.
Hold on, don't assume.
Appearances to the contrary, he's probably a victim.
Huh?
Hey. You've had a rough time of it, Accelerator.
Have we met somewhere before?
Now that's mean.
We just saw each other yesterday.
What happened here?
If you don't know, then I guess this really
didn't have anything to do with you lot.
What are you talking about?
You've got some impostors roaming around.
Huh?
DA? Never heard of them before.
And what's with the body?
She was inside that pile of junk.
She's been dead for two days.
Huh? What's going on?
Her vectors are all different from a living person.
She's been preserved, and looks clean enough,
but she's not freshly dead.
He's right.
This body belongs to Hitokawa Hasami.
Power Level
1st-year at Ninoude High School.
Ability
Power Level
She committed suicide by drowning three days ago,
and was pronounced dead by the EMTs.
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
Name
Ability
Power Level
But you said the robot was
using esper abilities, didn't you?
The guys posing as you stole the body,
stuffed it inside this junk,
and must have drawn her
ability out of her dead brain.
Even assuming that's all true, she's a Level 2.
Any way you look at it,
it would take a Level 4 to create a scene like this.
Heh, so they didn't just draw it out,
they raised its level, too.
I've never heard of that happening before.
What does it mean?
It's your job to look into that, isn't it?
Did you come into contact with the patients?
Contact with the patients was prohibited.
The way things played out, it was unavoidable.
But more importantly,
that coffin was all but useless!
We can't fight against espers with those things!
Yeah, I don't know what to tell you.
I did warn you that it was just
an experimental prototype.
You're the one who insisted
on taking it with you, right?
But you said the thing had
Level 4-class power, didn't you?!
That's right.
Mm-hmm, the boost is based on
the level of the subject.
What you saw was the result of
the ability being elevated that much.
For that to get beaten must mean that
you got pretty unlucky, or, mm-hmm,
you were taking on a Level 5-class opponent.
A certain someone who suggested you not
come in contact with the patients might know.
Oh, now, it doesn't really matter, does it?
We did secure the objective.
First order of business is to
get her delivered to Dachshund.
Without her, we can't move the
Waste Recycling Experiment to the next phase.
Mm-hmm, that's right.
What's the matter?
Hurry and get her over here.
The thing is, while we did
have her in custody, she got away.
Huh? Seriously?
Nobody could have anticipated what happened!
This isn't on me!
No, it definitely is.
You clearly failed. My client will be disappointed.
Justice that cannot correct evil has no value to us.
DA is supposed to be an organization that brings
about perfect justice in Academy City, isn't it?
I have no intention of keeping dogs that are all bark.
W-Wait!
Dachshund, can we leave this up to you to deal with?
Yeah, I guess. Mm-hmm.
All right.
The Qiong Qi alone should get it done, right?
W-Wait... I can still bring about justice!
Nah. Your body is useless to me,
so I'll just dissolve you.
D-Don't... Stay away... Stay away! Stop! Stay away!
Fire Hydrant
Hold on...
"Where have you been?"
asks Misaka as Misaka worries
about you having a night life...
I just went to buy a can of coffee.
"I told you, you shouldn't drink coffee at this hour,"
says Misaka as Misaka expresses concern...
Little kids shouldn't be awake at this hour.
Hurry on back to your room and go to sleep.
"Hmph, you shouldn't talk like that,"
says Misaka as Misaka...
Tch!
"What?" Asks Misaka as Misaka tries
to express suspicion of your attitude.
You're not going anywhere, right?
Huh? What are you talking about?
No, I'm not going anywhere.
Now, go back to bed.
Mm-hmm.
Fire Hydrant
Huh?
Who are you?
My name is Esther Rosenthal.
Thank you for saving me.
I need a favor.
It may sound brazen,
after you already saved me once,
but I can't stand against them all by myself.
I need your help—
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm no champion of justice.
For you to intentionally come back in here,
the inside of your head
must be a pretty happy place.
No, you aren't a bad person.
Huh?
From the look in your eyes when that
body came out of the coffin prototype...
Those weren't the eyes of a bad person.
That's quite the entertaining story, isn't it?
Here, let me prove how bad
a person I am by wringing your neck.
That's fine by me!
Huh?
But in return, please use that power
to do something about them!
The way things are headed, this city—
no, the whole world is at risk!
I'm the reason that girl—
that body—ended up like that.
I was the one who taught them
how to control dead bodies like that!
And so many more people
are going to die because of me!
I wanted to fix everything, even if I was alone!
They're trying to use Last Order
and shift the world into a new level.
After you tear me to pieces,
make sure you do something about it!
Please!
I tell you I'm a bad person,
and you decide to dump your work on me?
You touched in the head?
How rude. I'm right as rain.
Tell me where they are.
Huh?
Those phony Anti-Skill guys' hideout.
Whatever it is they're after,
all I have to do is go there and smash it.
A-All I know is the warehouse
where they kept me locked up.
I think it's just one of several hideouts they have.
Lead the way.
R-Right.
You say I don't look like a bad person?
No. You don't.
Hmph. I'll show you how a villain operates.
Hiding in my shell
Holding in all the emotions that I feel
Shackling my mind
But the shackles laugh at me, I find
Swallowing the pain
Savoring the rotten taste because I know that
Worse flavors lie in my future
Someone, take this cup
I'll keep repressing my feelings
Just run away from the torment
I know that I am to blame for
All your suffering
This mind has lost its sense of
Anger and jealousy
Never again to empathize
As I desperately struggle ahead
Possessed by my fears and doubts
Why can't I live a decent life?
I'm fed up with my past, yet I can't let go
I can't forgive myself
Don't I still deserve to suffer?
That's the question nagging at my heart
As it rots
Next Time
Numbers