You evil, frazzling meanie,
I'm gonna teach you a lesson!
Frazzling?
Sh-Shut it!
Who are you, anyway, you frazzling meanie?
I'm Miho Ayumu.
Who are you?
Kashimura Sana! Amazing, right?
Where are we?
How did you do this?
Looks like you finally understand your situation.
This is Wonderland!
I made this place so I could catch you.
Everything in this room
happens the way I want it to.
In here, no one can beat me!
Is this some kind of magic?
Magic?
It's nothing like that.
I'm not letting you leave this place...
until you apologize... got it?
C-Crying won't work.
I don't care if you get hungry, either!
And you can't use the bathroom!
Stay here and think about what you've done!
Wait a second!
Mirror, mirror, on the wall
I want to change this world
The streetlight brightens up the night
And brings forth a sea of light
That reaches far into the distance
I dream upon a restless star
As I wait for the night to end
So I can continue searching for the future
The curtains covering a new stage
slowly part
as I wake up
Wonder drive! Let's start running now!
Wonder drive! To the world ahead of us!
Uncertainty, hesitation, and confusion
Just throw it all away!
Wonder drive! Keep charging along this path
Replace that clock's rhythm with your own
We are walking along a road
No one has yet dreamed of
Mirror, mirror, on the wall
I want to change this world
The Little Queen
Let go!
Don't follow me, darn it...
J-Just wait!
I'll apologize, so please listen to me!
What? I don't care about that!
Now, let go!
I'll apologize! I'm sorry!
I've been searching for you for so long!
Huh?
If you know something about
that weird power, please tell me!
My...
My most precious friend is forcing
herself to endure horrible pain!
Wait... What?
Ugh, darn it!
I feel all frazzled!
Darn it all!
I hate feeling frazzled!
Even Yonaga and Asahi were worried
about that friend of yours!
That's just not right.
Why do I have to feel like this?
It's weird!
U-Uh, listen...
Shut up!
Sheesh, now I'm all confused again!
Listen, you! I'm angry.
I'm angry, you hear?
I know. I'll apologize.
I'm sorry.
Darn it... Listen to me!
Quit apologizing like that!
B-But you told me to.
What will make you forgi—
Sh-Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
Uh-oh. He's calling.
Hide for now.
W-Wait.
Be quiet. Got it?
Hey, what is all this?
Where did you put my bathroom?
U-Uh...
Huh? This is a bathroom?
You just looked me in the eye
and tried to run, didn't you?
I-I was just...
What's going on here? Explain this!
Huh?!
I'll take your order when you're ready.
Huh?
Thank you!
Hey!
Huh, what?
Hey, you! Over here!
It's me.
Huh? Ms. Kashimura?
Ms. Kashimura...
Ms. Kashimura, huh? I kinda like that!
The other day, that girl with you...
The one with the red thing in her hair.
You mean Hatori?
Do you like her?
Why? She's an evil person.
Well...
I don't know.
She's my friend.
Your friend?
Yeah.
Are you guys close?
We've been in the same class since first grade.
First grade?
Oh, you mean school?
You go to school?
Yeah.
Wait, you don't go to school?
No, I don't.
Is school fun?
Yeah. I don't like studying too much,
but I get to see my friends, so it's fun.
But...
Even though Hatori loved school,
she stopped coming.
I hate the idea of never being
able to play with her again.
But I don't understand anything about magic.
I don't know what to do.
Do you feel frazzled, too?
You said that earlier.
What do you mean by "frazzled"?
Frazzled means frazzled.
Want some?
So good...
Maybe even as good as pancakes...
I swear... The moment I finish lecturing her,
she's talking in her sleep.
Grandpa!
Huh?
The bathroom's so big...
And so cute.
Oh, maybe I'll make this my room!
You seem like a good person,
but that Hatori is evil.
Aw, you're so clingy today...
Just like a baby.
Mom, I'll be with you forever, okay?
Where's this coming from?
Of course you will.
Mom...
What is this?
Where am I?
Those look good!
Go get Sana.
Sure!
Sana?
Sana!
Wow!
Look at what's in here—
Ow!
Sana's gotten pretty clever, huh?
How cute—
Ow.
Went to catch
the evil girl.
I'll eat my
snack later.
"Evil girl"?
That's weird.
It's like a little kid made only this part.
So you're Hatori...
I'm going to catch you!
Um, who are you?
Well?
Can't tell who I am, can you?
I'm a really scary grown-up.
I made this whole room!
Right now, you're basically in my stomach!
How about that? Scared, aren't you?
You evil girl!
You don't have to tell me I'm evil. I know I am.
I don't know who you are,
but you don't scare me at all!
Huh?
That's a lie.
Because I'm incredible.
I can do anything.
I could crush you like a bug
or lock you up in a really scary place!
And I mean scary! No bathroom or snacks!
You're the girl I met in Harajuku
a while ago, aren't you?
N-No!
Liar.
I-I'm not lying...
I-I'm a really scary grown-up. I don't even know you!
Grown-ups don't speak like that.
Also, I can tell right away if you lie,
no matter what you try.
You know absolutely nothing.
Did you say something?
Forget it. I'm leaving.
W-Wait!
Ow! Darn, it's too cramped in here!
Y-You won't get away!
You're trying to run because you're evil.
That's bad, you know!
That's true.
I knew what I was doing when I turned evil.
Huh?
B-But you're not supposed to do bad things.
You'll get yelled at...
I know that. That's obvious.
You see, I'm a witch.
An evil witch, at that.
I'm no longer a normal human.
No one in this world is on my side.
Th-That's...
Only one person is left who really cares about me.
I've ruined everything.
U-Uh...
No need to tell me...
I'm evil.
There's no way you could understand how I feel.
She really is evil.
But Hatori is still a really good girl.
Th-That's a lie.
She's an evil person!
She turned everyone all weird, including Zouroku...
Hatori is always very kind,
and she's way smarter than I am.
And she's cute.
She's nothing like me at all.
I wish I could've become a witch, too.
Move.
No.
I have nothing to say to you.
No. I feel all frazzled.
Ugh, I don't get it!
Don't get what? Frazzled?
Didn't you want to make me pay?
So hurry up and do it.
Shut up! I don't get it!
Y-You're both weird.
I know you're evil!
But when I asked, she said you aren't!
Huh?
And she's a good person...
She asked me to help you.
It doesn't make any sense!
Wait.
Do you mean...
I hate being frazzled all the time!
Who is "she"?
Oh, right... How did you know where I live?
Who told you?
No way.
Ayumu told you about me?
I... I don't know.
Don't lie!
B-But it's a secret.
This is an order!
Did Ayumu tell you that?
Answer me!
Why?
What's going on?
Abnormal situation in Wonderland.
Energy emission increased.
Spatial wave factor rising.
Report of an abnormality detected in Hidakamioka.
Quantum entanglement observed.
Jodorowsky space is about to collapse.
What's going on?
Alert level upgrading to yellow!
What in the world is going on
in Wonderland?
What is this?
A giant Ferris wheel has appeared in Kyoto?
Dreams of Alice are appearing everywhere.
Is it possible to get an actual count?
Ma'am, Wonderland is expanding!
In such a broad area, it'll take some time.
Breaking News: Ferris Wheels Appearing Throughout Kyoto
The details are still unclear,
but we've never seen effects like this.
She said she was
going to Hatori's house.
I hope it'll be okay.
Hello? Mom?
What's up? I'm almost home.
Hatori...
She's gone?
Sana still isn't back, huh?
Grandpa?
I'm going out to look around.
Welcome home, Dad.
Thanks. Is your mom home?
Not yet.
Mom's helping Hatori's mom search for her.
I see.
I got a call earlier, too.
I'll go out and join your mom.
Where's Daiki?
He had dinner and went to bed.
You eat your dinner, too.
And go to bed.
Hey...
No.
I know you're worried,
but it's dangerous for a kid to
walk around outside at this hour.
It'll be fine.
Hatori has a good head on her shoulders.
She'll turn up soon.
Hatori
No Answer
Hatori? Where are you?
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Have you eaten anything yet?
Hatori
No Answer
Hatori? Where are you?
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Unread
Have you eaten anything yet?
What's
Went to catch
the evil girl.
I'll eat my
snack later.
Who could this evil girl be?
The research facility isn't around anymore...
Grandpa?
Did you find Sana?
Oh, who knows where she wandered off to?
Sheesh.
Do you think she's okay?
Well, I'm sure she'll come home
when she gets hungry.
Hello?
Oh, Ichijou?
Perfect timing.
Sana?
No, she isn't here right now.
Then I was right.
What does that mean?
A few hours ago, something strange
happened in Wonderland.
It's difficult to access at the moment.
I don't know the details.
But I believe Sana must be trapped there.
And it appears someone else is in there with her.
I'm on my way there, so if you would—
Okay. I'm going, too.
No, wait...
Right now, Wonderland is expanding.
It's very dangerous!
All the more reason why I should go!
Those kids are stuck in there.
Isn't getting them out an adult's job?
S-Someone!
Isn't anyone there?
Hey!
I knew it was you.
Shut up.
Hey, this won't open.
You want me to open it?
N-No...
I should only have to think
about it opening for it to open!
I-It's true.
It usually works.
If she asked me to help and I did,
I wonder what she'd do.
That was easier than I expected.
I know I'm not nearly as strong as Ayumu.
Is this girl...?
Hey.
Where are we?
Please... I need to get home.
I get that you're amazing, all right?
And I will apologize.
So please send me home.
Oh, well...
Yeah.
Listen...
I'm not sure.
But we might...
not be able...
to go home.
Hidden beneath this scab
Are a great many things all working in unison
So please hold on just a little bit longer
Because I'll change myself starting from there
When do I start
To truly become myself?
Let's go meet the people who deserve my affection
We'll find them scattered across the world
I want to learn so much about them
One person, another person, more and more people
Three, four, five, six, the number rises and rises
Finding out the truth
Can sometimes be painful, but...
The world will keep moving
On and on, forever and ever
Even far into the future
Remaining unchanged
Next Episode
The Queen and the Witch
The Queen and the Witch.