Kazamatsuri, a quiet, peaceful
city abound with greenery.
But, unbeknownst to all,
two major forces that divide the world in two
are locked in conflict beneath its surface.
Guardian, who seek to destroy
the Key and keep the world as it is.
And Gaia, who want the Key to destroy the world.
I've infiltrated both groups as a member.
Having engaged with both
but belonging to neither as Suzuki Bond,
I...
Kagari, how about you and I
try preventing the planet's death?
That has always been my desire.
I'm here to fulfill my promise to the Key.
This is where it all begins.
I have a meeting with Gaia's Saint, Kashima Sakura.
She's the linchpin of the group's old guard,
which is at odds with Suzaki.
Deceiving her won't be an easy task.
Come in.
Following the path of pain
kutsuu no michi wo tadori
Was too much to continue moving forward
ashi wo tometa darou
My time was frozen
kooritsuita toki mo
Keeping my distant memories out of reach
ima wa tooi kioku wo kasunde
If there are no sacrifices
nanimo gisei ni
Is that the definition of strength I can try to achieve?
sore wa tsuyoku nareru no ka to
But I lack even the courage to let go of your hand
nigitta mama no te mo mada hodoku yuuki ga motenakute
I'll become a hero
eiyuu ni naru
I've learned that
narenai kara
For me that's impossible
sono koto ni kidzuiteta
If nothing else, I'll wish for the strength I need to protect you
semete kimi wo mamoritai sou negau
I'll forge my body into a blade
kono karada wo tsurugi ni kaete
And take the path full of obstacles
are wo deta michi wo yuku
I moved forward by defeating even my own weak self
yowakatta jibun sae kiritaoshi susunda
I wonder if I'll ever reach
itsuka todoku no darou ka
The future you wish for
kimi ga nozomu mirai ni
I'll protect you until the very end, when we welcome that day
sono hi wo mukaeru made wa boku ga mamorinuku yo
Episode 22
"Battle Behind
the Scenes"
So yeah, that's what's happening right now.
I see.
That's all you have to say?
Of course.
I already promised you what
you'll get for your help.
What I'll get?
If you help save this planet,
I will even fornicate with you,
in the worst-case scenario.
That's...
Is that Kotori?
Kotori is doing a fine job.
The day she completes this thing,
she will rule over the earth.
Is it just me, or are you getting dumber by the day?
That's not true.
One daemon can't do squat,
no matter how strong it is.
Just like how even the strongest
superhuman can't destroy tanks.
Tanks?
Weapons that Homo sapiens use, right?
I just had a great idea.
If tanks are stronger than superhumans,
then let us acquire one
Super Kagari-chan Tank
and use it to take over the earth.
Kagari...
Why are you patting my head?
Out of pity.
You were talking like someone with a feeble mind.
Do not insult me.
Not like that was my intention.
I just want to do something of value.
Something somebody's got to do.
Like protecting my comrade's wish
and the home of those kids who called me family.
A daemon?
You got lost again?!
Oh, you're out catching bugs?
Wait, those are daemons you caught!
Tch.
Excuse me.
Coming.
Nagai?
Right, she must've had her memories
erased when she quit Guardian.
Ah, never mind.
I just found her in the forest.
Thank you very much.
She ran off the moment I took my eyes off her.
Uh, sorry to ask,
but are you a member of Martel, too?
That's right.
My name is Tsukuno.
I've been working here recently.
Is that so?
Akane-san, did you find any beetles?
Yay! That's amazing!
You made a friend, huh? Good for you.
Nagai's forgotten who she used to be
and found a home for herself in Martel.
As well as for Senri Akane and that other girl, too.
Guess I'll go see Kotori's parents.
Hello?
What? Right now?
The report you submitted the
other day was most interesting.
Thank you.
By the way, I heard you met with Kashima.
Yes...
And you felt that wasn't worth
mentioning in your report because...?
I decided that specifying any names
at this stage could be misleading.
A textbook answer.
There's nothing I hate more than
ignorant brats trying to pull one over me.
Resist
Don't
Suzaki-san!
Y-You misunderstand!
You're right, I did meet Kashima Sakura, but...
Very well.
I understand.
You prefer working under Suzaki.
My deepest apologies.
It's fine.
Believe it or not, I fully recognize
how capable Suzaki is.
It appears you were telling the truth.
Takasago.
Still, you were awfully honest with her.
I didn't think I could deceive her.
True, that woman is rather terrifying.
Suzaki-san.
What is the Key?
The Key?!
Where did you hear that?
Oh, right.
Here's a piece of advice for you.
If you wish to climb the ladder in the Suzaki faction,
you should approach the Key.
The Key?
Yes.
It's something they're chasing in secret,
even going as far as killing people...
You're quite the greedy one.
I like you.
You want to know about the Key?
Yes.
Blindfold me all you want.
If I keep track of my steps and the direction,
I can figure out my current location.
We're below the temple now...
The fifth underground floor?
Welcome to the City of Stone.
What is this place?
A compressed world that has existed
alongside Kazamatsuri for no short while.
We call it the City of Stone.
The City of Stone?
Simply put, it's something akin
to an alternate dimension.
It was formed by the accumulation
of a power imperceptible to humans,
or so some researchers say.
Imperceptible?
Like the power to create daemons?
Yes.
You could even consider this
entire city as one big daemon.
Just how big is it?
Not very.
It's a copy of Kazamatsuri,
but only a small part of it.
And it lacks infrastructure,
including power and a water supply.
Still, it could be used as a shelter of sorts.
It may very well have been
built for that very purpose.
If need be,
we could use a bit of several
summoners' life forces
to expand it.
But that's...
I'm simply speaking of possibilities.
Expanding it beyond its current
size isn't a realistic option.
Kazamatsuri's "spirited away" incidents.
Surely you've heard the rumors, too?
Well, yes.
It seems this place was the cause.
This place is connected to Kazamatsuri
in ways others can't see, by being its copy.
And sometimes it draws certain people in.
Is that so?
Now, the most we can do is use those links
to transfer daemons between realms.
The Key is essentially a sensory
organ the planet creates.
It acts as the planet's eyes and ears.
The massive planet probably can't
notice its own wounds otherwise.
What will you do when you find the Key?
Earth is at its limit.
If things continue as they are,
Kashima will get what she wants.
The Key will destroy the world.
Is there no way to avoid that?
No.
With that said,
where should we look for help?
Don't tell me...
You're really planning to use this as a shelter?
I had experts investigate.
They said we could port a small ecosystem here.
Even if the planet dies,
we can keep greenery alive here.
How many people could this place sustain?
Less than a hundred thousand.
With no infrastructure,
they'd have to return to a primitive lifestyle,
but we do have an argument
that can convince them.
Do you really have magic words that can do that?
Of course.
All we need to say is,
"This is an artificial afterlife."
Hey, did you hear?
The usual Harvest Festa op is canceled this year.
Really?
Well, our friends over at Gaia
ain't making any major moves,
and we ain't doing anything, either.
May I join you, gentlemen?
Whoa!
You're eating an awful lot again today, Esaka-san!
Yeah.
I've been posted overseas.
So my Japanese cake adventures
will be put on hold for a while.
For a while after that,
it was one peaceful day after another.
After Esaka-san moved overseas,
I took over management of his café.
And I kept living a double life as
a member of both Gaia and Guardian.
Suzaki's artificial afterlife project
garnered a lot of resources, both human and financial.
He sold rights to live in the
"afterlife" at exorbitant rates
and used those funds to develop the City of Stone.
As the City of Stone approached its completion,
the Key became an indispensable
trump card for Suzaki.
Gaia's split became a foregone conclusion.
Suzaki, who sought survival in the artificial afterlife,
and Kashima Sakura,
who sought destruction at the Key's hands.
Beneath the surface,
the two were waging a cold war...
A harbinger of the impending conflict.
Where's Kagari?
Went out.
Again?
I tried to stop her, but she left anyway.
Didn't you want to help Kagari as a druid?
There.
Go find Kagari!
I met them.
Your parents.
This might sound awful,
but those things are no longer your parents.
They're daemons.
Deep down, you know that, don't you?
That they won't come back to life.
You're wrong.
Give it up already.
Quit living like this.
Your parents wouldn't have wanted this.
Also, this job is dangerous.
I know that.
No, you don't.
We're skating on really thin ice right now!
But if you just quit now,
you can go back to a normal life!
A normal life?
Without my mom and dad?!
I see.
She has nowhere to go back to.
I refuse!
What do you hear?
All kinds of words.
Is that how you learn language?
But, as much as I may have learned,
there's something I've yet to understand.
The human heart.
I'm not surprised.
There is a massive gap
between your thoughts and actions.
You cling on to the status quo very dearly,
never risking your current happiness
in order to hold hope for the future.
So long as you're content with the present,
you do not care what tomorrow may hold.
I find that thinking extremely disgraceful.
But that's just human nature.
We're all scared of facing reality.
I fail to understand.
Oh, I just had an excellent idea.
You should just put an end to class conflict.
You make it sound so easy.
Super Kagari-chan Tank
Assign roles in a much more
efficient and rational manner,
and charge into the future!
Super Kagari-chan Tank
What?
I just had to.
I dislike being patted on the head.
Okay.
I'll stop, but in return,
would you hold on to this?
Pick the one you like.
I don't really get it,
but I feel like I'm being insulted.
You're not.
Then...
I shall take this one.
If you have that,
I'll be able to tell where you are, even if you go out.
So keep it on you at all times.
Very well.
Anything for my great cause.
Do you know this Tsukuno woman?
No.
She's a summoner Kashima
recently picked as her protégé,
but it seems she used to be a hunter.
Kashima Sakura's keeping
a former hunter by her side?
Yeah.
Isn't this a bit of a scandal?
No, a very grave state of affairs.
Do you suspect Tsukuno
of leaking the information?
She works at the House of Ties,
a facility officially run by Martel.
Kashima must've found
her successor as Saint there.
We already have a good idea who.
It's this girl.
If she kept a traitor close at hand,
and then suddenly had her successor disappear,
how badly would that damage our great Saint?
We'll put the finishing touches on ourselves.
Pull this off, and it'll make it
much easier to promote you.
What do you say?
Refuse
Accept
I accept.
Did they die?
The plan will be put into action at once.
They must be holding an emergency
meeting at HQ right now,
where Kashima Sakura will be condemned.
Suzaki already has the other executives
who are attending the meeting on his side.
As soon as we receive word,
we'll capture Tsukuno and Akane.
They will never be heard from again.
All to further the artificial afterlife project.
Can't make an omelette without
breaking some eggs, after all.
That's why...
My fellow executives.
Thank you so much for attending,
even though it's so late into the night.
The thing is—
May I say something before we start?
Go ahead.
There's something I want
to announce to you all tonight.
I have chosen the next Saint.
It's a girl named Senri Akane.
Also, this will be the last time the title
of Saint will ever be passed down.
Well, Suzaki?
This decision should be quite agreeable to you, no?
I've already asked a woman
named Tsukuno to guard Akane.
She used to be a hunter,
but she is completely dyed in Martel colors now.
She is a most trustworthy individual.
If you take this as a scandal,
I'm willing to retire immediately
and entrust Martel's future to Akane and you all.
No, of course not!
We need your leadership.
Hello?
The operation is canceled.
I don't need to explain why I called you here, yes?
I can trace the life force used
in daemons that approach me.
Why did you save me?
Or was there perhaps someone
else you wanted to save?
Why do you keep repeating such
mistakes time and time again?
I won't make any excuses.
Why?
You understand what will happen
if the planet dies, do you not?
Even if my mind understands,
my feelings,
my heart won't listen.
You probably can't understand,
but that's just how humans are.
Disgraceful.
I know.
I have a question, Kotarou.
Were you close to the individual you saved?
No.
We're practically strangers.
Then why?
Maybe because I don't want to lose
any ties I have, no matter how trivial.
What if the planet fell to ruin
because of your trivial ties?
If it comes to that,
I'll accept ruin.
You're awful!
Kagari, did you gain emotions?
Do you people lack even the will to survive?!
Kagari?
Why were you even born, then?!
The planet can't support re-evolution anymore,
but the remaining reserves, if used wisely,
should be enough to produce fond memories!
And yet...
And yet!
You've all but given up on survival!
Kagari?
Hey, Kagari!
Life could not have
come into existence
to give up...
Kotori!
K-Kagari-san's...
The Key's...
Go back home!
I'll do something about this!
But...
Just go!
Damn.
I can't get close to her like this.
Oh, I get it now.
I...
Kagari!
Even if our minds understand,
our feelings, our hearts, won't listen.
That's just how humans are, Kagari.
I have been shamed.
Why are you toying with me?
Kagari, I'm not helping you out
because I wanted to save the planet or anything!
It's because I was drawn to you!
Because I thought you'd give me,
Tennouji Kotarou, and not Suzuki Bond,
a special place to belong!
Wha...
I fail to understand!
Are you saying you worship me?
No!
When I say I was drawn to you,
I mean I love you!
That's more humiliating than
being marked with your scent!
Cease your humiliation!
I can't.
Not anymore.
Then I don't need your help!
Remove yourself from my presence at once!
I refuse!
In that case...
I'll just have to leave myself.
The world you live in
nemuru koto no nai
Is one that never sleeps
anata ga tatsu sekai wa
And it's still so pure
mada muku na mama de
If I can leave something
moshi kono daichi ni
In the ground here
nanika wo nokoseru no nara
Let it at least be some kind of a trace
semete omokage wo
I can't even do a simple thing like gaze at the sky
sora wo miageru sonna kantan na koto mo
So I close my eyes
yurusarezu hitomi tojiru
I was only ever looking
tada hitotsu dake
For one thing
mitsukete hoshii no
Sunken in memories
kioku ni shizumu
Feelings of love
itoshisa wo
At the ends of time
ikusen no hate
I hope you stay safe
tadoritsuku anata ga
Until we meet again
sukuwareru you ni
It's fine as long as my song reaches you
kono utagoe todoku kagiri