I'm sorry, everyone...
It's all because I'm filthy.
I'm so sorry...
Episode 5
Asahi Haruka
The cursed girl, Asahi Haruka?
Yeah.
We got a letter in the
Monster Mailbox Shizuru set up.
Mail
Let's see... "Are you all familiar
with the story of Asahi Haruka?
If you attempt to investigate
her and disturb her slumber,
you will be placed under her curse.
In a certain forest, there was an orphanage.
After a girl called Asahi Haruka arrived there,
strange things began to occur.
Windows and mirrors would shatter on their own,
and the pets would suddenly pass away...
Before long, the children
and teachers were affected, too...
In the end, the orphanage was closed down."
This story sounds somewhat familiar.
"Seven years ago,
a boy from that orphanage transferred into
the school I was attending at the time,
Kazamatsuri 7th Municipal Elementary School.
A few days after he told us
the story of Asahi Haruka,
he died of a strange, unknown illness.
He was cursed for disturbing her slumber.
His name was Kishida Ryuugo,
and he was in Class 4-1."
Things got awfully specific all of a sudden.
Right?
If he was in 4th grade seven years ago,
then he would've been the same age as us.
I'm pretty sure Yoshino is
from 7th Elementary, too.
Corroborating this story
should be a simple matter,
and then I'll get to touch Prez's boo—
By the way, where are Shizuru and the class rep?
Maybe coming here feels awkward,
considering what happened yesterday.
Are you still fighting?
It's not like we fought or anything...
Good grief.
Before investigating,
we've first gotta fix things
between Chihaya and the class rep.
Why Lucia wears gloves?
Yeah.
Sure, she may be a clean-freak,
but it seems a little excessive.
And given what happened yesterday,
I figured I should at least ask why.
Kotarou...
Are you Lucia's friend?
I would think so.
Then I don't mind telling you Lucia's secret.
Secret?
So long as you will be Lucia's friend forever...
The class rep's secret, huh?
What do you want?
I'm a little occupied at the moment.
Oh my, out on a date?
I'll kill you.
By the way, you went to 7th Elementary, right?
In 4th grade, which class were you in?
What's it to you?
Sorry, but I'm not playing along.
Disturbing the dead ain't my thing.
Does that mean a transfer student named Kishida
really did die due to some
strange, unknown illness?
Like I'd know!
And I wouldn't tell you even if I did.
I may have never spoken to him,
but he was still my friend.
I see.
Sorry about this.
Wait. Why are you sticking your nose into all this?
Something about it just stuck out in my mind.
This case just doesn't sit right with me.
Tennouji.
I'll give you one warning.
If things start looking dicey, back off.
What do you mean, dicey?
If the glass shatters, watch your back.
Glass?
What do you mean?
That's all I'm going to say on the matter.
This is all the help I can give you.
Get by on your own luck from here on out.
That roster is a part of my history.
Give it back as soon as you're done with it.
Thank you, Yoshino.
Could you make copies of this for the whole class?
Yes.
I'll lend you my copy card.
Please use as little
copier paper as possible.
Let's use recycled paper.
-Vice Principal
Class Rep!
What is it, Tennouji?
Hey! This isn't for personal use!
It's just one copy.
Pretend you never saw it.
Jeez...
What are you copying?
Sorry, but it's a secret.
If you knew, you could be cursed.
Did you say "cursed"?
Owe ya, Class Rep!
Honestly...
I guess I should give everyone a call.
Wait, Tennouji!
You left this in the tray.
It's yours, right?
Do not wake me.
Or else, you will...
What is this?
I don't remember copying anything like—
If the glass shatters, watch your back.
It couldn't be, right?
It couldn't be what?
Oh, nothing...
What are you plotting this time?
Depending on your answer,
Tennouji Kotarou, I might have to...
So you're telling me that both
the note and the shattered glass
are warnings from Asahi Haruka?
Do not wake me.
Or else, you will...
No.
Do not wake me.
Or else, you will...
The copier must've spat out the wrong sheet.
But that note...
Probably just used paper.
Maybe a recycled sheet got mixed in?
But...
As for the windows, someone must
have thrown a rock or something.
You don't believe it's a curse?
Well, you could say I have a reason
for not wanting to in this case.
Anyway, I want to prove there's
no such thing as curses
and clear that girl's name.
Clear her name?
If Asahi Haruka is being hurt
by all this even to this day,
as a part of the occult club,
I just can't leave it as-is.
You have a point...
Then it's settled.
Let's close the book on this cheap horror story!
Y-Yeah.
Close the book, huh?
Oh, yeah. The forecast did say it was going to rain.
Why do you wake me?
Huh?
We are both burdened by the same sorrow, too...
Do not wake me...
Or else...
You will...
No!
Th-The glass!
Um, are you okay?
That's why I said no!
It's just like four years ago!
The curse hasn't gone away!
Uh, hang on!
Seriously?
Strangely, every person I called got really scared
the second I brought up Asahi Haruka
and refused to answer any questions.
In addition, after my call,
they all mysteriously experienced
their windows or mirrors breaking...
I left contacting the girls up to the class rep...
All right, one more person!
Oh, is this Wada Kenji-kun's residence?
Sorry to call so late—
Huh? He isn't there?
That's for the best.
Remember our suffering...
N-No.
I decided to face it!
That is impossible.
After all, we really are...
cursed.
I wonder if Class Rep is absent?
I thought I would get to
apologize to her today for sure...
Class Rep
It's not like her to be absent without leave.
Hi there, Tennouji-kun!
Inoue.
I caught wind that you're after a dangerous scoop?
How do you know that?
About that story... Quite frankly,
it's considered off-limits among us reporters.
Huh?
Kazamatsuri
Middle School
Someone who was researching
it got into an accident.
This has a column written by him.
Accident?
If you call yourself my rival,
pursuing the mysteries of Kazamatsuri,
then handle the rest on your own.
Just to let you know, you owe me one.
Hey!
Baraki Kunihiko's Column
Baraki?
This is a recording from
7th Elementary Class 4-1's reunion.
All the glass in the entire venue
shattered outta nowhere.
And, on the way back from the event,
a huge billboard fell right in front of me.
If it had actually hit me, I'd be dead for sure.
I hear the rumors exaggerated it somewhat
and say I got seriously hurt, though!
In the end, all I was able to get out of anyone
was that late Kishida Ryuugo lived in
an orphanage called
"The Santa Brosia Peace Garden."
Do not wake me.
N-No way...
Class Rep?
Do not wake me.
This is your final warning.
Class Rep!
Hey!
Damn!
Hang in there.
I'm here for you.
No, Sensei...
If you touch me...
What's wrong?
It was a dream?
Are you okay?
Thank goodness.
You came to?
Tennouji?
I see.
That's what happened?
Uh, about your clothes, um...
I thought you would catch a cold.
I-I didn't look, a-and I didn't touch
your skin or anything, either.
I see.
That's good.
Watch.
Wh-What just happened?
It's the curse of Asahi Haruka.
When I touch plants, they wither.
Don't tell me...
Is this my fault?
Were you cursed in retribution
for me not giving up on my investigation?
Don't worry about it, Tennouji.
Even if that were the case,
it would change nothing for me.
Lucia experienced unfortunate
incidents when she was young.
She made the plants and
animals raised in her class
wither and die one after another.
Surely it was just a coincidence?
Lucia convinced herself
that it was her fault, though.
She thought it was because
her hands were filthy...
That's why Lucia is too afraid
to touch any living thing to this day.
Lucia has faced that trauma
head-on in her own way.
She's attempted to overcome it.
And her gloves provide her the most respite.
I could just wear my gloves forever
and never touch anyone.
Nothing will change.
Nothing.
Nothing!
So it won't be painful...
I'm filthy.
I'm unclean, so—
No! You're wrong about that!
You don't understand!
Not my sorrow, nor Asahi Haruka's suffering!
I always knew.
There's no world that can
accept people as filthy as us.
I...
We will live the rest of our lives
never touching another person,
all alone, in solitude.
That's how it has to be!
Why did it turn out this way?
I just...
Santa Brosia Peace Garden
No Trespassing
Class Four Industrial Toxic Waste Treatment Plant
Unauthorized entry is strictly forbidden
This is the entrance to the orphanage?
Well, I guess I've got no choice but to check it out.
It does look like children used to be here.
This is Kishida Ryuugo?
Asahi Haruka is...
Found you, Asahi Haruka.
Or should I say...
Konohana Lucia!
How did you know it was me?
This.
The roster?
Yeah.
The Wada Kenji on this list doesn't
live at this address anymore.
He moved.
And yet, the glass in that house shattered, too.
Surely a curse wouldn't make mistakes, would it?
The only ones with this roster are Yoshino, myself,
and you, Class Rep.
I see.
I made quite a pathetic mistake.
When I made that copy,
you looked at the data left on the copier
and figured out what I was
trying to investigate, right?
That said, I couldn't figure out
how you shattered all that glass.
You're right.
By forging that warning and shattering the glass,
I tried to get you to stop your investigation,
but you just wouldn't give up.
Class Rep.
No, Lucia.
Why are you doing this?
I can't touch anything alive.
I was born normal, but was reborn
this way at a certain place.
"This way"?
You'll never understand
if I simply tell you about it.
But the curse residing within this hand is real.
I can shatter glass without
laying a finger on it, too.
The poison that dwells in these hands
can take the life of anything
they touch, not just plants.
I didn't want anyone to know
about my hideous past, or my true identity.
I see.
That's the curse's true form?
This area is still heavily laced with my poison.
I'm saying this for your own good.
Leave this place immediately and seek treatment.
You can still make it in time.
Tennouji?!
Hey!
Don't tell me, back then...
G-Get to the hospital now!
No.
The hospital can't help anymore...
I'm sorry, Tennouji.
What have I done?
No, I'm the one who should apologize.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
If only I'd been strong enough to
withstand your poison back then,
I could have prevented you from suffering again.
That's not your fault—
No!
To be honest, I've got an unusual power myself.
A power?
Wh-What are you doing, Tennouji?
I have to rewrite my body.
Rewrite it into one that can withstand the poison.
Ow...
I've accepted Konohana Lucia's world!
How?
This is my power.
That's the only way I can explain it.
What are you?
Don't tell me...
I'm Tennouji Kotarou, Konohana Lucia's friend!
My friend?
Yeah, so...
Never again say you'll spend your life
all alone, never touching anyone...
It's just too sad.
Tennouji...
And besides, you're not alone at all.
You have Shizuru, you have me,
and you have everyone at the occult club, too.
Chihaya and Kotori were worried about you!
And well, Prez too, probably.
You know, friends don't let friends be all alone.
Impossible.
It's a miracle...
What's wrong with a miracle or two?
After all, this is a chapel, isn't it?
Yeah.
Yeah!
Oh dear, are we interrupting?
Wh-Who are you people?
I-It's all right.
They're, um... my allies.
Allies?
Hi!
That was a surprise.
It's hard to believe you're resistant
to Lucia-chan's poison by nature.
Forget about that.
Who are you and the others?
You avoided the question the other day,
but does Lucia have something to do
with Shizuru's organization, too?
You know about Shizuru, too?
Guardian.
That is our organization.
Nishikujou-san! You can't mention that name!
It's better than having him snoop around.
This incident made that quite clear, no?
Well...
Our organization is gathering people
with special powers for a certain purpose.
Lucia-chan and Shizuru-chan
possess those special powers.
Special powers?
So what in the world is this
organization trying to do?
We're protecting the Earth.
Protecting the Earth?
Right now, Kazamatsuri City
is in a volatile situation
due to an individual who holds the key
to Earth's survival or its destruction.
That doesn't sound pleasant.
You believe us?
All this nonsense about how
Earth could be destroyed?
Well, I doubt you'd lie in this situation.
We call that individual the Key.
The Key?
The Key's existence
could have a profound effect on
the world and all of its religions.
As such, we cannot even
make their existence public.
To make matters worse,
there are those who would shelter the Key
and advocate that Earth should perish.
What the heck?
Are they a cult?
It's an organization we treat with utmost caution,
since they wield considerable power.
They call themselves Gaia.
Gaia?
It's a fanatical organization that believes the Key
will bring about Earth's regeneration.
I'm sorry, but that's all we can tell you right now.
Now you have no choice but to keep this secret.
We can trust you to keep quiet about this, right?
Otherwise...
In that case, I have a condition of my own.
Oh, what might that be?
I want to eat a lunch made by Lucia!
What?!
Why a lunch made by me?!
By the way, you must wear
a maid's uniform while doing so!
This is non-negotiable!
Y-You reprobate!
Wh-Who would wear something like that?!
Oh, and also, call me Master—
Don't get carried away!
ma ga sashita toka waraenai
Saying you've been tempted by a devil isn't funny!
kirai suki suki kirai yo
I hate you but I love you but I love you but I hate you
odoroite bakari no kimi to ataranai hana uranai
Fortune-telling with flowers together never worked, but it was full of surprises
houkago ni hirari fuwari to
After school we spent a light, soft time
maiorita amai wana wa
Leading to a sweet trap
nogasanai onnanoko no aizu
If I make this girly sign you'll never escape
lock on
"Lock on!"
hashiridaseba todoku kyori ni iru no ni mada
If I run, I might get close enough to reach you
kotoba mo kakerarenai no ka na
But even then the words won't come out
fukashigi na sekai ni mayoikonda arisu wa
The Alice who found herself in Wonderland
watashi no koto na no soretomo
Am I like her now? Or...?
karakau furi no mama oitsudzuketai no
I want you, pretending you're just teasing, to chase after me
akirameta setsuna encounter
But just when I'm on the verge of giving up, we find each other!
kokoro no naka ni wa mou
Within my heart already lies
umareta kanjou moeteiru wa
The blazing feelings that were sparked
hikaeme na new face
When I saw how kind you could be