What is happiness, I wonder?
Consequently, Gaia devised the Song of
Destruction's ceremony to bring about the Salvation.
Tennouji, if you want to ward off our destruction,
kill the Key.
You may be able to do it, given how unguarded it
is with you.
Think hard and decide whether you will secure
this planet's future, or mankind's present.
Is it similar to youth?
What is youth, then?
"Something radiant."
Those were Kotori's words.
"The hell should I know?"
"Waste of time thinking about it,"
Here they come.
...said Yoshino, dismissively.
Let's go, you bastards!
Take this!
A long time ago,
someone said, "Life is like walking a tightrope."
All three of their opinions seemed correct to me.
It's something dazzling,
mysterious,
and terrifying.
Of course it's hard to answer.
Because there's no right answer to that question.
Regardless,
I decided to set out on a journey to look for it.
Yes...
All I wanted
was to spend that thing
called "youth" with everyone.
That day, mankind heard it.
Help me!
Hey, what the hell are you doing?!
The song of destruction
which signaled the world's demise.
It's morning.
Rise and shine, sleepyhead.
We've gotten separated from everyone,
so I'm feeling lonely.
What the heck is that?!
That creature feels familiar.
Huh?
I suggest you not rely on your
rewrite ability so readily.
Overuse it, and you will cease to be human.
Is that you?
Where am I?
Kagari.
Kagari...
Kotarou.
Is it time for my morning feecof?
Oh?
I don't hear that hair-raising song anymore.
You're right!
The song of destruction stopped at some point!
Kagari!
Thank goodness!
Seriously!
I honestly thought I'd never get to see you again.
Kotarou?
Is that the Key?
Esaka-san.
You don't seem particularly surprised.
Something told me you would show up.
Then I trust you are aware of what I'm after.
I will put an end to the Key, here and now.
I won't let you.
Kotarou-kun!
I never expected you to have an ability like that.
This guy is strong!
I'll never land a hit unless
I shift up one—no, ten gears.
You...
What?!
A lesser-skilled opponent would surely look...
for a surprise attack to my blind spot.
But no matter how fast that attack may be,
it poses no trouble when I'm anticipating it.
I was naïve!
Even if I step it up ten gears, he's still way beyond me!
In that case!
Don't, Kotarou-kun!
I just have to keep stepping it up until I reach him!
Gotcha!
Kotarou...
Sakuya...
Sorry, Captain.
This is the end of the line for the
Bayern Knights of the Green Sword...
Hit, and you'll be hit back.
That goes for Gaia and Guardian alike.
And when it's over something
important, that goes double.
Bloody hell. Talk about a sinful life.
If there is a world after this one, then...
As long as I can make delicious ramen,
that'll be plenty enough for me.
Your attacks lack variety!
Damn it, again!
They're powerful, but little else.
Don't expect a heavy swing like that
to connect more than once!
Attacks should be simple,
but with force behind them.
Kotarou-kun!
Damn!
Just a little more!
The bleeding stopped?
That power...
I see.
Your body appears to have remembered.
What does that mean?
That's irrelevant to you as you are now.
Furthermore,
I cannot stand to see you
in that sorry state any longer.
Tennouji...
If only you hadn't come back
in such a half-baked condition...
What the hell are you going on about?
M-My body—
The only mercy I can offer you
is to end this in one swing.
This is farewell.
Kota—
Sto—
Kotarou!
What?!
Shizuru!
Kotarou.
How utterly reckless.
Gramps...
You won't regret this?
I won't!
I see.
Then the time for words has passed.
En garde!
Kotarou...
Kagari!
Guess I went up too many gears.
Crap.
My body feels like it's going to rip apart!
Kotarou-kun, are you all ri—
Looks like the tab I've racked
up is due for payment.
I'm like a daemon, aren't I?
Sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Kotori?
I did this to you...
Ah, I see.
I now understand why I was drawn to Kotarou.
I am inside him.
This was your doing, wasn't it, Kotori?
The day the Key appeared from the power spot,
I came to the forest for you,
in order to fulfill my promise as a druid.
For some reason, Kotarou-kun was there, too.
Kotarou-kun! Kotarou-kun!
And he was at death's door.
All I wanted was to save him,
Please, save Kotarou-kun!
so I begged you over and over.
Please!
I embedded your ribbon inside
Kotarou-kun's right arm,
and managed to save his life.
I wanted him to live.
I didn't want him to disappear somewhere far away,
like Mom and Dad.
But that just ended up making him suffer more!
H-Hey! Hang in there!
It is all right.
He has simply lost consciousness.
My power is too much for humans to handle.
While it amplified Kotarou's powers,
it also placed a terrible burden upon him.
Then, what should we do?
You could remove my power and return it to me...
But then, what will happen to him?
Your power is what closed his wounds,
and is keeping him alive.
I do not know,
but at this rate,
he will definitely lose his life.
Aw, guess we ain't got no choice then!
Indeed.
Put simply, a huge hole will open
up in Kotarou-san, correct?
In that case...
Yeah!
For a big guy like me,
ain't a hole that can't be plugged up!
Wait!
Do you realize what you're saying?
It just happened to work out that way,
but we did form a contract.
We have to make ourselves useful once in a while.
Understood.
See ya!
Though it was only for a short time, it was fun!
Kotarou-kun?
Kotori.
Want some morning feecof?
Sounds nice.
Of course,
we don't have any beans, hot water, sugar, or milk.
But you're walking around
with cups in this situation?
Don't push yourself.
You're just barely alive right now.
Gil and Pani aren't here, huh?
Those two ran away.
They said they couldn't deal
with us, and went far away...
I see.
Well, knowing them,
they'll be fine wherever they go.
What's happened?
Nothing much has changed
since that song stopped.
I see.
Well, I guess I changed a little.
How so?
You have not evolved from the same foolish, rash,
blockheaded human you always were.
Hey, you don't have to force yourself.
Kagari!
Kotarou-kun, this is...
Yeah.
Damn it, I hear it!
The song of destruction!
Kotarou-kun!
Why?
He doesn't have Kagari's power anymore!
Survival is utterly without meaning.
This land is filled with naught but sorrow.
That being so, life is unnecessary to this world!
Let this song resound!
Destruction is the one and only Salvation
you foolish lifeforms shall be granted!
The pump has been sufficiently primed.
Everything is in order.
Now, Key!
Grant these sinful lives Salvation!
Kagari!
Kotarou-kun!
Kagari! Kagari!
Let me go, damn it!
I still need to talk to her!
Kagari!
No! Not the face!
What will I do with you, Kotarou?
You're always so mean to me...
You must be super-duper totally in love with me.
Shut up.
This is the Salvation?
The world is going to end, due to my ruling?
No.
The other Kagari is the one
who made the final ruling.
No, it was me.
I'm sure there must still be some other way.
The feecof was delicious.
Huh?
The internet and school were both fun.
Kotori and the others were
noteworthy humans, as well.
What are you...
And, most of all, the days I spent with you
were the finest, most irreplaceable memories.
Kagari?
Will you...
save this world?
Do you know what you're saying?!
Yes.
I wouldn't mind dying if it was at your hands.
Kotarou-kun!
Huh?
You think I could actually bring myself to do that?
You idiot!
I... care too much about...
Kotarou, among all the humans in this world,
you truly are the most
helplessly foolish of them all.
Shall we go?
Mom?
I'm hungry.
Let's have some saury.
Dad,
Mom,
and Shizuka...
Let's all eat, together.
Yeah.
Let's do that tomorrow.
We aren't alone anymore.
We...
We have everyone...
They're disappearing!
The world!
Humans!
And us!
Akane...
Shimako...
Are you okay, Sakuya?
I'll pick you up now.
I never knew.
You were this heavy, huh?
From now on,
I'll be the one carrying you...
It was never easy,
but we did everything we could, huh, Chibi-Moth?
Little one?
Pero?
Is that you, Pero?
You were with me all this time!
I wonder if we'll get to see everyone again?
That sure would be wonderful...
Everyone is ascending.
Gaia, Guardian, the Key.
I was involved with them all,
but I couldn't do anything.
If I had a little more time,
I wonder if I could have done everything better?
It's all right.
I'm sure you could, Kotarou.
Yeah...
owariyuku jidai ni mo
Even as the end draws near
Episode 13
The Promise I Made With You
tashika ni mebuku inochi ga aru no, hora
There's budding life still here, see?
hitomi wo tojita nara
If you close your eyes
ima wa sono kodou ga yasashii
You'll feel the gentle heartbeat
nureta hoho wo naderu
That gently caresses your damp cheeks
kaze ni yureru kusa no you ni
Like a wind that makes the grass sway
kimi to futari yorisoi mitodokete yuketara ii ne
I wish I could see the end by your side
kurayami ni kakuretemo
Though hidden in the darkness
hana no kaori mo
The scent of the flowers
mushi no haoto mo soko ni aru no
And the buzzing of insects are there
wakariaeta no nara
If you understand
kanjitoretara te wo tsunagou
If you can feel them, let's hold hands
The world welcomed "demise"
I have to rewrite it all.
I'll do things better next time.
Route
Starts January 2017!