The barrier has been breached?
And by brute force, at that...
What did you say?
Who did this?!
Pardon me.
It would seem I knocked a little too hard.
Sakuya!
Is it time for my morning feecof?
You idiot! Stay away!
My, what a surprise.
I was not expecting even Lady Key to be here, too.
What?!
I'm already collecting Kotori-san,
so while I'm at it, why don't I bring you along too?
Oh, please rest assured.
We at Gaia treat our guests
with the utmost hospitality.
Sakuya!
If you are to pretend to be a knight,
weak as you may be,
I do hope to see the limits of your capabilities.
Well then, I'd be happy to oblige!
What might this be?
Yay! You finally showed up!
Gil?
The time has come for me to take my revenge!
Okay, Sensei, if you would be so kind!
Gil-chan, you are truly and utterly pathetic.
As you can see, my spies have been exposed.
Do you understand how perilous
the current situation has become?
With that said, would sir and madam
happen to require an all-purpose butler,
capable of cooking, cleaning,
laundry and, perchance, even fighting?
Huh?
Little by little, the ripples drew apart from one another
sukoshizutsu hamon wa hanarete itta
And before we knew it, they no longer overlapped
itsu shika hitotsu mo kasanaranaku natta
But it's okay as long as you're here with me
sore demo ii kimi to itara
When did I start feeling this way?
konna kimochi itsu kara idaita
This is the love story of a certain boy
tada hitori no shounen no koimonogatari da
To protect you till the end of time
eien ni kimi wo mamotte miseru
I'll etch this upon my heart
kono mune ni kizamikomu
When did it start being just the two of us, again?
itsu kara futarikiri ni natta n da kke
But it's okay
mou ii ka
Just smile
sonna koto waratte yo
On the eve of this world's end
owaru sono hi ni wa
Here lies
a traitor.
It was a spur of the moment thing!
Episode 10
Simply, As Friends
I simply got mixed up in all of this!
'Tis a fine barrier.
However, and do forgive me for saying so,
it would be somewhat lacking
in both defense and strength
if pitted against an elite
summoner or superhuman.
R-Really?
So, that's how you sent
those two here to manipulate us?
Indeed.
Well, to be precise, I was the one sent here.
Huh?
It appears we will need to take
some precautionary measures.
Can you take care of this, Sakuya?
Please keep an eye on Tennouji,
and if possible, any activity in his vicinity.
Hm? I'd rather not.
Hey!
Well, jokes aside,
doing so would mean leaving Chihaya-san's side.
No worries there!
I mean, look!
I have this power that you gave me, Sakuya!
Very well, then.
Prez and Chihaya sent you?
I cannot act too overtly, however,
given Chihaya-san's position.
Support is all I can offer.
Not a problem!
Having you here is really reassuring!
Thank you very much.
Please allow me to support you as your butler.
In that case, please train me!
Please.
My training is not for the faint of heart.
How long are you gonna keep me waiting?!
Dear me.
How impatient you are, Slowtarou-kun.
Half-baked imitations of my skills will be
of little use against professionals or daemons.
If there is anything that I can impart upon you,
it is pain and experience.
That won't do.
You mustn't allow your mind to go blank
over such minor things during combat.
Oh, by all means, use those blades
in your right hand as well.
Otherwise this will be over in an instant.
Fine! God damn it!
K-Kagari!
Wh-What is it?
Kotori, what is Kotarou doing?
Training with Sakuya-san.
Don't interrupt them, okay?
He's working hard for your sake.
Good! Let 'im have it!
Ah, Kagari-san, you are so loved!
When a man starts pushing himself this hard,
it's usually for the one he loves.
Loves?
He's working hard for your sake.
You're all beat up.
Right, Kagari?
Allow me to offer this to you.
It is the ultimate feecof,
which Kotori taught me how to brew.
You made this?
What brought this on?
How is my Kagari-chan blend?
This is definitely your sort of flavor.
But thanks.
Huh?
Hey, what are you doing?
Oh my.
Gathered together for a tea party, have we?
Kagari made us all coffee.
Would you also like some, Sakuya-san?
How very intriguing!
I shall gratefully partake, then.
It is quite... skillfully made...
A-As a token of my gratitude, allow me to serve
you coffee I have put all of my skill into making.
Your feecof is gross, Sakuya.
You broke his heart!
Frankly, coffee that's on sale for 55 yen
a can is good enough for Kagari.
How truly absurd!
Very well!
Allow me to show you a butler's true capabilities!
How about directing even a single percent
of that enthusiasm toward me?
All right!
Damn it!
Damn!
We have completely run out of supplies!
Huh? For real?
It was originally only supposed
to be me and Kagari here,
so we need to go shopping.
I'll go, then.
It's boring here, and Sakuya's feecof is gross.
Uh, the butler over there is in
a rather hilarious state right now...
I don't really want to let Kagari leave this place...
In that case, I shall accompany her as a guard.
Fortunately, the Harvest Festa
begins in the city today.
Neither Guardian nor Gaia should
have perfect surveillance in place.
Okay. I'm counting on you for the rest.
Gotcha!
I'm on the ball again today!
Come on. Let's go to the library.
Sounds good!
That was close.
I've been holed up in the forest
and skipping school lately,
so it's kind of hard to face the guys from class.
Well, then.
Now that the shopping has been completed,
there is someone I would like
the two of you to meet.
And who would that be?
Go ahead. She's behind this door.
Welcome, gypsy,
to my mystical room.
It wasn't even that long ago,
but this is kind of nostalgic, Prez.
You're right. It certainly is.
However, today I'm not here
as the president of the occult club.
I'm here as the Martel Group's next saint.
Saint?
Wait, Martel?
On the surface,
it's an environmental protection agency,
but behind the scenes,
it's an organization that has fought tooth
and claw over the Key since ancient times...
Gaia.
The Martel Group was actually Gaia?
I suppose that's where your
mysterious influence came from?
Kagari-san, was it?
If you can understand me, then there
is something I've always wanted to ask you.
For what purpose does an avatar of the planet
go out of its way to judge human beings,
as trifling as we are?
I don't know.
I'm currently searching for myself.
I think I'll understand once
I find what I'm looking for.
P-Prez?
What the hell?
If that's how you are,
then what have I...
Even petty, minuscule humans
have created many wonderful things.
Like the internet, and the internet...
Not to mention, this feecof is right up there.
I will give it to you, so cheer up.
Of the gifts Kotarou has given me,
feecof is my favorite.
Something like this won over the Key?
Tennouji, do you remember this?
If I recall, this is from back then...
Q25) You have power and are discontent with this world. Tell me, do you wish to change this world? Or do you wish to change yourself?
The World
Myself
I never expected you would answer like this.
I don't know.
I will do what I can, in the place I belong.
No matter how futile it may prove to be.
My time with you... No.
My time with all of you wasn't bad.
See you.
This really will be the last time we meet.
Please wait, Prez.
Aren't you forgetting something important?
Something important?
Yes!
Namely, boobs!
Huh?
You promised I could touch your boobs
if I proved the occult exists!
This whole ordeal is, without a doubt, the occult!
Hey! You're going to ruin
the whole mood with that?!
Boobs transcend all reason and situations!
That's just how boobs work!
Wh-Why you...
What's all this about boobs?
There! Go fetch!
Wait...
That's the nuisance taken care of!
Y-You beast!
Oh, fine!
Do whatever you want!
Don't mind if I do!
Time's up.
I've got to get back.
Huh?
We'll continue this in the
occult club room sometime.
You fool.
According to the analytics team,
it's extremely likely that
the Key has appeared this year.
We can expect it to show up
at one of these three points.
What's that spot with the different color?
In the forest,
there's a wide area in which we can't
get a consistent read from aerial maps.
It's rather suspicious.
Oh, right. We have new intel.
We aren't sure of the connection,
but we've confirmed this schoolgirl
has been in the same area repeatedly.
Please leave scouting that area to me!
Trust me, I'm definitely not considering a cover-up
in case that girl turns out to be my friend Kotori!
They delegated me to logistical
support for some reason...
It's not exactly an unreasonable
decision on their part.
But why did Kotori disappear,
only to show up in the forest?
Could Kotori be part of Gaia, too?
Kotarou disappeared, too.
I have to do something.
Shizuru, forget about the occult club,
Kotarou and the others already.
Lucia!
For now, focus on subduing the Key.
Got that?
Honestly!
We're late because you left
the luggage with Chibi-Moth-san
and went on a side trip!
What's wrong with slackin' off
a little once in a while?
Okay.
The entrance to the barrier is around here, right?
Please be careful.
Gaia's summoners occasionally patrol this area.
Miss Kotori!
We just got back!
What an ugly sight.
After consuming this planet
to their heart's content,
they do not even realize that there
is nothing remaining underfoot.
What utter foolishness.
Indeed.
Your face betrays your lingering attachment.
When I took custody of you, you were empty,
so I'm glad you grew up
into such a fine young lady.
However, you will most
definitely yearn for destruction.
That is the burden we saints must bear.
I... am aware.
Where do you think you're going, Shizuru?
Lucia, please overlook this.
I'm sure you understand this isn't a situation
where you can act based on personal feelings.
But Kotori is our—
If we leave the Key alone,
not only will Kotori and the others perish,
so will all of humanity!
I know that.
Even then, I...
You're disobeying orders?!
Lucia?
You're not thinking rationally at the moment.
So I'll go instead.
Don't worry.
I won't do anything bad.
Take this!
Not bad, I must say.
You are starting to make fewer rash decisions.
"Not bad" isn't enough.
In that case...
And speaking of rash decisions,
here is a fine example.
I suggest you not rely on
your rewrite ability so readily.
Rewrite?
A power where you rewrite your own limits
and draw out your abilities freely.
So you do know about my power!
Yes, I know it all too well.
I also happen to know the
heavy price with which it comes.
The price?
To be absolutely frank with you,
overuse it, and you will cease to be human.
There will be situations where
you have little choice but to use it,
but even then, keep it to the bare minimum.
Let us conclude here for today.
Y-Yeah...
Kotarou, can I ask you something?
Huh? What is it?
Why are you trying so hard? It is a mystery to me.
Well...
To protect you?
Does that mean it's because you love me?
L-Love?!
Am I wrong?
It is true that I'm doing it for you,
but I'm sure that's not all.
For years, I've been looking
for a place where I'd fit in.
And I finally found it...
I hope this becomes a nice place
where you fit right in.
But the place where I finally fit in
slipped through my fingers all too easily.
I won't lose it this time.
And...
K-Kagari?
Ow!
Hey, the hell you doing?!
Oh...
I have been very curious about
your right arm since the other day.
Curious...
Kagari?
Homo...
N-No! Who would even want to see SakuKota?!
Homo sapiens...
Kagari?
Is something the matter?
Don't gimme that!
This area is already Gaian territory.
Are you here, Kanbe Kotori?
You're sure it's up ahead, Midou?
Yeah.
I definitely saw some puny
daemons go through the barrier.
Is it really inside the barrier?
No doubt about it.
It's a presence I've felt plenty of times
since coming to this country.
It's the Key.
You don't even have eyes that can discern the Key.
You're a beast, all right.
If what those puny daemons
said is true, the Apex
and that stray superhuman who can
use that odd power should be there, too.
Not that I give a damn.
I'll crush them and the Key to pieces!
Not that it's anything new, but he's insane.
A little late to bring that up.
A stray superhuman?
Could he mean Kotarou?
If so, Kanbe should also be there.
Why are they with the Key?
No, more importantly...
If I let them go, I can confirm the Key's location.
However, if those two really are there,
they'll definitely be killed.
Don't hesitate!
The Key is our top priority!
Nothing else...
You know, friends don't let friends be all alone.
kurenazumu machinami ima futari de aruku kedo
Walking together around this town that's slipping into darkness
I'm such an idiot.
What could possibly take priority
over protecting my friends?!
te nanka tsunaide mite hazukashikute utsumuita
Embarrassed at the thought of holding hands, I stared at the ground
You want me to go to where Sakuya is?
Yes.
And not just temporarily. I mean forever.
Wait, do you mean...
Leaving the organization.
hitori de wa dame na no hora minna ga yonderu yo
We can't stay alone—look, everyone's calling us
You were always skeptical of Gaia's
policies anyway, weren't you?
B-But if I leave, who will help you?
Uh, the only job at this organization
I could really leave to you
nanimo itsuwaranai watashi ni nareta
I was able to become an honest person
is looking after Shimako, anyway.
You meanie!
That aside, can I ask you
to take care of something for me?
Understood...
You're better off by Sakuya's side.
moshimo wo negau no nara ashita ga ii deshou
The time left for my wishes to come true is running out
You're too kind,
so I doubt you could endure
what's going to happen next.
This is war, after all.
hanasazu ni kono shunkan wo kamishimetai
So I want to cherish this moment while I still can
Damn! Tenma! Tenjin!
I haven't killed them.
You understand why, right?
You hunters are a piece of work!
It's all over for them if they die,
but as long as they're still breathing,
they're a burden!
I won't let a single person past this point!
watashi ga hitori de naita nara
If I cried here all alone, would that be enough
I'll end this before he summons his daemons!
You use fire daemons?
Close, but no cigar.
kimi wa soba ni ite kureta no kana
For you to come over and stay by my side?
What's this?!
A lava daemon?!
Correct!
Come out and say hello, Fogo!
Give this to Tennouji.
ichiban hayaku ano hoshima wo kakeru
I want to become a flower as soon as possible
A letter?
Yes, a very important one.
Once you meet up with Tennouji and the others,
choose whichever path you believe is best.
Once this is over and peace has returned,
hana ni naremasu you ni
To soar through the star-filled sky
let's all get together again.
Yes!
You, Kotarou, Kotori, Shizuru,
and Konohana-san!
You bastard!
What are you thinking?!
Don't you realize this is a forest?!
Yeah, it burns up real good!
That's a pretty neat trick you've got!
But how long can you keep it up?!
Lava is mostly made up of silicon.
If you reconstitute it,
then as you can see,
it crystallizes into silicon dioxide!
My high-frequency blade is at a huge
disadvantage against his flames!
In that case...
I have no other choice!
I'm sorry.
Hey, a hunter is kneeling before me?
What a riot!
Don't misunderstand.
The one I'm apologizing to is this forest!
nee donna sekai nara yuruseru
Hey, what kind of world is allowed to exist?
What?!
My flames...
kotae wa isso shiranai mama demo ii
I'm fine with not knowing the answer
What the hell did you just do?
No matter how much lava you may have,
it's pointless if there's nothing to burn.
You monster!
Yes, that's right.
But even monsters have things
they want to protect!
watashi ga hitori de naita nara
If I cried here all alone, would that be enough
Yeah, keep running your damn mouth!
You moron!
It doesn't matter how
many times you cut Fogo—
kimi wa soba ni ite kureta no kana
For you to come over and stay by my side?
Wh-What?
My body...
A daemon and its master are linked, right?
Then, even if a slash has no effect,
poison should work.
Bingo, huh?
Y-You bitch...
nee donna mirai wo tsumugeru no
Hey, what future can we weave?
Rest assured.
I'll ease your pain now.
You're pitying...
Looking down on me?
Don't fuck with me!
yogoreta mama no watashi de ii no
I wonder if I can remain as impure as I am now
Kotarou...