Prepare to die, Hida Kizuna!
Don't make me laugh!
I knew you'd try to assassinate me.
Kunoichi Aine
Assassination Apocolypse
Stop it!
You have such an adorable moan.
You won't...
...get away with this!
And what exactly will you do to me?
Stop this now!
There's no escape.
St-Stop...
Stop it...
In your dreams.
So soft.
Ow...
Exquisite.
St-Stop...
Is it pleasurable?
O-Of course not...
Your moans of pleasure say otherwise.
No!
Squirming won't help you escape.
You've gotten quite sensitive.
Hidden Art
Heart Hybrid
Th-That's...
Hidden Art
Heart Hybrid
...what you wanted, isn't it?
Hidden Art
Heart Hybrid
Do you know why we call female ninja "kunoichi"?
Because the strokes for "woman"
can be read as "ku", "no", and "ichi'.
That's not it.
Let me tell you: it's the number of orifices.
Two eyes and two ears;
two nostrils; one mouth; one navel; one anus.
All together nine, or "ku", orifices.
And then there's the one men don't have—
Number ten, the "plus one".
No...
According to some
Stop...
Isn't this what you wanted?
No...
Yes, but...
Not like this!
Your body is more honest than your mouth.
I'm not...
Stop resisting. Let me hear you scream.
No... No... No!
Not there!
You sure are enjoying this.
That's just not true...
You really wanted this, didn't you?
No!
Oh?
Give in to the pleasure.
A-Amazing!
This is the Hidden Art: Heart Hybrid?
Kunoichi
Photo Collection
What am I thinking?