Psychic Powers
Summer sweeps across the whole country! Take precautions against heatstroke!
Summer has arrived in Japan!
Channel, change!
Summer sweeps across the whole country! Take precautions against heatstroke!
Summer has arrived in Japan!
Brother, people don't develop
new superpowers so easily.
Summer sweeps across the whole country! Take precautions against heatstroke!
Summer has arrived in Japan!
Rino, use the remote control
and change the channel!
Summer has arrived in Japan!
Please stop it.
Summer sweeps across the whole country! Take precautions against heatstroke!
Summer has arrived in Japan!
Here.