Morning!
Very impressive, Sakura!
Huh?
You set a new quad-to-classroom record!
I'm just glad the teacher's not here yet.
I guess I was last to class again.
About that...
G'morning!
Syaoran?
It's not every day you show up after me.
Thing is, I got a phone call this morning.
From who?
From my mother in Hong Kong.
Did she need something?
Syaoran?
Please take your seats!
Okay!
I have some sad news for you all today.
Hiiragizawa Eriol will be returning to England.
What?!
No way...
That sucks.
Wow.
I'm gonna miss him.
Sakura and the Two Teddies
But I still haven't done enough to thank you, Eriol...
I'm the one who should be thanking you.
That's not true at all!
Listen, Sakura...
How did you feel when you heard
I was going back to England?
Really let down.
I have a favor to ask of you.
The next time this happens to you—
learning someone very close
to you is going far away—
ask yourself how different
their leaving feels from mine.
That should help you figure out
which one of us you treasure the most.
What do you mean?
You'll understand before long.
Huh?
Hi, Syaoran!
How'd you know it was me?
Just a feeling.
What do you say we walk home together?
S-Sure.
It's gonna be quiet without Eriol around, huh?
Yeah, true.
Oh, I almost forgot!
What was it you wanted to tell me
after we got back from Tokyo Tower?
I think that I...
That I... like you.
Huh?
I like you
more than anyone.
That's all I wanted to tell you.
Be careful on your way home.
Did you hear Ms. Mizuki's back at school?
Yeah.
I didn't know she and Hiiragisawa knew each other.
Clow Reed, was it?
He's proving to be a real nuisance.
Still, I'm sort of grateful to him.
If he hadn't created my true form,
I wouldn't have met either Sakura or you.
Is she still holed up in her room?
She's been in there ever since she got home.
I wonder if something happened?
Something did.
You know about it?
I've known for a while.
And I know what happens next.
There's a reason I could never stand that brat.
S'the matter, Sakura?
Does your tummy ache? Ya got a fever?
No...
I'm fine.
I like you... more than anyone.
Syaoran...
How do I feel about Syaoran?
Of course I like him—we're friends.
Or are we more than that?
No... No, we're not, but this feeling...
It's not like how I felt with Yukito, so...
what could it be?
So this is goodbye.
Yes.
It's sad to see you go.
I wish I could've seen you off at the airport.
Well, you have class, so that's that.
But thank you.
Do you mind if I keep writing?
By all means!
I look forward to hearing from you.
Oh, right!
Please, take these. Souvenirs from England.
Thank you very much!
We really appreciate it!
And one for Syaoran.
Syaoran had an errand to run this morning, so...
R-Right...
It's almost time!
Please keep my words to you in mind.
I look forward to the day we can meet again.
See you!
Man... sucks that I won't get to play with
Toya and the others back in England.
I hope you mean play together, not play with.
I play together with Toya,
and play with Yukito, duh!
Bet those two are gonna be crazy sad
without yours truly around.
No, they'll probably be better off.
Excuse me?!
You're gonna be lonely, too,
with no Cerberus to keep you company!
Huh? What's that supposed to mean?
Can I ask you something?
Yes?
You're head-over-heels for him, Spinny!
...Why did you create those two?
I certainly am not.
Where'd you get that idea from?
At Tokyo Tower,
I knew Yue and Cerberus would attack me
in order to protect Sakura.
Their intervention was key.
Are you sure there's not more to it?
Ruby and Spinel must be at my service.
Were they not, Cerberus and Yue...
would have continued to search
for Clow Reed within me.
Especially Yue.
But it does go a bit deeper than that.
In my own way, I am quite fond of those two.
By which you mean that deep down, you love them?
Yes, perhaps.
I hope Sakura's "love" gets a happy ending as well.
No, no...
This is Sakura we're talking about.
She'll be fine.
I wonder what kind of errand Syaoran had to run.
T-Tomoyo...
Yes?
Uh, the thing is... Syaoran...
H-He... He told me...
He told you he likes you?
H-How'd you...?!
I can tell just by looking at you, Sakura.
What's your answer?
I don't know.
When I think of Syaoran,
it feels like something's squeezing me,
and I start getting so confused...
I don't know how I should feel...
The hardest thing for a person
to understand is ultimately themselves.
Especially what's in their hearts.
Tomoyo...
Only you will ever know how your heart truly feels.
Your answer's already there inside you!
Is that a souvenir from the lady
'round Tsukimine Shrine?
Yep.
What is it?
Wow! It's a bear-shaped brooch!
It's adorable!
Not somethin' to eat? That's a bummer.
The bear I meant to give to Yukito...
You ended up staying here at home, huh?
That bear Syaoran left behind...
Whoa there, Sakura, you're beet red!
Ya got a fever?
N-No!
Uh, I need to go give Ms. Mizuki's gift to Syaoran!
Why's Sakura start blushing
when she looks at you now?
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
I'm a million
times cooler than
this darn thing!
Does my face really get that red?
I... like you.
Tomoyo said the answer's
already inside me, but…
Anyway, I have to give Ms. Mizuki's gift to Syaoran!
But... But my answer...
Is someone moving?
H-Hi, um... M-Ms. Mizuki wanted you
to have this souvenir from England!
Thanks.
And... uh...
I-Is someone moving out?
That's a lot of boxes.
I am.
Huh?
I'm going back. To Hong Kong.
Syaoran...
I first came to Japan in order to
search for the scattered Clow Cards.
But even after we gathered the cards,
you stayed here!
That's because a lot of stuff happened afterwards.
But now it's all over.
The Clow Cards were turned into Sakura Cards.
And it's all thanks to you.
You know it wasn't all me!
It was all because Tomoyo and
Kero and Yue all helped me!
And because...
Because you were here with me, Syaoran!
It's nice to know that you think of it like that.
Do you really have to go back?
Yeah.
There's some stuff I have to do in Hong Kong.
When are you leaving?
Tomorrow.
Tomorrow?!
I was planning to stop by your place
if I didn't run into you today.
But I'm leaving tomorrow.
So soon?
I'm glad I came to Japan.
And met you.
No...
Because I met you, Sakura.
Excuse me! Can you confirm the given destination?
Sure.
If you could check this part right here...
Looks good to me.
Thank you very much.
Sakura...
Syaoran's going back to Hong Kong.
He's going far away...
Will we meet again?
It hurts... my heart hurts so much now!
The next time someone
very close to you goes far away,
ask yourself how different
their leaving feels from mine.
When I heard Eriol was leaving,
it made me feel really sad.
I had all kinds of thoughts,
like "I hope we can meet again,"
and "I'll have to write to him,"
but hearing about Syaoran...
I'm going back. To Hong Kong.
You can't!
Man, ya practically barged through the door.
Hey, what's with the sewing kit?
You rip something?
No, I'm gonna make something.
Make what?
Something important.
Sakura?
Sakura, what're ya doin' still up?
I have to finish this by tomorrow!
But you've been sewing away
since the moment ya got home!
You can head to bed, Kero.
This must be pretty important to ya.
Yeah.
I take it there's nothin' I can do to help out?
I want to make it myself. The whole thing.
Gotcha.
I don't wanna get in your way,
so I'll head to bed.
But if you need me at all,
wake me up no matter what!
If there's anything I can do to help,
you can bet I'll get to it.
Thanks, Kero!
Y-Yes?
Sorry to bother you at this hour, Sakura.
Yukito...
Looks like I was right on time.
Thank you so much! Did you make this yourself?
I only helped out. It was all Toya.
What? My brother did?
Toya was embarrassed,
so he had me bring it up
and went on back to his room.
Is that what you're working on?
Yes.
Is it for somebody?
It is...
I guess you've found the person you like most.
I have!
Is it someone I know?
Yes!
Care to properly introduce me to him sometime?
That might not be possible.
Why not?
He's going... far away.
But it's not as if you'll never
see each other again, right?
No matter how far he goes,
you can always meet again.
As long as you both want to see each other.
Yeah, maybe...
I was thinking...
When the magical powers
of my true form, Yue, run out,
both Yue and I will disappear from this world.
If I had known that beforehand,
what would I have done?
I think I would've searched for a way
to keep from disappearing.
I would've done anything in my power to do so.
Because I could never stand the thought
of never seeing you and Toya again.
Honestly, it's not like there's much I can do.
That's not true!
Hahahaha
That's
not true!
Hahahaha
Shake Shake
Thanks.
But if you truly wish to see this person,
and this person truly wishes to see you,
you're bound to meet again.
If you both feel the same way, it'll all work out.
Thank you so much!
All done!
Ya finished it?
Yep!
Daidouji Tomoyo
It's Tomoyo!
Hi, Sakura?
I was told that Mr. Terada
will be coming to today's chorus
competition to cheer us on!
I also heard that Syaoran will be leaving
for Hong Kong on a 10 a.m. flight!
10 a.m?!
If his flight's at 10 a.m.,
he's probably already left the house!
Sakura?
No... No way...
If I can't give it to him...
If I can never tell him how I feel...
No!
Get a hold of yourself, Sakura!
You can still make it in time!
You've got your invincible spell, after all!
Everything...
Everything will be okay.
What's the hurry?
I only have 5 minutes!
I've got to get to the airport bus stop!
Huh? 5 minutes?
Even on roller blades, that's impossible!
But I've got to!
Sheesh...
I'll take you on my bike.
Toya!
My heart beats in my chest
As it carries different feelings
And with each heartbeat
I learn something important
I never got to hear her answer...
Every time I close my eyes
Still...
Syaoran!
I can see your smile
Sakura!
I...
Every time I listen closely
I finally know how I feel!
I can hear your voice
I like you more than anyone, Syaoran!
The sky holds so many promises
I'm glad.
As every ending is yet another beginning
Is it okay if I name this bear "Sakura"?
The time I spend with you is priceless
Can I name the bear you gave me "Syaoran"?
Sure.
You're my beloved one
I'll be back. I promise.
When?
When I finish all my business in Hong Kong.
Syaoran!
Will you wait for me?
Every time we're apart
Yes! I'll wait! I'll be waiting!
I miss you so much
But it helps me gather strength
I'll wait forever if I have to.
The strength to face forward
Because...
I like you more than anyone in the world, Syaoran!
As a rainbow comes after the rain
I can see our future at its end
And as I reach out my hands
I feel like I can grasp our dreams
The sky holds so many promises
I'll always believe they'll come true
No matter how far apart we are
You're my beloved one
See you later!
So pretty!
I wish I could've seen this with Syaoran...
The first cherry blossoms of junior high school...
Syaoran!
Prologue: Sakura and the Two Teddies