You're beautiful...
I'll take you to the flower garden.
Remo.
Grandma!
Dr. Daniel Dawson develops
ViOS
(Violet Operating System)
Dr. Diana Dawson develops
Mother
(environmental control program)
Control is initiated
To an ideal earth...
Japan
Dual!
I did it! I won first prize! I can't believe it!
Well done.
I can finally go to London in the spring!
Maybe I can even study there!
Your dream might come true.
Yeah! I've always dreamed of traveling
the world and playing piano for everyone!
You've always been there for me.
Thank you so much.
I couldn't have made it this far without you.
Sumire...
I'm sorry.
What?
This backup data
is infected with a virus.
It can't be restored.
I'm not the Dual that you know.
This is a backup copy of 21st-century Japan.
A virtual world being stored
within the Box of Wisdom.
Is something wrong?
We're out of time.
What?!
This world has been completely infected by a virus.
And so have you, Sumire.
No way! What's going on?!
Deleting data!
What is this?
Is this some sort of dream?
Am I dreaming?
It isn't.
The world you were living in,
however, was a dream.
A dream...
It was all a dream. You and I are both just data.
What are you saying? You're Dual.
We've always been together!
For you, it may seem that way.
However, I reconstructed
this world only a short while ago.
You and your memories are nothing
but recently re-assembled data.
I don't get what you're saying!
Infected data...
must be deleted.
What are you playing at?
What do you mean?
What do I mean?
Don't play dumb with me!
Get yourself together!
That world was supposed to be mine!
I guess.
You guess?
There you go again! Stick to the rules!
I've been waiting for ages.
Didn't you see?
See what?!
I was meant to delete that world.
What?
Sumire believed I was her childhood friend.
So it had to be me.
What, you felt some kind of
responsibility toward her or something?
I mean, sure, you were supposed
to be her friend in that world,
but ultimately, she was just a scrap of
human data in a virtual world program.
A world that was only just
recently reconstructed, too.
Why do you bother sulking over every deletion?
Just hurry up and delete that data, too.
It's been happening a lot since the upgrade...
Us getting integrated into reconstructed worlds
as a friend or a family member.
It never used to happen before.
Humans do the most annoying things.
She said her dream was to become a pianist.
Her dream, huh?
Not that I understand.
You've been acting strange lately.
You're getting attached to data
that's meant to be deleted.
We're just programs.
All we need to do is get rid of viruses
in accordance with our algorithms.
Man, this is getting on my nerves!
This is happening because
we're both anti-virus software.
Why did they install both of us?
Maybe they're trying to see which one is superior?
In that case, I'd win. Hands down.
My, aren't you talkative?
Maybe you've been infected.
I'd rather say that you
have a bug in your system!
Dorothy!
Shut it!
Huh?
Who's that?
Hey! Don't run off on your own again!
Deleting data.
Bring it on!
There are so many viruses lately!
You hear that, you creeps?
I miss the days when we were
just fixing bugs in the system.
Almost done.
Get out of my way!
You get out!
Compress.
Shut up!
Delete.
That was a tough one.
I could have handled it myself though.
I feel like there have been more viruses lately.
You're right. It's pretty weird.
Where are they all coming from?
Hey, she doesn't seem to be infected.
No virus detected.
Could be a Trojan.
We should delete her, just in case.
We're not authorized to delete this program.
Wait a second.
Don't tell me you're taking her with you?
Fixing bugs is part of our job, too.
I know, but come on!
Hey!
Don't you think you're being mean, Dual?
How so?
I can't enter without your permission.
Go back to your own zone. I'll stay with her.
Are you crazy?
If she's some new breed of virus,
my zone might get infected too!
What a pain!
If you weren't around,
I'd have this place all to myself...
Wh-What?!
Wh-What's happening?!
She fell asleep?
Who are you?
I'm Dual.
You were attacked by a virus, weren't you?
What are you?
Are you an anti-virus program like us?
You're a virus, right? Just admit it.
We told you who we are!
The least you can do is tell us your name!
Remo...
Remo? Is that your name?
What kind of program are you?
Flower...
Flower?
I have to return to the flower garden...
Where? Is that some place in the backup data?
I...
Why were you installed in the Box of Wisdom?
What are you programmed to do?
This is really weird.
She's an anomaly. She's suspicious.
She's also dangerous.
It'd be a good idea to delete her.
We can't delete data that isn't infected.
We can quarantine her or something, though.
Programs can't act on their own free will.
If we just did whatever we wanted,
we'd be no different from viruses.
I think she's just unstable right now.
She might recover on her own in due time.
I'm telling you, Dual.
If that girl is a virus,
we'll have to delete her right away,
or else we'll be in danger, too.
I know.
Level One?
Right. This is Level One.
Besides Dorothy and me,
you're the first to set foot in here.
The Box of Wisdom is divided into three levels.
We found you in Level Two.
That's where all the backup data is pooled.
Backup data?
Restorable data for various time periods and places.
Dorothy and I are in charge of
monitoring the Box of Wisdom.
If we find any bugs or defects, we fix them.
If a virus appears, we compress and delete it.
We access the archived data and scan it for viruses.
This is all backup data.
Virtual reproductions of various eras and lands.
What's this?
Don't be scared.
It's the remains of a virus we dealt with.
We compress it
and then delete it.
So if I were a virus, like Dorothy said...
You aren't a virus.
Do you want to see a virus scan?
You may remember something.
Whoa!
She's so cute! Is she a celebrity?
This is Level Three.
This world, along with everyone living in it,
only just came into existence.
Do you recognize anything here?
Not really. I wonder why I got so excited.
Did you remember something?
No.
I'm sorry. I wasted your time...
That's okay.
I just felt like eating something.
This looks so yummy!
Yummy?
I guess a human would
find things delicious or cold.
You don't?
Delicious, beautiful, fun, interesting.
I understand the concepts,
but I can't experience them.
Anti-virus programs have
no use for such functions.
What about feeling joy or sadness?
I don't know.
I think I've felt something close...
I guess humans call them "emotions",
but I'm not sure if what I felt was that.
Perhaps human data has emotions,
as well as memories and dreams.
Dreams?
But those are only programmed in.
You're amazing, Remo.
Can you taste things?
I get the feeling it's probably delicious.
Maybe you're human data.
I don't know.
But if you tell yourself something is delicious,
doesn't that make it delicious?
It does seem delicious if I tell myself it is...
Delicious, huh?
You guys know what that feels like?
You went and reconstructed another one!
I told you it was my turn!
I wanted to show Remo.
You always do as you please.
This is fun.
So, did you figure out where the flower garden is?
No.
I knew it.
Hurry up and remember!
These humans don't know that their existence
is like a dream.
Who made the Box of Wisdom?
Why back up data of different times and places?
And even the humans who live there?
Who would do that, and for what purpose?
No idea. We just do the job
we were programmed to do.
I'm glad this place wasn't infected.
What if it was?
I'd have to compress the whole world and delete it.
So, the real world exists outside this Box, right?
"The real world"?
The reality where humans live.
I guess.
We can't see it, though.
Do you want to talk to them?
To the humans who created us?
To humans?
I'd never even thought about it.
You have such an imagination.
Really?
Am I a weird program?
Remo.
I feel like cleaning!
Morning!
Pleasant dreams?
We don't dream.
For us, sleep means shutting down to upgrade.
I see.
When one of us upgrades,
the other one upgrades automatically.
Humans provide us with upgrades.
Humans do?
What's wrong?
N-Nothing. I just...
What are you doing?
Cooking!
I wanted to make something for you.
Dig in!
Why are we doing this?
Don't ask me.
I just had an urge to cook.
Where did you get the ingredients?
From the backup data.
What? Don't you start doing as you please too!
Once I got started, it was so much fun!
She didn't bring back any viruses, did she?
Nope, I guess not.
So? How is it?
We can't tell if it tastes good or not.
I guess that's true...
But if I tell myself it's delicious, it seems like it is.
Really?
Yeah.
Yay! Dorothy, you try it too!
I have no interest in human culture.
Come on!
I see you don't trust your own virus scan.
What? Are you kidding?
Well, I guess I could find this
delicious if I tell myself it is.
That's great!
Is that really something to be happy about?
Hold it! I can wipe my own mouth!
You're good.
You brought these, too?
Yeah.
I like the data from this place.
Look! I can juggle three of them!
Even I can do that much.
What's that tune?
Schubert's Lullaby.
You have some strange talents.
They're strange?
At the very least,
you're not anti-virus software like us.
When I'm with you,
I almost understand how delicious
food tastes or how beautiful music sounds.
That's probably because I
find them delicious and beautiful,
and those feelings reach both of you.
Both of us?
Is that how it works?
Yeah. It means our hearts are in sync.
Is there a song you want to hear?
I told you. We don't understand music.
Do you know this one?
How can you play it?
I don't know.
My dream is to become
a pianist and travel the world.
Music can transcend time and borders
to bring people together, right?
I want to do that with my music one day.
Piano can make miracles happen.
That's all I remember.
Looks like my memory's a little fuzzy.
What's wrong, Dual?
Are you crying?
We never cry, because we don't need to.
Don't worry. It's not your fault.
Sorry. I'm fine.
Can you play it again?
But I don't know the rest.
That's fine.
If you say so.
I still think you're a fragment
of human data from somewhere.
Human data?
Yeah. You must've come out of
one of the backups stored here.
How else would you know
so much about human culture?
Yeah. You do have a point.
Right?
You probably came from some
flower garden. I'm sure of it.
Man, I'm so brilliant!
What's so funny?
Nothing.
It just hit me that you're worried about me, too.
I'm not worried at all!
I just can't rest easy unless I know who you are.
That's all.
It's gonna be a pain to check
every single backup here.
We can scan for viruses at the same time.
I guess...
We don't want her getting lost again, though...
You're still holding on to that?
If we use this as a tag,
we can find Remo wherever she is.
I think it'd look better on you, Dual.
It's a memento from a girl named Sumire.
Sumire?
Human data that Dual was friends with.
But she was infected, so we had to delete her.
Thanks. I'll take good care of it.
What?
We're like three sisters.
You're one strange program.
Let's go!
When time was flowing so softly and quietly
I thought that all we needed to do was protect this world
But then...
My heart became one with yours
It was full of feelings I wanted to share with you
I have so many great memories of our own world
A world so perfect and beautiful
So if you feel at least a little bit happy
Then I would be really happy too
Let us talk some more
So you can feel the same way I do
My frozen heart has begun to awaken
I want to feel more, learn more, and experience more
Being alone was such a natural thing to me
But now that I know how it feels to have friends
I'm not as I was programmed to be
I'm seeing the world in different colors
I want you to tell me about all the things I don't yet know
With the magic of your words I would learn all about things like
Happiness, sadness, loneliness, and joy!
And somehow, in some way, it would make me feel alive
Ah, I want these feelings to engulf me!
I want to feel them all
Because it seems like so much fun!
Smiling with everyone will surely bring me happiness
It really does make me so happy...
Happy birthday, Dorothy!
Here's my present to you...
A hat!
I thought it would look good on you.
It's beautiful!
I got you some candy.
You love sweets, right?
I love them!
And this is from Mommy.
I think you'd look nice in a dress like this now.
Mom made it herself.
She'd been working on it for ages.
We helped a little, too.
Thank you!
And this is from Daddy.
Oh, my!
A puppy!
How cute!
You've wanted one for a long time.
Take good care of him.
Thank you.
Okay, Dorothy.
They say that if you make a wish as you
blow out the candles, it'll come true.
What's your dream, Dorothy?
Well...
I want us to be happy together forever!
Dorothy...
That world was infected by a virus.
I had to delete it.
They were just programmed data,
but they truly believed that
I was part of their family.
Dorothy...
I'm fine.
That cake...
If I'd eaten the one my mom made...
I'm sure it would have been delicious.
I'm getting just as weird as you guys.
I don't get it.
Why does backup data exist?
Only the humans who created
the Box of Wisdom would know.
Where do viruses come from?
Why did they suddenly increase in number?
Does infected data really have to be deleted?
Is there no other way...?
Our role is to do what we've
been programmed to do.
There's too much I don't
understand about this world.
Why am I even here?
I still love this world, though.
That's why I've protected it for all this time,
and I'll keep on doing so.
Keep it down. You woke me up.
For some reason, housework really calms me down.
You sure have it nice. You don't have to upgrade.
It doesn't matter if you sleep or not.
Maybe you're just a support tool for us.
Maybe the flower garden isn't even real.
The flower garden...
I feel like it's something important...
A support tool, huh?
I hope that's true.
Why?
That means we can be together forever.
A moderate-level virus alert.
Where are they all coming from?
Stay here, Remo.
Why? I want to come.
Don't bother. You'd just get in the way.
That's mean!
A new variant?
I've never seen this type before.
Still a piece of cake, though!
Compress!
And delete.
I wonder what happens to the viruses we delete...
Deleting them means that they just disappear.
Why do you care?
I remembered what Remo once said.
I think you're going crazy.
Another one?
It's huge!
It's all yours!
What are you doing?!
Give it back...
Sumire!
Please give it back...
Give me back my dream.
Your dream?
Sumire's dream?
What are you spacing out for?!
You and your stupid functions...
Dual!
Dorothy...
If I get infected, eliminate me...
Take care of Remo.
Stop talking nonsense!
I'm coming to save you!
Dorothy! Dual!
You idiot! Why did you follow us?
I just...
What?
Remo!
Remo! Remo!
Where's Remo?
Over there!
She's not infected.
Let me check you, too.
You're clean.
What does this mean?
I thought the virus infiltrated both of you...
What happened to the virus?
I don't know.
There was this bright light...
And now there's no sign of it.
Maybe she's infected after all.
I don't detect anything.
Maybe her memory's coming back.
Did you say "Sumire" earlier?
I saw her inside the virus.
But wasn't she deleted?
Deleted viruses are destroyed.
That's what we always thought.
Right. They cease to exist in the Box of Wisdom.
That's the end of it.
But what if it's not?
I'm starting to wonder about things
I've never even considered before.
When the virus engulfed me...
What about it?
You tried to help me.
Thank you.
Whatever.
Connecting to the host. Initializing remote link.
Remo!
Measuring virtual coordinates
of the Box of Wisdom.
Separating protocol. Initiating search.
Remo!
Remo, who are you?
Why were you installed in the Box of Wisdom?
To search and collect data.
Data? What data?
Data for an experiment.
What experiment?
What do humans want from you?
Not humans...
Then who programmed you?
Humans are probably...
all... de...
Did you understand that?
Hey.
Dorothy, how much time
has passed since our installation?
Dunno. I've never checked...
Uh, five years?
Maybe time inside the box flows at
a different rate than it does outside.
Like how time in backup data flows at
a different rate than here in Level One.
Perhaps far more time has
passed in the outside world.
Fifty or maybe even a hundred years...
Perhaps even more.
What are you thinking?
Remo! Remo!
She's not going to stay like this, is she?
Is there anything you need?
Piano...
Did she just say piano?
That tune...
Does she want to hear that lullaby?
Could it be?
What are you doing?
Remo appeared when I deleted Sumire's world.
That song may trigger something in her memory.
You can play the piano?
Enough to make a sound.
I watched Remo play.
It's working.
Keep going, Dual!
Remo could only play to this part, right?
It's just like before!
Remo!
Keep only beautiful things...
...for Mother.
Mother?
Everything else is unnecessary.
Again?
Over here!
Remo?
What the heck?
Remo!
Jeez, it's like a maze!
I know! Find her with that tag we put on her!
This way!
Are you okay?
Remo!
She can't hear us!
She's going too fast!
She's exceeding the maximum processing speed!
If we go any faster, we'll...
Really drives home how foolish
mankind was, doesn't it?
I'm enjoying my last drink, at least.
This colony is on its last legs, too, isn't it?
Yeah.
I'm a little upset...
Who knew we'd be witnessing
the destruction of mankind?
Destruction...
...of mankind?
Remo!
Did you regain your memories?
It's my fault.
You had to delete so many worlds.
What do you mean?
Explain it to us!
What was that about the
"destruction of mankind"?
The Box of Wisdom was created
to bring about an ideal world.
The research of Dr. Diana Dawson,
who lost her child during an environmental protest...
We can create an ideal Earth!
Here is Dr. Diana Dawson, daughter of
Dr. Daniel Dawson, the developer of ViOS.
I promise you that the tragedy that befell
my daughter will never happen again!
The year 2100.
Humans entrusted the monitoring
of society to a program called Mother.
Make Mother Earth's wish come true
The network brought peace
and stability to the world.
However, it also led to the stagnation
and eventual demise of human civilization.
Social stagnation led to lower birth rates.
The human species was dying out.
But that was all part of Mother's plan.
After all, humans were the only destructive species.
They were unnecessary in Mother's ideal world.
Humans, and their free will, were a hindrance.
And so, a program was run
to phase out the human race.
At the same time,
Mother began compiling backup files.
It archived humanity's history
and culture as data in a virtual space.
All of the human data in that space was
copied from the personalities of humans.
From people that actually existed in the real world.
And from all that data,
she is extracting only the beautiful things
and assembling them to create an ideal human.
An ideal human?
A human that wouldn't harm the Earth.
A creature without free will.
But that's not human.
What did the humans do?
They tried to delete Mother, of course.
Delete?!
But...
Humanity no longer had the power to fight Her.
What do you mean?
The moment Mother was deleted,
humanity died out.
Are these flowers those
so-called "beautiful things"?
Why are there so many of them?
Because I'm gathering them.
Who was sending us our upgrades?
That's right. Humans are gone, right?
After being stripped of their "beautiful things",
the data remnants unexpectedly reactivated.
Reactivated?
What remnants?
Because of that, your algorithms were rewritten
to identify remnants of stripped data as viruses.
So...
Mother is still active?
Remo!
Mother Remote.
I don't have a name.
Mother...
Remote...
Remo...
You're...
Mother left behind one hidden backup program.
I am Mother.
My job is to collect beautiful
things until I'm ordered to stop.
The sun!
A virus!
This level's firewall has been breached!
Remo!
What?! What is this?!
Remo...?
You're back...
...to normal?
This seems like some sort of shield.
So they weren't actually viruses.
But we still have no other choice than to fight!
Let's protect her!
Yeah!
They're after the flowers!
They're trying to retrieve the data
that was stripped from them?
Give it back.
Mommy!
Daddy! Sis!
Dorothy.
Dorothy...
Give it back!
Give us our world back!
Dual!
Sumire...
No!
Remo!
You too, Sumire?
So you're the same then, Daniel.
Diana.
Mom said she looks like you.
Did you see it?
I did! I saw the news!
Grandpa looked embarrassed.
He sure did.
That was Dr. Daniel Dawson's press conference.
He announced a revolutionary
OS named after his wife.
She's a world-famous pianist.
She must have inspired him.
It's getting warm.
Try tying up your hair.
You're so brusque.
You were always like that, Dual.
I'm entering a piano competition soon.
My instructor said I have a shot at nationals.
Really?
I want to keep improving.
One day I want to play piano for the whole world!
Sumire...
You're deciding your future
with your own free will, huh?
That's what it means to dream.
Isn't it the same for you?
Help me.
Together,
we'll protect everyone.
Sumire...
Restarting program. Initiating upgrade.
ViOS!
Give it back. Give it back.
Dorothy! That's enough!
Shut up!
What?!
Just wait.
Dual?!
What happened?
Let's go!
This is one amazing upgrade!
Actually, it was a pretty major downgrade.
Really? It's fantastic!
This is how we really look.
This is the version before Mother's updates.
So we just reverted? Is this how we used to be?
Sumire's memories and feelings
all came flooding into me.
Sumire's feelings, huh?
Is she safe?
Good.
Remo.
Are you okay?
I wanted us to be together forever.
Yes. The three of us.
We'll be fine.
Why?
Our bodies!
Sumire! What's happening?
A forced format?
What does that mean?!
Mother was waiting for you
to send an error signal.
Dual, Dorothy.
If both of you detach yourselves from Mother,
the Box of Wisdom will be abandoned.
Remo...
But why?
Mother felt threatened by your heuristic engines.
She saw them as the last vestiges of human will.
Grandma.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
You have a name.
Really?
Of course.
Good!
Grandma...
I found something I want to protect.
But I don't know what I can do to help them.
Remo...
Only you can do it.
Ask your mom.
Humans deleted Mother.
Why are her protocols still active?
I don't know.
Remo! Why?
Thank you.
Why are you saying that?
You two are anti-virus programs
that are embedded in ViOS.
I heard that from Sumire.
Tell me that sooner!
I'm also a core program of ViOS.
So you're one of us!
And Mother gave me the authority
to rewrite your algorithms.
So the formatting program is inside you?!
Bingo. It's a trap Mother embedded in me.
I detect a virus.
No! Why?!
Dual! What should we do?!
We'll end up erasing Remo!
Sumire!
Remo is lucky. She has something to protect.
Dual...
The forced format will delete the three of us,
along with all other data in Level Two.
That's fine! Let's all disappear together!
You think I'll allow that to happen?
It's fine! Let it happen!
I won't.
It was fun.
Mom.
There are people I want to protect
from the bottom of my heart.
Your precious friends?
Yes.
I'm glad you're not alone...
Remone.
You're anti-virus programs.
And I'm a virus.
Delete me and you can save
the world and everyone in it.
Promise me you'll protect the world together.
Promise me, please.
I promise.
Dorothy.
I had fun with you, Remo.
Me, too.
Thanks for teaching me how to cook.
And how to juggle.
I won't lose next time.
Thank you for cleaning.
Thank you...
Thank you, Remo.
It's been destroyed.
Yeah.
It was fun.
What should we do now?
Keep this place safe so Remo can come back.
So she can see the future
with everyone living here.
Sounds good. I'll help you.
Really?
Of course.
We have to rebuild our house.
Yeah.
With a kitchen big enough for three.
Let's make it really spacious.
Remo likes to clean.
She'll love it.
For sure!
I guess this is what it means to dream.
Remo said this would look good on you.
Maybe the Earth didn't need us.
No. Dr. Dawson never wished
for mankind to perish.
This is our last hope.
Indeed.
ViOS...
When I was watching a flower
Swaying gently in the wind
I suddenly thought about you
I remembered a melody
From my distant memories
That felt oh so nostalgic
I know that you're here
Here in my heart
And it feels so warm
It's as if you're alive
As the time continues to pass
I don't want to forget these feelings
So I'll keep them here in my heart
I can see how dazzling
the past we shared has been
So I'll send a wish to the stars
So I say goodbye, I'll see you tomorrow
We made a promise
Let us meet again, here in our special place
I know I can believe
That this whole world
Is full of feelings
That are ours only
Stars connected in constellations
Are like us holding hands
Together we are closer to our dreams
Your smile was like
A flower blooming
It seemed so fragile
We want to sing you a lullaby
That flows from our hearts
I wanted to protect you
From the bottom of my heart
Now we can feel it clearly
This whole world
Is full of feelings
That are ours only
Our meeting was fated
So when we hold hands
We can make our dreams come true
We can make our dreams bloom