Before
and
After
Year 2014
Our daily lives were, for the most part, peaceful.
The man who started making games for someone else's sake (44)
Each day passed without a second thought to it.
The woman whose hand someone held onto (37)
Just an endless stream of "normal" days.
Some of us had someone to share in this bliss,
while others woke up in the morning
feeling crushed by the world.
The woman who took a step towards the future (21)
There's no such thing as fate.
Miracles are just wishful thinking.
On the days where all
we wanted to do was just give up,
The man who was guided by something (21)
we had friends to weather them with.
Some of us were at times deeply hurt,
and others are soon to face hardships.
The boy who stopped bragging (15)
Still...
Eventually, those bad experiences will be a thing of the past.
They'll become a source of strength,
gently pushing them forward.
They hold in their hearts important lessons.
The girl who fell in love with the piano (8)
Never give up hope.
No matter how grim it seems.
No one is ever truly alone. Never.
The boy whose life has only just begun (0)
As long as you're alive,
you'll always have another chance.
They may be walking their
own separate paths right now,
never able to return to the castle again, but still...
Southern Tokyo Careo Shopping Mall Food Court, 2014
Someone out there is a bit mischievous.
And...
An incredible miracle broke free of wishful thinking.