Labor wreaking havoc in town.
hiro @h_i_r_o_4_6   1m
That's a Hishii Bulldog in Nippori, isn't it?
#LaborBulldog
DRIVE MEGA @drivemega1988   55s
This thing's in the middle of Ginza
#LaborTerrorism
Asobi Assistant Teacher @AP_ASOBI   37s
This looks bad.
Dude, the guy's streaming on Nico!
#NipporiLaborTerrorismUpdate
STUDIORIKKA @studiorikka  22s
All right, show time.
The perpetrator is leaving a trail
of broken homes in his wake.
Th-The Labor just stopped!
We demand stricter laws
regarding Labor operations!
As you can see, a Labor can be used
for good or evil depending on the pilot!
This modern age of social media
is a major pain in my rear.
I'm still waiting.
We're trying to apprehend him ASAP.
But the bastard went into
a narrow shopping district!
Just deck-up there, then.
But what about the civilians?
No buts.
He's already destroyed thirteen residences.
Preventing more destruction
is worth a few angry citizens.
That's ice cold.
Wh-What was that?
This again?
Government thieves!
Isn't this unlawful property damage?
Never mind that!
Huh?
Unit approaching!
What?!
What's with this guy?
There's no way a Construction
Labor can move like that!
Stop it! Someone could get hurt!
Please!
That's why I'm holding back!
It's this way!
What late-night anime is that from?
Unit 01, follow the road and push him into Nippori.
There's a graveyard west of the station.
That's better than the middle of town.
Roger!
My family's Buddhist!
I'm not doing anything wrong, am I?
Unit 02, you listening?
Take the Yamanote line to our position.
The train bound for Ikebukuro will soon...
All passengers: A Tokyo Police Department
transport will be passing through on line two.
Please stay behind the white line.
What are you doing,
letting a Bulldog push you around?
What do you mean, push me around?
He's got you beat in speed and power!
I'll show you who's top dog here!
Now we're talking.
Calm down! If you hit the cockpit...
Use it.
Huh?
Since close-range combat isn't working,
we need to fight at range.
"Be flexible in the field,"
is what our old captain used to say, isn't it?
Unit 01, fire at will.
Roger!
You're gonna fire at a citizen?!
In this situation, you are not a civilian!
You're a rampaging Bulldog!
Stand strong in the face of danger.
Whoa, what the hell?
Seriously?
Captain, you're ice cold.
All good?
We're done here.
Thank you for your help.
Bring 'er home, boys!
The subject has been arrested in Nippori
for unlawful property damage.
Roger that.
Survey the extent of the damage.
I'm just glad he didn't fire at that range.
He should have. Our bullets are all blanks, anyway.
Captain, you gotta tell us that stuff!
Didn't I?
I'm telling you, Labors are dangerous!
Yeah, yeah. Tell it to the judge.
That was a dirty trick you used!
We're not characters in some robot anime.
We're police officers upholding the law
to keep the people and town safe.
Up yours, jerk.
What'd you say to me?!
Aw, come on!
Such fire.
Labor is the name adopted to describe
robots developed for industrial use.
Labors became prevalent
in earthwork and building construction,
but their ubiquity brought
about criminal uses as well.
The Tokyo Metropolitan
Police Department established
the Special Vehicles Section 2
Patrol Labor Company to meet this challenge.
And thus, the police force nicknamed the Patlabors came into being.