Akari!
I brought you a fancy outfit for the occasion!
Special
What? For me?
Yes!
Star of the Day!
It's time for you to shine, Akarin!
You're the star of the day, Akarin!
Star of the Day!
Akarin!
Akarin
Star of the Day!
Kyoko...
She'll let me be in the spotlight!
Wait, it's too bright!
YuruYuri's 10th Anniversary!
It's YuruYuri's tenth anniversary!
Here we go!
YuruYuri's 10th Anniversary!
Star of the Day!
Akarin
Special
Merry mayhem, merry mayhem
Merry mayhem, YuruYuri
YuruYuri
Time passes in the blink of an eye
But our youth is still far from over
Let's do spring, summer, fall, and winter again one more time
One more time
Things that make your heart miss a beat
And stupid everyday happenings are all exciting
I hope these days will never end
You listening, God?
However many decades pass, let's spend another year like this
Together again
Together
With you
Without fail
With you here
We'll always end up creating
Merry mayhem
Tomorrow, and the day after
Forever
And ever
Whatever happens, we'll have happy days
Next week, and the week after
Forever
And ever
Next year, and the year after too
We'll walk together, hand in hand
Because I
Love you
Merry mayhem, merry mayhem
Merry mayhem, YuruYuri
YuruYuri
What on earth are you people doing?
We're playing cavemen.
We were planning on reminiscing about
the past ten years, but we went too far back!
It was fun, though!
C-Calm down!
YuruYuri
Tea
Ceremony
Club
Ah!
So ya wanted to do somethin'
special for the tenth anniversary.
How does that turn into playing cavemen?
You're as good at startling me as ever-Everest!
E-Everest...
Instead of doing something weird,
why don't you throw a party like normal people would?
A party, huh? Sounds a bit too normal.
Actually, yeah. A party sounds good!
We'll go all out! And in about three days from now.
Good idea.
That sounds much better
than fooling around like this.
Yay, a party!
I love parties!
We'll decorate the place
and bring a bunch of snacks.
We can invite Hima and Saku too!
Hey, don't just decide on your own!
Sakurako
Yay! Let's party!
Himawari
I would love to join you.
They said they'll come!
That was fast!
Me and Ayano'll be there too.
Chitose!
As vice president, ya gotta keep
ya eyes on 'em so they don't go too far.
W-Well, when you put it that way...
That settles it!
YuruYuri
You want to learn how to bake cookies?
Yeah! I want to bring some
to the party in a couple of days.
Are you free after school?
I would be happy to teach you.
I was just thinking of bringing something myself.
Akari! Let's make decorations together!
Hooray! Thank you!
Sure!
We'll start by pouring flour into the sieve.
Okay!
Is this right, Coach?
Please don't call me that. It's embarrassing.
Oh, it's looking good!
Really?
What is this delicious cookie?
You are a natural, Chinatsu!
Be my wife!
Would you mind mixing this next?
No problem!
China-hah-tsu!
All right!
Time to bake some delicious
cookies and make Yui happy!
e..e.ee..ee....e.....e...e......e....e.....e..e....e.......e......e...e..e..e..ee...e..e.......e....e....e....e....eee..e.....e...e...e...e...e
eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
b
e..e.ee..ee....e.....e...e......e....e.....e..e....e.......e......e...e..e..e..ee...e..e.......e....e....e....e....eee..e.....e...e...e...e...e
eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
b
e..e.ee..ee....e.....e...e......e....e.....e..e....e.......e......e...e..e..e..ee...e..e.......e....e....e....e....eee..e.....e...e...e...e...e
eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
b
e
eeeee
ee
eeeeee
eeeee
eeeeeeeeee
eeee
ee
e
eeeee
ee
eeeeee
eeeee
eeeeeeeeee
eeee
ee
e..e.ee..ee....e.....e...e......e....e.....e..e....e.......e......e...e..e..e..ee...e..e.......e....e....e....e....eee..e.....e...e...e...e...e
eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
b
10 Minutes Later
Look, look! I mixed it perfectly!
Really?
What happened? I only looked away for a second.
C-Could I borrow that for a minute?
Sure!
eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
e..e.ee..ee....e.....e...e......e....e.....e..e....e.......e......e...e..e..e..ee...e..e.......e....e....e....e....eee..e.....e...e...e...e...e
b
eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
e..e.ee..ee....e.....e...e......e....e.....e..e....e.......e......e...e..e..e..ee...e..e.......e....e....e....e....eee..e.....e...e...e...e...e
b
e
eeeee
ee
eeeeee
eeeee
eeeeeeeeee
eeee
ee
e
eeeee
ee
eeeeee
eeeee
eeeeeeeeee
eeee
ee
e..e.ee..ee....e.....e...e......e....e.....e..e....e.......e......e...e..e..e..ee...e..e.......e....e....e....e....eee..e.....e...e...e...e...e
eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
b
Another
10 Minutes Later
I managed to salvage it somehow.
Now I just need to roll out
the dough with this, right?
Indeed.
Here I go!
There!
How? All she did was roll it out.
eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
e..e.ee..ee....e.....e...e......e....e.....e..e....e.......e......e...e..e..e..ee...e..e.......e....e....e....e....eee..e.....e...e...e...e...e
b
eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
e..e.ee..ee....e.....e...e......e....e.....e..e....e.......e......e...e..e..e..ee...e..e.......e....e....e....e....eee..e.....e...e...e...e...e
b
e
eeeee
ee
eeeeee
eeeee
eeeeeeeeee
eeee
ee
e
eeeee
ee
eeeeee
eeeee
eeeeeeeeee
eeee
ee
e..e.ee..ee....e.....e...e......e....e.....e..e....e.......e......e...e..e..e..ee...e..e.......e....e....e....e....eee..e.....e...e...e...e...e
eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
b
Yet Another
10 Minutes Later
There is more to Yoshikawa than meets the eye.
Wh-Why don't you cut out the cookies next?
Okay!
Wait for me, Yui!
China-hah-tsu!
There!
It's so cute!
Is this some kind of magic trick?!
And then Kyoko and Yui wanted
to play video games in the clubroom...
Sakurako! Akari!
Oh? That's Chinatsu!
I can smell cookies!
Welco—
Wow... Those look great...
Aren't they cute?
Have a cookie, Sakurako!
Chinachu!
What do you think?
I-I can see you put your heart into them...
YuruYuri
Tea
Ceremony
Club
The Following Day
Look at this, Himawari.
What about it?
Darn boobs! Darn boobs!
Stop that!
Chinatsu, could you hand me the masking tape?
Here you are, Yui.
Look here.
Wow, that's really cute!
Yours is cute too.
You look like you're struggling, Ayano.
Special
Lemme try.
That about does it!
Special
Here you go.
Shwink.
We have to clean up.
Let's pop the balloons together.
Now this is one ripper of a party.
The party is tomorrow, you know.
Special
Right, that's everything.
I'm counting on you for the food, Yui, my boy!
Yeah, I know.
Let's call it a day, then.
Yeah.
Oh yeah, I left something in the classroom.
No need to wait for me.
Akari, you're such a scatterbrain!
You are one to talk.
And after fetching what I left behind...
It's time to deck the place out even more!
Ya sure seem fired up, Akaza.
Ah! Ikeda!
I thought you went home with the others!
I couldn't help bein' a stickybeak.
Um...
I was planning on surprising everyone
by putting up even more decorations.
All right, I'll lend ya a hand!
Thank you!
Let's make it real fancy!
Yeah!
YuruYuri
Anniversary
th
Here's to ten years!
Is it just me, or did the
decorations get even fancier?
Me and Akaza did it together after
yous all went home yesterday.
We did our best to surprise you all!
Wow, you did?
Thanks, you two.
Great job!
I'm glad you like it!
Here, Yui!
Have some China-cookies!
Th-Thank you, Chinatsu.
Chinachu!
I think I saw something...
You got a taste of our future together!
Himawari, these macarons are delicious!
I made a lot, so help yourself.
th
Anniversary
Chef Funami's pie sure is great.
Unlike Himawari's boobs.
What is that supposed to mean?
th
Anniversary
What's your problem?
Oh?
Where'd Toshino go?
Now that you mention it...
She snuck out a while ago.
Where did she run off to?
th
Anniversary
What?!
Wh-What happened to you, Kyoko?!
Well, I figured I'd commemorate
the day with a makeover.
What'cha think?
Her neck!
That's a wig, Sakurako.
A wig?
What's the deal with that thing?
It's not a real party without cosplay!
Ta-da!
I've got one in Yui's hairstyle too!
Why?
All right, time to play the straight man!
Do something silly, do something silly!
Yui wouldn't say something like that!
Oh no! It's the Yui police!
Let's play around with these!
Wow, looks fun!
What? This is too loud for me.
Boss!
What do you think, Yui?
Y-You look good in a bob.
Isn't this a bit too much?
Looks pretty good, actually.
What'cha think of this one?
You went for that without a second thought?
Why was this the only one left?
I look like I'm a general in a period drama!
Congratulations!
Looks like everyone's havin' fun.
Y-Yeah, looks like it.
Hey, you two.
Congratulations!
Don't just stand there.
Toshino Kyoko...
Wow, not bad, Ayano!
It looks great on you!
O-Of course it does!
Check it out, Ayano.
Whaddya think of this hardcore wig?
With this on, no one'll notice my nosebleeds!
How about not bleeding at all?
All right, photo time!
Timer, set!
Here we go!
Say "cheese"!
Congratulations!
YuruYuri
Let's do this next!
th
Anniversary
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Jobs Edition
IMPRESSION
The rules are simple!
Anything can happen! Make the game exciting!
Comes with three new cards!
Sakurako, don't tell me that's...
Let me explain...
You flip a card, and then you do
an impression of the job shown on it.
IMPRESSION
Job Card
Maid
IMPRESSION
Would you like something cute with that?
Maid
Job Card
IMPRESSION
Maid
Job Card
IMPRESSION
Maid
Job Card
IMPRESSION
Maid
Job Card
IMPRESSION
Maid
Job Card
IMPRESSION
Maid
Job Card
IMPRESSION
Maid
Wait, why do I have to do this?!
IMPRESSION
Maid
Job Card
Wow, sounds fun!
Let's get started!
I'll go first!
Job Card
Assistant Director
I'm an assistant director!
th
Anniversary
Job Card
Cut!
Hey, you over there. Your boobs are too big!
Switch places with someone else!
Magnifique!
That is just a weird person.
Job Card
Doctor
Delicious!
th
Anniversary
Oh, I'm afraid this patient has
something wrong with her head.
What was that?!
Okay, let's see what I get.
Job Card
IMPRESSION
Nio Statue
I-Is that really a job?
My turn...
Job Card
IMPRESSION
Nio Statue
O-Okay, my turn to flip a card.
Job Card
Baseball Player
Um...
Oh, I know!
L-Leadoff home run!
That wins us the game,
and the crowd goes yay-yay Yale!
Th-These are some rules.
Job Card
Comedian (Straight Man)
Congrats! It's your full-time job!
What a pro.
Looks fun.
Guess I'll flip one too.
Job Card
Comedian (Straight Man)
Oh, me too?
I'm not too used to this.
Ikeda, give me your best retort!
Come on, come on!
Come on!
Wh-What's up with that face?
That's so cute.
I'll go last, then!
This game's got duplicate cards.
If Toshino draws the doctor card...
It's time for your examination.
I think you might be sick.
Yes...
Love sick.
I can feel it comin'!
A tsunami of blood!
Job Card
IMPRESSION
YuriTuber
A YuriTuber!
Why'd ya pick that?!
YuriTuber
A perfect one out of nowhere?
How's it going, yuris?
YuruYuri
th
Anniversary
All right, folks.
I have the perfect game to finish off the party!
Yay!
I call it "Hyper Rock-paper-scissors"!
Every time you lose, you have to act more hyper.
What a weird game.
That sounds really fun! Let's do it!
Okay, here we go!
th
Anniversary
Rock, paper, scissors!
Oh, I lost.
All right, Akari.
Act a bit more hyper than usual.
What?
Yay! Are you having fun?
Let's play some rock-paper-scissors!
I didn't expect her to go that far.
Okay, round two!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Hooray!
I guess Akari loses again.
Man, I sure messed up there!
Guys, let's get the next round started!
Don't you wanna play rock-paper-scissors?
W-We do...
Yeah, that's right!
I'm glad you feel the same as me!
Rock-rock-rock,
rock, paper, scissors!
Why do I have to lose every round,
you think?
Y-Yeah, I wonder...
But I mean, it's not like losing
consecutively can't happen.
Yeah...
You know, I want to see all of you
acting hyper as well!
Oh? What's this?
Is it just me, or has the mood gone down?
Y-You think so?
You haven't lost a round yet,
so it's not like you have to act hyper,
but I never gave you permission
to bring the mood down!
That's a no-no.
Oh, right.
Sorry.
M-Maybe we shouldn't.
Y-Yeah.
Hey, so—
Okay, guys!
Time for the next round!
Rock, paper,
scissors!
It's so fun to lose!
This makes me wanna dance!
D-Don't you think this has gone too far?
Sakurako!
You don't look very excited.
That's not like you at all!
Come on, show some spirit! Are you excited?!
Y-Yeah...
Boo-yah! Here we go!
I went and lost again!
I'll die at this rate!
YuruYuri
Huh? I...
Did I really...
That can't be.
I'm the main character!
And this is our tenth anniversary!
I don't want to die!
Akari, Akari!
Sakurako?
Akari, thanks for always hanging out with me.
It was a lot of work practicing for the
stand-up routine, but it was really fun.
When I heard that you water the
flowers in the classroom every morning,
I grew even fonder of you.
I'm so happy we became friends
so quickly after we started school.
I-Is this...
I was so happy to see ya eatin'
my pickled veggies with a smile.
I'm sorry for scaring you
with the gas mask back there.
Whenever we're chattin',
I feel warm and peaceful inside.
I'm looking forward to getting
to know you even better.
You two...
Akari!
You're so easygoing that I
sometimes worry about you.
Just like I said then,
if anything happens, I'll be there for you.
Chinatsu!
Kyoko! Yui!
Akari, look at this.
Graduation
Ceremony
You sure were a handful with your bawling.
Though it's not like she was the only one crying.
We told you, "We'll wait for you
in middle school, so hurry up,"
but you took a whole year!
You don't say.
But you came in the end, so I forgive you!
Kyoko!
Akari, I hope we'll always be friends.
And...
Happy Birthday!
Akarin
Happy Birthday
Huh?
Akarin
Happy Birthday
Weren't we having our tenth anniversary party?
Happy Birthday, Akari!
Huh?
That's right. Today is your birthday.
Ayano talking about throwing
a party gave me the idea.
We decided to celebrate your birthday too!
Yui picked up on it immediately.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
Akari!
Happy Birthday!
G-Guys...
We all love you, Akaza.
Ikeda!
Looks like the surprise party was a success.
Remember what I said, Akari?
You're the star of the day!
Thank you so much!
Promise me we'll always be friends!
In 20 years, 30 years,
no matter how much time passes,
we'll always be together!
Ding-dong ding-dong, YuruYuri
Ding-dong ding-dong, it's starting
One, two, let's go!
That's the end of classes for today
All right, let's race to the club room!
Ready, set...
Kyoko, that's cheating!
Everyone thinks the end of classes is where you say goodbye
No, no, this is where it all starts, classes are just a long lead-up
Let's go
Ding-dong ding-dong, the Amusement Club
I have no idea when this turned into our usual place
Let's run so fast our shoes fly off
I don't understand, there's nothing special here
Yet it's all so fun
Yes, somehow I'm so happy being here
There's no reason for it
We're still in our growth spurt
And our hearts are growing big as well
I want to listen to the sound of the school bell together forever
Ding-dong ding-dong, here comes verse two
Ding-dong ding-dong, stay with us
Only one potato chip left, time to have a thumb war
Having trouble deciding, let's start with rock
Rock-paper-scissors!
Ding-dong ding-dong, now it's mine
We'll be in our youth forever
Take it easy with a smile on your face
I'm going to tickle you, get ready
No, I don't want to go home yet
I still want to play some more
Yes, I never want to leave you
I want to stop time
Still middle schoolers in ten years
That sounds good to me, don't you think?
Do you think we'll ever miss the taste of school cafeteria food?
Ding-dong ding-dong, YuruYuri
Ding-dong ding-dong, one, two, tres, cuatro
Ding-dong ding-dong, let's skip ahead to nine, ten
Ding-dong, ding-dong, there, there, there, there!
Ding-dong ding-dong, keep it going, keep it going!
Ding-dong ding-dong, huh?
Ding-dong ding-dong, something's wrong!
Ding-dong ding-dong, Yui!
Ding-dong ding-dong, oh no! Time won't stop rewinding!
It's about time for the bell to ring
School bell, don't send us home yet
We'll all sing together to block it out
I don't understand, there's nothing special here
Yet it's all so fun
Yes, somehow I'm so happy being here
There's no reason for it
We're still in our growth spurt
And our hearts are growing big as well
I want to listen to the sound of the school bell together forever
Ding-dong ding-dong, YuruYuri
Ding-dong ding-dong, that's it
See you again!
Tea
Ceremony
Club
Hey.
So there's one thing I've been wondering about.
Special
Where did you get all those photos of me yesterday?
Oh, that's...
Special
Someone volunteered to help
as soon as we explained the situation.
Special
Huh?
Who could that be?
Akari
That's great.
It looks like the surprise party was a success.
All I care about is seeing Akari happy.
Oh, Akari!
Akari
Thank you for being born!
Hallelujah!
Akari
Special
Well, let's just say it's poor form
to ask about the details of the surprise.
That's true.
Now then...
Let's do something fun!