Merry mayhem, merry mayhem
Merry mayhem, YuruYuri
YuruYuri
Time passes in the blink of an eye
But our youth is still far from over
Let's do spring, summer, fall, and winter again one more time
One more time
Things that make your heart miss a beat
And stupid everyday happenings are all exciting
I hope these days will never end
You listening, God?
However many decades pass, let's spend another year like this
Together again
Together
With you
Without fail
With you here
We'll always end up creating
Merry mayhem
Tomorrow, and the day after
Forever
And ever
Whatever happens, we'll have happy days
Next week, and the week after
Forever
And ever
Next year, and the year after too
We'll walk together, hand in hand
Because I
Love you
Merry mayhem, merry mayhem
Merry mayhem, YuruYuri