If we're late, then let's just walk
If we're sleepy, then let's just sleep
If we're hungry, then let's just go home
Let's make some excuses
After we cut our bangs, let's go play
If that doesn't suit us, then let's get depressed
If we have the same hairstyle, we can laugh
Isn't that kind of life just great?
I want some movie-like miracles to happen
I can't use magic like they do, though
But if we fix our bed hair, the world will change
Tomorrow too, you'll have to smile! It's a promise, so see you then!
Just by being together
We get to see more of the blue sky
When it's clear and then gets cloudy
When it starts pouring suddenly
If we don't panic and hold hands, it'll all be okay!
Let's follow the rainbow and walk!
I pray that this small happiness
Continues forever and ever
It's not really anything important, but let's chat
Until we hear the school bell chime...