I love Yui!
If I did something like that,
would it make you happy?
Nope. That's gross.
What should I scream then?
You don't have to scream at all.
At least say something!
Oh right! There's been
something on my mind recently...
I sorta want to try taking a bath with my clothes on!
I see. Seems kinda erotic.
A bit, yeah.
Huh?
What about you, Yui?
Anything you wanna do?
I want to eat some beef hot pot.
And your clothes?
They'll be staying on!
Ow!
The noodles would make the broth splash, after all.
You're concerned about that?
Oh, Yui, are you sleepy?
I'm still good.
I wonder if the girls having a sleepover
at Ai's place are still awake.
Oh, it's two. They should still...
Knowing Ai, she wouldn't be able
to keep her eyes open, the cutie!
It'd be fun to make her stay awake till she cried!
Let me sleep already!
Just let her!
Or until she starts flailing around!
Let me sleep already!
Please, just let her...
How about we message her?
Sure! Let's take a picture!
Chiho, your phone.
Thanks.
Oh, it's from Nonohara!
Oh, so they're still awake.
No license.
What on earth are they doing so late at night?
Where would she even get a license to ride you?
Huh?
At a driving school, I guess?
Does it take long to get?
Not if you work hard!
What about the costs?
It's free!
I'll work my socks off, then!
We're starting to sparkle
And our glittering silhouettes
Make the world go round and round
The sun shines through the trees arching over the streets
The sky above us seemed so vast
As the gust of a midsummer's breeze
Circled around us only to disappear in the distance
As if trying to balance our different paces
The seasons change the scenery around us
The fragments of our memories are as yet unseen
But each and every one of them is a gift to the current us
Special
!
They're the very things that keep us moving forward
As we start to sparkle
Giving birth to countless glittering days
Special Episode
Messing with People, and Being Messed With
So yesterday they were talking about habits on TV,
and apparently I often put
my hands in front of me like this!
Oh, you do, you really do.
Really?!
Like, when you're explaining something,
you sorta punctuate your words with it.
What?! But...
Oh, no, I'm doing it again!
Morning!
Oh no what?
Hi.
You know, apparently when I'm explaining things,
my hands end up like this when I realize something!
Oh, they do, they really do!
See?
Yukari! There's a whatsit stuck to your I dunno!
Her habit's not for you to use.
I've been used!
Here.
Oh, many thanks!
Well, looks like I've used morningtime Yukari.
"Morningtime"...?
Would you like to use evening Yukari then, Yui?
"Use"?
I'll do my best!
You don't have to, really!
What? I don't have to do my best?
You don't have to, no.
So it's okay not to do our best?
Oh, sorry, I didn't mean to laugh like that.
I take it back. At least try a little.
I'm starving!
I don't wanna move.
What? All of the bread will sell out, you know.
You should know what I want to eat, Yui.
I'm counting on you!
Really? That's a total pain...
What could she want?
Probably not something sweet, since she's so hungry.
School
Shop
But nothing too rich either,
or it'd make her even more lethargic.
Something deep-fried would definitely be bad.
Maybe something with a filling that's also light?
Or maybe three smaller things?
Should I throw in some rice balls?
Genius.
Cod Roe
Mini Pizza
Mixed
Sandwiches
Toyoto
Milk
Y-You're a genius.
They'll sing your praises as far north as Aomori!
That's it?!
Cod Roe
Toyoto
Milk
At least make it a bit further north.
But look, the Tsugaru Strait's in the way.
Bread
Bread would get stuck in it.
Cod Roe
Toyoto
Milk
What are you talking about?
Ah, because it's like this?
Like what?
Ah, Fall...
A bug!
I caught it!
You got it?
Is the bug caught?
It was a worthy opponent. Here I go.
Okay.
Ta-da!
Ta-da-dam!
Ta-da-da-dam! Da-da-dam!
Ta-da-da! Bmm tss tss! Tss tss bmm!
Open it already!
Were you lying? Did you not catch it after all?
I'm not lying.
It's here.
If it's not in here, I'll do it.
I'll make cat sounds!
What the heck?
Okay, here I go.
Meow.
So it's not there?!
Meow!
What happened to the bug?
It went somewhere.
Oh, found it.
It's dead.
Ah, now I feel like I wasted a cat credit.
A cat credit?
Squeak, squeak...
Ah, it's a mouse!
It's a mouse of cancelation!
I don't get it!
I don't get these rules at all!
To be honest, I just played along
even though I didn't get it.
Was I on the right track?
Yeah, you were!
You two really are made for each other, huh?
We understand each other completely!
We do!
You two are hopeless.
So what are your favorite animals?
Cats!
Dogs!
You don't match at all!
But I like Yui too, for example.
So we match! We do match!
You two really are hopeless.
Hup!
You know, I just had this really
powerful urge to snag your leg!
But I somehow stopped it
with nothing but my willpower!
I see... Thanks for that.
Oh no! I couldn't stop myself!
Right...
I see.
That was kinda cute.
I guess.
Yukari, fight it! Hold it back!
Sheesh...
She can't stop! It's so adorable!
Well, we're done.
Daily dose of messing with Yui fulfilled.
We're done.
"Daily dose"?
All that's left is messing with Ai, right?
Now hold your horses!
But it's only 30% messing with Ai,
and 70% messing with you!
I'm fine if you focus all 100% on me...
I would be fine with 30%, though...
Huh? Something wrong?
Ah, I just overheard a conversation...
It's kinda fun to mess with people,
and get messed with, don't you think?
Can we mess with you, then?
Sure, go ahead.
Not that I would.
So can we mess with you 100% of the time?
Well, that'd just be annoying.
Look, we're just a "Mess With Yui" brigade.
Totally!
What's that?
My fan club?
It is!
So you're my fans...
Keep doing what you do!
Yeah, thanks.
But if that's the case, what kind of fans
mess with who they're fans of?
We're really sorry! It's because we love you!
We love you!
Is this meant to be some kind of tough love?!
Data Processing Club
The psychology behind wanting
to "mess with" people...
Teasing that remains good-natured
is a friendly way to assert oneself.
Exactly.
Let's see...
Totally.
Hey Yui, take a look at this!
Yeah!
Hey Yui-chan, do this thing!
Do it!
That's plenty assertive!
Oh, it says that some apply the technique
of being kind after teasing someone.
Is everything all right, Yui?
You aren't cold, are you?
Right on cue!
Yui, do you want me to breathe on your hands?
Do you want me to warm
your cold hands with my breath?
No thanks!
Who goes there?!
Are you an enemy?! Or do you like bread?!
Why those two options?!
Data Processing Club
You must be someone big-chested!
I guess this is a bad time...
Ah, you must be finding it awkward to enter!
Excuse me...
Sorry about that.
All righty, you get to use Yui's chair!
Oh, okay...
So how is it? How does it feel to sit in Yui's chair?
Are you an idiot?!
Pro cess ing
How is everyone doing?
Mom!
Great!
My, it's unusual for you to have guests here.
To be honest, it isn't her first time here.
Right!
Really?
Come here anytime you want, Aikawa.
O-Okay.
Wow, she's like an actual mother.
When I have time, I often come here.
Oh, I see.
Are they gonna talk about getting sore shoulders?
What?
The lady wishes to know if they're darn well
gonna talk about getting sore shoulders!
Are they darn well gonna?
No, they darn well aren't!
Hey, Ai, how about you call our teacher Mom too?
Please, just once! Just this once, for me!
Are you some kind of desperate boyfriend?!
M-Mom?
Yeah, that's great. Now look at her.
What's with you?
For the love of... Seriously? Like, seriously?
Data Processing Club
Well then, I'm heading back.
Okay.
See you later!
Bye.
Is it Okano?
Yeah, Fumio says that she's
finished with her club activities.
How did you three become such good friends?
Ah, well...
In the classroom, the first person to
start a conversation with me was Oka...
Before I'd realized it, I was getting
along great with Fumio and Oka,
and that's how we ended up together.
Really?
I'm not very good at starting conversations myself,
so I was really happy.
That's great.
Data Processing Club
I wonder why they decided to approach Ai.
Maybe because she was cute?
What?!
Data Processing Club
Yo.
Sup.
Heya.
We were just talking about how you three met.
Oh, really?
Why were you the first one to talk to Ai?
Hm?
Because she was cute.
The cutest.
Oh, I see.
Yup.
What about you, Hasegawa?
How did you become friends with Okano?
Because I felt bad for her?
What?!
Yuyushiki!
September!
It's October now, you know.
I know. I just like how September sounds.
December!
So you like the "ember" part?
Oh, it's an ear cleaner!
Oh, yeah.
Okay, this is perfect.
Yui, come here.
I don't want to. Not happening.
But why? Let's have an ear cleaning party!
Let's do it!
What is that? What does it even involve?
Um, ear cleaning and...
Exchanging presents?
I see.
It's still about ear cleaning, at the end of the day.
That doesn't sound too exciting.
What?! It should!
It's fun!
Fun? How?
How about a curry party, then?
You jump from ears to curry?!
I'd prefer that, though.
Should we have a curry party next time?
Good idea!
Though can we include a bit
of ear cleaning, at least?
Is this an obsession for you or what?
Maybe we could have a cake party too!
Good idea!
But still, please!
Your obsession's starting to get creepy.
So we can't...
You fell for it.
That hurts.
Yui is so easy to trick!
It works every single time!
Look at this girl. Every single time!
Aw, she just can't stop!
Oh, come on, Yui, you're too easy to trick!
Are you gonna be okay?
Won't you go extinct, Yui?
What are you talking about?
There's only one representative of
the Yui species, as there should be.
Ah, I see!
Oh, that's sorta...
Amazing! There's only one of you in this world!
It's the same for everyone.
That's scary!
It'll all be over if you keep falling for stuff like this!
I guess.
You can't let yourself get tricked anymore, Yui!
You're the sole member of your species!
Okay.
There's no hope for her anymore! No hope at all!
Come on, Yui...
Man, we really need to take you into protection.
Protection?
I wouldn't fall for this if just anyone did it, you know.
Really?
Only by mine and Yukari's?
W-Well, I guess.
Oh, what should we do with her?
There's really nothing we can do.
I know, I'm sorry.
So, now that Yui's learned her lesson,
shall we go somewhere?
Yui!
It's quite chilly, isn't it?
It is! I wonder why.
Why, you ask?
Well, we went outside, but where do we go now?
I want to go to school.
What?
Oh no! I wasn't sure of where to go,
so my mature side ended up showing!
Your mature side?
It shows quite often.
You're rather mature, you know.
Like I'd say that.
Too much maturity to contain, huh?
I'm sorry.
Well, she actually is pretty mature.
She's good at studying, a flexible thinker...
Yukari isn't shy or timid around people either...
They seem almost like adults.
It's already October of our second year...
So, where do we go again?
Yui's place?
We're home!
Welcome back.
I wasn't expecting it to be that cold.
Right? The bookshop was so warm, too!
Okay, Yui. Read the book you bought aloud.
I don't want to.
Read the love scene at the start!
Read it!
There aren't any love scenes!
There aren't?
I thought you'd pick a book
that would flabbergast us!
Flabbergast you?
Well, this is you we're talking about, after all.
What exactly do you think of me?
Oh right! Yukari's birthday is next month!
That's right.
What do we do for her birthday next year?
Celebrate this year's first!
Though the devil's in the details
when you plan too far ahead.
Right.
Devil. Party crasher.
I don't think birthday parties are his cup of tea.
Who knows what the devil's
cup of tea is anyway?
This is the devil we're talking about.
What do you think he'd drink?
Uh, what?
Blood?
Like, human blood?
Ew, creepy!
Think he eats humans with salt?
So he prefers them salted?!
Lemon juice?
To barbeque them with?
All this effort to make humans tasty is scaring me.
So? What were we talking about again?
About what we'll do for Yukari's birthday.
By the time we celebrate it next year,
we'll already be in our third year.
Yeah.
This year and next year,
let's do a whole lot of things!
Yeah, let's do everything!
Everything?
Let's do everything, and let's remember everything!
Yeah!
That's impossible.
I definitely want to go on a trip with you two!
I do too!
Oh, can we shake you off during the trip?
Don't!
Seriously don't! I mean it!
I'd like to enjoy the trip, you know!
Well, I'd enjoy it!
Same.
I bet.
I always thought what you enjoyed
was watching us have fun.
What am I, your father?
I thought that was your only true source of joy.
A father with nothing else to live for?
Oh! I want to take a bath!
I wanna jump in the bath and go "Sh'pon"!
For what purpose?
W-Well, it's hard to explain...
I'm sorry, it's just...
I feel this in my heart, not my mind!
The "Sh'pon" in my heart.
I want to say "Sh'pon" too.
See?
Let's say it today during our baths.
You'll make your families worry about you.
You think?
I think "I want to die" would worry them more.
That's true, but...
What about "I don't want to die!"?
Holy cow! That's super worrying!
Yeah.
A bit too worrying, in fact.
It's not even funny.
Neither is "Sh'pon".
If someone in my family said
"I don't want to die" during a bath,
what would I do?
I wonder...
I'd be too choked up to even
swallow gelatin noodles!
But they're really easy to swallow!
Did you put too much vinegar on them?
That could be why.
Then use brown sugar syrup instead.
Well, I'm going home.
Don't cry, Yui!
Don't be stupid!
It's already gotten pretty dark.
Be careful.
We'll be fine.
Okay! Let's take a bath when we get home!
Oh? What do we say in the bath again?
"Peace to the world!", was it?
First the bath, now the world?!
No, it's how you translate it.
Just what language is "Sh'pon" supposed to be in?
See you, Yui!
Bye.
Don't forget to say "Sh'pon"!
I'm not saying it!
Oh, there is one.
It's a sort-of love scene.
Not that it matters.
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
There was a love scene.
Yui
Inbox
Okay, time for a bath!
I guess I'll take a bath.
Sh'pon!
Sh'pon...
If we're late, then let's just walk
If we're sleepy, then let's just sleep
If we're hungry, then let's just go home
Let's make some excuses
After we cut our bangs, let's go play
If that doesn't suit us, then let's get depressed
If we have the same hairstyle, we can laugh
Isn't that kind of life just great?
I want some movie-like miracles to happen
I can't use magic like they do, though
But if we fix our bed hair, the world will change
Tomorrow too, you'll have to smile! It's a promise, so see you then!
Just by being together
We get to see more of the blue sky
When it's clear and then gets cloudy
When it starts pouring suddenly
If we don't panic and hold hands, it'll all be okay!
Let's follow the rainbow and walk!
I pray that this small happiness
Continues forever and ever
It's not really anything important, but let's chat
Until we hear the school bell chime...