A Friday's
"good morning"
All right!
Oh, good morning, Sena.
Morning, Akari.
8:07.
The usual Platform 2.
Second car.
And you know, I made lunch
today too, but in the end...
I wonder if he'll be here today?
He is!
Always at this hour, always in this train...
Always here.
Though I see him every morning,
I've never heard his voice.
He's wearing the same uniform...
Would it be weird if I went and said hello?
Day:
Fri
It's Friday... I won't be able to see him for two days.
I wanna say something.
Morning!
'Sup!
Good day.
Good morning!
Morning...
If only I just had a simple chance...
I'm thinking about giving it a shot today.
Oh, right, I found the place
that does amazing cakes!
I'll say "good morning".
...but I dunno. It was with cheese, you know.
Oh, but then...
Wait! At this rate I'll miss another chance!
It sure started pouring suddenly, huh?
Yeah.
What happened?
Akari, could you do me a favor?
Um...
Use this umbrella if you'd like.
Thank you.
Sorry about that. And thanks.
It's fine.
I got to hear his voice!
And I dozed off while watching TV yesterday!
Good morning.
Morning!