I'm... going to die?
The Oracle cells have acclimated
to your body and will continue to spread,
eventually consuming you.
If you continue to use your God Arc,
I have no doubt that your
compatibility rate will accelerate.
What if I stopped using my God Arc?
Then I'd give you another
three years to live at most.
I'm sorry, but you can't
stave off the inevitable.
My advice is to retire as a God Eater
to give yourself more time.
Though, even if you do,
we'll have to continue regulating your Bias Factor.
My Bias Factor?
Like any Aragami, the Oracle cells
in your body have a bias inclination.
If left unchecked,
they'll run rampant, and you will die.
Since you've become a God Eater,
you can no longer leave Fenrir.
If you still want to fight
knowing this, however...
I will restore your God Arc.
It's your call.
Who else knows about this?
Only Licca and myself.
I want you to think about it.
This is a huge step forward for mankind.
There's no sign of rejection at all.
His compatibility rate is stunning.
A hybrid of man and Aragami...
By analyzing this child's compatibility...
we'll be able to engineer humans
that can stand up to the Aragami.
A God Eater, you might say...
Look at this reaction!
Wh-What a monster...
Damn it...
There's a rat in the bedroom.
Send for a cat.
The giant protrusions around the world,
which were causing damage on a global scale,
have stopped as mysteriously as they began.
The U.N. is directing all available resources
towards rescue and reconstruction.
However, the unknown lifeforms
that have appeared since,
dubbed "the menace of the gods" or "Aragami",
have proven impervious to every weapon
used against them, and casualties are—
If we had reported this sooner...
Johannes...
You're right. Maybe we could have
reduced the number of casualties.
Paylor!
Don't you think it's strange?
Amidst the darkness,
only those marks emit light.
That light...
You don't think the higher-ups
used that technology...
Let's call it the Bias Factor.
Those protrusions sure are picky eaters.
Does that mean Fenrir
anticipated this happening?
It makes you wonder.
Paylor...
Do you think the Bias Factor
can be weaponized?
It's hard to say for sure
without running more tests.
Johannes?
Drastic times call for drastic measures.
We're resuming our research.
Humanity will need weapons
to fight the Aragami.
You are all here today
for the installation of the guiding device
that is the keystone of Operation Meteorite.
The work will be done by a special
tech team, but there will be risks.
Your mission is to protect them.
There are five devices,
so you will be divided into five units.
Those who will lead
the units are as follows:
Tachibana Sakuya.
Oomori Tatsumi.
Brendan Bardell.
Gina Dickinson.
Utsugi Lenka.
Lenka... is in charge?
Wow!
I'm a unit leader?
But I don't have a God Arc...
I won't stop you if you choose to drop out.
This is a critical mission for Aegis.
Is it too difficult for you?
Aegis...
No. My apologies.
I gladly accept.
Good. With that...
Soma, you'll be in Utsugi's unit.
Roger.
Soma... sir.
I'm honored.
Forget the formalities.
I feel sorry for you.
Watch your back around the Grim Reaper.
"Grim Reaper"?
Have you made your decision yet?
No, not yet...
I... just wanted to help...
If nothing else, it can serve as a shield.
That's fine.
As I explained earlier, using your God Arc
will affect your life expectancy.
If you can't accept that, resign now.
If you're teamed up with Soma,
you might not need to use it.
About Soma...
People keep calling him the "Grim Reaper".
"Grim Reaper"?
Fate is cruel.
It would be fair to say
that both of you are victims of it.
If you want to know more,
look him up in the database.
You can decide what
to think of him after that.
Soma...
Schicksal...
All right!
It was working on them before!
Retreat! Pull back!
The reports say it stopped working again.
No doubt the Aragami's
bias inclination has changed.
So the Aragami are evolving...
I told them it was too soon
for practical application!
But we have proven that it works.
We've already saved so many.
But I'm worried about claiming
that it'll solve all our problems.
Three more Eastern European nations
have agreed to use Fenrir's technology.
This makes over 50 nations
to sign contracts with Fenrir.
There's a limit to what
existing weaponry can do.
If we perfect the
Bias Factor in our weapons...
That Bias Factor will degrade the moment
it's extracted from the Oracle cells.
Take a look at this.
This is...
Did you design this?
Yes.
It's the only way a refined
Bias Factor will work in weapons.
But this isn't a conventional weapon...
It's a living weapon.
A morbid yet brilliant idea.
We can cultivate Oracle cells ourselves
to create artificial Aragami.
However, there's one problem.
If it's made up of Oracle cells,
it'll devour anything it touches.
Can't it be controlled remotely?
It's a living being and as such,
would be hard to control.
Analyzing it would be a long process.
There is one possibility...
We could inject the Bias Factor into
a human and let their body adapt to it.
That's...
Indeed, that would be
the most effective method.
But to do something so hellish...
We'd need an incredible amount
of volunteers to test it.
Administering it via the womb could
make adaptation far safer than a direct dosage.
Maybe so, but who would
possibly agree to it?!
I will.
What?
Or should I say that we will.
I hear you're going on the mission
with the New-Type.
It's an important device, so don't break it.
Hey.
Rindou.
Quit staring off into space.
I've been looking for you.
I just wanted a change of scenery.
I haven't seen you around either.
Where have you been?
Huh?
Oh, you know, I was on a date.
Nothing special.
A ladies' man, huh?
You and Soma have a mission?
If left to his own devices,
he'd go out there to die.
Keep your eyes on him.
That's all I wanted to say.
His mother, Aisha Gauche, died at Soma Schicksal's birth.
So we need to place these stakes
around the guiding device?
Yes.
Once activated,
a mock defense wall will be formed.
And until the operation starts,
the devices will be safe from the Aragami.
This technology is still being refined, however.
We won't know how durable it is until it's tested.
Come in.
Major Amamiya, the new recruits
will begin training at 1200 hours.
Understood. I'll be there shortly.
That's it for explanations.
The guiding devices are vital.
You know what to do, Utsugi.
Um... Major Amamiya.
Why did you step down as a God Eater?
Have you ever seen an Aragami being born?
No.
If you did, you'd think the same...
That Aragami cannot be exterminated.
No way!
However...
I have faith that some day this will all end.
So I chose to nurture the next generation
and entrust the future to them.
The future...
You'll understand in time.
I'm told the guiding devices are invaluable.
If we fail, the completion of Aegis will be delayed.
Let's work together to make this a success.
Any questions?
Not really, but...
I'm a little nervous.
People who go out with Soma...
don't come back.
It's just a rumor, but—
Hey.
If you don't want to die,
then stay away from me.
You too.
If worse comes to worst,
forget the device and run.
The guiding devices have been set up.
Good work.
Soma, sir!
Incredible...
Don't just stand there.
Get on with it.
R-Right.
All right.
Objective complete. Let's head back.
Wait.
What is that?
An Aragami?!
Have you ever seen an Aragami being born?
They came right out of the ground...
Aragami cannot be exterminated.
Look.
It's working!
The wall!
This is bad! What do we do?
Damn it!
Soma, sir!
Come at me.
Is he going to protect the guiding device?!
Bring the copter down!
What are you doing?!
Retrieving the guiding device!
You've gotta be kidding!
It's over for us if the wall is destroyed
while we try to salvage the device!
Are you even able to
protect us with your God Arc?
That's...
You guys stay on board.
You'll only be in the way.
Leave the device!
You can't take all of them on!
Soma, sir!
A monster.
All of his partners die...
A Grim Reaper.
An unholy child who killed
his mother to be born.
If anyone dies, it'll be me.
Don't tell me...
you're pregnant?!
A-Are you serious?
Congratulations, Johannes!
Oh, but...
Considering the situation...
Paylor's idea is the best possible choice.
As a fellow researcher,
I would be the ideal candidate.
But if this should fail...
You... and our baby...
There's got to be another way!
Let's keep thinking!
I agree with him.
Besides, we don't have to decide now.
There's no time left for mankind...
Don't worry about me, Johannes, Paylor.
I want...
to give hope to my baby
and to the future humanity.
No way.
Position the copter above the device!
Utsugi?
What are you doing?! Disconnect the device!
Soma, attack like you did
before and kill them all!
There's no time to reposition...
Shoot!
You didn't kill your mother to be born!
You...
You were entrusted with hope.
Hope that your mother passed on to you.
I don't see the Grim Reaper in you, so shoot!
Soma!
Damn it!
Damn!
I told you.
You're not a Grim Reaper.
Utsugi...
Hey! Utsugi!
You're awake.
What happened to the device?
It's fine.
You looked me up in the database, didn't you?
You think you know what kind of person I am?
Maybe not, but I think I understand a little now.
Because I have people who make life worth living.
Why'd you accept the mission in your condition?
In order to complete Aegis.
What good is completing something like that?
You can't destroy Aragami
unless you destroy their cores.
And even if you destroy their cores,
the scattered Oracle cells will amass again
and give birth to more Aragami.
It's a cycle of despair.
Then pass it on to someone.
The same way your mother did.
You can't die until you connect
your life to someone else's.
I didn't die,
so you don't get to die either.
Soma?
Like the Indian legend?
Yes. Do you not like it?
A nectar of the gods that bestows
the force of life to mankind...
I believe that it's something humanity needs now.
You're right...
It's a fine name.
I'm glad.
We can't wait to see you, Soma.
A dam?
Yes... It was surrounded by a forest
and there were people...
Amamiya Rindou seems to have
some association with these people.
Yes.
Everyone seemed quite close.
You didn't heed my warning.
I'm sorry.
And you understand what that means?
Yes.
I see. Then you'll retire—
Please fix it.
Please fix my God Arc.
What did you say?
One more thing.
Please don't tell anyone about my condition.
You certainly are fascinating, boy.
Very well then. I'll restore your God Arc.
But let me ask you one thing.
Why?
Is this the thing that's calling out to them?
This is the Aragami that devoured
your mother and father.
Mother... Father...
But don't worry. You can fight now.
Tell me what I taught you.
You can pull the trigger.
You... taught me...
One...
Two...
Three...
Good job.
This is your enemy.
An Aragami.
Doctor...
Are you saying that... this is a God Arc?!
I designed this with his compatibility rate in mind.
Aisha...
The hope for the future which you entrusted...
I won't let anyone get in the way of it.
Lemme rest a bit.
Rindou!
What's going on?
I will destroy...
Get out there, Utsugi!
I'm entrusting this God Arc to you!
My family...
Only darkness.
Can humanity rise to become gods?
We'll turn this around!