Hamazura's taking too long.
Doing what?
Oh, I had him take out some garbage.
And buy me a salmon lunch on the way back.
Hamazura, you slowpoke.
So this is where you were hanging out.
Dark Matter, you bastard.
I'd prefer you'd use my real name.
It's Kakine Teitoku, you know.
So, I've come to proclaim my victory.
I don't know who you were,
but I'm sorry you only have me to see you off.
In this town, if you don't
have power, you're just trash.
No one will come to your aid.
Wonder how long I'll last.
Incoming Call
Kinuhata Saiai
ACCEPT
Incoming Call
Kinuhata?
Kinuhata Saiai
ACCEPT
Incoming Call
Kinuhata Saiai
ACCEPT
Incoming Call
I just now finished up.
Hamazura!
Go get the car super-quick!
We're under attack from SCHOOL.
One of their targets is Takitsubo.
They probably learned about her
AIM Stalker and came to deal with it.
If we can protect her, we can turn things around.
You have to take her—
Kinuhata?
I'm super okay.
I can fight too.
No. You just stay put.
There!
Huh? What's up in here?
Oh, impressive.
I guess Sunazara and his
magnetic sniper rifle bit the dust.
I'm going to stop you!
Your Level 4 Offense Armor can't beat me.
This is far beyond the kind of difference
you could find a clever way around.
A Certain Magical Index
The Level Fives
If I go there, I'm dead.
If I run, I'll get sent to the incinerator.
Damn it!
Kinuhata!
Huh?
Let go of her!
And who are you?
You can't seriously think
that toy would work on me.
Oh, I see, you're sacrificing yourself.
Your boss, Mugino, ran away a while back.
That bitch!
Don't!
Run away, Hamazura.
I'm Level 4. You're Level 0, I'll protect you.
Takitsubo...
What's that?
Shit!
Do you want to interfere with my
AIM Diffusion Field and take over my ability?!
Hurry, Hamazura.
I didn't ask for any help.
Oh, you. Long time no see.
You're that bitch!
Oh, I see.
Yeah, she used a Body Crystal.
What's a Body Crystal?
It's a chemical that causes a rejection reaction
and makes the esper's ability run wild.
In most cases, they're too
dangerous to be worth using.
Even if you can produce good outcomes,
if you keep using them...
Takitsubo!
She can only use her power one or two
more times before breaking down.
We don't even need to bother killing her.
Measure Heart.
I shortened the psychological
distance between the two of us.
Right now, I'd say we're like friends.
You wouldn't shoot a friend, would you?
Some kind of telepathy?
Damn it!
Takitsubo!
ACCEPT
Incoming Call
Mugino Shizuri
ACCEPT
Incoming Call
Mugino Shizuri
ACCEPT
Incoming Call
Mugino Shizuri
ACCEPT
Incoming Call
Mugino Shizuri
ACCEPT
Incoming Call
Mugino Shizuri
Mugino?
Hamazura! Is Takitsubo with you?
You bitch!
You ran away and left the others!
Stop screaming over small stuff.
We're going on counterattack.
I'll have Takitsubo use her power to track SCHOOL.
That's reckless!
They're gonna kill us all!
And Takitsubo isn't well!
Oh, so she's still alive. That's good.
Because even being dead is no excuse.
Now, let's deal with you.
Run, Hamazura.
I don't want you to die.
So did you help the people who were asking for it?
The reason people have been
making fun of you isn't about power.
You should take care of such
stupid illusions yourself, you shithead!
Yeah, I get it!
You're right!
Damn it!
Hamazura, do you know what my job is?
I'll give you all the explanations you need later!
Just get this girl somewhere safe now.
She's on the brink of a breakdown
because of these Body Crystal things.
Body Crystals?!
Hamazura! Did you just say Body Crystals?!
Yes, so just—
Hamazura!
You made me go looking for you.
And I had to haul this thing around.
I don't need to purge you too now, do I?
Hey! What's going—
Just go!
Wha—
I can't leave you here! You're just a kid!
Just go already!
Please!
I have to protect her.
I've been mulling it over for a while now,
and I finally figured out that's what I want to do!
So, please go!
I can't protect her on my own.
If you don't help me with this, I'll lose everything!
That gave me goosebumps, Hamazura.
How did you get that?!
You can't make Takitsubo
use her ability without it, can you?
Serves you right, bitch!
Hamazura.
You're so dead.
Such a nice spot.
How kind of you to go into an unmanned facility.
It's best to die alone.
Right, Hamazura?!
Hamazura.
Why don't you stop being a pain
and hand over the Body Crystals?
I won't be satisfied until I slaughter
everyone from SCHOOL.
Body Crystals, please.
No!
I won't let you feed Takitsubo
any more of this stuff!
She's reached her limit!
So what?
If she breaks down,
I'll just get someone else in her place.
Well, she's the only one who can
track down AIM Diffusion Fields.
But right now all I care about is finding
those shitheads from SCHOOL.
I'm sorry, but I'm out.
You can't beat that Kakine bastard.
You ran from him twice already.
Oh, look, you have a screw loose here.
Shall I tighten it back up?
Takitsubo. Even though I'm a selfish prick,
she said she didn't want me to die.
Such a person deserves to be happy!
A Level 0's ear for a Level 5's eye.
That was a good deal.
Hamazura!
It doesn't matter!
Even if you tore off my arms
and legs and crushed my insides,
I'd still be stronger than you!
I can kill a Level 0 like you a hundred
times over without lifting a finger!
I'm not a complete idiot.
Level 5's not that big a deal, is it?
Man, I really got off easy.
Hama...zura...
Hamazura!
It's Hamazura.
I don't need that Anti-Skill backup anymore.
A Certain Magical Index
Yes, it's all over.
Any progress on the analysis of
the data from using the Tweezers?
Yes, it's no good.
This data still isn't enough to allow me
to stand my ground against Aleister.
I need to work on it a bit more.
So you're still going to do it.
I'll kill the esper ranked first in Academy City.
What?
So BLOCK's plan to assassinate
a board member ended in failure.
I'm a lucky man to have such capable underlings.
You sure don't feel like living much longer.
No, I mean it. I'm really grateful to you this time.
And so as a personal reward,
I have some useful info for you.
It's about a threat to the life
of serial number 20,001, Last Order.
By the way, what happened with the lost child?
Did your frizz stop clicking?
"Misaka has no frizz,"
says Misaka as Misaka answers dejectedly.
"Definitely sensed him moving
about in this area a minute ago,"
says Misaka as Misaka tries to show
her frustration toward her wasted efforts.
"M-Misaka wants one of those!"
Says Misaka as Misaka, who is without her purse,
tries looking sparkly-eyed at Uiharu.
Here.
But come back here afterward.
All right, in the meanwhile,
I'll turn my attention here.
Excuse me, young lady.
I'm looking for someone.
I haven't seen her.
You should probably report a missing
person at an Anti-Skill post.
Maybe you're right. Thank you.
Oh, and young lady,
I forgot to mention something.
I know you were walking around
with Last Order, stupid.
Where is she?
Tell me and I'll let you off.
...never find her.
What?
Didn't you hear me?
She's somewhere you'll never find her.
Fine then.
Say goodbye to the world then.
Oh, you showed up earlier than I expected.
For crying out loud, stop making a fuss
with your stupid games, you small fry!
You think you're a fairy tale princess or something?
Don't worry, I know how they look.
Let's add a little more fun to this party.
I'll teach you how a proper villain should act.
So, you know, this world is entirely
made up of elementary particles.
But that doesn't apply to my Dark Matter.
It's made up of a material
that doesn't exist in this world.
It's not a matter of it being undiscovered,
or existing in theory. It actually doesn't exist.
Nonexistent material is governed
by nonexistent natural laws.
For example, it can change
sunlight into a deadly beam.
Finished reverse-engineering.
Accelerator,
I've heard that you reflect everything,
but that's not completely correct.
Unconsciously, you compose filters
of harmful and harmless things.
Then you reflect just what you don't want near you.
I put 25,000 vectors into that sun beam
and into the wind gale just now,
and I observed how you reflected them,
so I can attack from the directions from
which you unconsciously let vectors in.
That's what Dark Matter is about.
A space filled with foreign material.
It's unknown territory for you!
I'll claim the right to meet with Aleister in person!
That's what I got these Tweezers for,
but I guess it's quicker to just kill you,
the current first rank.
You still care that much about those numbers?
Aleister works on many projects in parallel.
And all of them have a plan B.
I'm plan B for you.
So if you kill me, you'll be on top of that totem pole.
Yes. And then Aleister will
have to take me into account.
You too?
I don't know or care what tragic event broke you,
but the moment you thought it was fine
to kill regular folk for your cause,
your evil became too cheap.
You yourself crushed some regular
folk just now as we were fighting.
Truly the words of a villain with no class.
Do you know why I was assigned
first rank and you second?
Because there is an
insurmountable wall between us.
D-Don't tell me you've been making sure
not to hurt people while fighting me?!
Are you messing with me?!
How can you have so much control?!
Did I make you angry, you small-time punk?
This is what a real villain is like.
This is my world!
You're wrong.
If I redefine this world's elementary
particles to include dark matter,
I just have to find your formula and you're done.
You think you understand my power that well?!
It's not that complicated.
Barely anything to understand.
So long, small fry.
Well, at least you won't have the
sad fate of getting killed by a good guy.
Hold on!
Let me have that handgun.
It's not like you need it, do you?
I'm a villain.
In that case, I'll stop you.
Are you serious?
I don't know how to make a different choice.
I'll never give up on you.
I'll drag you out from the place you're in.
That's why I stand in your way now.
For the children that I should protect.
For the peace I love.
For a world where you, and Last Order,
and everyone else, can live with a smile.
You don't need that gun
in order to achieve that future.
You're not that kind of small time villain, are you?
In the end you're the same as me.
You can't protect anyone.
Am I wrong?
You've let so many people die
just like this, haven't you?
Wow.
Now that's malice.
So you're capable of it after all, villain.
I see now why my Dark Matter
was relegated to plan B.
But that doesn't necessarily mean
ranks will decide this battle!
What did you—
This is what a true villain is like.
Is that what your role to play is?
Put down your guns!
Stopping him is...
"The lost child
is found,"
says Misaka as Misaka tries
her best to firmly address him.
"It's fine," says Misaka as Misaka
tries reaching her hand to him.
Accelerator, you...
Open fire!
Stop.
"You don't have to do such things anymore,"
says Misaka as Misaka
tries to communicate the truth.
"Thank goodness,"
says Misaka as Misaka tries to express her relief.
When I least expect it, you're gone
And loneliness hits me hard in the chest
SCHOOL needed the Tweezers
in order to collect certain nano-devices.
In the night filled with signs I look up at the stars
Nano-devices?
Yes.
Aleister has secretly scattered about
I bite my lip and pray
50 million surveillance nano-devices
in the air of Academy City.
Every time the dawn comes I run to you
They're called UNDER_LINE.
They form the core of Aleister's direct-feed
information network that spans Academy City.
You try to hide behind a smile that you're covered in wounds
You can probably guess how
much data each piece holds.
But I notice, because I'm not a child
Ah, there it is.
Secret code names from the Dark Side.
GROUP, SCHOOL, ITEM, MEMBER, BLOCK.
I'll protect you even if I have to make an enemy of the entire world
The names of the organizations?
We already found those the hard way.
This strength comes from the light you've given me
Wait, there's more.
There's one more at the end:
I don't want to just wait for a miracle
DRAGON.
I want to start a revolution that changes who the two of us are
I'll get ahead of you.
In every respect.
And this is the night before it starts
Next Time
An underground district beneath Academy City.
The transient peace is torn to shreds
in an instant by his appearance.
Next time: "The Third Layer".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.
Collect all the stamps to