How could DA have possibly come
from the same roots as Anti-Skill?
They may have the same roots,
but theirs have gone rotten.
Th-They're... Nakimoto's cleaners?
Where are you headed, Santa?
It's not even December.
That's the huge bag with the girl inside
they mentioned over the radio...
Damn it, I just can't catch a break.
But then again,
this is just what my rehab needed.
Everything reflects the darkness
A Certain Scientific Accelerator
The pitch-black town is coated
In light from countless windows
It shines across the barren streets
I sneer at all the shadows
As I remain constricted
By the chain wrapped around my neck
Everything reflects the darkness
When it's inside of my hand
Shadow is the light
I will bear the burden
Of the hell that's in my past
These bloodstained memories I bear
Though they haunt my mind
Fighting dark with darkness
I will still destroy all of
These shadows cast in days gone by
I'll never change
Everything reflects the darkness
When it's inside of my hand
SCAVENGER
Corpse Eaters
They managed to take out that ridiculous
weapon with just the four of them?
None of them are listed in our esper database!
Why can't we find any info?!
A dark-side group, then?
What a nice bonus.
If we can bring back the girl in the bag,
they'll tack on some extra pay.
Show me what you can do.
All right, here I go!
Let's see...
How good I'm feeling today!
Pretty good!
Hey, Naru!
Watch it, will you? Learn some restraint!
Oh, sorry about that.
I just got a bit excited,
thinking I'd be able to kill another teacher.
And... up we go.
All right then, how should I kill her?
Wouldn't it be fun to pull
her arms out of their sockets?
Don't treat me like a doll!
Or maybe I'll snap her neck
and watch her twitch around?
I said I'm not a dollasdlaksfn.
Take that!
Which would be better?
Why do you hate instructors that much?
Instructors? Oh, you mean teachers?
Yeah.
I mean, aren't you guys the root of all evil?
Yeah, it's just common sense.
Academy City is basically just a huge school.
It's obviously the teachers' fault
if the school isn't being run well.
If we smash up all of the teachers
who neglected this city one by one,
we might find the dean or the principal.
They're definitely the root of all evil,
so if we smash them up too,
then we can make this a bit of a better place.
Don't you think?
You do, don't you?
Yeah, I do.
No!
I'll admit, there are people like DA around.
But we of Anti-Skill have the resolve
and determination to put our necks on the line
to protect the students of Academy City.
Are there really teachers like that?
No way!
Didn't think so.
You little shits!
Brats like you should just sit down
and do as you're told!
Die, you stupid brats!
Oh, one of the DA guys was still alive?
He's a former teacher, then.
He's just shooting at a student
without even trying to talk.
What a scumbag.
Yeah, there's just no helping teachers after all.
Shit! Shit!
Yaku, can you finish him off?
Gotcha.
Get out of the way!
Wh-What?
That's minus 269 degrees.
It's my own special refrigerant!
I-I still haven't enacted my justice...
I make it by manipulating relative densities.
My justice... On this city...
Bye-bye!
How could you?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You're up next, teach.
Take her and run!
I'm counting on you!
There's no way a toy like that
would help you against me!
Don't let her die, Huotou!
Understood.
See you later, teach!
Who the hell are you?
You've been meddling this whole time!
Maybe some goody two-shoes
that showed up to save the teacher?
She doesn't seem like a regular esper.
If you're a goody-goody then you
should know you need to wait your turn!
Just take out the teacher's pet too, Naru.
No, get the teacher first.
Keep it down over there!
I'm the one doing the work!
Get the brown-noser first.
That'll make the teacher
fall into despair before she dies.
You got it!
Huotou!
Yes, Adonai.
Adjusting enemy's estimated
combat strength value substantially.
Removing muscle limiters in order
to execute elimination sequence.
Increasing muscle tearing tolerance to ten percent.
Roughly ten minutes of combat will be possible.
Executing.
Stay still, damn it!
Don't touch my work of art!
This super cool onesie can transform
between attacking and defending modes!
Are those religious charms? No, it's something else.
Her paper is imbued with her psychokinesis,
making it as hard as a tungsten alloy
but as pliable as cloth.
And her ridiculous modeling
and combat skills combined with that
make her one of the best fighters around!
Time to skewer you!
Huotou!
Take this!
She's dead!
Huotou!
I'm running fine, Adonai.
Huotou...
This isn't going to work.
Huotou is just going to get taken out.
I can fortify her muscular strength with magic,
but it wont help if she's in that state.
Body damaged to level four.
Revising possible combat duration.
This teacher's pet works pretty hard.
I have to save Huotou!
Think! What can I do?
All right, here I go again!
Maybe I can use this!
This is it! Giant Stomp!
Pancaked!
She's definitely dead this time.
Naru?
It's all tingly!
Wh-What the heck is that?
It's the armor of the dead!
Is she a psychokinesist like Naru,
using dirt as a medium?
Damn it!
Do you think something like that
can stop an attack from my special onesie?
Killer Punch!
It's all tingly again!
That won't work.
I don't know who you guys are,
but I'm beginning to lose my patience.
Back off!
No way.
Oh dear.
Scrape it away, Naru. It's just dirt.
No matter how hard the earth,
humanity will dig holes.
Oh, I get it!
Time for a new work of art!
This is my tunnel-boring version!
Hey, don't run away!
Damn it! Damn it!
Stop running around!
I got you this time!
The world is spinning...
It looks like she's having a hard time
controlling a unit as complicated as that.
One blow would definitely finish her off,
but the attack is too telegraphed and leaves her vulnerable.
We need some bait that she'll jump at.
Naru, go for the blonde one.
Huh?
Just do it!
Oh no, I can't move right now!
Take this!
Huotou!
She took the bait.
Yay, my first hit! Let's speed things up!
Huotou, get back!
I'm fine. Please get out, Adonai.
Stop, Huotou!
Your safety is my top priority, Adonai.
Man, I really can't stand ass-kissers.
Gonna spin even faster!
Stop already...
Please... Stop...
Not
a
chance!
How? How can you do something like this?
Hmm... Maybe it's for the sake of justice?
This isn't justice!
Oh yeah? Well, your idea of justice
isn't the same as ours.
Not that it matters.
Time to get back to work.
Okay, I'll kill the teacher's pet first,
and then next is the teacher!
And you're last.
You're going to despair before we send you off.
Why?
Why is there only despair in this world?
It's all the teachers' fault, you know.
But don't worry.
We'll kill them all for you!
This is it for you!
A Certain Scientific Accelerator
Wh-Who is that guy?
Naru!
What was that?
God damn it.
Have your art exhibition on your own time.
Or else guys like me might show up!
He's got such a great expression.
There's a look in his eyes that's
a bit murderous and a bit insane,
and his mouth is crooked as if
he's desperately fighting the world.
He gives off the same scent as me.
Hey, you're pretty good!
Do you want to join us on our teacher-hunting trip?
Geez, I really wish our leader would stop doing this.
You still there, Naru?
She gets the slightest bit interested in someone
and can't resist inviting them along.
You're not even hurt that bad, Naru.
So, what do you think? It'll be heaps of fun!
Thanks for saving us.
You're in the way.
Huh?
Piss off and take them with you.
Okay!
Hey, I'm talking to you!
If you join then there'll be exactly five of us.
I'll even let you be the black
Power Ranger if you want!
Pretty good deal, right?
So how about it?
Stop ignoring me!
Tch.
Say something!
Something, huh?
Something.
Huh?
What?
You're the one that told me to say "something"!
I'm gonna squash a bug with another bug!
Leader!
Who is this guy?
He's bad news!
Time for a tactical retreat?
But we'll get demoted!
What do we do, then?
She's right, none of our powers will work!
Man, you guys just don't shut up!
We'll all attack at once.
Huh?
No one's ever managed to escape
from SCAVENGER's unified attack.
We're the undefeated
SCAVENGER!
Hey, let's pick up where we left off.
All right! People can't move if there's no friction.
Naru!
Art is all about explosions!
Okay, done!
Yaku!
Oh, the teacher's pet and blondie are back!
You guys sure took your time.
He's in there, if you're looking for him.
This is a liquid thermite reaction.
The exothermic reaction heats to 4000 degrees.
I don't think there will even be any bones left.
N-No way...
The iron maiden is a fitting end
for someone so sinful.
All right, next is the teacher.
Gotta get that pest of a teacher.
We won't listen even if you beg for your lives!
Can you shut up with this teacher thing already?
I'm the teacher now!
I'll show you guys how to be a real villain!
Y-You're kidding!
Our attack was perfect!
Impossible!
Who is this guy?
Accelerator!
Accelerator?
I've heard of him.
Pale complexion.
White hair.
Red eyes.
W-Wait, this is the rank-one esper?
Level 5s are this strong?
Come on, did you guys already
run out of your little tricks?
What's with those looks?
You're making it hard to get invested.
Lucky you! I've found you a nice bed!
Did you know the human body
uses something called "bioelectricity"?
I'll play around with yours a little, so enjoy it!
Come on, at least try to look like you're having fun.
Well, I guess that's asking a bit much.
This bed doesn't look that comfortable, after all.
How dare you do that to Seike!
Leader, your orders!
We need to take him down!
You fucking bastard!
Naru, wait!
What do we do? What can we do?
Go to hell!
We have to beat the rank-one esper?!
Tch.
This is so boring.
It really is.
Little tricks like that
won't do anything to me.
Naru!
Leader, he took out Seike and Naru!
The strongest esper in Academy City, Accelerator.
He has the power to control vectors.
He can freely control the magnitude and direction
of any and all forces that exist in this world.
Get it together!
We have to do something, even if it's just the two of us!
Leader!
Is she broken?
Too slow.
You're the only one left.
But even a villain like me wouldn't hurt
a little kid that's not even trying to fight back.
So, what'll it be?
Come on. You know, say something!
Who would've thought there would be brats
loitering around here pissing their pants?
Of the 2,300,000 inhabitants of Academy City,
there are only seven Level 5s.
We must have terrible luck
to have run into one of them.
Forget the bonus,
the client is going to cut our pay for sure.
Tch.
Accelerator!
Huh?
Is it over already?
Damn it, you call that a rehab session?
Hiding in my shell
Holding in all the emotions that I feel
Shackling my mind
But the shackles laugh at me, I find
Swallowing the pain
Savoring the awful bitter taste because I know that
Worse flavors lie in my future
Someone, take this cup
I'll keep repressing my feelings
Just run away from the torment
I know that I am to blame for
All your suffering
This mind has lost its sense of
Anger and jealousy
Never again to empathize
As I desperately struggle ahead
Possessed by my fears and doubts
Why can't I just live a decent life?
I'm fed up with my past, yet I can't let go
I can't forgive myself
Don't I still deserve to suffer?
That's the question nagging at my heart
As it rots
Next Time
Time Limit
Download