Above here.
Isaac's core is up there.
We're finally here.
Wh-What's this?
At last, I've attained it.
The Rosenthals' wish for 400 years—
a perfect soul and a perfect body!
This is a being on par with being a god!
The perfect golem!
This power... Don't tell me
Isaac's evolution is complete...
It looks like time is up.
I can't reflect! The fuck is this power?
Everything reflects the darkness
A Certain Scientific Accelerator
The pitch-black town is coated
In light from countless windows
It shines across the barren streets
I sneer at all the shadows
As I remain constricted
By the chain wrapped around my neck
Everything reflects the darkness
When it's inside of my hand
Shadow is the light
I will bear the burden
Of the hell that's in my past
These bloodstained memories I bear
Though they haunt my mind
Fighting dark with darkness
I will still destroy all of
These shadows cast in days gone by
I'll never change
Everything reflects the darkness
When it's inside of my hand
Something to Protect
W-We are going to enact
absolute justice in Academy City!
We are justice!
Justice!
What's this oppressive feeling?
Is this part of that monster's power?
If that flash from earlier is used in an urban area,
the damage will be tremendous.
This is it! This! This!
The more I eat, the greater my power becomes!
I can keep gaining power like this.
I'll become the ultimate being, beyond even a god.
Once that happens,
I can bring true justice to Academy City.
What did I just say?
True justice for the city...
Justice...
True justice...
Justice... Justice... Justice... Justice...
Justice... Justice...
Justice...
The power has vanished.
Doesn't matter,
as long as we can keep moving forward.
I can just barely make it.
There's no wind here.
But if I consider the rotation of the earth beneath us,
the sun's gravitational pull, and all other forces,
and adjust them to what I need...
Good, I can pull this off.
Wh-What the...?
Justice... Justice... Justice...
Wait, what is this?
Gah! There's so much noise coming from inside me!
This is my body!
Guess my battery managed to last long enough.
I knew it...
"What do you mean by that?", questions Misaka.
Master, thank you very much.
Allow me to take it from here.
Adonai, hurry!
Isaac!
Say your prayers!
Stop, Esty! I don't want to die again!
Adonai!
Don't fall for that, you idiot!
How low the Rosenthals have fallen,
if a dunce like you is our head!
That's absolutely right.
Just how big a moron are you?
I thought you were going to be the hero!
That's why you've come all this way!
So don't backpedal!
Like I told you,
if there's something you want to save,
then don't hesitate to reach out
and protect it for all you're worth!
All right, Master.
Tch, I told you, I'm not your master.
Done with your little talk? Then it's about time...
...to enact justice...
Justice...
Justice... Justice...
Huh?
Wh-What is this? What's happening?
Why, you! What the hell did you do?!
Despite having obtained a power
on the same level as a god,
you're still in Hirumi's form.
Which is to say, you're still hooked up
to the coffin containing Hirumi's body...
And so...
"...using the MISAKA Network,
we accessed the coffin and shut down its functions",
Misaka continues explaining.
It may be impossible to kill you,
but at least we managed to buy some time...
Why, you...!
"This is what you get for toying with
the memories of 10,031 Sisters' deaths",
declares Misaka with a smug look.
Why, you!
What a shame. You lose.
A-After coming this far,
I can't afford to be beaten now!
I will fight with you, Adonai.
"Misaka will help, too,"
says Misaka, finding her reason for being here.
S-Stop! Don't do it, damn you!
I still have so much I want to do!
Don't do it!
What a shame. You lose.
Go ahead, hero.
Wh-Who are you? All you've done is
interfere with me! Who the hell are you?!
A villain.
A son-of-a-bitch villain, just like you!
Esty...
Hirumi...
Was I useful to you, in the end?
Welcome back...
and farewell... Hirumi...
Bye-bye, Mikihiko.
Hirumi!
I didn't get to be a hero... mm-mm...
Is it over?
What's that?
A Certain Scientific Accelerator
"Ah, this is—
The vast, uninterpretable power
built up inside Isaac's body
is causing distortions not only in space,
but in the MISAKA Network as well",
explains Misaka.
So what if it is?
"If this energy is released upon Isaac's death,
it will cause an explosive disintegration,
leveling everything for several kilometers.
Furthermore, the shockwave
will devastate Academy City",
Misaka continues to explain.
Oh, no...
I can't disperse it with vector manipulation.
Does this have more of that crap mixed in with it?
Either way,
it has to be done.
If that damn hero isn't around, I'll have to do it!
If nothing else...
...if there's a chance that it might reach her...
...then I can't afford to worry about looking tough.
I'll pour all my remaining juice
into just doing the calculations.
There's no need to keep standing!
Everything... Everything I have...!
Master!
I'll take control of everything!
Master...
Master... Master... Master!
Please wake up, Master! Please, open your eyes!
Master! Master!
Electricity... exhausted.
Reason... unknown.
The damage is extensive.
If we hadn't been down here when it happened,
we might have been in danger as well.
It's like I say, this is the safest place to be.
Yes, sir.
The darkness runs deep in this city.
Not even that light that pierced
the heavens can reach this place.
I wonder how far the first-ranked power can reach.
"Jeez!
Why did you skip today's checkup?!",
asks Misaka as Misaka tries lecturing you!
Buzz off. Once you're done lecturing, go away.
"Misaka will do anything for you,
but not go away because she's annoying you",
says Misaka as Misaka draws a line in the sand.
Okay, then go buy me one of those
whatever-they're-called cans of coffee.
The one they only sell in School District 14.
"Mm-hmm, okay",
says Misaka as Misaka rushes off to buy one,
thrilled at the importance of this mission!
Does he have a child, at his age?
No, that couldn't be.
But she couldn't be his girlfriend...
Well, this seems like a sensitive subject.
Yo.
You're looking well.
Tch, if I really look that way,
you should see an eye doctor.
Oh, don't be like that.
I'm here to apologize for this whole affair.
Huh?
This incident has wiped out DA.
We've caught all of the survivors.
I'm terribly sorry.
But as a result, we were able to excise
a sickness infecting Anti-Skill.
Tch.
Still, what was that thing, anyway?
All the report said was that an experiment
by a researcher named Hishigata Mikihiko
had gotten out of control and ended up like that.
But it was so gruesome,
I have to believe there was more to it than that.
Since you were at the center of it,
you must know something, right?
No, I don't.
Seems like some villains tried to
manipulate each other, and it went badly.
Yeah, but...
There wasn't any other damage done, right?
You guys did everything you could
within your limitations.
Isn't that enough?
Morgue
I'm sorry, Huotou.
I...
There is no need to apologize.
I am a pseudo-soul that obeys your commands.
I'm now going to release the spell.
I will return the body of
Hitokawa Hasami to her family,
and you will return to the charm...
...losing all of the memories
I have gained. Isn't that right?
I knew this was what would happen,
right from that moment.
One should not keep using
necromancy to tamper with death!
I lost a friend, and when I tried to
bring her back to life, lost her again!
We should not tamper with death.
As we fought together, I came to understand...
...that your decision was not wrong.
Huotou...
Your master said something.
If you're going to be a hero, don't hesitate to
stretch out your hand and save what you must save.
If you would, Adonai.
All right.
Um...
My memories will disappear,
but will I remain in yours?
Of course you will. I'll never forget you.
I promise.
Promise?
Yeah. I promise.
Right.
Also, let me tell you something.
This isn't a memory; it's more of a reminiscence.
Hiding in my shell
Holding in all the emotions that I feel
Shackling my mind
But the shackles laugh at me, I find
Swallowing the pain
Master...
Savoring the awful bitter taste because I know that
I'm not your master. Don't make me keep saying it.
Worse flavors lie in my future
Thank you, Master.
Someone, take this cup
I'll keep repressing my feelings
Tch.
Just run away from the torment
I'm not your master, but here's a warning.
I know that I am to blame for
Half-assed folks like yourself
All your suffering
shouldn't get any more involved
with any damn darkness.
This mind has lost its sense of
Anger and jealousy
Never again to empathize
Keep going, and you'll only accelerate.
As I desperately struggle ahead
Possessed by my fears and doubts
I'll find a path that will lead me
to where the sun shines.
Why can't I just live a decent life?
Both as the head of the Rosenthal family...
I'm fed up with my past, yet I can't let go
...and as a pupil of my master.
I can't forgive myself
Don't I still deserve to suffer?
Can you do that, all on your own?
That's the question nagging at my heart
Yes.
As it rots
Because I'm not alone.
"But you see...
...Misaka can look after him just fine on her own",
says Misaka as Misaka rejects
an unsolicited busybody!
"Misaka is only coming to pay
a visit to thank him once again",
pleads Misaka, in a nurse-like mood,
her heart all aflutter.
Misaka is doing this!
Misaka will do it.
No, Misaka will!
Misaka is doing it!
No, Misaka!
No—
Same crapheap of a city as always.
As usual, this was all caused by
villains scheming in the shadows.
As long as we stay in this city,
villains have to stay villains.
Otherwise, we won't be able to protect anything.
Huh?
Honestly,
this city never gets boring.