I do not like rain.
My hair gets super frizzy
when it is humid.
What? But your hair looks as great as ever.
It looks fine right now
because I am controlling
it as best I can.
Really? What happens
if you stop trying to control it?
It looks fine right now
because I am controlling
it as best I can.
How does that even work?!
I guess I can see why you'd end up hating the rain.
In that case, I'll tell you about something
that'll make you like the rain.
One of the Seven Wonders of Karai High:
"The Umbrella of Love."
If a girl offers to share an umbrella with
a boy on the way home on a rainy day,
the two will fall helplessly in love.
Well? Do you like the rain yet?
I like rain a lot!
The moisture makes my skin feel
very nice and firm.
Sorry, Nanako.
I just wanted to see you smile,
so I made that whole thing up on the spot.
Words silently float down, I start to feel lighter
As my feelings begin to take shape
It looks like love's in the air
It feels as though the rain is more calming than ever
Whenever I'm with you
Which are the words I need to write out
To make them last and for them to never fade?
If nothing changes, this'll be nothing more than a distant memory
Isn't that right, God?
The moment before a droplet breaks, or before the train comes
I pray they will never end
"Please let it go on forever"
Is that too much to ask?
Verse 7
Nanako and the Rain
Wonder
Verse 7
Nanako and the Rain
Wonder
Wow, Busujima's totally soaked.
Don't you know? Delinquents don't use umbrellas.
For real?
E-Ei, you will catch
a cold if you stay like that!
Please take a towel!
E-Ei, you will catch
a cold if you stay like that!
Please take a towel!
Thanks!
I've got an umbrella with me, but it's not worth
using unless it's really comin' down, y'know?
He really doesn't use it...
Umbrellas?
If you both have one, just say that you
forgot yours or lost it, and borrow his.
Hm? What's up, Nanako?
Hey, Ei, can we please
go home together today?
Is that fine with you?
Huh? Sure...
Hey look, it stopped raining!
Hm? Something the matter, Nanako?
There is nothing wrong!
I was just worried about
my laundry at home.
Huh? What do you mean?
Hey, Yukishiro.
Weren't you on the clean-up committee?
It seems the rabbit hutch is in an
awful state after the typhoon yesterday.
Could you look into getting it fixed up?
Apparently there's a rumor that a
demon is occupying the broken hutch.
Well, what's this?
You're here to help out?
Hey, Ei, so you know...
I think being in charge of
animals suits you.
Really? Well, I don't mind animals.
Isn't it awful though?
The rabbits were all moved away
from here at least, so they're fine.
Those ears certainly
seem to make you happier.
Would you not agree?
Stop saying lame stuff like that!
This is only for camouflage!
When they see me,
the rabbits all run for their lives,
so I didn't have a choice.
Still, looks like this'll basically
have to be rebuilt from scratch.
What are you up to,
you damn loveb—I mean, you two?
Hey, Tao. We're doing committee work.
Hey, Tao, can I ask
which committee you are on?
Would you please tell me?
The newspaper committee, I guess.
In that case, how about gettin' us a front-page
article about the fixed-up rabbit hutch?
Sure, I can do that. The headline will be...
Tragedy follows
a moment's carelessness!
This is what I saw.
Don't base your article on fortune-telling!
Tragedy follows
a moment's carelessness!
And wait, I'm gonna screw up like that?!
Well then.
Don't just leave like that!
Help us make sure that doesn't happen!
Oh well...
Hm? Helping a man wearing
rabbit ears brings good fortune.
I see. Well, let's start by moving the broken parts.
Right!
Okay, next please!
Oh hell no, she's here.
My, Eiji!
What's wrong? Worries about sex?
No, and get off me!
I gotta get this load of splinters outta me!
Gotta let a load out, huh?
Sure thing. Just lie down on the bed right there.
How do I lie on this?!
Kino.
Kino is here too
because she is on the same
committee as me.
Heya.
That's reassuring.
Here we go!
Huh?
What is this avant-garde work of art?!
What'cha think?
I think that you might
have a strange idea of
What'cha think?
what a hutch looks like.
You think so? I hadn't realized!
I doubt the rabbits would find this relaxing at all.
Right?
Animals
Man, we finally finished it.
Right?
We did finish it.
It is so much fun
Right?
to build something outdoors with
all of my good friends!
Right?
These guys can finally settle in.
Wow, you did it!
Did you all build this together?
That's awesome!
W-Well, it's nothing major,
but feel free to take a look.
Something major is getting away though!
What? No way! The door hinges were loose!
My fortunes really do come—
Never mind that, we have to catch the rabbits!
This is a message from the broadcasting committee.
Ten rabbits have escaped from the rabbit hutch.
We ask everyone to cooperate
in capturing the rabbits.
If you capture one, we ask that you
bring it to the rabbit hutch ASAP.
Wh-What's with this sudden announcement?
And hold on, don't tell me this voice is...
This was a message from
the broadcasting committee.
Prez?!
Animals
Thanks for the help.
I will be taking my leave, then.
Bye!
Sure! Thanks for today!
I'll head home after I've fed them.
Huh? What's up, Nanako?
Hey! did you forget
Hey! Did you forget
the promise that we made to
go home together?
Oh, you're right. My bad.
Why don't you come help me out, then?
Yes!
The heck? Why's it raining again?
We're done feeding the rabbits.
Guess we'd better get home already.
Hey, Ei, I forgot
to bring an umbrella to
school with me today.
What? Wanna borrow mine, then?
Hey, Ei, I forgot
to bring an umbrella with
me to school today.
Ah, sorry. I guess I forgot mine too.
Wanna go like this?
This actually works pretty well.
Seriously, you both forgot your umbrellas?
Oh, Prez. Thanks for the broadcast.
Here, you can borrow this.
But wait, President,
how will you get home today
without using it?
without using one?
Don't worry, I've got a spare folding umbrella.
Good luck.
If you do not have
any better plans in mind,
any other plans in mind,
would you please join me?
R-Right.
Huh? Wait, isn't this... a little intima—
Well, whatever.
Prioritizing others' love before your own, huh?
Well, I wouldn't really say that.
You just can't help wanting
to watch over them, huh?
We two are so different that it's funny
Even our reflections in the display window
When you smile, it's like the sun
And I can feel a gentle wind begin to blow
Even these ordinary uneventful days
Start shining when I'm with you
No matter what might happen
Even if we sometimes hurt each other
I'll keep believing in these unremarkable days
The next episode
of Senryu Girl is titled:
"Nanako Changes—
—Into a Swimsuit."
Next Time, Verse 8
"Nanako Changes Into a Swimsuit"