Hey there, Nanako.
No club today?
Gotcha.
Oh, that's right.
You're on summer break, right?
Why don't you invite some friends over?
I'd actually like to meet that delinquent kid, for one.
Huh?
I've been Nanako's father for fifteen years now.
Nanako has shown me all sorts of expressions so far.
Her smiling, her angry face, her crying...
They're all very dear to me.
However...
That is one face that I've never, ever seen before!
Words silently float down, I start to feel lighter
As my feelings begin to take shape
It looks like love's in the air
It feels as though the rain is more calming than ever
Whenever I'm with you
Which are the words I need to write out
To make them last and for them to never fade?
If nothing changes, this'll be nothing more than a distant memory
Isn't that right, God?
The moment before a droplet breaks, or before the train comes
I pray they will never end
"Please let it go on forever"
Is that too much to ask?
Verse 9
Eiji Meets Nanako's Dad
I guess sticking to this uniform
during summer's gonna be tough.
Hm? It's from Nanako.
Ei, are you doing
"Ei, are you doing
anything today or are
you free by some chance ?
you free by some chance?"
Gotta reply... Ah!
My phone is flavoring my modest lunch!
Huh? I-Is your brother okay?
If he's that loud, it's actually a sign that
nothing's really wrong, so he's probably fine.
I see, so your phone was accidentally submerged.
That's right.
Have you backed up the data?
No one's ever backed me up into a corner before.
BACK
I-Is that so...
I'm undefeated.
By the way, what did you drop it into?
Oh, uh...
Salt... No, miso?
I don't care about the flavor of ramen!
It's gonna take a whole day to repair it?
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
Whatever. Guess I'll just wander around
for a bit, seeing as I'm already here.
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
Have some tissues!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
KARAI MARKET
TREASURE HUNTING MARKET
You read that right, it really is a treasure hunt!
Please take some!
What are you up to, Koto?
Oh, Eiji!
I got a part-time job handing out these tissues.
Here's a pack for you, too!
Oh, thanks.
If you double them up, they won't tear as easily.
Keep that in mind when you're using them!
The hell are you talking about?
Oh, huh. It's Prez.
She's studying at a coffee shop. Wow.
She looks way more mature than usual.
Oh, she's getting the staff's attention.
But no one's noticing her.
She stretched to hide the fact
that she raised her hand!
Thank goodness she's her usual self.
I'm starving. Guess I'll go for a beef bowl.
Make yourself at home.
Huh? Tao?
Hm?
I-I don't have to divine to tell.
"Having a beef bowl all alone
during summer break, what a loser."
That's what you're thinking!
No, I'm not thinking that at all!
"You normally dress in gothic lolita fashion,
but on your day off you just wear a normal T-shirt?"
You're thinking that as well!
Sorry, that one did cross my mind.
Oh, Prez is still there.
Wow, she's drinking her coffee black.
She really is mature.
That burns!
Ah! It was too hot! That was a pretty loud scream!
Oh wow, she played it off as if she was
on the phone! Talk about quick thinking!
Not again!
Her luck's as bad as ever, though!
Oh, Kino's sketching.
Huh. I guess observation is an
important part of the process.
Hey, Kino.
This thing's been standing here
since before I can remember.
What're you drawing?
Hold up...
Detective
Gorilla
Totally unrelated!
What were you even observing just now?!
Detective
Gorilla
Tee-hee
Tee-hee!
Man, I'm sure running into a lot of people I know.
Haven't I run into just about everyone now?
No, wait. I didn't come across Nanako.
Well, not that I mind.
I'm practically ignoring her message, too...
I wonder what she's up to right now...
Hold up! What kind of lame train of thought is that?
If someone read my mind right there,
I'd die from embarrassment!
I can't see a thing!
Impairing my vision? How sly!
My sense of sight only slows
me down! I'll gladly give—
Oh, hello there, Ei.
I did not expect to meet
you in such a place.
Hey, Nanako! I was just hoping to meet—
No, I mean, uh...
I didn't mean it like that!
You see, uh...
I-I've been running into a bunch of people, like Prez,
so I figured if I ran into you
I'd complete the collection, you know...
Is that truly it?
What exactly is it that
you wanted with me?
Well, you know, I-I only meant that
it'd make for good closure to my day.
B-But, I guess if I'm putting it like that, then...
I wanted to see you.
I was just thinking about you.
As it so happens,
I was thinking the same thing!
Who would have figured?
I-It's not like you've been
running into everyone, right?
Hm?
Hey, if you are free,
would you like to come over
to my house today ?
to my house today?
What? Your old man wants to meet me?!
Pardon the intrusion! I'm Eiji Busujima!
Many apologies for the imposition.
I am so very grateful that you allowed me to visit!
Welcome. So you're Eiji!
Make yourself right at home.
I see. So you're Busujima. Come, have a seat.
U-Understood! Excuse me!
Now, Busujima, forgive me
for getting straight to the point.
Um, you... Exactly what is your—
What is your relationship with Nanako?
Our relationship?
Should I just say that we're in the same class?
Class C
Well... We're together in the same class.
Together, eh?
Together?!
What do you mean, you're together?!
How dare you?!
Huh?! What's wrong?!
You bastard!
Wait! What's wrong, dear?
Sorry about that.
My temper got the better of me.
No, it's fine. I should have realized
how that could be confusing.
I should've picked my words better.
To go back to the point,
you're just friends with Nanako, yes?
Y-Yes, that's correct!
And that's what you think too, Nanako?
Nana—
Daddy's going to take a little nap now.
Mom! Dad's doing that thing again!
Wait, what thing?
Is he okay?
Dad, I really think
Come on, get a grip.
you should take a little rest.
Come now, off to bed.
Sorry about all the ruckus.
Oh, don't worry about it.
For what it's worth, he does have his reasons.
Reasons?
Well, you know,
Nanako always speaks in meter, yes?
She was bullied a lot in
elementary school because of that.
In the end, she stopped going outside much.
That made her father very worried.
But after going to a senryu gathering in her
third year of junior high, she perked right up.
Apparently someone told her something.
Who in the world could it have been?
Y-Yeah, I wonder...
B-By the way, did Nanako say
anything about that person?
She said that she'd found the one person,
other than family, who she wanted
to spend the rest of her life with.
Oh, is that right... N-Not that it concerns me.
Ah! I have to go and collect my phone!
Please excuse me!
Oh dear. Do come by again!
We two are so different that it's funny
Even our reflections in the display window
When you smile, it's like the sun
And I can feel a gentle wind begin to blow
Even these ordinary uneventful days
Start shining when I'm with you
No matter what might happen
Even if we sometimes hurt each other
I'll keep believing in these unremarkable days
The next episode
of Senryu Girl is titled:
"Nanako, Fire—
—flies, and Tests of Courage."
Next Time, Verse 10
"Nanako, Fireflies, and Tests of Courage"