Yumeno Apartment Complex Information Board
Building No. 1 - Yumeno Apartment Complex
It's morning-
Darn it.
Mew-
I fell asleep at the heated table
while I was studying.
Mew-
Jeez. Seems Yayoi did too.
It's morning. Wake up.
You're gonna be late for school.
Gotta pee.
Me too.
Oh, Uzuki, Satsuki.
Help me wake Yayoi up.
Is this what I think?
Can't you move at all, Haruki?
At all?
Pounce
Now's our chance to do whatever
we want with him, Satsuki!
Okay, Uzuki.
Tickle, tickle, tickle!
Stop that! Hey!
How about here?!
Or here?!
Take this, this, this, and this!
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle!
Look...
Oh, Yayoi, you're... up.
What do you think you're doing hugging me, stupid Haru-perv?!
You need to get rid of your violent habits right away!
Waking up to you that close
to me is bad for my heart!
You were the one clinging onto me!
Wow! They're fighting!
That's gross!
Wow!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
You guys are making too much noise.
You're going to disturb our neighbors.
I'm not making breakfast for either of you.
And you two used to get along so well...
But Mutsuki-nee! Haru-jerk was—
No, she was—
They've been busy hugging and moving
around a lot since early this morning.
What?
Nod, nod.
We weren't!
You two...
What you just said could
be easily misunderstood,
so don't repeat it to anyone.
And you two should get ready soon.
Should I tell our vacationing mother
to cut your allowances for this month?
Wait, Onee-sama!
Man, that girl has some nerve...
And to think I was up all night
helping with her studies...
Yay!
Uzuki was here first! Out!
Hey, wait! Use it after I'm done!
Don't wanna! You're a meanie, Haruki!
Fine, fine.
You can go first.
Chokehold!
Let go of me!
I don't wanna! This is fun!
Uzuki's in trouble!
Satsuki to the rescue!
There!
So heavy...
My back! My back!
You got this, Haruki!
Exercise more.
We're going now!
Now!
Don't fall over.
We're not kids anymore!
Hey, Haruki.
Hm?
Stop blocking the doorway.
Yeah, yeah. Sorry about that, Yayoi-sama.
Your tie's crooked.
And your hair's a mess.
As my older brother, you should put
more care into your appearance.
If you did, you'd actually look pretty cool.
Did you say something?
I didn't say anything!
Take that!
Hey, now. I thought you two had left already.
ashita no koto wa wakaranai kedo
We don't know what tomorrow will bring
kyou mo wa kitto ii hi ni shiyou
So let's try to make today a good day too
Uzuki's gonna be the star
of next week's episode!
Building No. 2 - The Twins' Homework
Tune in next week!