Building No. 7 - A Pool In Our Apartment?!
We're all set!
Set!
Do you two have swimming class today?
Yup! We're going to school
wearing these under our clothes!
Clothes!
Make sure to bring something
to change into, okay?
Uzuki was so cute when
she forgot hers last time.
Satsuki! Don't tell them!
We're going!
Going!
Be safe!
What are we doing today?
Breaststroke!
So lucky!
I wanna go to the pool too! Or the beach!
You'll be shivering from head to toe
if you go at this time of the year.
I'm fully aware of that!
I wanna swim! I wanna have fun!
I've got it!
I'm home. It's hot!
What's going on? Is the heater broken?
This room is way too... hot. Huh?
W-Welcome home.
It's still spring. What are you two doing?
W-We kinda felt like wearing these...
You too, Big Sis?
Wearing swimsuits indoors
when it's not the season is kind of...
Well, a bit immodest—
What do you take us for, stupid Haru-perv?!
This whole thing is your fault in the first place!
I bought a new swimsuit last year
because we were supposed to go to the beach!
But at the very last minute—
Sorry. My grades dropped,
so I can't go anymore.
Tomorrow
Beach
What?!
Tomorrow
What was I supposed to say?
And I had to prepare
for my entrance exams too!
We can go this year—
No way!
I'll be facing my worst nightmares this summer!
Preparing for
entrance exams
This Year
Don't say that with such a smug look!
Okay, okay.
I'll be in my room playing games,
so do whatever you like...
Here.
No, I'm good.
I don't care! Strip, Haruki!
Wh—No! No! Stop!
What's this supposed to be?
It's a pool, as you can see.
All three of us are going to get in!
Doesn't this bring back memories?
We would do this a lot as children.
We did. It's all coming back to me.
Pool!
I was a shrimp back then.
Right when I'd jump in...
Hm?
Has this been thoroughly cleaned?
Of course!
Now, shall we?
Certainly.
Splash
Having fun?
What are we doing here?
I'm having quite a bit of fun.
I kind of am too.
I'm so confused...
Yumeno Apartment Complex Information Board
Yumeno
Apartment
Complex
We're home!
Home!
Satsuki was the one who forgot
to bring a change of clothes today!
Don't tell them, Uzuki!
Achoo!
What happened?
Happened?
It was a bit too early to play
in the water, don't you think?
Achoo!
mirai ga donna watashi ka wa wakaranai kedo
I don't know what the future has in store for me
demo chiisana shiawase ga ashita wo kaete yuku
But these tiny moments of happiness will shape the days to come
Building No. 8 - We're Related
I...
Building No. 8 - We're Related.
Building No. 8 - We're Related
A devil princess?