Building No. 6 - The Sisters and Multiplication
Welcome home, Haruki.
Your older sister here
will teach you anything.
No thanks.
I can study for tests on my own.
Even Haruki turned me down...
What's gotten into you?
When I offered to help Yayoi
with her studies earlier...
She was gone like the wind.
Well, you don't exactly teach...
To solve for x,
just rearrange the terms like this.
See? It's easy!
Wh-What? Wait!
Let's move on to the next one.
For this one...
Studying?
Yeah, my midterms are coming up.
Really getting into it, I see.
Not really...
Um, I know you're busy studying
for your own midterms, but...
Basics for the Future
Come on, teach me!
You're really good at teaching, Haruki.
No offense to Nee-san...
Well, if you really insist!
It's been a while.
Let's have an intense study session!
Okay!
She'd be a lot cuter if
she were always this honest.
Huh?
What does your test cover?
Everything from here to here.
I'm not even sure where I'm stuck
for these problems, actually.
Do you still have some of your old tests?
Um, my old tests?!
Well, I do...
I don't want to show them to you though.
I already know your marks are bad.
Why are you embarra—
Year 3 Midterm Exam (Science)
Year 3 Midterm Exam (Math)
Year 3 Midterm Exam (English)
Year 3 Midterm Exam (History)
Marks
Class
Seat
No.
Name
Nakano Yayoi
Yeah, they're bad.
Hit me again and I won't teach you.
After looking at these,
it's clear what you're struggling with.
Right now, what you need to focus on...
is multiplication!
You're joking!
Multiplication is elementary school-level math!
Write me the times tables
before you say anything else.
Easy peasy!
Four of them are wrong.
What?!
I'm sure they were just careless mistakes!
This is responsible for your bad marks.
I'm going to have you multiply till you drop!
I finished!
You made another mistake
in the eight times table!
No way!
Time for bed.
Bed.
Huh?
You're still making a lot
of mistakes! Keep working!
Are you studying?
Studying?
Don't look!
She has a test tomorrow.
Oh, a test? Good luck!
Luck!
By the way, I got full marks
on my multiplication test!
Me too!
O-Oh...
Yumeno Apartment Complex Information Board
Yumeno
Apartment
Complex
I'm home!
Welcome home, Yayoi.
How did the test go?
You studied hard for it, after all.
I'm sure your marks—
Not so fast, missy.
Didn't I help you out?
Let me see!
No!
This isn't what it looks like!
I just wanted to see Yayoi's test results!
Am I at fault for insisting that
they try to get along better?
ashita no koto wa wakaranai kedo
We don't know what tomorrow will bring
kyou mo wa kitto ii hi ni shiyou
So let's try to make today a good day too
Building No. 7 - A Pool In Our Apartment?!
Swimsuits?
This is fun!
Building No. 7 - A Pool In Our Apartment?!