It looks pretty old.
What is it?
Beats me.
I'm told it was involved in some incident or
other a long time back, and we confiscated it.
Okay...
So what am I supposed to do with it?
Straight west of here, across the sea,
you'll find the City of Freedom, Qunortz.
You're going to deliver that chest to the
United Magic Association's branch office there.
Uh-huh.
Just take it there, fulfil a request, and
receive your pay. Couldn't be simpler, am I right?
What? That's it?
If it's such a simple job, then why aren't you taking it?
Because I'm heading out on holiday
right after this, don't you know.
Holiday?
I work way too hard around here, and I'm beat!
"Whatever you do, don't open it."
That's what they told me, and now I'm telling you.
There could be something pretty nasty inside.
Aye aye, sir!
Under no circumstances will I open it!
Then off I go!
Now then. I should be off too.
As illusions start to gain colour and shapes
irodorarete ikeba gensou ga
While they slowly start to become real
katachi aru mono ni naru you ni
I will give them form
egaite yukeru
And grant their wishes
kanaete yukerunda
As the gently blowing wind
yasashiku fuita kaze ga
Stirs the pages of an aged book
furui page mekuru you ni
I may turn back now and then
furikaeru kedo
But rest assured, it will be all right
uun ii no yo
Tales of meeting and parting once more
shiranai koto darake no
All so full of new, yet-unexplored things
deai wakare no hanashi
I gently brushed the words set down in blurry ink
nijimu ink wo sotto nazotta
Where are you going to?
doko iku no
Somewhere just a little far away
sukoshi tooku made
Let the things I left behind turn into dreams
oitekita mono wa yume ni
Choosing what I like best, and in the process
suki dakara erabu erabinagara
Slowly growing into myself
watashi ni natte yuku
"Oh, do let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
"And make it a promise, too!"
yakusoku dakara
You said to me, grinning from ear to ear
anata wa sou hohoenda
"Yes, let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
Linking fingers, we sealed our vow
koyubi no majinai
And as I heard a voice calling to me
dareka no koe ga shite
I opened my eyes
me ga sameta
The Two Teachers
You sure seem to have a thing
for stuffy, old-fashioned workplaces.
Has it been a year already?
Time and tide wait for no witch, I see.
Ah, where do the days go?
That's deep, Granny.
So? Are you ready to go yet?
Don't know why I bother asking,
since you never are, but still.
Wait just a bit. I'll be ready shortly.
What is it, Miss Fran? Has some urgent work come up?
Oh, no. I'm going on holiday.
Holiday?
Goodbye, then.
Okay, boys and girls. Don't let
your teacher hear you were slacking off.
What's that? You took on an apprentice?
Her name's Saya.
She seems to know all about your apprentice.
Saya...
She's the girl Elaina helped
become a novice, isn't she?
It's a small world.
Tell me about it.
I ran into Elaina herself, too.
My goodness!
When I told Saya about it, I seriously
thought she might die of jealousy.
Isn't it a funny world?
Who'd have ever thought that you and I
would be taking annual trips together like this?
You can say that again.
Used to be I couldn't stand you.
The feeling was quite mutual, Sheila.
This is a tale from back
when I was but an apprentice witch,
travelling with my teacher.
Huh? What did you just say, Teacher?
I've been thinking of taking on an apprentice!
Aren't I your apprentice?
Yes, but I think I might like to have one more.
I believe that's your decision to make, Teacher.
But if I go off and do it without
consulting you, you'll be cross with me.
But you've already decided on who
your second apprentice will be, haven't you?
Correct!
I knew it.
It will be all right, Fran.
What will?
She's a good girl.
I know you'll just love her!
Yo! Up here!
Hey, Teacher! Where the heck you been?
You've got some real stones, keepin' me waitin'!
Sorry about that. It took some time
to persuade my apprentice.
It'd be lovely if you could not
toss off lies so casually, please.
Well, well. So this here's my senior apprentice?
Not exactly hot stuff, are ya?
Huh? What's your problem?
Who do ya think you're lookin' at? Wanna go?
Teacher, is this your idea of a "good girl"?
She's talking trash to someone she only just met!
Say that again, I dare ya!
Now, now.
You two are sister apprentices now.
Get along, will you?
Understood.
I hope for your favour. May I have your name?
No name the likes of you has any business knowin'!
Sheila, meet Fran. Fran, meet Sheila.
Do be nice, now.
Teacher! I don't think this is going to work out!
And that was how my teacher and I,
and also Sheila, set out on a journey together.
In short, the two of us got along like oil and water.
What shall we have for dinner?
Fish?
Or beef?
Fish sounds nice.
Beef, obviously.
What?
What, what?
Wanna go?
Is that all you can say?
You're like a broken record!
Are you stupid?
Or perhaps you're dumb?
Is that all you know how to say?
Before you come for me,
how 'bout you expand your vocabulary first?
In that case, we'll compromise and have bread!
What?
What shall I teach you today? Fire spells or ice spells?
Ice spells sound good.
What? Obviously fire spells!
Are you touched in the head?
In that case, we'll compromise and take today off!
If your wands were taken away in the midst of battle,
how would you go about continuing the fight?
Martial arts! Let's learn some hand-to-hand combat!
Please teach us how to use a bow.
What?
What, what?
In that case, we'll compromise
and learn how to use knives!
Knives?!
You conceal them right here.
Then, you draw them out...
Like this.
Be sure to strike a sexy pose.
If there's one thing I know, it's that
me and you are never gonna be friends.
Oh my, what a coincidence!
I'm even more certain you and I will never be friends!
Several months into our journey,
we received a request from the United Magic Association
that took us to the City of Freedom, Qunortz.
"Magic users not wanted"?
"Live not in fear of magic users"?
"Magic Users: Offspring of the Devil!"?
The hell's this? Are they tryna pick a fight?
It seems they don't welcome witches here.
I wonder.
A few signs like this aren't reason enough
to turn our backs on the entire city.
That would make us no different than
the people who put those up.
Welcome to our city!
We've been eagerly awaiting
your arrival, honoured witches.
Forgive my haste, but as to our request—
What does it pay?
I'd like to tell you what we're asking you to do first...
Your payment will be ten gold coins.
Look at her! She's overjoyed!
So, what does it entail?
Ah, yes.
There's a shady group calling themselves the Antique
Company slinking around in the shadows of our city.
I see, I see. The Antique Company, huh?
I'm sure you've already seen the posters and signs
all around town saying horrible things about magic users.
Ah!
Oh, them?
This Antique Company is a band of bandits,
made up of those who can't use magic.
As they have no magic power of their own,
they despise nothing more than
magic users who try to thwart their plans,
which is why they carry out that libellous campaign
and many other forms of harassment.
How come you don't just arrest 'em, then?
You can all use magic. Should be a piece of piss, right?
Are you so desperate to stop them that you'd
resort to offering travellers like us
this huge sum to do it for you?
I see your point, but—
There's something else to this story, isn't there?
The Antique Company has an arsenal
of very strange weapons.
Strange like how?
Swords capable of cutting through anything,
guns that can shoot an infinite number of bullets,
matches that create illusions of fierce
mythical beasts when struck, and many more.
Even though they lack magic,
this strange and terrible arsenal gives them power
to equal any magic spells—or even surpass them.
That's what we're up against?
Yes, indeed.
These bandits use their weapons with such skill that
they're able to toy with any magic-using pursuers
like cats with mice, and escape every time.
Our people's faith in magic users
has been driven right into the ground!
Very well. You have my word
that this matter will be resolved.
Thank you so much!
I'm sure they'll be no match for
your awesome power, honoured witch—
Oh no, I won't be taking care of it.
These two will!
What?!
Go round up this Antique Company together.
They may have a few tricky tools,
but that should be no problem
for any apprentices of mine!
If you mess this up,
I'll expel you.
Expel...
I'm quite certain that the same idea
popped into both of our heads.
"I'll take down the Antique Company myself,
and then she'll be expelled!"
W-Wait! Wait a second!
I know what I did was wicked! Please, spare my life!
Your life you can have.
What I want is your weapon there.
The sword?
Fine! Here, I'll give it to you!
Now I have a few questions I'd like you to answer.
Hey. Not so fast.
I saw him first.
That means this is my score.
Excuse me, but I'm the one who cornered him.
That's what you think. I used you to corner him for me.
That means I'm the one on top here. Got that?
There's nothing to "get".
And I'm certainly not handing him over to you.
What?
What, what?
What is wrong with you?
Do you just enjoy getting in my way?
Or are you trying to score points with Teacher?
Shut your trap! Not everything's about you, y'know!
And on and on we went in this fashion,
doing nothing but trip one another up.
As a result,
day after day passed, and neither of us managed
to catch a single Antique Company bandit.
Here you are!
Thank you.
Might ye be the magic user by the name of Fran?
How do you know my name?
Don't be concerning yerself with that little detail.
Tell me now, has that task been coming along well?
Does it look that way to you?
Hmm. "Antique Company leader vows revenge,
beheading of magic users assaulting comrades", eh?
Goodness me, things are getting awful gruesome.
Not at all. This is very good news for me.
Why might that be?
They're after yer pretty little head, lassie.
It means that my target is about to come to me.
It certainly saves me the trouble of
having to hunt them down.
Yer a bold one, lassie. Confident, too.
Of course I am. After all,
here you are, right in front of me.
You're the boss of the Antique Company, aren't you?
Don't go thinkin' ye can resist.
One funny move and I'll make that headline
come true and chop yer pretty little head right off.
Take her away. We're going to make short work of her!
Aye aye!
Wow, great job getting your useless self captured.
Real impressive, senior apprentice.
Big talk from someone who's
tied up right behind me.
I suppose this shows how little
my junior apprentice is capable of.
Fie on all ye magic users. Every time it's the same.
You can't resist sticking yer noses into our affairs!
It's thanks to the lot of yer that we can hardly
do an honest day's thieving any more!
Ooh, I can't bloody stand ye!
And as for you, ye sorry lot!
How can ye let a couple of useless little apprentice
witches get the better of big blokes like you?
We worked so hard to blacken
the name of magic users in this city,
and ye'd put it back to how it was
with your addle-brained fumbling?
Are ye tryna waste all our hard work away?
Aye, a credit to the name of
the Antique Company, you are!
Look alive, ye lunkheads!
Aye!
We heard every word the pair of ye said
about yer teacher and what-have-ye.
What's what, eh? Are you trifling with us for a laugh?
This isn't even enough to make me laugh.
Kicking your asses is way too easy.
Why, the cheek of ye!
Boss!
Get rid of the both of 'em, and make it snappy!
Aye!
Have a taste of this!
Boss!
Why you—
Wh-What do ye think ye're doing?
I want them dead! Hurry it up!
Aye!
I think I see now. You let them
catch you on purpose too, didn't you?
I figured I'd sneak in here
and round up the whole gang.
And how's that working out?
No worse than yours!
How awesome yer powers be, honoured witches!
Now I see that we're no match fer—
I'm going to rest for just a minute,
and then I'll get in touch with the Association.
Sounds good to me.
What made you want to learn magic from Teacher?
It's not like I had some big important reason.
I taught myself magic.
Hey!
Wait!
I was using it to get by.
Then one day I tried to pinch the purse
of this woman. That woman was Teach.
She caught me like it was nothing.
That was the first I learned that
there were such things as witches.
You'd never known before that?
Didn't have anyone to teach me.
But she did.
She taught me how strong witches can be,
and how people respect them.
I thought if I were a witch, I wouldn't have to
live in the gutter like a stray cat anymore.
So I asked her if she'd make me her apprentice.
See? Told you it wasn't for any important reason.
How 'bout you?
My reason's even more unimportant.
There aren't any witches where I'm from.
If I became a witch, I'd get to be
the only one in the whole country.
I'd be set for life. That was what I figured.
That's my reason.
You became a witch to a real self-serving end, huh.
You could say that.
What the heck?
Don't tell me we're no different.
I'm afraid so.
Thus, Sheila and I rounded up
the entire Antique Company together.
Damn ye lassies! I'll have yer rotten guts for garters!
Won't they go right back to their old tricks
once they're released from jail?
Perhaps so.
Very well done indeed, both of you.
We continued journeying with Teacher,
and when we returned to her homeland...
All right! I finally did it!
Thank you so much!
They suit you beautifully.
You are now both full-fledged witches.
Yes!
As for your witch titles...
Fran, your hair is black,
so you'll be the Stardust Witch!
Hm?
Sheila, your hair is shiny,
so you'll be the Midnight Witch!
Huh?
Since my hair is black,
shouldn't I be the Midnight Witch?
And if my hair's shiny,
shouldn't I be the Stardust Witch?
It's because stardust and midnight compliment
each other that each one can sparkle!
Uh, I don't really get it.
Oh, I get it now! It's like, no matter how
far apart we are, we'll always be together.
That's what you were trying to say, right?
Bullseye, it seems.
But why base our titles on our hair?
Because it's cool!
And that was how our journey
with Teacher came to an end.
I returned to my homeland
and became a teacher myself,
and quite unexpectedly, Sheila took a job
with the United Magic Association.
You certainly have changed.
Nah, not all that much.
But I've gotta say, I like our relationship now
better than back when all we did was fight.
It's way less stress.
You really have changed.
We've both grown up, that's all.
Sun's going down. Let's get a move on.
All right.
That chest...
I know what it was!
Change of plans!
Hey, what's gotten into you?
Never mind that now! Just come on!
You're still as inconsiderate as ever.
Wait for me!
On that day, I was heading to a certain place,
one I remembered well from
volume four of The Adventures of Nike.
It was where the friendship between Nike's apprentices,
Fura and Sheilan, first blossomed,
a veritable holy ground for Nike fans.
That's right—it's the City of Freedom, Qunortz!