Ever since I was a little girl, there was nothing
I loved more than reading books.
The one I loved most of all
was called The Adventures of Nike.
Recorded in its pages
was a travelogue the witch named Nike
had written while journeying all around the world.
I want to travel to lots of different places, just like Nike!
In that case, you'd better start studying
so you can become a witch just like her!
If I become a witch,
will you let me go on a journey too?
Of course we will!
Right?
Sure!
Though only after you've grown up
into a full-fledged witch, okay?
Really?
Really for real?!
Really for real!
I will become a witch!
I get how we feel about people
tooting their own horn,
but I was a diligent worker,
studying tirelessly from dawn 'til dusk every day.
As a result,
I became the youngest graduate
in the history of the peaceful country of Robetta
to pass the magical skills exam.
Now, the fourteen-year-old
novice witch standing before you...
Why yes, that would be me!
Elaina, the Apprentice Witch
Congratulations on passing the exam, Elaina!
We're so proud of you.
What's wrong? Aren't you happy?
All the other candidates were awfully weak.
So I suppose it's just a matter of time
before I become a witch!
Deary me.
The exam was only the start of the road.
To be considered a full-fledged witch,
a novice must become an apprentice
of an established witch.
On my way!
How can I help you?
Uhm, w-well...
I'm a recent graduate of the magical exam,
and my name is Elaina—
Yes?
Well, well. Who have we here?
I'm a recent graduate of the magical exam,
and my name is—
Word had gotten out about me
being the youngest graduate ever,
and it seems the witches in
my home town were not impressed.
I just can't! Sorry!
I asked and asked, but every single witch
would just turn me down on the spot.
I'll never become a witch at this rate.
What to do?
I've heard there's a very odd witch
who's made her home deep in the forest nearby.
Oh, I've heard the same rumour.
They call her the Stardust Witch.
So off I went to pay this Stardust Witch a visit.
If she isn't part of the grapevine, she'll be less likely
to refuse my apprenticeship, I thought.
Oh?
Could that be her?
My, oh my!
The Stardust Witch?
There you are! And there! And there!
Time to turn back.
Whee!
Yes, that's lovely!
There! And there!
Pardon me.
Oh?
Oh my.
Uhm, well...
Would you happen to be Miss Elaina?
You know who I am?
Yes, I do.
You passed the magical skills exam on your
first try at only fourteen, isn't that right?
Your reputation precedes you. For good or for ill.
What brings you here?
Nothing. Excuse me.
Might you be here to request an apprenticeship?
If so—
I know, I know. You can't.
I'd be fine with that.
Huh?
I have plenty of time on my hands.
But—
Um...
Are you sure?
I'm not like those Robetta witches.
It doesn't matter to me
what sort of girl my apprentice is.
Please grant me the honour of
making me your apprentice!
And that was how I met
the Stardust Witch—my teacher, Fran.
Good morning!
Good morning.
I'm famished. Would you whip up something to eat?
What would you like?
Let me see...
I feel like a steak this morning!
Wouldn't that be a bit heavy for breakfast?
In that case, I'd be fine with a bowl
of the weeds from outside.
Awfully far in the other direction, don't you think?
All right, I'll settle for bread.
I'm going out to gather herbs.
Pardon me, but I'd really like
to learn some magic today...
All in due time.
I'll return later.
Have a pleasant outing.
The time I'd spent as her apprentice
turned from days to weeks,
and Miss Fran had still yet
to give me any sort of training.
Elaina, my cupboards are getting bare.
Go into town and take care of the shopping.
Okay.
Elaina, I need some lizards for my research.
Go catch me five or so.
Okay.
Elaina! How long until dinner?
Okay!
For a brew to relieve pain, let's see here...
Elaina! There's a spider in the bath!
Would you please get rid of it for me? It's scary.
Okay.
She snuck these into the stew, didn't she?
You don't care for mushrooms?
A witch can't be picky.
Elaina, massage my shoulders.
Okay.
Ooh, that feels marvelous!
Why aren't you teaching me any magic?
Ah! Right there! Harder!
Ahhhhh!
And we carried on like that until a month
had passed without her teaching me a thing.
I've done nothing but take care of her chores.
What am I even doing here?
Are you finally going to teach me some magic?
Oh, no! There's no need for me to teach you.
Is that right?
And I'm not in the mood for stew today.
Make something else.
Okay.
I suppose the time has finally arrived.
Elaina.
Yes?
I'm going to test you now.
What?
Miss Fran, what did you mean by testing me?
You and I are going to battle.
You are joking, right?
Now then. Let's begin.
If that's how you want it,
I'll blow you away!
Is she trying to kill me?
What's the matter?
Is that the best you can do?
You overwhelmed everyone else on the exam.
Give me a better challenge than that.
My, my. Done already?
It seems the young prodigy
isn't all she was cracked up to be.
I-I-I'm sorry! I didn't mean for you to cry!
Oh no, oh no!
Why, look at this! I know how much you love butterflies!
That's you, not me!
W-Well, in that case...
Behold! A crown made of weeds, just for you!
Don't want it!
Okay, then!
How about this?
One! Two!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Hmm, now what...
How about this?
Calm down.
Stop it! What do you think you're doing?
I truly am sorry. I see now that I went too far.
Stop joking around! You were having
such a fun time picking on me!
Fun? Heavens, no!
You never had any intentions of
helping me become a witch!
I hate you! I hate everybody!
I really believed, and I endured so much for so long,
telling myself it would all be okay!
But I was wrong! You're the same as
the witches in Robetta!
I trusted you, but you never even noticed
how much blood, sweat, and tears I shed!
All I wanted was for someone to acknowledge...
I am sorry. From the bottom of my heart.
I truly understand how you feel now.
You've endured everything so well.
Do you think you can fool me with that again?
No. I won't be deceiving you any longer.
I can't stand any more of this either.
The truth is, your parents asked me to do this.
Huh?
If she continues going on like this
when she reaches adulthood,
I'm concerned about how she will end up.
So you want me to make her my apprentice
and teach her what failure feels like?
That's right.
Well, I don't know...
Of course, we wouldn't ask you to do it for free,
Teacher.
Dear me, do I look like a witch who can be
so easily swayed by money to you?
With great reluctance, I answered your parents' plea.
At first, I planned to make you go through
hopelessly rigorous training,
and thus learn what the frustration of that feels like.
But you proved yourself incredibly skilled,
and willing to stop at nothing to fulfill my commands.
And you were very conscious of
how others perceived you.
I started to think that harsh training
wouldn't do anything for you.
You were sure to endure it
and go right back to how you were.
But...
Truth be told, that's one of your flaws.
You hold yourself back too much, Elaina.
You don't have to simply endure everything.
If you can't stomach it, fight it.
Learn to speak your mind and
call out bad things for what they are.
This is for your own self-preservation.
Then the reason you never taught me any magic was...
I was waiting for you to hit your boiling point.
It took an entire month to get there.
That's what today's test was about.
I really am sorry.
"Don't simply endure."
That was the first time in my life
anyone had told me that.
Teacher...
You have the knowledge and the talent.
If there's one thing you're lacking, it's experience.
On that day, my real training began.
In order to gain as much experience as I could...
Good morning, Miss Fran!
Good morning, Elaina.
I'm hungry. Fix me something to eat.
Here you are. A bowl of weeds, just for you.
Have I done something to get on your bad side?
You taught me not to endure too much abuse,
so I decided to speak my mind about what a pain
making breakfast for my teacher is.
Just kidding.
Will the leftover stew from yesterday and
some crusty bread do? Because that's what you get!
Okay.
The days I spent
training together with my teacher
came with their share of hardships,
but they were so meaningful and fun.
You've grown so much stronger.
I finally won!
Now your training is complete.
What?
You've done well this past year.
I have nothing more to teach you.
Congratulations, Elaina.
I, the Stardust Witch, hereby
recognize you as a full-fledged witch.
Thank you!
Also, concerning your witch title,
how do you feel about the "The Ashen Witch"?
Where did that name come from?
Your hair. It's coloured just like ash.
Isn't that a little too simple?
Oh, but I think it sounds really cool!
Come to think of it, how did you get
the name "The Stardust Witch"?
I chose it because it sounds cool!
So? What do you think of being the Ashen Witch?
Fine by me.
Then that settles it!
Elaina, the Ashen Witch.
Keep on doing your best.
I will.
Then I'll be on my way now.
Where to?
As it turned out, Miss Fran was in truth a
distinguished witch from another country.
That was the first I'd heard of it.
Then what brought you here?
There was someone I was hoping to meet.
Who would that be?
And were you able to?
I'd love to take my time and talk with you more,
but there are many people
awaiting my return back home.
Farewell, Elaina.
I hope we'll meet again someday.
Me too!
Farewell, Teacher!
Father, Mother,
I've become a witch.
Please let me embark on my journey now.
There's no need to be hasty, is there?
Have you made up your mind?
Yes, of course!
Off you go, then.
All right.
But first, I want you to promise me three things.
First: That when faced with danger, you flee at once.
Second: To not believe that you are special.
Remember that you're equal to everyone else.
Third: To come home someday and
let us see you happy and healthy.
Can you keep them?
Yes!
D-Do you really have to go?
Her mind's made up.
Let's see her off with a smile, okay?
Really, dear.
If a little trip has you bawling like this,
I worry for the day she'll return with a spouse.
It looks very becoming on you.
You don't think it's a little plain?
As illusions start to gain colour and shapes
irodorarete ikeba gensou ga
On the contrary, it suits a traveller just right.
While they slowly start to become real
katachi aru mono ni naru you ni
Take this too, just in case.
But isn't it identical to the one I'm wearing?
I will give them form
egaite yukeru
It's good to have a spare in case
the wind blows one away.
And grant their wishes
kanaete yukerunda
A spare!
As the gently blowing wind
yasashiku fuita kaze ga
That's right.
Thank you, then. I'll take it.
Stirs the pages of an aged book
furui page mekuru you ni
And one more thing.
I may turn back now and then
furikaeru kedo
A diary?
But rest assured, it will be all right
uun ii no yo
Tales of meeting and parting once more
shiranai koto darake no
Keep a diary of your travels, just like Nike.
And when you come back home,
tell us all about them.
All so full of new, yet-unexplored things
deai wakare no hanashi
Then I'll gladly take it too.
I gently brushed the words set down in blurry ink
nijimu ink wo sotto nazotta
Look forward to the tales of
the Ashen Witch's adventures!
I will.
Where are you going to?
doko iku no
Somewhere just a little far away
sukoshi tooku made
Have a safe journey, Elaina.
Let the things I left behind turn into dreams
oitekita mono wa yume ni
I'll be going now!
Choosing what I like best, and in the process
suki dakara erabu erabinagara
And with that, I set off on my journey,
heading wherever the wind and
my own fancy carried me,
Slowly growing into myself
watashi ni natte yuku
travelling here and there and seeing many
new things over the past three years of travel.
"Oh, do let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
"And make it a promise, too!"
yakusoku dakara
You said to me, grinning from ear to ear
anata wa sou hohoenda
Now then, here's a question for you.
Who might that witch be,
"Yes, let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
the sight of her as she flies over the stark
mountain range lovely enough to take your breath away?
"And, linking fingers, seal our vow!"
koyubi wa majinai
As I heard a voice calling to me
dareka no koe ga shite
I opened my eyes
me ga sameta
Why yes, that would be eighteen-year-old me!