Thanks, Mister!
Yer welcome, missy!
Kohaku!
I'm finally back, Mom!
Oh wow, I really missed
that motherly smell of yours!
You really took me by surprise,
telling me at the very last moment.
And you must be my precious little granddaughter.
Nice to have you, Hitomi.
Grandma...
Many nights I felt like I'd lost my sense of self, my heart and soul
Many nights I felt like there was no love left for me anymore
I wanted to see the world clearly as the sun rose
But I've come to doubt even my own hopes
It was so bright, so dazzling, blinding me from the world around me
I couldn't even tell what colors your feelings were
As the seasons change, and people change with them
We all run through life to not miss this chance
It might be so far, so distant from here
Yet our feelings become one in this wish
We're running to find what our lives can become
Like the clouds parting to reveal a rainbow in the sky
Looks like Tsukishiro's back!
That girl?
It's the Crazy Mage!
The Evil Witch!
What's with those names? This isn't an RPG.
She's totally the final boss.
Things are gonna start to get interesting.
May I have your attention, please!
I brought back tea leaves as souvenirs for everyone!
Pick whichever one you fancy.
The infamous Tsukishiro brought these back for us?
Earl Grey's my favorite!
Hey, should you really be taking ten of them?
I'm not falling for this.
Here you go!
You get one too!
Looking forward to being classmates for the year!
Y-You too.
Hey, what kind of magic did you learn there?
Show us, Kohaku.
Sorry, but I'm not the same person I used to be.
I learned that you mustn't
use your powers recklessly.
You're staying with Kohaku, aren't you, Hitomi?
Yes.
Well either way, you're going to be
an amazing mage in the future.
Oh, not at all...
But it's really sad that we don't
get to see your magic anymore.
Yeah, it really brightens our day.
I know, right?
I mean, if you put it that way, how could I say no?
Ahem.
Magic must only be used
to bring blessings to the people.
Hitomi! Gimme a hand over here!
Is this okay?
Perfect! Now, don't move a muscle.
Gueas Agas Soras,
Wrath of the Wind, Shower of the Light!
A sight trapped within the photo,
as I command, appear before me!
Wow...
It's beautiful!
Where are we?
England.
The school I was studying at.
Oh, the magic school?
It feels like a movie.
Wow.
It's on a whole different level to mine.
Huh?
Can you hear something?
What's that sound?
Letter of Apology
Nagasaki Prefecture,
...Minamigaoka High School
Tsukishiro Kohaku
Year 2 Class 7
I, Tsukishiro Kohaku, used magic without getting permission from
my teacher, violating the agreement I signed, and brought the
scenery from a picture into the classroom. Unable to control my
own magic, I damaged public property and property belonging to
the school. I also put the people around me in danger and
caused them a lot of trouble. I deeply regret this and I have
reflected on my actions. I have received multiple warnings
concerning my usage of magic, but failed to heed them, resulting
in the current situation. I realize the fault is fully on me being
an inexperienced mage. From now on, I will ensure that it does
not happen again, and I will put in as much effort as possible to
become a mage who brings people happiness instead. Once again,
I offer my sincerest apologies.
My, I wasn't expecting to receive this so soon.
Same!
Oh.
Would you like some souvenirs, Vice Principal—
Harmony
No, thank you.
Souvenirs—
Kohaku's a very fun person, isn't she?
That was the first time I've seen that spell.
You can't buy it at the magic shop.
Yeah, me too.
I like cute spells.
I'm a bit jealous of those who can use magic.
Hitomi, let's go home together!
Sorry, I have club activities now.
Hitomi joined our Photography and Art Club.
Oh, really?
Fire
Hydrant
Over here, Asagi!
Sorry for being late.
It's okay.
Huh? Why are you here, Kohaku?
Who?
She's a mage in her second year.
You're related to Hitomi, right?
Yeah. I tagged along to take a look at the club.
Do you usually have your club activities here?
Of course not. This place is run by Chigusa's Family.
Since Aoi and Chigusa work here,
sometimes we just hold our meetings here.
Without paying, of course.
Welcome.
I'll have the baked cheesecake
set with a tangerine juice.
I'll also have the same.
Me too.
I'll have a castella with a herbal tea, please.
Right away.
On today's agenda is deciding what we're
going to display at the cultural festival.
I was talking with Yuito the
other day, and we thought that
doing an exhibition every year was a bit boring.
So we were thinking that this
time we'll decide on a theme
and make a work incorporating
both photography and fine art.
How about we choose our favorite locations,
and visit each of them for photo shoots?
As long as they're within walking distance.
What theme are you thinking
for the photo shoot, Shou?
Good question.
How about some night shots?
But we're always looking at those.
Even if the scenery's mundane,
taking a photo might let you find something new.
Something new, huh?
In night shots?
If we take the shots in monochrome,
the bright colors will all just be white.
They won't be as overpowering,
and we might see things differently.
Come on, won't it be the same
no matter who takes the shot?
Yeah, they come out pretty good in auto mode.
Well, since you're in the Photography Club,
shouldn't you start with how to press the shutter?
So expensive!
All right, it's decided then.
For starters, let's get permission
from the school to do the night shoot.
Is it okay if I come as well?
As long as you promise not to do
anything that would require us
to write a letter of apology, then sure.
Huh? How did you know about that?
The news has already spread throughout the school.
The only one who doesn't know is you.
Grandma's so amazing.
She's already friendly with everyone.
Hey!
I've got a camera at my place.
Would you like to come over?
The other day, you said you wanted to take
monochrome photos, right, Tsukishiro?
Yes.
No, I didn't.
Oh right, you're both Tsukishiro.
Talk about confusing...
Kazano Photo Studio
Feel free to use this.
Is that all right?
Needing to get permission to use the school's
camera outside is really inconvenient, isn't it?
When I first got into photography,
I borrowed a camera from here too.
Dad always scolded you
for breaking the camera, though.
Thank you.
I'll be very careful with it.
We thought it would be a good idea
to have you get used to
the camera before our shoot.
Do you know how to use it?
N-No.
Wow!
In that case, I'll start with the simplest parts.
So cute!
The camera you're holding is a basic one.
He's our mascot. His name is Choco.
Basically all it does is takes photos.
So fluffy! I'm so jealous! I wanna cuddle him!
I know, right?
I see.
Sometimes we bring him over,
so please do come and see him.
Don't worry too much about the complex stuff.
It's important to actually start taking photos.
I found this while cleaning your room.
Career Path Questionnaire
Are you really going straight to the workforce?
Should I not?
I'm not saying you shouldn't,
but didn't you want to go to an art college?
It's not like I want to become an artist or anything.
Career Path Questionnaire
Year         Class           Name
Further Study
Employment
Other
Further Study
Ranking
Details
First
Second
Third
I see...
And you don't know what
you're gonna do from here on out?
Yeah.
Do the others know about your color-blindness?
But y'know, don't you think it's a little exciting
when you don't know what the future holds for you?
Huh?
Let's figure it out together!
If we help each other out as two fellow mages,
something might come out of it.
I can't use magic as well as you think I can.
That's not true!
The locomotive this morning was all your doing.
Huh?
It was in the album.
That locomotive... it was this photo, right?
I think you have some hidden powers.
But it seems like your magic has lost its way.
Ahem... By the way, I... um...
Wh-What kind of person did I marry?
Oh, you mean Grandpa?
Actually, I take it back!
I just said how exciting it is when you
don't know what the future holds, so...
I'll forge my own future!
You really are my grandma.
Will you please stop calling me "Grandma", Hitomi?
Call me Kohaku!
Episode 4
Stop Calling Me Grandma!
Good evening!
That bag is huge!
Kohaku, don't demolish the school, please.
Yessir!
Oh, school at night seems cool.
That reminds me, didn't our school have this
big ghost incident prior to its construction?
Huh? What? Don't tell me that now!
I heard about that!
The rooftop of the old school building, right?
Quite a lot of people saw something there...
it's a famous rumor.
Um, the rooftop?
Prez, is today's photo shoot...
It's the view from the rooftop.
But the story goes that it was before construction.
There was a high school girl who went missing
Fire Hydrant
and is now a ghost looking
for a "home" or something.
Fire Hydrant
Booooooooooo...
Oh...
Kohaku, stop!
Dang, you got me.
I think... I'll pass on the roof.
What?
You're way too chicken.
And whose fault is that?
Boo...
What are we gonna do for the shoot, then?
I guess I'll leave it to you guys?
But wouldn't it be scarier to stay behind all alone?
Y-You're right...
Chigusa, stay with her.
Huh?
It's your fault she's scared.
Damn, I drew the short straw.
Here.
Thank you.
Isn't this nighttime view of the city just so beautiful?
I thought that when I came back, too.
Yeah.
How does it look to you, Hitomi?
It's very similar, but slightly different.
It's slightly different, but very similar.
What's that supposed to mean?
You should try your best, too.
Can I really do this?
How's it going? Think you got it?
That camera's a basic model,
and it's easy for night shots to come out blurry,
so use this tripod.
If you increase the ISO sensitivity too much,
it might get too noisy.
Keep it low to increase the exposure.
Oh, you can set the depth by using this dial.
Okay.
Want one?
Oh, thank you!
.Potato
Chips
Otter March
Wow, you brought so many snacks!
Popocky is Hitomi's favorite, you see.
Is that right, Tsukishiro?
Y-Yes.
No, not me but Hitomi—
Oh...
Right, you're both Tsukishiro.
May I have one?
Sure, go ahead. I'll pour some tea.
This is rather confusing.
How about we call them by their first names?
B-But...
No need to hold back.
Okay, then...
H-Hitomi and Kohaku.
Your face is all red, Shou.
Try saying it yourself! It's super embarrassing!
It'll be fine once you get used to it.
Potato
Chips
Please do.
Potato
Chips
Kohaku and...
Tsukishiro.
What was that?
Why just me?
We just need to differentiate, right?
That's true, but...
Ah, this place looks pretty nice!
Huh? What part of this is nice?
We can't even see anything.
Let's go to the rooftop.
No way in hell.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say you were making excuses to be here
alone with me, my adorable little Kurumi.
Are you an idiot? Why would I want that?
Can I take a picture of your ear?
You're taking your fetish photos too far now.
Huh? But it's so cute...
Is that supposed to be a compliment?
Or are you just an idiot?
I feel like continuing with scary stories now.
No! Just stop!
Ow! Ow, ow, ow! Ow!
I'd like to capture both the city and the stars.
It'll be titled
"The Constellations of Heaven and Earth".
But there's a big difference in brightness,
so we need to alter the
exposure time for each of them.
And then, the girl—
Stop! No!
Ow, ow, ow!
Oh my! Just say it already!
Did you take a nice picture?
Um... It came out like this.
Monochrome pictures
have this special vibe to them.
For me, it's the same as always,
so I don't really understand.
Monochrome photos are similar
to ink wash paintings.
I feel like the lack of color allows the
imagination of the viewer to fill the gaps.
Having less colors makes you
understand other things better.
Um... I'm looking forward
to seeing your new drawing.
Sure.
What happened?
It appeared!
There was something!
We got one! A ghost photo!
No! No! No!
Show us!
I-It was right in front of us!
It's definitely a ghost! No doubt!
It was floating!
Like that?
This is the ghost from Halloween.
It's a very basic magical prank.
Kohaku's magic?
It was a prank?
I was so scared...
It felt like a test of courage.
Sorry.
We said we didn't want to have to
write any apology letters, remember?
Wasn't this a bit too much, Grandma?
Magical pranks are a bit...
Why?
We shouldn't just use magic as we please.
If it makes everyone happy, what's the harm?
Huh?
Get up already, Granny.
Sorry, dears.
All I want is to see their smiles.
I want to bring smiles to
everyone's faces with my magic.
After all, the gods gifted me with these powers.
I must repay the favor to the world.
I can't think of it that way.
I don't like magic—
You'll come to like it someday.
After all, you're my grandchild.
She just said "grandchild".
Grandchild?
What's going on?
Why don't you explain it to them?
But...
It's all right. There's no need to be scared.
They'll definitely accept you.
I-I...
came from the future.
Huh?
The future?
Really?
How far in the future?
S-Sixty years.
That's quite some magic.
I know, right?
Seems I'll be that powerful of a mage in the future!
So magic can do even things like that?
Yeah, I'm surprised.
I thought she transferred
here like a normal student.
But is it all right to keep it a secret from the school?
Yeah, she might attract a lot
of attention if others learn about this.
It's not exactly an everyday thing.
That's right. Bad guys might even come after her.
What do you mean, "bad guys"?
Dunno, maybe like someone from the
Twins Research Institute or some secret organization?
You've been watching too many movies lately!
Anyway, it's okay if we keep everything
the same as before, right?
Yes.
I've always thought of magic
as more like, cute little things.
Just like the stardust from the magic shop.
Well, magic is supposed
to bring a little joy to people.
You're right that they might not be
the most useful of spells, though.
A small, gentle spell is enough.
After that, Grandma and I worked together
to create a flying train in the night sky.
And finally, we captured it in a photo.
That was so pretty!
Thank goodness!
It was really pretty, but you know...
Huh?
I didn't say anything,
since I wasn't sure how you'd react.
I wonder what kind of person you are in sixty years.
You are who you are.
A pretty old lady, of course!
Lady, you say?
Not being able to call someone
by their name is so childish.
People might take it the wrong way.
Especially girls like Hitomi.
What are you looking at?!
Hey, calm down.
It's really late, so be quiet.
Is she going to go back someday?
I don't know... yet.
But sixty years is quite something, don't you think?
Yeah...
Those are some really nice pictures.
We're gonna merge them with
Aoi's drawing and make a poster.
Huh? Why's there a photo of an ear?
Oh, that's one of my interests, you see.
Which drawing are you planning to add to it?
Delete it immediately.
What?
I'm still thinking about it.
Ah, is this the photo of the ghost?
Yeah, I was so scared.
Wait, this photo... I don't remember it.
Something like this.
Oh, special effects? That's pretty interesting!
What?
I'm joking!
That settles it! I'll be joining as
the sole member of the Magic Club!
The Magic Club?
Yeah, last time there was some trouble
and it ended up being disbanded.
If I'm with you guys,
I can probably get that decision revoked.
Of course, I'll help out with photography events.
We're always happy to have new members.
It'll be fun to take photos like last time as well.
Then it's decided!
Together, we're the
Magic, Photography and Art Club!
Huh? Why is magic at the front?
Once I've climbed up the hill overlooking the twilit town
Expanding before me was a scenery out of a dream
A moment so fleeting yet special
It was all like a gentle spell
Magic caressing my skin, whispering into my heart
I felt frozen in time, left behind by this vivid world of colors
And yet this scenery was like an echo of the future
Even if I were to drown
In my monotonous life slipping from out under my feet
As long as I embraced this ever unchanging world
The distance between us would surely close
Romance is the worst.
Wait, are you serious?
It seems like mages fight
over the same things we do.
What are you talking about?
But everyone's here.
I wonder why.
I'm the one who decides my own future.
I can't do it.
Episode 5
A Gentle Recipe