You're...
The intruder...
U-Um... Did you draw that picture?
Huh?
Oh, uh...
Could I possibly get you to show it to me again?
Um, hold up...
More importantly, what were you doing
sneaking into someone's house?
N-No, I wasn't...
Not to mention this.
That... belongs to me.
It was lying in my room.
I-I'm very sorry. I can explain.
"Trespassing into someone's
house without sufficient cause
may result in up to three years' hard labor or a fine
of up to one hundred thousand yen," is what it says.
Would you even believe me
if I tried to explain the situation...?
I'm happy to listen if you
do have a legitimate reason.
It's because of magic.
Huh?
Many nights I felt like I'd lost my sense of self, my heart and soul
Many nights I felt like there was no love left for me anymore
I wanted to see the world clearly as the sun rose
But I've come to doubt even my own hopes
It was so bright, so dazzling, blinding me from the world around me
I couldn't even tell what colors your feelings were
As the seasons change, and people change with them
We all run through life to not miss this chance
It might be so far, so distant from here
Yet our feelings become one in this wish
We're running to find what our lives can become
Like the clouds parting to reveal a rainbow in the sky
My Grandma just suddenly told me to go,
then I boarded a strange bus,
and before I knew it, I was in that room.
All I knew was I had to
figure out what was happening.
To be honest, I still have no idea why I'm here...
Um, so... This probably makes no sense...
but magic's to blame for me being in your room.
I'm very sorry for all the trouble I've caused.
It's fine.
A-Are you sure?
Nothing was stolen, so no harm done.
I am truly sorry.
Well, just be careful from now on.
That said, can you even really
be careful when it comes to magic?
I-I'm not sure...
It was my first time dealing with it.
I don't really understand the situation
with you mages, but just be more careful.
I understand.
Bye.
W-Wait...
I wanted to know more about his drawing.
Battery at critical levels.
Please bring into charging range as soon as possible.
I wonder why I was able to see the colors just then.
The azurite will go into standby mode now.
I'm... I'm back.
Welcome back.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Not really. I just feel like
I got out of an interrogation.
What do you mean?
Anyway, I managed to find my azurite.
It really does look like it's been
passed down from our family.
Sorry about the wait.
Please, take your time and enjoy.
Aoi, tell me more about your girlfriend!
Huh?
Why was your girlfriend escaping
from the window yesterday?
She's not my girlfriend.
Then why?
"Magic's to blame" or something.
Well... I'm not really following at all.
That makes two of us.
Come on, stop making such bad excuses.
Your girlfriend is really cute.
I said, she's not—
And here I thought you were only into drawings.
Look, she's—
Oh, come on, no need to be embarrassed.
Let me get a photo of her next time, okay?
I want her to model—
I was able to get in touch with Kohaku!
With Grandma?
Oh, right. She's your grandma
60 years in the future, isn't she?
This is how she looks now.
This is Gran—Kohaku?
She said she's going to cut her overseas
studies short and try to get back soon.
She's dying to meet you.
Anyway, until then you'll be staying with us.
Thank you.
I don't even know how to go back,
or what I'm going to do now...
Don't worry, when the time comes, you'll know.
How much magic do you know?
I don't really like magic...
I haven't practiced for a while.
Oh, that's a shame.
The letter even said that you were very talented.
No matter how hard you train,
you won't learn much if you don't like it.
In any case, there was nothing in the letter
about how to return to the future.
In order to return home,
you might be required to learn a powerful spell.
As important as magic is, you are in high school,
so how about just going to school for now?
I agree. You mustn't neglect your education.
I'll prepare the transfer letter right away.
How about Kohaku's school, Minamigaoka?
Mornin'.
Morning.
I really should have made
my reluctance more clear...
Am I really going?
Don't worry, that blazer looks very smart on you.
I've already explained to the teachers
that you're a relative of ours
and you're here to learn about magic.
Here, your lunch.
See you later!
I know, right?
With our club activities...
Ha! What's with him?
I was first today!
I just want to be alone...
What did I even come here for?
And with that said, I hope you'll have an
enjoyable and fulfilling time here at our school.
Yes, sir.
And just before you go, if we could
get you to sign that document, please.
Agreement relating to damage of personal property caused by magic
.I, Tsukishiro Hitomi, in accordance with transferring to Minamigaoka High School,
pledge to adhere to the following rules:
"Agreement relating to damage
of personal property caused by magic..."
Basically, unlike Kohaku, we'd like you
not to set off fireworks in the schoolyard,
freeze the pool solid or blow up
the walls during science experiments.
Kohaku's mother comes over often to apologize.
We hope you won't be as reckless as her.
And that's why she'll be staying at
Tsukishiro's place to learn more about magic.
Tsukishiro Hitomi
A relative, which means...
Be sure to give her a warm welcome.
She's also a mage, right?
Play with fire and you'll get burned.
You said it!
Tsukishiro Hitomi
I'm Tsukishiro Hitomi. A pleasure to meet you all.
It's her...
Let's have the person next to you share
his book with you for today, Tsukishiro.
Y-Yessir!
F-Feel free...
Thank you.
He seems to be keeping his distance.
Oh, you're the girl from before.
What a coincidence that we're in the same class.
I'm Kasano Asagi.
You can call me Asagi.
Nice to meet you.
Is it okay if I call you Hitomi?
S-Sure.
Is something bothering you?
That's...
weird.
What's weird? The board?
Um...
I felt like the person next to me
was keeping his distance.
Oh, that's probably because
they heard you're a mage.
Here, I'll show you some of
the photos from our first year.
This one was Kohaku flying
through the ceiling on a broom,
this one's her ramming into and breaking the board,
and here she destroyed the
doorway of the O'Free hall.
No way...
Sometimes our Kohaku just goes a bit overboard.
We've all been together since first year, so it's not
hard to see why some people are scared of mages.
So that's why...
But don't worry, most people will
get along fine with you, I'm sure.
Oh, we can have lunch together, if you want.
I'll go grab an O'Free.
Me too.
Aoi, I got a juicy scoop!
Look!
You're right! It's Yuito's girlfriend!
She's not my girlfriend.
Don't get all flustered now.
Hey, introduce us to her, yeah?
As I already said, you're mistaken.
What are you guys doing here?
What about you, Kurumi? What are you doing here?
I heard from Asagi.
Aoi's girlfriend transferred to our school.
I wanna know more!
No way! I'm gonna grab a rice ball, then.
Hello! It's me from before!
Do you remember us?
Yes. Thank you so much for your help.
I'm Kawai Kurumi, a third year student
who's also in the Photography Club with Asagi.
This is our President, Yamabuki Shou,
and Fukazawa Chigusa
here is a first-year student.
Hey there!
Oh, could I get you to model for my—
And last but not least!
Thanks for taking care of our Yuito.
Um... Thank you for the other day...
You're welcome.
Huh? Why are you guys speaking
as though you don't know each other?
Because we don't know each other.
She said she just somehow ended up
in my house because of magic.
Again with the excuses. Just admit
that she's your girlfriend already, Yuito.
No way! Those two are going out?
Isn't he that good-for-nothing
guy from the Art Club?
I heard he was only interested in drawings.
That girl only just transferred
today and he's already...
Man's got guts, hitting on a mage.
Hey, sorry to bother you, but...
Yes?
Could you do me a favor?
Wh-What is it?
Will you show us your magic?
No one believes me when I say that
you just somehow ended up in my room.
Surely it's troublesome for you, too?
You only just transferred here and
there are already rumors about you.
I'd feel bad for you if the
misunderstanding isn't cleared up.
You can use magic, right?
I don't mean to doubt you,
but I'm still not fully convinced...
Will you believe me if I show you my magic?
Of course.
I'll give it a go, then.
Did you hear that?
She's going to perform magic.
So she can use magic after all!
Hey, sounds like the new girl's
gonna perform some magic.
Seriously?
Are we gonna have another
hole blown in the ceiling?
But doesn't it sound interesting?
I-I'll conjure some stars.
Let this light illuminate the land,
as though it were the stars!
Huh? Was that it?
It's quite different from Kohaku's magic.
I got excited over nothing.
Wasn't that just like this stardust?
This one looks way better!
I know, right?
I think it was wonderful.
I mean, the classroom's still intact.
It was cute.
You say something too, Yuito.
Huh... Why me?
I can't do much more than that.
I'm sorry.
Oh, she ran away.
Episode 2
I Hate Magic
Nothing's changed. I hate magic.
Hitomi!
So you were here, Hitomi.
Sorry things got a bit awkward up there.
You even went and showed us your magic, and yet...
No, it's not your fault...
To make up for it... here!
Is this what O'Free looked like in the past?
The past?
It's tasty.
You can come and watch our club activities
after school if you want, Hitomi.
I'm always welcoming to new club members,
so feel free to take a look around.
You're a bit lonely 'cause you
don't know anyone else, right?
Visitor number one has arrived!
Oh, Tsukishiro, was it?
Welcome.
S-Sorry to interrupt.
No need to be so tense.
We're not super strict about our club activities.
What she said. It's just the four of us, plus Yuito.
Basically, we just take photos for fun.
We usually go out to the suburbs to take some photos,
hold a camp during summer break,
or organize the graduation album
as some of our activities.
But the biggest event of the year is probably
the unveiling of the Fall Cultural Festival Display.
This is the dark room.
Our Prez loves traditional film photography.
Here we can develop our own photos.
Though we can't do anything
besides monochrome ones.
Monochrome...
Do you like cameras, Hitomi?
Well, I don't really know anything...
Asagi's family runs a photo studio
and Yamabuki works there.
They're both very smart,
so feel free to ask them anything.
Yeah, you can depend on us.
And by the way, Chigusa here is the son
of the owner of where Aoi works,
and he's been coming here regularly
even before he was a first year.
My photography skills are better than Kurumi's,
so if you model for me I'll make sure—
Cut it!
That was quite the expression
you had there, Kurumi!
Hey, delete that right away!
Don't mind them. It's always like this.
After this, as our kind of extra-curricular activity,
we're going to just wander around—
Is something the matter?
Oh, um... no.
Are you maybe looking for Yuito?
He's the only one in the Art Club,
and we as the Photography and Art Clubs
are using the club room together.
It makes it feel like we're in the same club.
Is he working today?
Hm... dunno.
He's probably on the rooftop again.
He always just disappears
somewhere when he draws.
Please keep the door closed as
cats may enter the D wing
Not coming along with us, Hitomi?
Maybe next time.
Well then, see you later.
Again with the bugs?
They're cute.
I don't see it.
So in the end, were those two dating or not?
Seems like it was a misunderstanding.
It'd be fun if Hitomi joined our club!
Yeah, it would.
Oh, I ran out of film.
Sorry, I'm going to go and grab
some film from the club room.
I want to see those colors again.
U-Um...
S-Sorry for disturbing you...
It's okay.
What are you doing here?
I-I was looking for you.
Huh? Me?
I'm very sorry about what happened earlier.
I'm not very good at magic.
But I really wanted to make you believe me.
I don't know what you think of me,
but that's the best I can do for now.
I should apologize too.
Huh?
I mean, I made you do something
you didn't want to. I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
I had an ulterior motive.
Huh?
I want you to show me your drawing!
The one from before?
Yes.
I don't really like showing them to others.
That drawing holds something very special for me.
It showed me the colors
I thought I had long forgotten.
It brought light into my
gray world for a brief moment.
Please. Just once more.
Will this do?
Thank you very much.
Finished?
Yes. Thank you very much.
I'm sorry for bothering you.
Hey!
Um... uh... well...
Could you show me your magic again?
I think conjuring stars and stuff is pretty amazing.
It's much more impressive
than my drawing. It really is.
You don't have to show me right now.
I never thought someone would ever say that to me.
Could you show me your magic again?
I never thought someone would
ever be happy to see my magic.
I... hate magic.
Once I've climbed up the hill overlooking the twilit town
The scenery was like something out of a dream
And you were trying to capture it
Magic brushed against my ears
Whispering into my heart
Feeling frozen in time
Left behind by this vivid world of colors
But the future comes like the rain
Chasing, blurring my path forward
I nearly drown in its puddles of monotony
I wish tomorrow never changes
So I embrace the life I have today
Hoping to close the distance between us
I see one! A cute girl!
Hm? Did you mean me?
No way! No, no, no!
In the end, we still have zero new members.
Could you... not tell?
How did you...
It's definitely the power of magic, isn't it?
Episode 3