I'm pleased to announce that the inclusion of
the Magic Club has been approved without issue!
Art Classroom
Congratulations!
So does that mean "Magic, Photography
and Art Club" is the official name now?
That's long! Even longer
than Sri Jayawardenepura Kotte!
Still not as long as the official name of Bangkok.
Wait, seriously?
I'm super happy to finally be able
to start club activities with you guys!
Official name of...
Oh, it really is!
Krungthepmahanakhon Amonrattanakosin...
Our high school lives should really
be enjoyed together with friends!
Therefore! I have a proposal!
Let's throw a party to celebrate
our fresh beginnings!
Oh yeah! Let's do it!
Hold yer horses! What about the budget?
We can bring our own food.
And we can do it at my place.
That sounds like a lot of fun!
If you don't need to budget,
then it's all okay on my end!
I'll ask my parents and let you guys know
in the group chat on the Honey app thingy.
Sounds great! I can't wait!
Well then, let's get to work.
Starting today, we'll be teaching the newbies
how to use the chemicals in the dark room.
The Magic Club is off to do
field fortune telling, then!
What's that?
Many nights I felt like I'd lost my sense of self, my heart and soul
Many nights I felt like there was no love left for me anymore
I wanted to see the world clearly as the sun rose
But I've come to doubt even my own hopes
It was so bright, so dazzling, blinding me from the world around me
I couldn't even tell what colors your feelings were
As the seasons change, and people change with them
We all run through life to not miss this chance
It might be so far, so distant from here
Yet our feelings become one in this wish
We're running to find what our lives can become
Like the clouds parting to reveal a rainbow in the sky
Hey, what will you ask about?
It's a secret!
Your good luck charm is an hourglass​.
\ Ask me anything /
Field!
Love Fortune Telling
With Magic
Field!
Love Fortune Telling
With Magic
If you write the name of your crush using a pink pen,
your luck with relationships will go up!
Really?
According to the fortune, now's your chance!
Just be confident in yourself and you'll be fine!
Thank you very much!
Next customer please!
Um, excuse us...
We're just here to see how everything's going!
There's a huge line outside. Great job!
Thanks.
Since we're already here, why don't you
tell us our romantic fortunes as well?
How's that sound, Asagi?
I-I don't really...
A-And then?
O Light, shine!
O Orb, tell me!
Ha!
No—
"No"?
N-No...
No foreseeable problems if you just use your bunny!
What...
Are you trying to pull a fast one on us?
Is Asagi's romantic luck really that bad?
Um...
Do you want the honest truth?
Y-Yes, please.
If you stay on your current path,
you'll have terrible luck.
"A rival shall appear and his
feelings for you shall fade", it says.
Well, I wouldn't worry too much!
Next! My turn!
Tell me whether I can get a boyfriend!
Ah, probably not.
Come on, just tell my fortune!
Looky over here!
Kazano Photo Studio
All right, one more.
Thank you very much.
Excellent job, Shou.
Oh, not at all.
If anything, I'm the one getting
to learn a lot of things here.
Dad, I'm going to borrow your computer for a bit!
Sure, go ahead.
Oh, nice shot.
You think so?
Always with the bunnies, huh?
I like them a lot.
It's such a waste of your talent that
you don't show off your pictures more.
It's embarrassing...
Why don't you try hanging them in the
studio or printing them on postcards?
You never know until you try.
Pretty please, Hitomi?
Look after the store?
Sorry, but there's somewhere I just gotta be!
B-But I've never worked at a store before...
Perhaps I should just stay instead, Hitomi?
Oh, no, I...
I guess a while won't hurt...
Thanks a million, Hitomi!
Sorry about this, but we'll be back before dark.
See ya later!
I'm worried about her.
It feels like we left a dog all alone.
It'll be fine! Worse comes to worse,
Grandma'll be there to help her.
石橋
Ishibashi
Hm, I guess you're right.
石橋
Ishibashi
I'll have the usual one, please.
The "usual one"?
That's right. The red stardust.
The red...
The one that gives you nostalgic dreams.
Oh!
Batch number 17,
nostalgic-dream-inducing stardust, all done!
Thank you very much.
Are you all right?
Yes. Somehow.
Do look through the catalog
if there's anything you don't know.
Thanks, I'll do that.
Do you know where Gran—um, Kohaku went?
She went to take a look at some old magic books.
There's actually a shop which lends such books.
Yanagidou Used Magic Bookstore
Used Books
Rental Books
She seems to be studying magic even
more passionately since you came here.
She was saying she has a feeling
that she'll need her magic one day.
She was?
I'll also do my best with the shop!
Oh.
You guys have so many types of stardust!
There's even more you can order if you
need something specific to your needs.
It feels like a pharmacy.
Kohaku always says that stardust is like
a supplement for putting more
color into your everyday life.
Really?
My friend is opening an exhibition soon.
Is there anything you'd recommend as a gift?
In that case, I have some stardust
that brings you the scent of a forest...
Would that be fine?
Sounds good. I'll have that, then.
I'll gift wrap it for you!
How's your new drawing coming along?
Ah, well,
I've been having a bit of artist's block lately.
If only there were a type
of stardust that helps with drawings.
Please wait!
This one?
No, this one should be better...
But maybe this one...
Don't worry about it. I wasn't being super serious.
I'm sorry. I'll do a proper search later.
Hm... is that what happened?
Can you help me find the right spell?
Oh my, are you actually being
positive towards magic for once?
I mean, being able to see a drawing full of colors
is something I myself care about as well.
Is that all, now?
And I hear you're putting a lot
of effort into learning magic too.
I see, I see.
Then why not go try making stardust yourself?
Huh?
Would this be your first time
making stardust, Hitomi?
I'm sure you'll be able to do it as long
as you practice and get the hang of it.
I can't—
Don't wanna hear it!
Weren't you the one who said
it's something you care about?
I'll give it a try.
Attagirl!
W-Wait!
Now that's my granddaughter!
What are you—
You can face any challenge!
It's okay to fail.
Good girl! There, there!
I can face any challenge...
That was quite a line!
I know, right? It went all the way to the stairs.
What are you doing, Hitomi?
U-Um, I don't know how...
Ah, how to use it?
That's all right. I'll show you.
Thank you very much.
Apparently she's never used it before.
I'm glad she managed.
What an interesting girl she is.
I usually just teach new members the basics,
but if you want to take photos in monochrome,
I think it'd be interesting to try using film.
I think we'll call it a day.
Thank you very much.
Um, is it all right if I use this room for a bit longer?
Why?
I want to practice my magic,
and a dark room would be best.
That's so cool! Is it okay if I watch?
Huh?
I guess a bit won't hurt...
Let this light illuminate the land,
as though it were the stars!
It was supposed to look like a planetarium.
Seems you still need a bit more practice.
Yes.
I have to say though, I don't remember
you being that eager to use magic.
If I'm able to bring joy
to someone through my magic,
then I might as well give it a go.
Oh? Yeah, I feel you.
When I see someone delighted by my photos,
it motivates me to try even harder.
Good luck with your practice!
Thank you.
Let this light illuminate the land,
as though it were the stars!
But I followed the recipe to the letter...
Man!
Let this light illuminate the land,
as though it were the stars!
Read
Today
Meeting ASAP!
2 pm at Magic Shop! No being
late     ty — — — — — — — — —
👍
You never know until you try.
I... can't...
Episode 5
A Gentle Recipe
Hello!
Oh, welcome.
I came by early to give you a hand.
Am I the first to come?
Yes.
Hey, Asagi,
how does this color look?
It's such a beautiful bright blue color! Stardust?
I made it myself for the very first time!
That's amazing!
I made something too!
Oh!
It's so good!
That's a relief.
You're so talented!
I've always loved baking.
Ever since I was a kid,
I've always been a bit of a wallflower.
I enjoyed being alone, so I'd always just
play house or look at photos at home.
Really?
Shou was my only friend.
Come on, Asagi! Let's go!
When I was young,
I was always dragged outside by Shou.
He's always looking out for people, that Shou!
That reminds me, he showed me
how to use the O'Free machine.
You too?
We have so much in common, don't we?
'Scuse us!
Oh wow, something smells really good!
I brought cookies.
Fresh out of the oven!
Should we lay out the food we brought?
Everything's fried...
All right, everyone. Cheers!
It's so good!
Kohaku told our fortunes!
About our... luck. In. Love!
Wait, seriously?
Wanna know?
Nope.
As if I'd tell you!
So this whole fortune telling
thing is really popular, huh?
The line was crazy long.
Oh, here.
Thank you.
So you managed to make it.
Y-Yes, last night.
Congrats! You should give it to him!
Wait, right now?
Sure, why not?
But the others are all out there.
What's wrong with that? The more, the merrier!
Oh, I see...
Oh, drats! We're all outta drinks!
Hitomi, go with Yuito and get some more!
Sorry 'bout that! Thanks!
Are we out of drinks?
It seems so.
Where's the closest store again?
You okay with taking the scenic route?
Huh?
Just in time.
How does it look to you?
Even without color, I can see how beautiful it is.
Oh, um... here!
I wasn't able to find anything good, remember?
So I made one myself instead.
I promised to find you a good spell,
so I made some stardust that conjures stars.
Try it for a change of pace.
You made this? For me?
Thank you.
I'm really looking foward...
to your next drawing.
You know, I remember you saying...
That you can only see colors in my drawings?
Yes.
That makes them really important to you, right?
I wonder why...
I've lived for so long without a sense of color.
The color of the sky, the colors of flowers,
even sunsets or rainbows.
That's why I had given up on many things.
But when I saw your drawing for the first time,
the colors burst out right before my eyes.
It was like they were trying
to remind me what they looked like.
I don't know why it's like this,
but your drawings are very important to me.
I see...
I'll try using this stardust tonight.
Do you think that in the future
you won't be using cash?
What makes you think that?
Hitomi looked really confused when
she was at the vending machine.
O'Free?
Yeah.
She's a strong girl. Getting thrown
60 years back in time must be tough.
I know, right?
Just watching her makes me want to work harder.
At what?
Like the cultural festival
or our future in general, I guess?
That's such a vague answer.
I'll be merciless when it comes to club activities.
So intense! Spare me!
You too, Asagi.
You're a senior now, so be more confident.
Try being more assertive—
You mean be like Hitomi, right?
Um... sure, something like that.
Yes, Prez.
What's wrong, Asagi?
Denser than lead.
Huh?
Shou... stuff like this is why
you'd bring fried food to the table.
What is she talking about?
Dunno.
It seems the fortune was correct.
As one would expect from the great Kohaku.
Obviously, since I'm going to be
an amazing mage in the future!
But fortunes are nothing more than hints.
You alone decide your own future, always.
I hear Hitomi made some stardust for the first time.
She's working hard as well.
She has no talent for magic,
so even creating stardust was difficult for her.
Do you want to know how many times she failed?
I approached Hitomi because
I saw a bit of myself in her.
But it's clear I was wrong.
I want to change as well.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
I don't even need to tell your fortune to see that.
What the hell!
We're all outta ingredients to make stardust!
Mom's gonna be mad—
Who's going to get mad?
Huh? Wait a minute. What happened?
Kohaku! Didn't I tell you to only use
old ingredients when you're practicing?
But it's easier to do magic
with high-quality ingredients!
You told her to use these so you
could get her to succeed quickly
and be done with teaching, didn't you?
Yes...
These ingredients don't grow on trees, you know!
Do you know how difficult
it was for me to gather them?
You're going to clean them all
to make them usable again.
What's going on?
Something about supplies.
Mages argue over the same things as we do, huh?
My sister also yells at me when
I use her expensive make-up.
So you're saying your skin's—
You say summin'?
—skin's so beautiful!
Shut yo pie hole!
Shou.
I was thinking of making bunny postcards.
That sounds like a great idea!
Will you help me with them?
Of course.
That reminds me, when we were young,
you were talking to me casually like you are now.
I stopped in middle school because
my classmates kept teasing me.
Really?
People were asking if we were dating and stuff...
Right, I remember there
being weird rumors like that.
Sorry for causing you trouble, Asagi.
It's okay. I'm used to being more distanced.
I'm fine with the ways things are.
Thanks for having us.
Later!
My back is killing me!
My hands are all black...
Keep the cost in mind when doing magic.
Do you understand?
Yes...
We're very sorry.
Oh right, did you give him the stardust, Hitomi?
Yes.
Awesome!
Well, it's really just a little something
for a change of pace, I guess.
I hope it'll help him.
o sleep,
o sleep,
Hitomi
"Please use this before you go to sleep,
but turn the lights off first."
Once I've climbed up the hill overlooking the twilit town
The scenery was like something out of a dream
And you were trying to capture it
Magic brushed against my ears
Whispering into my heart
Feeling frozen in time
Left behind by this vivid world of colors
But the future comes like the rain
Chasing, blurring my path forward
I nearly drown in its puddles of monotony
I wish tomorrow never changes
So I embrace the life I have today
Hoping to close the distance between us
Aoi's drawing...
I haven't been able to draw anything lately.
Are those... colors?
I have to tell you everything.
I came inside.
Are you all right?
I don't like scary things...
Mages are—
Don't say any more!
Just say it!
Episode 6
The Golden Fish
I wonder how I can change...