Let's see... Gotta change to the domestic
terminal at Edinburgh to get to London.
Touma...
My beef or fish was ruined
and I didn't get to eat anything!
I'm so hungry I could collapse any second!
I'm going to die if I don't eat something right now!
L-Long time no see.
Wh-Why is the sexy fallen-angel maid here?
A Certain Magical Index
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
Carrying a ticking time bomb
The Earth keeps on turning, so hurry up!
No one can pretend it's not their business anymore
Suddenly common sense is out the door
Opposing fates fail to reach each other
Drenched in the rain of resentment
But why? Fear and doubt keep building up heavy in my heart
My racing heart is flooded with ambition
Ready!
Everyone that's drawn to this place
Has gone beyond the meaning and color of desire
My heart wants to stay strong
I feel it deep inside me
With all my soul, this one thing
Dive into a heart
The Maze of Great Britain
Oh, okay.
I'm sure you're investigating a number
of things due to the recent terrorist attack,
but I ask that you deliver the liquid food
to the families in need as quickly as possible.
Princess Villian,
the heads of the Knight unit and Christian unit
and our young guests have arrived at the palace.
We will be meeting them shortly.
Please get ready.
Understood.
William...
Whoa.
Wait, why did we even get called here?
Tsuchimikado didn't tell you anything?
That was his job.
He gassed us out of nowhere
and left us at the airport—
You made it.
Knight Leader.
We're about to begin a tactical meeting
of sorts here at Buckingham Palace.
We've told people that it's an audience.
I would've preferred if you
had dressed up a little bit.
Dressed up?
Why are we having a tactical meeting?
Are we planning for something?
It has come to light that
magic may have been involved
in the Eurotunnel explosion.
Her Majesty will give you the details.
Her Majesty?
Man, putting on a dress is such a pain,
can't I just wear a tracksui—
One moment.
Hey! You could at least knock!
Allow me to apologize, but...
You were about to show up to official business
in sweats again, weren't you, you insolent hag!
I'm kinda sleepy now that I've eaten.
But this is what we came here for!
Man...
You may enter.
Queen Elizard has woken up.
A sword?
This is the sword Curtana,
a weapon held exclusively by royalty.
Thank you for visiting. Come closer.
Does that sword have some kind of crazy power?
One who wields that sword
can gain power virtually equal
to that of the seraph Michael.
Seraph?
They're the greatest and strongest of all angels.
O-Oh yeah?
But in the unfortunate event that this is destroyed,
no one would hold it against you.
You see, this is Curtana Second.
Umm, the names don't really mean anything to me.
This is a replica.
We lost the first sword,
Curtana Original, in some place or other.
Even if this one breaks, we can just make another.
Oh please, as if you could.
Although Curtana Second is indeed
a magnificently crafted copy,
the requisite knowledge to craft
such a sword has been lost.
She is the First Princess, Riméa.
If you had told me, I would have sent an escort—
No, I would have come myself.
Oh dear, this mustn't be!
What good could come of coming closer to betrayal?
I have no intention of placing
my trust in those who know of me.
Right.
Is my dear sister being a wet blanket as usual?
You may as well just leave this world
if you can't trust anyone in it.
Sister?
I'm the Second Princess, Carissa.
You should take some history lessons, boy.
Oh, you were here too, Villian?
She's my younger sister, the Third Princess.
Rather uninteresting, isn't she?
Now then, it's about time for the others to show up.
Let's escape while we can.
What?
Sometimes it's more effective to have
a short discussion in a small group.
I still don't see why I'm here...
We've got queens and princesses,
famous people I'd love to just snap a photo with.
What is it?
Didn't you want to take a picture?
CAPTURE
I can't allow you to have me,
of all people, left out of frame.
I'll have to get a little closer.
If we're doing this then I must be the one in control.
D-Don't mind me.
What do you mean by leaving me,
the lead actress, out of the photo?
Let's start with France.
What of it?
The cause of the problem
is the Eurotunnel explosion.
I have concluded that this is an act of destruction
initiated by the French government.
Based on?
Do you have any evidence?
I have summoned Index Librorum
Prohibitorum for this very reason.
She can tell us without a doubt if a French-style
Roman Catholic spell had been used.
We shouldn't think of this as a quarrel
between Britain and France.
It is a dispute between Britain and Academy City,
and Rome and Russia.
Britain is still without many allies.
That's right, but that's not the only problem.
I caught wind of an interesting fact
in the midst of the recent plane hijack.
What was it?
We had received the help of Necessarius
to resolve the incident,
but some third party interfered with their illusion.
That's not all.
This interference originated
in Scotland, a part of Britain.
So we have enemies both inside and out?
The situation between Britain and France
is already giving me a headache,
and now you're telling me we have
a separate group of terrorists within our borders?
It looks like we know who the terrorists are.
Their group is called New Light,
and they're comprised of four members.
Also, it appears they were recently
involved in some sort of excavation.
It would be reasonable
to assume that they've brought
whatever they'd dug up to London
to continue their activities.
If so, there are two things we need to do.
In order to deal with our external enemy, France,
we need to investigate the cause
of the Eurotunnel explosion.
For our internal enemies,
we must determine the affiliation and goal
of those sorcerers and deal with them as required.
I will leave the Knight unit in charge
of the Eurotunnel investigation,
and the Christian unit in charge
of the sorcerer group.
However, Index Librorum Prohibitorum
will be working elsewhere to aid our investigation.
So, what should I be doing?
Touma, you need to stop thinking you have to go
and do something whenever anything happens.
Can't we let him go?
Necessarius is lacking in manpower.
N-No!
I don't think exposing civilians
to danger is an optimal course of action.
Oh, that's right. If he's a civilian
then we can't force him to help.
Oh, sweet. I guess I'll just hang around here.
That being said,
those not serving the national interest
will be billed for their living expenses at a later date.
That's not a problem, is it?
Huh?
Come on, it's quite cheap if you just think
of it as booking two or three suites
in a gaudy five-star hotel.
It would be an honor to offer my services
to protect the peace of Britain.
Now then, is it finally time for the kick-off?
You can be the keeper, Lancis.
All good to go here!
The magic is all tickly!
In any case, we midfielders are going
to attack swiftly and settle things.
Lessar, I hope you haven't forgotten
that you're a midfielder too.
I won't let you get away with messing things up.
Don't worry.
Since we're doing this though,
I want to be a forward.
Have you already gotten the Skithblathnir ready?
We went through all the trouble of digging it up,
so we should put it in a nice case.
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
We're reforming Britain today, right?
As New Light.
Man, I didn't think you would be here.
I've had a lot going on myself, you know.
I made a bit of a deal with Britain,
so I'm helping them out now.
A Certain Magical Index
I guess I'll just carry the case to the designated
location and wait around for my next orders.
Oopsies.
Huh?
What?
This one's mine. Yours is that one.
Oh, all right.
Th-That was close.
Wait, which one is mine?
E-Everyone, hands up!
...Heading down Regent Street...
Looks like one of them messed up.
What's going on over there?
That's an explosion of suspiciousness!
Uhh, which one is it?
This one?
This one!
Let's clear away the people first.
And then one more...
Don't you think that was a bit much?
Not at all. In fact, this is kinda bad!
Hey!
You have no qualms, do you?!
Whoa!
You've gotta be kidding me...
Oh no!
I used the most important thing I had as a shield!
Hey, Orianna, she said that rectangular case
is the most important thing she has.
Oh yeah?
Don't you think it would be fun to
give it a punch with that right hand of yours,
just in case it's magical?
Oh, good idea!
I can't get taken down here!
Are you serious? We need to chase
someone that can move like that?
Not necessarily.
Help! Send help!
If worst comes to worst,
I need to make sure we activate at least one.
We are Necessarius,
the 0th parish of the Church of England.
You'll be coming with us to the Tower of London.
Would you like to hear your charges?
No, that's fine.
I don't intend to get caught
before this case is activated!
Itsuwa!
Got it!
I can sense that your spear belongs to Thor,
the god of thunder, from its magical symbol.
How simple do you need to be
to immediately assume that this is Mjölnir?
The god of thunder only once
ever used a different weapon.
This is a mystic artifact
created by dissecting that story.
One of the Steel Gloves.
It's much easier for a girl to use a weapon like this!
It's holding onto something?
Is this wind?
Dust?!
Is that all you've got?
I'd be happy to keep playing,
but I'm going to switch to Gjallarhorn.
You'd better stay down there if you
don't want to become a pile of ashes.
This can change the history of Britain.
Look forward to the change that's about to happen.
Whose orders are you taking?
France?
The Roman Catholics?
France and the Roman Catholics, huh?
Riméa isn't even coming in the end.
Did something happen to her?
She has a bit of a hard time trusting strangers.
Although France has been
involved in a series of incidents,
the Roman Catholic Church is definitely behind it all.
Is military negotiation the only
way we can speak with France?
If you want to change that,
then you'd better come up with a plan.
Riméa is the brains and I am the muscle.
Your specialty lies in your virtue.
You might be able to come up with
a more effective way of dealing with this.
You think so?
Time to focus. We're almost at Folkestone.
Damn it, this is all because Lessar
went and messed everything up!
This tunnel is supposed to be straight.
Why did I just go around a curve?
There are a number of magical
training grounds all over London.
Don't tell me!
According to our intel, New Light is a group of four.
It might be difficult for us to cope
if there's still three of them left.
I have some good news on that front.
There are only two left.
Can you be a bit less barbaric?
You don't look like a sorcerer or a Brit.
What reason do you have to pursue me?
Either way, if you're not British then you can't play!
You're disqualified!
Disqualified?
You don't need to understand.
All I can say is that we want to change the direction
Britain is going in at the very last moment.
It can't be! Reinforced glass?
I don't think I could handle a fall from this height.
What will it be, death or apprehension?
Apprehension, then?
Wait, I'm gonna die!
Wait, you're not gonna catch me?!
I'm gonna die!
That's gonna go on your performance review!
I'll get her, all right?!
Skithblathnir?
Yeah. That's what the cases they're using are called.
They can teleport the contents
of one case into any of the others.
You mean they can pass around whatever
they're carrying like a game of lacrosse?
It's probably a bomb or some other kind of weapon.
This sucks.
There are four members of New Light.
Two of them have already been taken care of.
Whatever they're transporting has to be
in one of the two remaining cases.
Hurry.
You've gotta be kidding me!
We know what you're after.
We've already caught your friends.
But you don't know where Lancis is, right?
The three of us are just relay points.
No matter who it goes through,
the plan will still succeed.
Relay points?
I'm amazed you didn't notice despite
knowing that these were mass produced.
What if there was a fifth Skithblathnir?
Who did you just send your cargo to?
Who has the fifth bag?!
Although I completed my mission,
we did lose the game.
If you want to shut me up, now is the time.
A sniper?
Orianna, call an ambulance!
Robin Hood?
What did you say?
This is a magical item used by
the Knight unit for long-distance sniping.
It was created by a unit directly under Carissa,
who is famous among military personnel.
If something like this was used
to silence New Light, then...
We were transporting Curtana Original.
The ceremonial sword
believed to be lost to the ages.
It substantially surpasses Curtana Second,
and is considered Britain's greatest mystic artifact.
It is the sword most suited to change Britain.
Inform every knight stationed across the country.
Begin the attack! Curtana Original is in our hands!
If you do not wish for your motherland
to rot away, rise up with me,
Carissa, the new head of state!
To build our new Britain, we will level the ground.
Destroy as much as need be!
When I least expect it, you're gone
And loneliness hits me hard in the chest
In the night filled with signs I look up at the stars
I bite my lip and pray
Every time the dawn comes I run to you
You try to hide behind a smile that you're covered in wounds
But I notice, because I'm not a child
I'll protect you even if I have to make an enemy of the entire world
This strength comes from the light you've given me
I don't want to just wait for a miracle
I want to start a revolution that changes who the two of us are
And this is the night before it starts
Next Time
The knights are attacking!
The chaos that ensues is put to
an end by his supreme authority.
His name is William Orwell!
Next time: "The Mercenary".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.