Inform every knight stationed across the country.
Begin the attack! Curtana Original is in our hands!
If you do not wish for your motherland
to rot away, rise up with me,
Carissa, the new head of state!
To build our new Britain, we will level the ground.
Destroy as much as need be!
The Knight unit is coming after even Necessarius.
I need to regroup with the Sisters
in the other fortress.
Oh shoot!
Witches 3 to 20 and 30 to 35, ready for takeoff.
All designated witches are to accelerate
in sequence and stop the Knight unit's attack.
What are we going to do, Smartvery?
We don't know if our attacks
will have any effect on those Knights.
I guess we'll just have to tough it out until
the Coven Compass makes it out of the country.
So we're just a decoy?
Knights sure love chasing
witches' skirts, no matter what era.
Here they come!
A Certain Magical Index
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
Carrying a ticking time bomb
The Earth keeps on turning, so hurry up!
No one can pretend it's not their business anymore
Suddenly common sense is out the door
Opposing fates fail to reach each other
Drenched in the rain of resentment
But why? Fear and doubt keep building up heavy in my heart
My racing heart is flooded with ambition
Ready!
Everyone that's drawn to this place
Has gone beyond the meaning and color of desire
My heart wants to stay strong
I feel it deep inside me
With all my soul, this one thing
Dive into a heart
The Mercenary
Our orders are to kill as few as possible,
but with this many of us duking it out,
I don't think I can guarantee that.
So you're telling us to surrender,
and no one gets hurt?
How kind of you.
You'll accept casualties, then?
What happened?
Search the area!
They can't have gone far!
Yes, sir!
I never get used to how well that works.
What are we going to do now?
Dear me.
I was planning to see Index Librorum
Prohibitorum before things came to this,
so she could analyze each of the princesses
and determine if any of them
were planning to threaten the peace.
Considering the number of knights involved,
I assume the second princess,
the military commander, is behind this?
Indeed.
I'm impressed she managed
to find the original thing.
Now this Curtana Second is pretty much worthless.
A marvelous plan, truly befitting a daughter of mine.
Stupid doting parents.
I'd love to just wring your neck, right here and now.
You will not be harmed
if you do not attempt to resist.
I trust you will choose wisely.
You guys must have it rough too.
That's not how Carissa does things.
My daughter would've given you an order more like
"If they don't listen,
then don't hesitate to kill them."
"If you decide to kill, then do so without mercy."
What?
Well then, what will it be?
They used a Roman Catholic destruction spell
based on the lore of the House of Loreto.
Is that so.
The original House of Loreto
was famously visited by Louis IX of France.
He analyzed its properties as a mystic artifact,
and now someone used that theory
to blow up the tunnel.
That's great news, for you and me both.
We now know for a fact that France
was involved in the explosion.
If you'd denied France's involvement,
I would've had to cut you down.
Issue France an ultimatum.
Then, mobilize the army and send
a destroyer squadron to Dover.
Make preparations to launch missiles
at Versailles depending on their response.
What shall we do about Academy City?
Forget them.
Our nation's military power belongs to us.
To Hell with the Church of England, Academy City,
the Roman Catholics,
the Russian Church, and their whole war.
Regardless of whether
the Magic or Science faction wins,
Britain, having dabbled in both magic and science,
will get the short end of the stick.
To only way to avoid that is to make Britain
an independent third side in this conflict.
Mother's tactics are far too spineless.
We need to win this war without external help
to ensure a bright future for our nation.
Now we need to deal with my mother and sisters.
I'd better kill them all soon, to reduce the
number of people who can wield Curtana.
As you wish.
Damn it, the Knights are everywhere.
We need to meet up with the guys
from Necessarius and get her treated soon.
The hell?
Golem Ellis?
Sherry's here?!
That sorceress is bad news.
Oh, her best friend was killed
by the Knights a long time ago.
Find a good opportunity amongst all this chaos
and take her to the Necessarius girls' dorm.
I'll knock out those knights while
they're preoccupied with the golem
and see if I can bring that
sorceress back to her senses.
Are you sure you can do all of that on your own?
I wish you'd just said "Thanks, I'll leave this to you."
Or would you prefer to leave
that girl behind and come with me?
Once you've taken her to safety,
go to Waterloo station and sneak onto the Eurostar.
The Knights should be using it
to move their units and supplies around.
What's the point of that?
That train will take you to Folkestone.
Carissa and Index Librorum Prohibitorum are there.
Thanks, I'll leave this to you, Orianna.
That's more like it. I'll take care of everything.
I was wondering how she knew to escape.
So you servants helped her flee.
She really lives up to her virtuous reputation.
Princess Villian's carriage appears to have
headed towards Canterbury via Dover.
That's where the Church of England's
public-facing headquarters are.
Not a bad idea, for my sister.
Let's go.
We don't have time to play
my foolish sister's games.
Have Villian disposed of immediately.
We're going to find where Riméa disappeared off to.
There's a plane incoming.
What?
Are they allies?
Unlikely.
We haven't received any word of reinforcements.
Let's shoot it down.
Too late. It's already here.
I doubt this will put an end to this immediately,
but I'll start by taking care of the leader.
I don't have time for you.
Allow me to handle this.
Were you trying to get me on board so incessantly
because you knew this would happen?
I truly did wish for you to spend
some time in a more ladylike manner.
However, it looks like it's too late for that.
Why are you so surprised?
This United Kingdom,
made up of Curtana and the four countries,
is bound by the rules of our
particular form of Christianity.
Within its domain, the monarch is a seraph,
and we knights are angels!
As long as we remain within this country,
even a Saint's power is no match for mine.
If there are still any Christians
left at the Canterbury Cathedral,
I have to ask them to at least save
the servants that helped me escape.
Give it up.
You can come out or stay inside,
but you're going to die either way.
Three.
Two.
One.
There's no point going to the Canterbury Cathedral.
Don't you get it?
We didn't do anything to make
you lose control of the carriage.
The Church has set up a mystic artifact
to interfere with any steering.
They've left you for dead.
No! It can't be!
It looks like this is the end.
You don't have a single ally remaining.
You're all on your own.
I've taken care of the Saint.
Nothing else stands in our way.
Then could you also take care of this?
A sword wouldn't make a very clean cut.
We should use an axe made to execute royalty.
I don't mind if you want to cry for help.
I'm sure someone around would want to.
But you'd better not get your hopes up.
Th-There's no one?
No one at all that will save me?
This is farewell.
Allow me to make one final promise.
I will do my utmost to ensure the beauty
of your head remains as it did in life,
so that those who see it will remember you.
You're back...
You're back.
You're back!
William Orwell!
Are you unhurt, princess of the realm?
You're late!
You're way too late! You ex-mercenary brute!
A Certain Magical Index
Bring me their heads.
Understood.
Bayard?
He's been set to go to Necessarius's hiding place.
Please use him.
What will you do, William?
I'll catch up with you shortly.
I'll be making some basic preparations.
Rest assured, they shall not follow you.
Are you planning to face the entire
Knight unit on your own?
Carissa has become the nation itself!
You've done enough, forget about me.
You were the only person
who ever came to save me.
That's all I'm worth.
Forget about me and take your leave.
That way, you'll be sa—
What are you doing, William?
My will to fight for you won't waver,
even if you don't believe in my strength.
Wait!
You fool!
Those words were the ones
I wanted to hear the least!
Why do you choose now,
of all times, to stand in our way?
It would make some semblance
of sense were you still a mercenary,
but what reason does
Acqua of the Rear of God's Right Seat
have to protect our nation's
third princess with his life?
So this is how it will be.
Regardless of your allegiance,
your actions remain unchanged.
I'm not surprised in the least.
Is that Hrunting?
I hold the ten years since you left in my hand.
I am no longer the man I was when
you knocked me unconscious at Dover.
How much stronger have
you grown these past ten years?
Allow me to show you what
these ten years have done for me!
I managed to leave Lessar with them
and sneak onto the train, but what now?
A patrol? I'm not about to get caught
after making it this far!
Hey.
Are you Japanese?
You don't look like one of the Knights.
Y-Yeah.
I feel like I've seen these clothes somewhere before.
Are they trending?
Help me out, then.
Huh?
I'm Floris.
I'm part of a kind of Magic Cabal.
Don't just sit there, come on.
We're almost there.
A Magic Cabal?
Wait, what did you even do
to get cuffed up like that?
Well, I don't think I did anything wrong.
Oh, these are mystic artifacts, by the way.
They won't come off unless you use the key.
What?!
Oh, uh, my right hand has this
power called Imagine Breaker.
This sorta happens to any magical item I touch.
Drop the chit-chat!
If you break them in such a crude manne—
Now what do we do?!
We're getting creamed
only ten minutes into the game!
It's too soon to give up!
Huh?
Hey, you can't be serious.
I totally am.
Are you stupid? If you want to die,
then do it in your own time!
There's a river just up ahead.
Now's our only chance to escape. Let's go!
We're really gonna die!
It's fine, we're going to land in the water!
That river is only a meter deep!
Wait, my right hand is gonn—
Hmph.
I can tell your wounds are aching with each swing.
Are you still suffering after
your loss in Academy City?
You speak quite a lot, my friend.
Are you no longer able to wield a sword and fight
without making excuses to yourself and to others?
How unfortunate.
I wish I could have fought this once-in-a-lifetime
battle with you in your best condition.
That isn't Hrunting.
You can control the patterns?
I should've expected you'd catch on this quickly.
I'd hoped to end this without having to use this.
That's quite unlike you.
Are you holding back at this
representation of the evil dragon?
Here I come!
Bring it!
What?!
Movement speed.
Weapon mass.
Cutting edge.
Attack range.
I've seen the extent of your ability.
You can't surpass my blade in your current state.
I'll give you a choice.
Cast aside your sword and leave Britain,
or fertilize Britain's soil together with your sword.
Which do you prefer?
Before I answer, allow me a question.
Do you truly think you can save this nation
by supporting the second princess
and beheading the third?
I cannot say that this course is ideal.
However, history is already in motion.
As such, my only choice is which side to take.
And I have chosen the side which
will bring the most glory to our nation!
Very well.
Flight or death—have you decided?
No, my two choices are to kill you or not to kill you.
It appears you have decided, then.
You will die here!
How was that?
I freed us from our restraints with such grandeur.
What are you talking about?!
That wasn't setting us free, it was just an explosion!
The end justifies the means.
But now the carriage is in pieces.
How are we going to keep moving?
I-I have an excellent plan.
What is it?
A-Are you really going to try it?
I've only heard of it in stories!
Tada, my brilliant hitchhiking plan!
Hey you, the driver of that filthy truck!
Would you fancy a road trip with this beautiful lady?
I'll get him for that.
Don't be stupid. He made the smart choice.
All right, let's go. To London!
You jest!
I've never done anything
as unrefined as horse-riding!
Hip hip!
Wait, are you going to just leave me here?!
Stop!
I'm not going to be able to hitchhike!
When I least expect it, you're gone
And loneliness hits me hard in the chest
In the night filled with signs I look up at the stars
I bite my lip and pray
Every time the dawn comes I run to you
You try to hide behind a smile that you're covered in wounds
But I notice, because I'm not a child
I'll protect you even if I have to make an enemy of the entire world
This strength comes from the light you've given me
I don't want to just wait for a miracle
I want to start a revolution that changes who the two of us are
And this is the night before it starts
Next Time
Its swing tears through the dimensions
and engulfs Britain in a sea of flames.
Will the sorcerers yield in the face
of such an overwhelming power?
Next time: "Curtana Original".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.