Hey, Touma, Touma!
What is it, Index?
It's been a while since we talked like this.
Yeah, you're right.
The last clip like this was a long time ago.
Why did we have so much downtime?
There's been some corporate politics and such...
Anyway, let's get on with it.
Go bald!
Go bald! Go bald! Go bald!
Ah, this brings back memories.
Take this! And this!
Ha-ha! Ha-ha-ha!
Ouch. Ouch. Ouch.
More! Have some more!
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
A Certain Magical Index-tan, Episode 6.
Thanks for paying for the bike rental.
Don't worry about it.
I received abundant funds for this mission.
Touma!
I feel like there is some ulterior motive
to this seating arrangement.
What? It's not like that at all!
I was just being chivalrous and let you
have the nicest and most thrilling seat.
No! I'm going to fall!
Here I go!
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
Who is this character?
Who's that character?!
Answer
Itsuwa
That's hot.
Maybe I should've gotten a cold one.
Did you come out to enjoy the night wind?
I totally forgot that we're underground.
Would you like to walk around for a bit?
Sure.
Wait, where's Index?
She kinda went missing at some point.
Now's my chance!
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
Who is this character?
Who's that character?!
Answer
Tsukuyomi Komoe
We already talked about this,
but how long has it been?
I don't want to put a number on it,
but enough time has passed for a cicada
larva to come out of the ground and die.
Yeah, I know.
The person behind the character ages in real-time,
so if there's a lot of downtime,
things may become a bit rough for them.
Hey now! You're not supposed
to talk about these things.
There are shows where you
can't tell at all, you know.
I know what you mean, but there are
others where you definitely can.
You're right.
If it becomes too tough,
you see a subtle change in casting.
Yes! That's right! That's what happens!
It's terrifying!
The cast members are replaced
and most people don't even realize!
It's like a sci-fi horror movie!
What? That sounds like an old-timey kind of plot.
How old are you?
Weren't you the one who said
we shouldn't talk about this?!
I wanted to take this in the direction
of the real person not aging at all.
You say that, but how old
is the person behind you?
30! Congrats!
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
Who is this character?
Who's that character?!
Answer
Musujime Awaki
Flour, ten parts.
Sugar, one part.
Salt and skim milk.
Flour, two parts.
Sugar, one part.
Half an egg.
I know what he's saying!
It's a recipe for bread or cookies or something!
Oh, so even Japanese people can tell?
You see, I'm on a low-carb diet,
so sometimes I get cravings for flour.
When that happens, it helps to imagine food
made of flour and scream its ingredients out loud.
Flour and eggs.
Lots of cabbage.
And the trick to making it extra tasty
is to add some stock to the dough.
You also add some tempura crumbs.
It's okonomiyaki!
Food made with flour is so good.
If you add yam it also becomes fluffy!
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
Who is this character?
Who's that character?!
Answer
Terra of the Left
Mr. Accel!
Mr. Accel
Whaaaaat?
A thrilling and amusing series about Mr. Accel
using his wits to solve hard problems.
Mr. Accel
Now then, Accelerator, you say you're evil,
so let me see you catch
the tiger on this folding screen.
And the mouse too!
Huh? What did you say, small fry?
Ha?! Wah?!
Words! Do you speak them?!
Can you do it or not?
And by the way, my ability is Dark Matter—
Wah!
Phew!
You've done enough. Good job.
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
Who is this character?
Who's that character?
Answer
Terra of the Left
Mr. Accel!
Mr. Accel
Whaaaaat?
A thrilling and amusing series about Mr. Accel
using his wits to solve hard problems.
Mr. Accel
Do Not Cross This Bridge
What are you going to do now, Accelerator?
Huh? What are you playing at, small fry?
My ability is Dark Matter.
That's a power word from the good old sci-fi stuff!
No idea what you're blabbering about.
If you tell me not to cross a bridge, I—
You've done enough. Good job.
But you can try to say that
to a girl when she refuses you.
Tehe!
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
Who is this character?
Who's that character?
Answer
Terra of the Left
Mr. Left.
Mr. Left
Yes, let's begin!
A thrilling and amusing series about Mr. Left
using his wits to solve hard problems.
Mr. Left
Someone here secretly ate a sweet bun!
It wasn't me, of course.
Didn't eat. Didn't eat.
I see.
I, of course, didn't eat, didn't eat any.
Didn't eat. Didn't eat.
That's a lie!
You're all covered in flour! Who else would it be?!
Didn't eat. Didn't eat.
I don't care if a low-carb diet
is good for your health or not.
But you're craving flour so much you ate
something made of it without even realizing!
Didn't eat. Didn't eat.
A society that simply equates
being slim with being good is wrong!
Didn't eat. Didn't eat.
I'll destroy that stupid illusion!
Didn't eat.
Have some rice.
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
Who is this character?
Who's that character?
Answer
Terra of the Left
I heard that people were really impressed at how
nothing had changed about the main character,
when they made a sequel to Bragon Ball P
more than ten years after the original ended.
Yes, that's exactly it, Touma!
That's what I was talking about.
Yeah...
But you know, someday you won't be
comfortable in a middle-schooler's body.
What's going to happen to you then?
Anyway!
Go bald! Go bald! Go bald!
Go bald! Go bald! Go bald! Go bald!
Let's stay friends even if ten years pass.
Sure.
Friends forever! Forever!
Well in ten years *** might not say ***.
No, I think he'd say it.
You think so?
I do.
Think it'll work?
Not sure if it'll work but—
Yes!
I'll protect you even if I have to make an enemy of the entire world
This strength comes from the light you've given me
I don't want to—