A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
A Certain Magical Index-tan, Episode 7!
Touma, Touma!
This is the last Index-tan for season three.
Yeah, you're right.
Even these leisurely bundles of random
bonus scenes we've been slapping together
are coming to an end.
You think of it as just slapping them together,
but the producer says that these
also have their birthing pains.
Birthing pains?!
Such a crybaby.
I know. It's just seven episodes.
Yeah, just seven.
Seven.
And you know, this is almost my main role.
Yeah.
I don't get any screen time!
No, you don't.
Say, don't you think we're
getting ourselves in trouble here?
Oh, no! You're right!
Gotta act like the main heroine!
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
Hamazura...
Hamazura!
Work?
Hama-zura.
Hamazura?
Hah? Mazura!
Hamazura!
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
I took care of it.
And bring a set of women's clothes.
What size? How should I know?
Also, send only women.
If I see any guys, I'm going to bust their balls.
Live however you want.
Whether you succeed or fail
in the rest of your life is up to you.
Who are you?
A villain.
You're such a good person.
I'm a villain.
You're actually a super good person.
I said I'm a villain, okay?!
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
Index-tan's
Seeing Pointy Teeth Makes
You Go "Terra!" Problem
Index-tan's Seeing Pointy Teeth
Makes You Go "Terra!" Problem.
What's this?
Terra!
All correct answers!
What else did you expect?
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
Did you know?
What we now call the "lesser panda"
was the first animal to be called a "panda".
But after those black-and-white bastards
were discovered, it got this "lesser" prefix.
What?! Really?!
I had no idea.
And what does "lesser" even mean?
The dictionary says
"not as important", or "inferior".
Ugh!
They showed up later but
overtook the position! I hate them!
Go back to your bamboo thicket,
stupid giant panda!
I'll going to call you ******!
That's already taken.
Then ******!
Wait a moment!
It also says "similar but smaller in size,
when used in animal names".
Rejoice, Lessar!
"Lesser panda" seems to mean "small panda".
It's too late for that.
It's in every girl's nature that if she starts
hating something, nothing can make her like it.
Sounds like a pain.
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
Mr. Accel!
Whaaaaat?
Mr. Accel
A thrilling and amusing series about
Mr. Accel using his wits to solve hard problems.
Mr. Accel
Get off me!
I said get off!
"If you move, the mochi will fall
to the ground, and we can't eat it.
And you're not that kind of person",
Misaka tries saying.
To hell with that!
I'm a villain!
I'm the baddest villain!
I don't care about mochi falling!
Go to hell!
"If you can stand with mochi
on your back before turning one,
you'll go to live far from your parents",
is what Misaka once heard,
but despite a small shudder of sadness, she realizes it has nothing to do with us.
Cut that crap out.
Want me to butcher you?
"I'll have Yomikawa make rice
cooker cookies out of this mochi",
says Misaka as Misaka tries making plans.
Don't go putting processed rice food
back into the rice cooker!
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
I did get screen time pretty regularly,
but because of that old lady,
I got treated as comic relief.
Why doesn't Mikoto
get more screen time?
I wanted to have some more
fun machinations of cruelty.
The story really suffered the lack.
Perhaps I should read some
fan letters to make up for it.
Let's see now.
"How old are you, Ms. Laura?
I love you so much, I'd put you in my pocket
and take you home, if you're of marriageable age."
Well, I have no interest in such things.
I'd rather enjoy my current life
than look forward to marriage.
And I'd love to live my life as I please
and gently slip into the grave.
Why doesn't Mikoto
get more screen time?
Next one.
Let's see now.
"I happened to see you in town the other day,
but I was too nervous to speak to you."
Come on, speak to me, you asshole.
It could have been a fateful encounter,
you piece of shit.
Oh, dear, maybe I should
really start thinking about it.
Beef or fish? Beef or fish?
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
Beef or fish? Beef or fish?
So why is it "beef or fish" anyway?
It's clear that beef is meat from cattle, but fish?
You know how many species of fish there are?
Cattle do have different breeds,
but nowhere near how many types of fish there are!
About a million.
So if you say "beef", it's pretty clear what
you're choosing, but the world of fish is vast!
White or red flesh?
Tuna or bonito?
Bream or flounder?
And so on.
I like white-fleshed fish.
Amberjack or sea perch?
No, that's for special occasions!
Clam or quahog?
That's true.
Wait! Those are shellfish!
And one's invasive!
Puffer fish or konjac.
It feels like fish, okay?!
Right, Touma?
I don't really care.
I've heard of "beef or chicken?" situations too.
And often it's between Western or Eastern cuisine.
Japanese airlines have been
making an effort in this respect,
but I hear abroad sometimes you
just get some snack like potato chips.
But in our story it's "beef or fish?"
so I want to discuss the fish part.
You know, there are still many
undiscovered species in the oceans!
Especially in the unexplored depths.
This blue planet has weird ocean depths!
You're right. Crabs that look like robots
are especially awesome!
Yeah, that's right!
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
I put in the proper effort,
trained quite a bit,
and managed to develop a cool spell.
And it was all because of the
time when you almost got me.
Reduce to zero!
Man, I'm on a roll!
Let's reduce everything to zero!
lish
Reduce to zero!
Account Balance (Yen)
Deer Esther
Actions
Dance
>>
Work
Eat
Sleep
Reduce to zero!
Deer Esther
Actions
Dance
>>
Work
Eat
Sleep
-
Unemployment
Rate
Zero!
-
Unemployment
Rate
Zero!
-
Monday
Tuesday
Wednesday
Thursday
Friday
Saturday
Sunday
Part-
Timing (Bro)
-
>
Talk Show
Live
Show
-
Monday
Tuesday
Wednesday
Thursday
Friday
Saturday
Sunday
Part-
Timing (Bro)
-
>
Talk Show
Presentation
Live
Show
Yoga
Concert
Lecture
& Dinner
Payday
Important!
Meeting
with designer
5:00 Start
21:00 Finish
Location Scouting
-
Party 1
Party 2
Live
Show
Meeting
Designer 2
Introductions
Meeting
Designer 2
Introductions
18:00 -
21:00 -
TV Station
(P) and (V)
Design
Discussion
Talk Show
Hiking
Fireworks
Meeting
Plot Meeting
14:00-18:00
Exploring
Location
New Product
Meeting @ 15:00
Stage
Lessons
Lunch Meeting
with Satou
BBQ
13:00
Yoga
Pressure
Training
Work
Excursion
BBQ
On-site
Sales Event
Delivery
Day
Amazing!
(
Zero!
At
Done
Cuts
Remaining
Chief
A.D.
Done
Key
Anim.
Done
Ep. Dir.
At
Done
Cuts
Remaining
Chief
A.D.
Done
Key
Anim.
Done
Ep. Dir.
At
-
Reduce to zero!
Zero! Zero! Zero!
Everything zero! Zero! Zero!
Yes! Zero! Zero! Zero!
Zero...
A Certain Magical Index-tan
Episode
What are you looking at?
Despite what I was saying before,
coming so close to the end feels sad.
Yeah, I know.
Say, Index, want to close off
with a hyped-up comedy skit?
What? Are you out of your mind, Touma?
What's the problem, Index?
The last memorable skit
of the main guy and main girl.
Hey and thanks for coming, I'm Kamijou!
Hey, I'm Index-tan!
Let's say it together.
I'm Index-tan!
-tan!
Touma, the sadness is welling up inside me.
Yeah, I know.
But the people watching this special
have surely purchased the discs.
If they spread the word about the Toaru series
and the disc sales go well,
I'm sure we can meet again.
That's right!
And to be even more explicit: buy the discs!
And now that Index has shouted
what others would be embarrassed to,
it's almost time to say goodbye.
Let's end with a song.
Let's go!
I'm not singing!
Let's do the thing.
One-two!
I'll destroy that illusion!
Spread throughout the whole world
Are hope-filled lights
As they connect, the future smiles upon us
I feel like this sad—