Shit!
Why did they have to choose this building?
Sorry, but take off now.
We're going to the building
over there with the private rooms.
Bad luck.
I was part of Academy City's air force.
Did you think a pilot wouldn't
know how to handle a weapon?
What's wrong?
Not going to answer?
Hamazura...
Takitsubo! Are you okay?
Where are you?
At the meeting place.
With the private rooms.
I heard what happened.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Takitsubo!
I'm hiding out of sight.
No one's found me yet.
What?
Then why are you all out of breath?
I just feel a bit ill.
It's nothing you need to worry about, Hamazura.
All right.
It'll be fine.
I'll head over there right now.
I'll rescue you for sure.
Just hold on a bit longer.
Don't!
Stay away, Hamazura!
There's ten terrorists armed with
submachine guns and grenades.
You won't be able to do anything
if you just barge in.
So stay away!
Shut up, I'm coming.
I said I'm coming!
Please.
You can tell the cops whatever you want.
I don't care if I'm sent to the depths of Hell.
Please help me save her!
Please!
You should've just said that first.
I've been hijacked.
The perpetrator has a gun and
a small container filled with liquid.
I'm going to comply with his demands for now,
out of concern for the local residents.
Thank you...
I can't just take off because some kid demanded it.
Also, I hope you don't think
they're going to just let us land.
Yeah, I know.
What's that?
Probably a fake tree.
A real tree up there would interfere
with takeoffs and landings.
That's good to know.
I made it, partner.
All the way to the depths of Hell.
A Certain Magical Index
Board of Directors
When are we going to
rendezvous with Stephanie?
It depends on what she's—
Team B on the roof has—
Th-This is the twenty-eighth floor!
Doesn't matter to me.
The hell are you?
What's it to you?
If you really want to protect this city,
you'll need to be at least this thorough.
Tell me who you are, or die.
Sugitani.
I pray that we never meet again.
See to it so that it doesn't happen.
Tsuchimikado?
Spark Signal has been eradicated.
Get your ass up here and see
if there are any casualties or traps.
Huh?
Did you just fall ill or something?
Better not be another pregnant lady...
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
Answer me! What did you do to Takitsubo?
You Level 5!
Fuck you guys, sneaking around
and doing all your dirty work in the dark.
If you're going to take someone
precious away from me again,
then be prepared to meet your maker,
strongest esper!
That's what I like to see.
You're not a bad villain.
It's over.
If you stay down, then I'll leave you alone.
If you try to get up, then I'll stamp you out.
It's your life.
You get to choose.
Do you even need to ask?
You don't even have a reason to back down.
Killing you might save me
some trouble down the road.
But don't you think that's unfair?
Takitsubo...
What will it be?
If you want to keep trying,
I'll make you bathe in your own blood.
But if that kid is going to get in the way,
we can do this again later.
This is what they call the aesthetic of a villain.
Wait, was I wrong about him?
Hamazura.
How pathetic am I?
I told you I was coming to save you,
and look at me now.
And of all things to do, I tried to pick a fight
with a guy that might have saved your life.
You're not pathetic.
You're the only one that
came all the way here for me.
You're not pathetic at all!
Yeah?
Then how come you're crying?
I haven't changed at all.
I'm still the same old Hamazura Shiage.
I'm fine with being some third-rate hoodlum.
But at the very least,
I want to be strong enough to protect her.
No Entry
They super-made a show of things.
Looks like I'm late,
so I should super-help them escape.
I'd be super-fine if it was just a shotgun.
An automatic shotgun?!
Yoo-hoo!
You're Kinuhata Saiai, right?
Looks like I made the right choice by using
random ex-Spark Signal members as bait.
I'm Stephanie Gorgeouspalace.
I'm a sniper that came to avenge Sunazara.
But don't you think it would be
a good time to say your prayers?
Every last person that tries to find out
about DRAGON is eliminated.
Looks like it's going just as Shiokishi planned.
What is DRAGON, anyway?
The magic faction seems to think that
the word "DRAGON" evokes
thoughts of religious metaphor.
Angels, for example.
Angels?
On the 30th of September,
an angel spread its wings across Academy City.
The virus that Kihara bastard
was using was also called "ANGEL".
If I were to consider angels
and DRAGON were somehow related,
then Last Order is connected to DRAGON!
Are you serious?
There was even more to that fiasco?
Someone's been planning all of this.
Looks like it was that Shiokishi bastard.
I guess we've become his targets too.
Well, it's a bonus for us now that
we know who we're fighting.
First up, we'll see who he's got with him—
My electrode's been disabled!
Shit.
My thoughts aren't lining up.
You?
It seems your body will still move
when it really needs to.
Thanks to that, I didn't have to let my savior die.
Who put you up to this?
Is this one of Shiokishi's traps as well?
You're right, I'm not unlike you.
But you saved someone
that means more to me than my life,
and that has nothing to do
with how dirty a human being I am.
I'm in your debt.
And I plan to repay it.
Fine.
Keep going straight.
How far do you intend to go?
I need to kill that asshole Shiokishi.
If he finds out that he didn't finish me off,
he's going to go after my biggest weakness for sure.
Cancel/Off
Set
Cook
Rice w/ toppings
Rice porridge
Electricity cost
Cancel/Off
Set
Cook
Rice w/ toppings
Rice porridge
Electricity cost
Cancel/Off
Set
Cook
Rice w/ toppings
Rice porridge
Electricity cost
Cancel/Off
Set
Cook
Rice w/ toppings
Rice porridge
Electricity cost
Cancel/Off
Set
Cook
Rice w/ toppings
Rice porridge
Electricity cost
Cancel/Off
Set
Cook
Rice w/ toppings
Rice porridge
Electricity cost
Cook
Set
Electricity cost
Cook
Set
Electricity cost
Cook
Set
She's not the only one I need to protect.
Am I going to try and protect
everything as I fight? Or...
Keep it simple. I'll just get him
before he realizes what's coming.
That's much more fitting for someone
who's shed as much blood as I have.
A Certain Magical Index
Okay, Accelerator,
keep going and head to
the observatory in District 21.
Huh? Is that where Shiokishi is hiding?
No.
But we need to make some political preparations
before we can get rid of him.
We need someone else with
the authority of the Board of Directors.
Do we really need them?
Oyafune Monaka.
She's holding a stargazing session for the children
who were captured by the terrorists.
She's the kindest person on the Board of Directors.
I'm not too fond of this MO,
but she owes us a favor.
Leave.
Ms. Oyafune is no longer living
a double life in the underworld.
Being from the underworld yourself,
you should know how difficult that is.
Yeah, I do.
Sorry for the trouble.
I have a question.
What happened to Oyafune?
Her daughter.
Huh?
While she was campaigning
to regulate our weapons exports,
she was sent a photo of her daughter
along with a loaded pistol.
Nothing came of it in the end,
but I have my doubts about Shiokishi,
considering he's such a war animal.
After that, Ms. Oyafune left
the forefront of the battle.
She'll be forced to rejoin if she works with you.
Oh yeah?
Excuse me.
Who might that be?
No one important.
I was just asking for directions.
I'm sure you knew this was going to happen.
And despite that, you still came here.
What happened?
What difference does it make?
It's better that you don't know what happened
between Shiokishi and me, for your own sake.
My apologies.
It's my problem.
I should've just taken care
of it myself from the get-go.
I'll be treated as a terrorist
once I finish with Shiokishi.
But so what?
I chose this path myself.
I'm going to continue to fight to protect that kid,
even if she becomes my enemy.
This doesn't change what I need to do.
What are you doing?
You're that hero, right?
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
You're going to fight again, right?
To save someone like me again.
I'm coming with you.
I'll fight with you!
Fuck off, you stupid kid.
Do you even know what you're saying?
I know you're going somewhere really dangerous.
If there's someone in trouble like I was,
I want to fight for them too!
I don't need your help.
I'm the strongest Level 5.
No!
I don't want to let those cowards
take over Academy City!
Come on.
Let's go.
It seems...
You're planning to fight, no matter what.
Ms. Oyafune!
Who are the cowards that boy was talking about?
Those who lurk in the darkness of the city?
Or those who know of the darkness
and refuse to fight?
I wonder what I should do.
Hell if I know.
It's your life.
Choose for yourself.
Ms. Oyafune!
I've finally seen the light.
Let's go to where Shiokishi is.
That would be our best bet.
Were you able to get in touch with Kinuhata?
No.
It won't connect.
Maybe something happened to her?
We waited a while and she never showed.
What are you going to do now, Hamazura?
She's a Level 4. She's a lot tougher than we are.
It would take quite a lot to get her killed.
What the hell's all this?
This really is quite a lot!
Look, Hamazura.
She could be in the underground mall.
This looks pretty bad.
What do we do?
Should we keep going, or head back?
Hamazura!
Kinuhata!
Super-get down!
Since your ability controls nitrogen,
I thought I'd do something about the air.
I thought I might be able to pump you full of lead
the moment an explosion creates a vacuum.
Hamazura, super-get out of here!
Kinuhata!
What? The peer authorization
system has been activated?
I can't believe they would use it here.
What shall I do?
Now that it's been activated,
the political defense we have here has been nullified.
Not to mention...
GROUP?!
Damn that sneaky woman.
Do you think they'll resort to force, though?
They will. This is about DRAGON.
They're definitely coming our way.
We need to be ready to greet them.
This is an all-out war.
Understood.
That's an AIM jammer up there.
It'll pretty severely limit our abilities.
They're totally prepared to take us on.
What will you do now?
Do you even need to ask?
We're bursting in through the front door.
Let's go.
You keep watch here, Tsuchimikado.
Oyafune, you'll be the one
negotiating with Shiokishi.
We'll break down all the walls
in between us and him,
but when we get there, you'll be up front.
Musujime.
There's no resistance.
Looks like something else
happened behind this bulkhead.
You're useless.
May I challenge you to a fight?
I prayed that we'd never meet again.
But you didn't listen.
You're the one that came to me.
I told you to see to it that I wouldn't have to.
Do you know about DRAGON?
It's poison.
Musujime has a higher priority than you,
since she can pass through walls.
What's your deal?
It's Koga.
I'm a descendent of Koga.
We're a group of cowards that have been
working in the name of justice for generations.
Oyafune is done for.
Once we dispose of her,
we can use Academy City's collective
power to get rid of you, Accelerator.
And once we secure Last Order, it's over for you.
My demands are simple.
I want to permanently revoke your power
to incorporate and consume the lives of others
as part of your plans.
That's all.
It's just common sense, after all.
Oh, could you also tell me about DRAGON?
Is that something you need to know?
It's part of my agreement with GROUP.
I'm merely taking care of all of the matters
I need to in order to protect Academy City.
DRAGON is the kind of thing
that's just as dangerous as it sounds.
You might call it barbaric,
but that's just because you don't know
the true nature of DRAGON.
I'm the same.
If the need arises, I'm not against being barbaric.
Have negotations broken down?
I think we have different things in mind
when we say we want to protect Academy City.
Is that so.
Did it never cross your mind?
That Oyafune Monaka might take steps
to protect her own life, just like you have?
Wh-What?!
Unabara Mitsuki!
Oh, are you sure that's
the name you want to go with?
I was sure you were going to call me Etzali.
Where's Oyafune?
Was that spineless woman just watching
from a safe place this whole time?
Who knows?
My magic uses human skin as an ingredient,
but Ms. Oyafune didn't hesitate for even a second.
I'm sure removing ten centimeters of skin
is quite painful, even if it is from your arm.
Now then, allow me to ask you about DRAGON.
Or maybe
you'd like to know just how much pain
the spineless Oyafune endured?
Minobe!
I always have security guards from two different
providers nearby, just in case someone betrays me.
They're trained to kill each other if they have to.
What, why?
Why are all the other guards dead?
It can't be!
Did it never cross your mind?
That there would be others that snuck into the
dark side of Academy City the same way you did?
Tecpatl! And Tochtli!
A Certain Magical Index
Fear never loosens its grip on me
But I hold back my tears
It's a lonely battle in this never-ending night
I wonder where you went
Just as the courage I was relying on was breaking down
I heard a voice calling me from afar
Your smile, so sincere it's almost awkward
Makes the lonely night turn into day
Spread throughout the whole world
Are hope-filled lights
As they connect, the future smiles upon us
I feel like this sad journey is
Coming to an end
Your voice will be what changes me
To change me
I'm not alone
May this never-ending song shine brightly
Next Time
It appeared in the form of Fuse Kazakiri.
Time passed from the Aeon
of Osiris to that of Horus.
"Do what thou wilt shall be the whole of the Law."
Next time: "DRAGON".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.