Through the sale of her hair ornaments,
Myne's world widened once more.
However, the heat of the Devouring
was slowly gnawing at her, day by day.
I have a wish, just one simple wish
Ascendance of a Bookworm
LOREM IPSUM DOLOR SIT AMET CONSECTETUR ADIPISCING ELIT FUSCE EFFICITUR LECTUS ID NISI RHONCUS PHARETRA NULLA QUAM VELIT TEMPUS QUIS ACCUMSAN EFFICITUR TEMPUS EU ANTE DONEC ULTRICES MOLESTIE MAXIMUS DONEC NON LOREM VITAE ANTE PRETIUM VESTIBULUM IN IN MAGNA MAURIS PHARETRA PLACERAT URNA AC FEUGIAT TORTOR AUCTOR EGET MAECENAS SIT AMET EROS FELIS ETIAM SAPIEN PURUS MALESUADA FERMENTUM VIVERRA VEL PORTA SIT AMET LECTUS CLASS APTENT TACITI SOCIOSQU AD LITORA TORQUENT PER CONUBIA NOSTRA PER INCEPTOS HIMENAEOS MAURIS VEHICULA DAPIBUS INTERDUM FUSCE SIT AMET NISI VENENATIS PLACERAT LIGULA ID CONDIMENTUM ODIO DUIS URNA JUSTO IMPERDIET UT COMMODO ID ULTRICES IN ELIT SED EGESTAS FACILISIS EX IN HENDRERIT IPSUM EGESTAS IMPERDIET
I hold it dearly in my heart and hope
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
It'll come true someday soon
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to
I don't have anything, nothing at all
But if I could have this one wish granted
It would fill the void inside my heart
I can feel the warm breeze blowing
And see shooting stars filling the sky
They make me feel as if
I can do anything, y'know?
In this wonderful world
Nothing is set in stone
The as-yet untold future
Shines brighter than the sun
I want to take hold of my future
With my own two hands
And write pages filled with hope
Into the book of my life
Chapter 10
The Second Winter Approaches
It's been a year since I came to this world.
Once again, Pig Day has reared its head.
The second winter will be coming soon.
It's been three days, huh...
It's been a while since I last
came down with a fever like this.
I'd just been thinking that my body
was holding up pretty well recently...
Stay in there,
heat of the Devouring!
I've just gotta... seal it inside the box...
Give the top of it a big hit...
And now we're good!
It's so weird.
I only got a little worked up, and yet...
As long as you have something
you want to put your all into, you'll be fine.
That's it.
Let's think of something fun.
Mr. Benno said to look through this.
I wonder what it is.
We're back home!
Myne, look!
Oh! Bacon!
I'll make soup right away so just hold on.
Thanks, Tuuli.
Hey, Myne.
Lutz!
Tuuli said you were feeling better,
so I decided to come see you.
You missed Pig Day again, huh?
Oh, yeah.
I didn't mind it turning out like this though.
Your fever was holding for so long
that I was getting worried!
The worst's already passed,
so you don't need to worry.
I remember Frieda talking
about that Devouring thing...
I don't really know much about it,
so I wasn't sure if I'd been
managing your health properly.
It's fine. You've been awesome!
Thanks to you, I haven't been collapsing outside.
Hearing you say that makes me feel much better.
I'll be able to go to the store tomorrow.
Actually, take a look at this.
Huh?
First:
first :
Be able to give proper greetings
and maintain a professional
appearance.
Be able to give proper greetings
and maintain a professional appearance.
Second:
second :
Be able to write all basic letters and numbers.
Third:
third :
Be able to
use a calculator.
Be able to use a calculator.
This is the curriculum for new
Gilberta Company apprentices.
You hear me? I want you to
master these during the winter!
All this over winter?
There's no way!
The biggest issue is the professional appearance.
So your fever's gone down?
Yes, sorry for causing you trouble.
Thank you very much for this.
So, we were wondering, what exactly
does a professional appearance entail?
To begin with, you'd need proper
clothes and shoes to work in.
It should cost about ten
small silvers to get those things.
Ten small silvers?! I don't have that sorta money.
We deposited our small silvers
into the guild's bank, remember?
We can just use those.
So we were saving them for a moment like this?
That, and to cover our expenditures
for when we make something else.
Remember how hard it was
when we didn't have nails?
Money comes first in every new venture.
Makes sense.
I thought that whatever I earned
should be shared with my family.
So I sorta felt like I was betraying them.
You earned that money yourself,
so there's nothing wrong with setting some aside.
That kinda takes a weight off my shoulders.
Thanks, Myne.
That solves the appearance issues, at least.
Also, Lutz, you need to work on your language.
As things stand, I can't have you talk to customers.
I think you should start by not using
contractions like "kinda" and "sorta".
I think that will be a kind of improvement.
Yeah, I will sort... that out!
Mr. Benno...
I don't know how far you'll get with him over winter,
but let's see what you can do.
By the way, regarding your all-in-one-shampoo,
we've run into some trouble.
What happened?
I was having a workshop make it for me, but...
Despite doing as you instructed,
it just won't come out right.
Do you have an idea as to why?
I mean, it's really just crushing and then wringing.
As things stand, I won't be able to sell it.
If I can't get it made, it will count
as a breach of the magical contract.
What happens if a magical contract is breached?
In the worst case, you forfeit your life.
The heck?!
Excuse me, I wasn't told about this!
We headed to the workshop immediately.
Oh. I've figured it out.
What is it?
What was the problem?
It's the cloth you're using to wring it.
The cloth?
The cloth you're using is of high
quality so it has very fine fabric.
Fine
Coarse
Since we only have cheap cloth
at home, it was very coarse.
If you wring it with a coarse cloth, impurities like
parts of the fruit and seeds also end up in the oil.
Those impurities are necessary
to clean the dirt off the hair.
I get it now. So we need to use coarse cloth instead.
So what we've made so far's unusable, then?
Not necessarily!
In fact, it'd be a waste not to use it.
Huh?
As long as you put scrubbers—I mean,
abrasives into it, it should be fine.
Make the right choices and you could actually
end up with an even higher quality product.
Wow, little miss, you really know your stuff.
I believe you know even more than that. Right?
Not good.
If I'm not careful,
things'll turn out just like with Lutz.
Myne.
I can't let anything slip here.
Any more info beyond this will cost you.
I'm not sharing trade secrets for free.
Very well.
Huh?
Would you mind if we borrow the conference room?
Ah, yeah, go ahead.
Huh?
W-Wai—
Myne!
Hold on!
We're just going to chat for a bit.
We are not to be disturbed.
Two small golds.
Excuse me?
I'm offering two small golds for
the information on how to improve it.
Specific plants to use, anything. I want to hear it all.
Two small golds...
Three small golds.
Three small golds, you say?
When money comes your way, you don't question it.
You take it and you take as much as you can.
Right?
Three small golds, then.
I'm not going any higher.
W-Wait a second!
Take it and save it for when you need it.
The only thing that can do something
against your Devouring is money.
Wait, how do you know...
I'd been suspecting it for a while.
The old geezer told me before, though.
Frieda talked to him about you
suffering from the Devouring.
Great wealth and noble connections saved Frieda.
All I can do is buy your knowledge.
Mr. Benno...
Sit.
Save up as much money as you can,
even if it means selling everything you know.
Prepare for when the day finally comes.
What day?
The day you won't be able to hold
the heat inside you back anymore.
It felt like the heat from the Devouring
had been growing stronger recently.
So it wasn't just my imagination.
I've come so far, and yet...
I don't want to die yet.
I still...
want to live!
Very well.
I'll sell the information to you for three small golds.
I sold the ways to improve the
all-in-one shampoo to Mr. Benno.
How he could use salt as an abrasive ingredient.
How adding citrus fruits would get dirt off easier.
I see.
Have you tested all of this?
No. My family is poor, so I wasn't able to.
You know it works despite not testing it...
Just who are you?
That's a secret.
Not one I'll sell for small golds, either.
I explained how to improve the shampoo
fully prepared for what would come from it.
So, are you going to throw me out
because I'm some creepy know-it-all child?
No. You're going to help make me rich,
and I'm trying to figure out how to keep
anyone else from getting their hands on you.
I'm a merchant, after all.
Don't forget that.
Mr. Benno...
Ah, right. The name "all-in-one shampoo"
is a bit long and hard to say.
How about changing it to "Hairshine"?
It's fine with me, but do you like it?
Well, how about "Head Sparkle" instead?
Hairshine will do.
We'll make plenty of Hairshine and
hair ornaments and they'll sell like crazy!
Sounds great!
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
What?
You're making more hair ornaments?
Yeah.
People heard about Frieda's
ornaments so we got a bunch of orders.
So you're going to start
your winter handiwork early?
Gosh.
Now is such a busy time as well.
That's why I had him pay us in advance.
Two medium bronzes per flower part.
Two medium bronzes?!
My motivational magic
came into effect immediately!
Do you want your old man
to make the pin pieces for you?
That's Lutz's job, so thanks, but no.
Lutz again, huh...
Oh, Dad, I'm going to the gate tomorrow.
Do you wanna go together?
What?
Yeah I do!
You were bedridden again, Myne?
Yes, but I'm fine now.
That's good to hear.
There's a trombe!
Lutz said that trombes were pretty dangerous.
This is happening way more often now...
I ended up getting a whole load of trombe branches.
I didn't think we'd be able
to make paper with it again.
If we'd have let that rare trombe wood go to waste,
Mr. Benno would have given us an earful.
Blegh, it's freezing!
A nice, hot steamed potato
would be really great right now...
We'd need butter, wouldn't we?
Going to the river might be tough when it's this cold.
Let's use water from the well tomorrow instead.
That works?
Thank goodness.
Yeah! Oh, don't forget the butter!
Butter?
For what?
Huh? Didn't I explain?
Oh yeah, is your handiwork going well?
Yeah. Dad wanted to help out too,
but I couldn't let him.
How's things on your end?
Not great.
I asked my brothers if they'd help out,
but they turned me down.
You just need to cast some
motivational magic on them.
Uh, what?
Here, Lutz.
You made five pins for me,
so you get five medium bronzes from me.
Wait, five medium bronzes?!
When you say pins, do you mean those
wooden stick things he was making?
One medium bronze for one of those?
H-Hey, it doesn't have to be just
Lutz that makes them, right?
I've told him not to become a merchant
since all they do is trick people.
Lutz can be so difficult sometimes.
He paid them for their help with his winter
handiwork, so he doesn't seem too bad to me.
I still worry though.
Why did he have to pick a job with no security
and huge swings in the money he'll make?
We're off!
Have fun!
Take care.
Lutz is a real lifesaver, you know.
He takes great care of Myne.
Really? Myne has seemed a lot better recently.
Yeah. Compared to before, it's like night and day.
I hope she'll stay like this for a long time to come.
Oh, they're just potatoffels.
You don't want any?
No, I'll eat it.
Wait, this is great!
What is this?
You don't have steamed food here, right?
If you put butter on it right after
you take it out, it's super tasty.
Peeling the Black Bark
After that, we processed the
black bark of the trombe wood.
Drying the Black Bark
If we leave them like this,
they should be fine until spring.
I finished cleaning up the tools as well.
Now that these are done,
we can make more trombe pap—
There was nothing making me
feel angry or uneasy, and yet...
Myne?
What's wrong?
You're burning up!
Your fever just flared up out of nowhere.
Myne, are you okay?
It's gone...
What's going on?
It's the Devouring.
What?
You didn't have any symptoms
at all just a minute ago though.
Didn't you say that you'd be fine a few days ago?
It's been coming on suddenly recently.
Before, it'd only happen if I got
angry or upset over something.
Myne…
That sure caught me off-guard!
Can't we do anything?
Do you remember what Frieda said?
It would cost lots of money.
Mr. Benno said the same thing.
I'll carry you.
I can't do much more than that.
Don't say that!
You've done so much for me!
Don't mind that.
Just get on already.
Okay...
What do I do?
I've read countless books throughout my life, but...
None of them could tell me
what to say to him right now.
He's just way too nice.
He stands by me no matter
how much trouble I cause him.
He even forgave me for not being the real Myne.
Lutz...
If I end up collapsing,
please don't feel responsible, okay?
I'm not giving up just yet, though.
After all, I haven't made any books yet.
Lutz. Come to the back office.
Master Benno, please save Myne.
I can't do it.
I can't do anything.
If there's anything I can do, just tell me, and I'll do it.
Then don't make Myne worry.
What?
She's not just a regular child.
She's able to smile and take care of you
even when things are tough for her.
If you're a real man,
then don't add to Myne's worries.
If you're gonna say that you'll make
whatever she thinks of next,
then go and make and sell every single
insane thing she comes up with.
Make money!
I finally like the look on your face.
The next time we met,
he was already back to his usual self.
I thought a good goal would be
to make around ten of them.
Who'd've thought we'd have
double that done already?
Having this many should help a bit, right?
Huh?
We need money to do something
about the Devouring, right?
Lutz...
Hey, can you think of anything
else profitable that we can make?
I promise I'll make whatever you think up.
Thanks, Lutz...
Ah, you've got the batch of hair ornaments ready.
Yes!
Here, your payment.
Mr. Benno, do you think this would sell?
I made these last year for my winter handiwork.
Gosh, those were yours too?
Every single mystery I've come across in the last
half-year has led straight back to you, Myne.
Uh...
Sorry.
Do you have anything tucked away in that mind
of yours that'll make more money than baskets?
Something perishable, like Hairshine?
Well, let's see...
How about colored and scented soap or candles?
Do you know how to make those?
Yes.
It might require some trial and error, though.
Great. Come spring, we'll get them made.
Sure!
We're really going to be keeping ourselves busy
if we're making both paper and candles!
Myne!
Myne?!
Are you okay?
This is bad.
Mark! Get the carriage ready!
tell me, oh my angel
oh my lovely, let me dream again
I gently brush my hair
And put a hairpin through it
In the sea of green
A flower ornament blooms
It is a gift from my angel
It touches my forehead
Oh so gently
And it reminds me
Of the warm light that gathered
To bring my angel into this world
This fever is making me delirious
Ah, these times are so dear to me
There must have been something more
Some greater force that led me to you
Our fates tangle and unravel as we become family
I have been always living
Inside a book
But then my heart melted
And now I have experienced
The real world
Next Chapter
The Final Decision and the Family Meeting
Please! Do something, Master Benno!
The guildmaster's gotta know something, right?
I've already negotiated with him.
I knew I could count on you!
Apparently he still had old magic tools
left from when Frieda needed to use them.
The one that'd probably break
after a single use costs two small golds.
G-Golds?!
I'll lend you it if you pay me back later.
Pay you back?
Master Benno, people like you are...
No need to thank me.
This is all part of my plan.
Why wasn't I in this preview?
Illustration:     Kazune