It was the day of her baptism.
Myne had gone to the temple and happened
to discover a library while she was lost.
There's so... many... books.
It's a chained library, too.
With the sole purpose of being
able to read those books,
Myne spoke to the high bishop and requested
to become an apprentice shrine maiden.
I have a wish, just one simple wish
Ascendance of a Bookworm
LOREM IPSUM DOLOR SIT AMET CONSECTETUR ADIPISCING ELIT FUSCE EFFICITUR LECTUS ID NISI RHONCUS PHARETRA NULLA QUAM VELIT TEMPUS QUIS ACCUMSAN EFFICITUR TEMPUS EU ANTE DONEC ULTRICES MOLESTIE MAXIMUS DONEC NON LOREM VITAE ANTE PRETIUM VESTIBULUM IN IN MAGNA MAURIS PHARETRA PLACERAT URNA AC FEUGIAT TORTOR AUCTOR EGET MAECENAS SIT AMET EROS FELIS ETIAM SAPIEN PURUS MALESUADA FERMENTUM VIVERRA VEL PORTA SIT AMET LECTUS CLASS APTENT TACITI SOCIOSQU AD LITORA TORQUENT PER CONUBIA NOSTRA PER INCEPTOS HIMENAEOS MAURIS VEHICULA DAPIBUS INTERDUM FUSCE SIT AMET NISI VENENATIS PLACERAT LIGULA ID CONDIMENTUM ODIO DUIS URNA JUSTO IMPERDIET UT COMMODO ID ULTRICES IN ELIT SED EGESTAS FACILISIS EX IN HENDRERIT IPSUM EGESTAS IMPERDIET
I hold it dearly in my heart and hope
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
It'll come true someday soon
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to
I don't have anything, nothing at all
But if I could have this one wish granted
It would fill the void inside my heart
I can feel the warm breeze blowing
And see shooting stars filling the sky
They make me feel as if
I can do anything, y'know?
In this wonderful world
Nothing is set in stone
The as-yet untold future
Shines brighter than the sun
I want to take hold of my future
With my own two hands
And write pages filled with hope
Into the book of my life
Chapter 13
The Option to Become an Apprentice Shrine Maiden
What did you do this time, Myne?
Well... uh...
I was looking for somewhere
I could get water... and got lost.
Then I fainted.
That's not the whole story, is it?
I found a library
and got a little excited.
A library?
Libraries are a gift granted to us by the gods!
They're truly paradises!
That is to say, they're rooms filled with books!
Yeah, I've heard enough.
I understand everything now.
There's something important
you've left out, isn't there?
Huh?
This young lady fainted after asking the high bishop
about becoming an apprentice
shrine maiden so she could read books.
Well—
The hell are you doing, you moron?!
I'm sorry.
We're going home before
you end up doing anything else.
Okay...
In hindsight I really should have given
this whole thing more thought, but...
I gained a new goal: to become a shrine maiden.
I even got them to agree
to read their holy book to me!
So I guess the results speak for themselves.
You really stood out at today's baptism, Myne!
Of course she did, she's absolutely adorable!
Say, Dad.
Yeah? What is it?
I was thinking about becoming
an apprentice shrine maiden.
Huh?
Try saying that one more time!
A shrine maiden... at the temple...
What are you saying?!
I'm not giving my daughter away to the temple!
D-Dad!
Why are you so angry?
Because the only ones who become temple
apprentices are orphans that have nowhere else to go.
There's no way I'm letting you become one.
Wait... It's that bad of a thing?
Yes!
If you get it, don't ever bring it up again.
Günther,
Myne didn't know about any of that.
Don't be so hard on her.
Yeah. You're right.
What makes you bring
that up all of a sudden, Myne?
There were books at the temple.
So those books are the reason you
thought about becoming a shrine maiden?
Give up on the books at the temple.
If you want books, just keep working
toward making them yourself.
Myne...
If you had to choose between cutting ties with us
to live at the temple so you can read their books,
or staying with your family like you
always have, which would you choose?
What?
I'd have to cut ties with you guys?
But why?
Apprentice shrine maidens become live-ins
at the temple and have to do hard labor.
That's definitely not something you
can do with the way your health is.
And what's more, books are very expensive.
Do you really think they'll just let some
random apprentice at them right away?
Do you really wanna become
a shrine maiden that bad, Myne?
You promised we'd be together, didn't you?
I don't want to be one that much.
I was just trying to find a way to read their books.
I'd never want to become a shrine
maiden if it meant losing all of you.
Thank goodness!
So you'll stay with us, right?
Yeah!
When I'm feeling better, I'll go to the temple
and tell them I decided against becoming one.
I'm glad you understand.
You're my precious little girl.
No way in hell am I handing you over to that place.
Your fever's flaring back up!
She's probably just feeling exhausted
after having this tough conversation.
Go rest now.
Okay.
Back when I was Urano,
I'd choose books over everything else.
I guess my family ended up becoming
really important to me at some point.
But...
I'd finally found books that were within my reach.
I wanna read them...
Two days later, the fever
from the Devouring finally let up.
Master Benno was saying he wanted to talk to you.
You still don't look too great, though.
I'm going to the temple tomorrow,
so I can go to Mr. Benno's after that.
Will you come with me?
Sure, but why are you going to the temple?
They said they were going
to read the holy book to me.
I'm gonna rescind my request to become
an apprentice shrine maiden while I'm there too.
I see.
Well, no matter how you look at it,
there's no way you'd be able to live at the temple.
Yeah.
And so, the next day came.
Right then, I'll be back for you at fifth bell.
Thanks, Lutz.
Don't go wandering off again.
Okay!
Sorry for the intrusion.
So you're Myne, then?
Yes.
I'm the high priest.
The high bishop has filled me in.
Now, come.
Thank you very much.
The high bishop asked me to read to you
from our holy book until he returns.
Please sit down here and listen closely.
O-Oh, um...
High Priest.
Could I...
If there's something you'd like to say,
please do not bottle it up within you.
I don't want to just hear the story.
I want to read the book myself.
I see.
Why is that?
Did you not want to hear of the gods?
I am interested in learning about the gods,
but I also want to learn new words.
I see.
However, this is a very valuable book.
Can you promise not to touch it
under any circumstances?
I promise!
Thank you very much.
Now, let us read.
I can actually read a book!
The God of Darkness spent his all
of his long, long life in deep solitude.
Then one day, the God of Darkness—
High Priest, does this say "Goddess of Light"?
Yes.
Then this would be "God of Darkness"?
That's right.
You're a fast learner.
If you grasp things this quickly,
you might be worth teaching.
Oh, I'm sorry to have made you wait.
The high priest was kind enough
to read to me from the holy book
so I had a lot of fun and the time passed in a flash.
I wholeheartedly thank you for your kindness.
Well, that is very nice to hear.
Thank you very much, High Priest.
So, what did your parents say?
They scolded me and said that
only orphans become shrine maidens.
It's not just orphans, there are nobles as well.
The majority of them are orphans
because there is nobody to look
after them or refer them for other work.
You don't have to be an orphan
to become an apprentice.
I want you to understand that.
Even so, my body's weak, so I wouldn't be able
to live at the temple or do much manual work.
So you didn't faint last time because you were sick,
but because you have a weak constitution?
Yes.
I have a sickness called the Devouring.
Did you say the Devouring?
Y-Yes. What about it?
Bring it here right away.
Understood.
Huh? Wh-What?
Praised be the gods!
Wh-What's going on?!
Try touching this chalice.
Are you sure it's okay for me to?
Yes.
Now, quickly!
Huh? What just happened?
Myne. We'd like to talk with your parents.
Mom, Dad, I'm sorry.
I think things just got real complicated.
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Lutz!
What's wrong?
Wait, did you end up doing something again?
I don't know what I did,
but I definitely think I've done something.
Gah. Again?
Master Benno is waiting for you.
Huh?
He said I should bring you in,
even if I had to drag you all the way there.
N-No, wait!
It's been a while, Myne.
Th-That it has...
Now, time to spill the beans.
Tell me everything that happened
after you fainted during the baptism.
Once I understand what sort of mess you've gotten
yourself into, we can come up with a battle plan.
I figured I'd just become an apprentice
shrine maiden so I could get into the library,
and went to ask the high bishop
about it immediately.
Use your head a little, will you?!
You damned fool!
Sowwy.
Well? Did you get permission?
When I went home and told my parents about it,
they scolded me and told me that
only orphans become shrine maidens.
The high priest said that some
of them are nobles too though...
There were shrine maidens and priests wearing
both blue and gray robes at the temple, right?
The blue ones are nobles,
and the gray ones are orphans.
The orphans don't receive any sort of wage
and have to slave away for the nobles.
And if you, a simple commoner,
were to become a shrine maiden, you'd be a gray one.
There's no way your parents would agree to that.
I get it now. So that's why Dad was so upset.
So, did you tell them that you wouldn't
be becoming an apprentice there?
Well, about that...
When I mentioned the Devouring,
my parents ended up receiving a summons
to the temple to meet with them.
Now you're completely trapped.
Our only hope now is that we can
at least negotiate with the high bishop.
You're lucky.
How so?
Mr. Benno told me about the current
state of affairs surrounding the temple.
A few years ago,
due to political upheaval in the capital
a large-scale purge of the nobility took place,
and as a result, their numbers dwindled.
If the number of nobles in the country decreases,
then so too does the nation's power.
The blue priests at the various temples
were singled out in particular.
Noble Society
Nobles considered bothersome by their relatives,
who ended up being sent to the temple,
gradually started returning to their homes.
Of course, that exodus meant that the amount
of donations made by blue priests decreased.
Since the ones using the orphans were leaving,
many orphans were left without jobs.
Even just surviving became a real problem for them.
That's absolutely awful!
There's something even worse.
The chalice you touched is actually a magic tool.
A magic tool?
Yes.
Usually it's filled with mana by the
blue-robed priests and shrine maidens,
but if it's lacking, it'll end up causing
problems with the year's harvest.
What? Even the harvest is dependent on magic?!
Yeah.
That's why, with the lack of nobles,
the temple is in need of people with the Devouring like you.
Um...
Is there some sort of connection
between magic and the Devouring?
Wha—
You didn't know?!
When commoners,
who usually have almost no mana,
give birth to a child with unusually high mana,
that leads to the Devouring phenomenon.
So that heat within me was mana all along?
Before the political upheaval, commoners born
with high magical aptitude—those with the Devouring
were nothing more than a nuisance to nobles.
That isn't the case anymore, though.
So the temple needs my mana?
Yes.
If you go to the temple, you'll be able to live.
However, there is also some danger involved.
As someone with both mana and money,
you're an ideal target for any noble.
With that in mind, how about
we sign another magic contract?
What sort of contract?
A contract that makes it so that
whatever you make, Lutz sells.
That way, even if a noble
were about to steal you away,
the contract would mean that
you'd be able to maintain contact with us.
Let's create a connection between you and Lutz.
A connection with Lutz...
But I don't want to cause Lutz even more trouble,
or expose him to any sort of danger...
Saving your life is far more
important than that, Myne.
Plus, I'd be worried if you were all alone.
Just thinking about the things you
might get up to makes my head hurt.
Oh, come on!
Do you understand now?
If you've already received a summons,
we don't have a lot of time on our hands.
First of all, let's get the Myne
Workshop registered with the guild
so we can secure a place for you to sell goods.
Okay!
If you can use money to change
the way they treat you,
then you can also use it to negotiate more
favorable conditions for you joining the temple.
Pave the road to your future ahead of time!
When you enter the temple, don't just get exploited.
Find someone that you can make use of yourself!
Look around you closely and think hard.
Struggle for your life!
Um...
Why are you going so far for me, Mr. Benno?
I-If you survive, you'll think of new products.
And obviously, I stand to profit from that.
Master Benno is always deeply concerned about
you and your tendency to get into trouble, Myne.
Wha—
Shut your trap, Mark!
I apologize for speaking up,
but Master Benno all but considers you family.
Of course, I also feel this way about you.
Thank you, Mr. Mark!
You're thanking Mark, huh?
Of course, I'm thankful to you as well, Mr. Benno.
Anyway, let's get to registering the Myne Workshop
and signing that magic contract.
My, you are registering the Myne Workshop?
I had thought you were going to become an
apprentice merchant at the Gilberta Company.
I decided to give up on that as it'd be
too physically demanding for me.
Why, that would suggest that anything made by
your workshop may also be sold to our company!
I've already sold you the
pound cake recipe so far, right?
Yes! Leise has been eagerly
researching ways to improve it.
You simply must come over to taste it!
And rather than bring Lutz,
you should come with your dear older sister.
Uh, if the goal is to improve its sales,
I think gathering a large number of people
to try it would give you better results.
Huh?
Get lots of people to try it, you say?
Yeah! Maybe something like
a pound cake sampling event?
Have lots of different types of
pound cake cut into bite-sized pieces
and then survey people to find out which was best.
Why, that sounds like a splendid idea!
Gosh, I will be ever so busy with this.
I shall have you informed when the date
for this "sampling event" has been set!
Have a wonderful day!
See, I'm telling you, you're pretty similar.
What?
They definitely are.
What's wrong, Lutz?
Hey, Myne... Are you really going to join the temple?
Yeah, probably.
I figured...
Hey, Lutz.
If there's something you wanna say,
you shouldn't bottle it up.
It'd sound lame so I don't wanna say it.
I see...
You lied to me, Myne.
You said we'd make and sell books together.
I'm sorry, Lutz.
You shouldn't be apologizing, Myne.
I know that I can't do anything to change this.
But...
it hurts so much.
You said we'd open a bookstore together.
I wanted to make books with you.
Yeah...
But even once I go to the temple,
I won't give up on making books.
That's my dream, after all.
To live surrounded by books?
Yeah.
Let's do everything we can to fulfill our dreams!
I...
I was able to do my best because I was with you.
I wanted to work together
with you at Master Benno's store.
I wanted to be with you...
for longer...
It's okay.
I might be going to the temple,
but things aren't gonna change.
If I want to make something, you'll be
the first person I go to and ask for help, Lutz.
There are lots of people who understand
the value of your inventions now.
You'll get plenty of help if you need it.
Well...
I feel like they'd try helping me,
but just end up causing me problems,
so I'd end up calling for you anyways.
Would you still help me?
You said you'll make the things I think up, right?
Yeah.
I'll make whatever you come up with, Myne!
tell me, oh my angel
oh my lovely, let me dream again
I gently brush my hair
And put a hairpin through it
In the sea of green
A flower ornament blooms
It is a gift from my angel
It touches my forehead
Oh so gently
And it reminds me
Of the warm light that gathered
To bring my angel into this world
This fever is making me delirious
Ah, these times are so dear to me
There must have been something more
Some greater force that led me to you
Our fates tangle and unravel as we become family
I have been always living
Inside a book
But then my heart melted
And now I have experienced
The real world
Next Chapter
Confrontation
I'm finally getting summoned
to the temple next time!
What on earth are you doing?
If it can make even the smallest difference,
I've gotta fight to improve my terms!
Leave that to your parents.
There's nothing you can do on your own.
This is about me, so I'll...
See, I told you.
Illustration: Nozomu Tamaki