"I want to make books."
As a result of this single-minded goal,
Myne succeeded in creating clay tablets.
In the end, however, it was not to be.
And so, seasons passed, and summer arrived.
The time had come for Tuuli's baptism.
I have a wish, just one simple wish
Ascendance of a Bookworm
LOREM IPSUM DOLOR SIT AMET CONSECTETUR ADIPISCING ELIT FUSCE EFFICITUR LECTUS ID NISI RHONCUS PHARETRA NULLA QUAM VELIT TEMPUS QUIS ACCUMSAN EFFICITUR TEMPUS EU ANTE DONEC ULTRICES MOLESTIE MAXIMUS DONEC NON LOREM VITAE ANTE PRETIUM VESTIBULUM IN IN MAGNA MAURIS PHARETRA PLACERAT URNA AC FEUGIAT TORTOR AUCTOR EGET MAECENAS SIT AMET EROS FELIS ETIAM SAPIEN PURUS MALESUADA FERMENTUM VIVERRA VEL PORTA SIT AMET LECTUS CLASS APTENT TACITI SOCIOSQU AD LITORA TORQUENT PER CONUBIA NOSTRA PER INCEPTOS HIMENAEOS MAURIS VEHICULA DAPIBUS INTERDUM FUSCE SIT AMET NISI VENENATIS PLACERAT LIGULA ID CONDIMENTUM ODIO DUIS URNA JUSTO IMPERDIET UT COMMODO ID ULTRICES IN ELIT SED EGESTAS FACILISIS EX IN HENDRERIT IPSUM EGESTAS IMPERDIET
I hold it dearly in my heart and hope
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
It'll come true someday soon
I'll Do Anything to                     Become a Librarian!
Ascendance of a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to
I don't have anything, nothing at all
But if I could have this one wish granted
It would fill the void inside my heart
I can feel the warm breeze blowing
And see shooting stars filling the sky
They make me feel as if
I can do anything, y'know?
In this wonderful world
Nothing is set in stone
The as-yet untold future
Shines brighter than the sun
I want to take hold of my future
With my own two hands
And write pages filled with hope
Into the book of my life
Chapter 5
Baptism and the Mysterious Fever
My, Tuuli, you look so cute!
Congratulations, Tuuli!
Thank you!
In this world, turning seven is a big deal.
As part of that celebration,
you're baptized at the temple.
Having girls must be nice.
Oh yes, with Ralph, Lutz,
and two more boys on top of that,
you must really have your hands full, Karla.
Good grief.
Sometimes I wish I'd had some girls.
Oh my.
Your hair is done so beautifully too.
You look like a real princess, Tuuli!
Myne did it for me!
Myne did? I guess she can do more
than just make weird dishes.
Wha—
Hey, look.
I've never seen a hair clip like that!
You're right. It's really pretty.
I wonder how they made it.
Amazing!
Was my hair clip that impressive?
Damn it!
I don't want to go to a meeting
on such an important day!
Don't wanna! No way! Not going!
Only kids are allowed into the temple anyway, right?
It is a father's duty to wait in the plaza
during his daughter's baptism.
And going to work to earn money
isn't part of a father's duty?
O-Okay, fine...
Let's head to the main street, everyone!
What's wrong?
Smile!
You're cutest when you have
a smile on your face, Tuuli.
Gosh.
Knock it off, Myne.
All right, let's get moving!
Come on, Dad, you've gotta get going.
Tuuli...
You're gonna miss your meeting!
You're late, Captain!
While Dad took care of his meeting,
I practiced my writing.
Otto!
Mr. Otto is currently in a meeting.
Oh, Myne.
I see... What should I do then?
Should I read it for you instead?
Wait, you can read it?
If it's a letter of inquiry or
a noble's letter of introduction
then I've learned about those from Mr. Otto already.
It's a letter of introduction.
If you would.
Upon the recommendation of Baron Blon,
this merchant wishes to meet with Baron Glaz.
The captain's seal will be necessary.
He's currently also in a meeting, so...
Have him wait in one of the rooms
designated for laynobles.
Seeing as this is a merchant
appearing on behalf of a noble,
they'll probably be understanding
if you explain the circumstances.
We're going home, Myne.
Quick, before Otto finds us.
Wait, Dad, I have something to report to Mr. Otto.
Oh, Myne!
Ah, Mr. Otto!
A merchant with a letter of
introduction from a noble arrived!
He was asked to wait in one of the
laynoble-designated waiting rooms!
It needs to be taken care of immediately!
Great work!
Top marks for my assistant!
She's my daughter, you know.
Dad...
So that's what happened, huh?
Oh yeah! The inside of the temple was
so amazing! It's huge, and so pretty!
Really? That sounds great.
Yeah!
Tuuli.
This is a present from me.
What is this?
How cute!
And it's tasty, too.
You cut them into interesting shapes.
You really do have a knack for cooking.
Thanks for making this, Myne.
And not just this, the hairpin as well.
I was super happy today.
Tuuli is such an angel!
Tuuli, your Mom and I got you a present.
These are tools and garments for your work.
Treat them with care.
Thanks, Mom! Thanks, Dad!
Work hard on your apprenticeship, Tuuli!
Will do!
Do you go to work every day
once you become an apprentice?
You work for around half
of each week to begin with.
For the other half of the week,
I'll be going out to the forest like before.
Oh, that's good to hear.
Your baptism is coming up next year too, Myne.
Have you decided where you want
your apprenticeship to be?
Yeah.
I want to open a book store.
A book store?
Well, it's where you sell books, so...
I guess that'd make me a merchant, perhaps?
Well, I don't quite get it,
but it's good to hear you've found something.
More importantly, this is for you, Myne.
What's this?
You'll start having to take on
some of Tuuli's work from now on.
This is going to be necessary for you
to start gathering firewood in the forest.
A knife!
I can use this to make wooden slips, can't I?
You cut a piece of wood horizontally into thin slices,
smooth it down by carving off the bark,
and voilà! You're done, and now you can write on it.
Make enough of them and
they can fill in for books just fine!
Long live the Ancient Chinese!
Yahoo!
This knife... is so heavy.
Lutz and Tuuli are so impressive...
I just have to take it one step
at a time and do what I can.
Well, Rome wasn't built in a day either...
This one might actually work.
So what's this?
Something to replace the clay tablets?
Oh, Lutz?
How did you know these would be
a replacement for the clay tablets?
'Cause you look like you're having a great time.
You looked like you wanted to rub
your cheeks all over that wood.
Back when you were making clay tablets
you seemed just as entranced by them.
Doing stuff subconsciously is so embarrassing!
So, what are you making?
Wooden slips.
"Wooden slips"?
Are you gonna try writing on these next?
Yeah, but I'll need to make a lot of them.
Oh?
Gotcha. I'll help you out.
Really?
Yeah, but in exchange...
Can you let me meet this "Mr. Otto"?
Huh? Mr. Otto?
I want to ask him about how
to become a traveling merchant.
I'm going to the gate tomorrow
so I'll ask him about it then.
Mr. Otto is kinda busy though,
so he might turn you down.
That's okay.
Thanks, Myne!
Mr. Otto, how do you become a traveling merchant?
What? You want to become
a traveling merchant, Myne?
Wait, is this my fault?!
The captain's gonna kill me...
Ah, no, not at all.
I'm just asking for a friend that wants to.
Don't scare me like that.
Tell them they should give up on it.
Oh, I figured you'd say that.
You expected this?
From how he talked about it, it seemed like
the sort of work that tends to face pushback.
Yeah, your parents would probably
lecture you for even bringing it up.
I was also thinking that the
lifestyle of a traveling merchant
isn't something that's easy for
a child from the city to adapt to.
If you thought that far ahead,
why didn't you just tell him that yourself?
I figured you talking about it from actual experience
would be better than someone like me,
who has never left the city, telling him.
Perhaps...
Mr. Otto, you still have connections
with other merchants, right?
If he tried to become a regular merchant instead,
he'd still be able to travel occasionally, right?
If you're going this far for him,
then you must be pretty fond of this kid.
Well, Lutz does always help me out with stuff.
I want to repay him for that.
I see.
Well, sure. We can meet up next time I'm free.
Thanks, Mr. Otto!
Oh, right. What do I use
to write on the wooden slips?
Slate pens are no good.
Mr. Otto, can we change
my pay from slate pens to ink?
If you work for free for three years.
Oh, and no advance payments.
No way...
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Ascendance of
a Bookworm
I'll Do Anything to Become
a Librarian!
Mr. Otto said that you two
can meet up next time he's free.
For real?
Thanks, Myne!
I hope that meeting goes well for Lutz.
All that's left is to let these dry.
As for the ink...
Maybe I can just get some from octopuses or squids?
I can finally write with this!
Where the hell is the ocean in the first place?!
Ash?
I might be able to use ash.
Mom, can I use some of the ash over there?
No. We use it for various things,
like making soap or melting the snow.
I see...
What about the soot then?
Oh my, you're gonna clean the hearth?
Wha—
Okay then, good luck, Myne!
I fought hard to get this stuff.
I ended up bedridden afterwards though.
Bedridden again?
Are you okay, Myne?
Don't worry, I'm fine now.
Now let's see if we can turn this soot
into something we can write with.
We can try adding water first, I guess.
It doesn't seem to mix well with water...
Maybe try writing with it?
It's kinda blurry.
Seems like a no-go.
What's next?
Well, the method used for
making ink is to dissolve it in oil...
But we can't get oil, right?
Yeah, Mom won't give me any.
If I had something else... Maybe not a fluid,
but something like a pencil or a crayon...
I've got it!
Let's try mixing it with clay.
Let's get to it!
We're done...
I wonder how long we have to leave these out to dry.
No idea.
Maybe we should try heating them.
Don't get any weird ideas.
Do you want another explosion?
I'll definitely be able to write
on those wooden slips with this.
We've gotten one step closer to making books!
Now I've just gotta leave these to dry somewhere.
Huh?
What?
They're gone?
Why?
What's wrong, Myne?
Mom, have you seen the
wooden slips that were here before?
Wooden slips?
I left some smooth bits of wood
of various sizes right here.
Ah, the firewood you gathered?
I've used it!
You used it?
Why...
I couldn't help but use the firewood you'd gathered!
It's so nice to see you helping out around the house!
I gathered them to write down
the bedtime story you told me, Mom.
I went through all that effort...
If you want to hear another bedtime story,
I'll tell you one next time.
That's not...
what I meant...
Myne?
What's going on?
Myne?!
I feel like I'm being eaten up by my fever bit-by-bit.
It's like I'm slowly disappearing...
Myne!
Lutz...
Myne, are you okay?
I heard you suddenly collapsed!
Thank you for worrying about me.
I'll go call your mother.
It was all for naught again.
Mom...
burned all the...
wooden slips.
I guess it just looked like firewood to her...
I'm never gonna finish my books...
This is never... gonna work out... is it?
Cheer up, Myne.
Lutz...
Next time, we should just use
something that can't be burned.
Lutz, you really are kind.
I-I'm just trying to get you
to introduce me to Mr. Otto.
Don't get sick on me now, okay?
Okay! Thanks, Lutz.
But the bamboo slips
Lutz brought for me were also...
That sound...
Mom, what's wrong?
I thought Lutz had brought us more firewood,
but apparently that isn't what that was.
So you burned it?
Oh, it's nothing you need
to worry yourself about, Myne.
Just keep resting up.
The anger of having something
you made burned to ash.
The pain of nobody being
able to understand your anger.
No matter what I do, the reality is that
I can't live surrounded by books.
I've had enough.
If the result is the same no matter how hard I try...
Then I might as well just disappear.
Myne!
I'll help you with whatever it is you're trying to do.
I'm just trying to get you
to introduce me to Mr. Otto.
Don't get sick on me now, okay?
That's right. I have to keep that promise.
I have to get better and introduce Lutz to Mr. Otto.
Huh?
It's fading.
The heat inside of me is dissipating.
Something is different about this fever.
It's like something is attacking me from within...
Coming and going in waves...
What exactly is wrong with this body?
Are you feeling better now?
I heard from the captain that your
fever held strong even after three days.
I'm feeling much better now, thanks.
You look pale.
There's something I'm having trouble with.
I want something and I've tried lots of different
approaches but I just can't make it myself.
What would you do in my situation?
Just hire someone to do it for you.
Hire... someone?
That sounds like a good idea,
but what do I do if I lack the means to?
Just guide someone into making it
for you out of their own accord.
If it works out, your wallet will thank you for it.
Spoken like a former merchant.
I'll take it to heart.
Oh right,
about the meeting we had to postpone.
And so, the day for Lutz and
Mr. Otto's meeting was set.
The central plaza at third bell, got it.
If you're introducing him,
he must be a pretty interesting kid.
I'm looking forward to a fun day off.
Huh?
What?
This isn't just going to be some casual meetup?
tell me, oh my angel
oh my lovely, let me dream again
I gently brush my hair
And put a hairpin through it
In the sea of green
A flower ornament blooms
It is a gift from my angel
It touches my forehead
Oh so gently
And it reminds me
Of the warm light that gathered
To bring my angel into this world
This fever is making me delirious
Ah, these times are so dear to me
There must have been something more
Some greater force that led me to you
Our fates tangle and unravel as we become family
I have been always living
Inside a book
But then my heart melted
And now I have experienced
The real world
Next Chapter
Meeting
High Priest, is there some sort of
deeper meaning to this upcoming meeting?
I am not well-versed in the affairs of commonfolk.
My, even the high priest doesn't know.
I may have a different theory in mind than you
but I won't share it until I have
gathered conclusive evidence.
If you have a theory, just tell me already!
Illustration:     Yo Shimizu