I guess she's still processing
what she just saw in the picture.
If she makes the slightest attempt to hide it,
I'll kill her.
It'd be a sign that she doesn't trust me,
and that she's now frightened and hostile.
But if she hands me the photo...
What is this, Nanna?
I'll save it for later.
As I'm drifting through an eternity
As
I'm
drift
ing
through
The souls of fragile beings crashing over me
The
souls
of
fra
gile
be
ings
crash
ing
o
ver
me
The heavens fracture
The
hea
vens
frac
ture
But clouds mask the broken sky
But
clouds
mask
the
bro
ken
sky
Using awkward circumstance to gain the upper hand
Us
ing
awk
ward
cir
cum
stance
to
gain
the
up
per
hand
I try to test the will of God
I
try
to
test
the
will
of
God
It almost felt as if I could deceive him
It
al
most
felt
as
if
I
could
de
ceive
him
When I found you at the end of my eternal search
When
I
found
search
I also found my lost tears
I
al
so
found
my
lost
tears
Kill all the enemies
of humanity.
Though I lie
Though
I
lie
To others
To
o
thers
Time after time
Time
af
ter
time
I don't need deceit to keep you
I
don't
need
de
ceit
to
keep
you
Smiling and pure
Smi
l
ing
and
pure
My one "talent" is my mercilessness
My
one
"
ta
lent
less
ness
I weave a tangled web of destiny and death
I
weave
a
tan
gled
death
My sins dispassionate and dull
My
sins
dis
pas
sion
ate
and
dull
Hidden deep down inside my soul
Hid
den
deep
down
in
side
my
soul
Sudden showers voice their assent
Sud
den
sho
wers
voice
their
as
sent
And mute the screams of those who meet their end
And
mute
the
screams
of
those
who
meet
their
end
The heavens warp but
The
hea
vens
warp
but
The clouds mask the broken sky
The
clouds
mask
the
bro
ken
sky
I found it inside Tsunekichi's clothes...
What on Earth is this?
Episode 6: Necromancer
It seems like Tsunekichi
wasn't actually seeing the future.
Wh-What?
But I think he's brought photos
of the future to school before...
His Talent probably used
to work properly in the past.
But he stopped caring
once he came to the island, right?
That's true, he's been skipping classes a lot.
I heard from his thoughts
that he was just projecting
his dreams onto the photos.
He probably couldn't bring himself
to tell anyone the truth,
considering his constant bragging about
being on a different level than everyone else.
S-So this photo is...
Yes, it's just a regular dream.
I think he didn't like how close Nakajima and I were.
Oh, he was jealous?
Maybe that's why he had that dream...
I'll get rid of this photo.
Could we keep this a secret between us two?
A secret...
Of course!
I actually wanted to ask,
what were you trying to do?
Oh, um...
I've never actually succeeded before, but...
I was trying to revive him.
He died in such a strange way,
and yet you didn't call the police.
Listen here.
There's no police on this island.
Who's going to keep us in line
if we do something bad, then?
If you were to do something bad using your Talents,
no one could stop you anyway.
Though we're supposed to rely on
the army in emergencies...
Michiru.
You can't keep using your Talent so recklessly.
Doesn't it shorten your lifespan?
Ah, I don't really mind.
I was scared at first,
but I don't really know how much it gets shortened,
so, um...
Look, don't they say you'll die young
if you keep eating junk food?
It's like, I know it's bad,
but I tell myself it's fine, you know?
I'd be devastated if you died
trying to revive someone, Michiru!
Th-Thank you...
The Committee also mentioned that the Talented
can further develop their Talents.
I see now.
I can't rely on the data gathered
at the time they were brought here.
Listen, everyone!
Don't you find all of this weird?
Tsunekichi didn't die of an illness.
Hiiragi claims he was murdered
by the enemies of humanity.
Seriously?
Kyouya!
This isn't funny! Don't scare everyone for no reason!
Before the body is cremated,
I'd like to perform an autopsy.
An autopsy? You can do that?
I was planning to wait for
the police to arrive first, but...
Can we talk first, please?
Is illness not a good enough explanation for you?
You're saying he just randomly
died of an illness while assaulting you?
He was very aroused at the time.
It wouldn't be unheard of.
You seem to be rather on edge. Are you okay?
Am I?
You know, sometimes you go feed a cat,
and the shed just randomly
explodes while you're in there.
Are you saying that wasn't an accident either?
I thought you could read my mind?
Yes, my Talent does allow me to read minds.
It sure was a shock to see it with my own eyes,
but I already knew about your immortality
before the shed exploded.
I learned about it that night when we talked
about Nakajima's watch on top of the cliff.
What are you trying to say?
Oh, I...
I'm not sure, exactly.
Um, I'd rather not consider such a possibility,
but assuming that someone's
behind all those incidents,
what could they have been trying
to achieve by attacking you?
It's not like they'd have been able to kill you.
She's right, this is strange.
Hiiragi can read minds.
Why would she attempt to kill me
before killing Tsunekichi?
It'd make sense for me to be her last target.
But who would try to kill someone immortal first,
only to follow with more crimes
arousing this much suspicion?
Only the Talented are supposed to be on this island.
I'm going to exploit that premise.
It won't be too big of a deal
if he learns that Tsunekichi was poisoned,
but I'd rather not give him any clues at all.
Either way, his cause of death
might tell us something.
Wait—
Come on, don't argue...
It's a funeral, you kno—
Please help me stop Kyouya!
Hey, you! Listen to what the leader says!
I'd rather not watch an autopsy.
What can the dead tell you, anyway?
I agree!
Tsunekichi was our classmate!
Please, let him rest in peace!
Why would you bother with an autopsy?
Wouldn't it be better to just ask the corpse directly?
Excuse me, what now?!
It's Shinji's necromancy...
One thing after another!
I don't know what's going on,
but you want to know how Tsunekichi died, right?
Can you determine that?
If the corpse remembers, yes.
Don't worry.
He won't rot or attack people
just because he's a zombie.
He never had much of a presence in class...
Scary...
So that's necromancy,
the power to control the dead...
Hold on a second here.
Um... I can see your reactions,
but Shinji's not a bad person, okay?
Get out of here, Yuuka.
I didn't ask you to interrupt me.
What?!
Listen here, you little...
I'm just worried about their impressions, you know!
So? What do you wanna do?
I can control corpses at will.
That includes being able to see what they see,
browsing through their memories,
and using the Talents they had.
I'm sorry, but what about the soul?
The soul? You mean his?
No idea, honestly.
Then I guess I can give this a try.
Please, let him rest!
It was just for a brief moment,
but I heard a bit of Tsunekichi's thoughts!
He seems to be in pain!
Seriously?
Awful...
Kyouya!
I know I was the one that wanted to do an autopsy,
but I'm not asking you to make him into a zombie.
Shinji, I also think that's enough.
So you want me to stop?
I don't really care either way.
I-I know I'm repeating myself,
but Shinji really isn't a bad person, okay?
Um, can I bring in the priest yet?
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Are you free after school, cutie?
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Shinji can appar-
ently control dead
bodies. That's really
impressive!
Kazama Shinji
Talent: Necromancy
Limitations: ???
Listen here,
don't you have a girlfriend?
Um, I don't approve of violence, just so you know...
She jokes that she
could open a hole in a person's
heart with a single finger.
She's a good person who's
always cheerful.
Sasaki Yuuka
Talent: Superhuman strength
She jokes that she
could open a hole in a person's
heart with a single finger.
She's a good person who's
always cheerful.
Sasaki Yuuka
Talent: Superhuman strength
Limitations: ???
She jokes that she
could open a hole in a person's
heart with a single finger.
She's a good person who's
always cheerful.
Sasaki Yuuka
Talent: Superhuman strength
Limitations: ???
She jokes that she
could open a hole in a person's
heart with a single finger.
She's a good person who's
always cheerful.
Sasaki Yuuka
Talent: Superhuman strength
Limitations: ???
She jokes that she
could open a hole in a person's
heart with a single finger.
She's a good person who's
always cheerful.
Talent: Superhuman strength
Limitations: ???
She jokes that she
could open a hole in a person's
heart with a single finger.
She's a good person who's
always cheerful.
Talent: Superhuman strength
She jokes that she
could open a hole in a person's
heart with a single finger.
She's a good person who's
always cheerful.
Talent: Superhuman strength
Skirt-chasing ass!
Hey, Yuuka!
Nana! What's up?
Do you know where Shinji is?
Shinji?
Yes, I was thinking that I don't
really see him at school often...
He's probably sleeping in his room.
He rarely comes to classes.
I see.
So him attending the funeral was a rare occurrence.
Why are you asking?
I'm the leader now, so I wanted
to learn more about everyone.
Right, true!
There are enemies of humanity here, after all!
Thanks.
I appreciate you thinking about Shinji.
He's a bit edgy, isn't he?
He makes a scene about being a necromancer!
And he doesn't have any friends.
Right...
But he really is a necromancer!
I was shocked when Tsunekichi moved.
I bet he just wanted to show off in front of everyone.
He's always been such a child...
Jeez.
She'll be the first one
to make a stink when Shinji dies.
Oh, I see now.
How convenient.
They can both die together.
Out on a tryst at this hour...
I heard their thoughts in the middle
of the night, so I came to check on them.
I'm on patrol as well.
You and Tsunekichi were attacked
at night with no one around, after all.
You still have the wrong idea about me, don't you?
Let's see, if I was the culprit,
I'd choose Shinji for my next target.
Can't have the dead disclosing the truth, after all.
Is someone there?
I'm so sorry to interrupt!
Were you watching?
Were this a horror movie, you'd already be dead.
It's the flirting couples that get killed first.
Um, it's not...
We're just childhood friends.
It's just her that thinks it's more than that.
I love no one but the dead.
God, you always say such creepy things...
I ask you to forget what you saw here today.
If you don't, I can't guarantee
you'll rest peacefully in death.
I hear your Talent makes you immortal.
I can use the Talents of the corpses I control.
I'm curious what would happen if I tried yours.
I-I see...
But wouldn't I have to die first for that to happen?
Yuuka.
See you.
So the two of you are actually dating?
More like, I can't leave him alone
since we've been friends for so long.
We grew up in the same town.
Our houses were close
and we went to the same school.
His hand looked injured.
Ah, actually, that's an old burn.
He tries to hide it.
I think it was five years ago or so?
We went to see a movie together,
but a fire broke out.
He might not seem like the type,
but he can be very kind.
He helped everyone evacuate during all the panic,
but because of that, he was late to evacuate himself.
And you saved him?
I guess it was all the adrenaline!
Even outside, I could see all the smoke
coming from the theater.
And when I thought about how
Shinji might be stuck inside...
I punched the emergency exit,
and bang, the door flew open!
That's when I first realized I had a Talent.
People were already calling me
a gorilla girl before that, though.
Anyway, Shinji had breathed in too much smoke,
so I carried him out of there.
Honestly, he's like a troublesome little brother.
So we may associate corpse-raising with villains,
but he's really a nice guy?
Yeah. He doesn't like being around people,
so he doesn't show up at school much,
but I don't want people to forget about him.
We have combat training next...
I'm not athletic at all.
I think I need to lie down in the infirmary.
Infirmary
Are you okay?
I was out on patrol until very late last night,
so I didn't get much sleep at all.
I see.
I'll let the teacher know.
If I go through this window,
I can get to the boys' dorm fast and unseen.
Considering Kyouya patrols at night,
it's now or never.
Where's Hiiragi?
Kazama Shinji
Estimated kill count
Over 300,000
Kazama Shinji
Estimated kill count
Over 300,000
Kazama Shinji
Estimated kill count
Over 300,000
Kazama Shinji
Estimated kill count
Over 300,000
Kazama Shinji
Estimated kill count
Over 300,000
Kazama Shinji
Estimated kill count
Over 300,000
Kazama Shinji
Estimated kill count
Over 300,000
Kazama Shinji
Estimated kill count
Over 300,000
Kazama Shinji
Estimated kill count
Over 300,000
Kazama Shinji
Estimated kill count
Over 300,000
Kazama Shinji
Estimated kill count
Over 300,000
Kazama Shinji
Estimated kill count
Over 300,000
Kazama Shinji
Estimated kill count
Over 300,000
Kazama Shinji
Estimated kill count
Over 300,000
You can stay asleep forever now.
Your girlfriend will follow soon after you.
I need to hurry.
It's possible Kyouya might notice something.
Infirmary
Um...
You seem to care a lot about Nanna, Kyouya.
We're friends, after all.
Are you okay, Hiiragi?
Kyouya, can you come with me for a second?
And please bring Yuuka too!
I was resting in bed, but then I heard a call for help...
I'm essentially admitting I was here,
on the road leading to the boys' dorm,
but I'm out of options.
Yuuka, could you use your Talent
to break the concrete and free the cat?
Huh?!
Ah, but...
I'm super sorry!
I can't use my Talent right now!
Huh?
What's this about? The limitations of her Talent?
Don't worry too much.
It doesn't seem to be hurt in any way.
Go get a can of cat food from my room.
The cat seems fond of humans,
so it should jump out if you offer it food.
What a troublesome little kitty you are.
Now say thanks to Nanna.
Thank you so much, Kyouya!
So you can read cat minds too, Hiiragi?
Well, only sometimes.
I'm sorry.
I was completely useless...
I'm allergic to animals.
It makes me unable to use my Talent, too.
What an adorable weakness.
I understand her less and less.
Could someone who saves a cat like that
really be a cold-blooded killer?
Sasaki Yuuka.
She doesn't seem like a bad person,
but a mission is a mission.
She'll die in her sleep like Shinji did.
Shinji saw everything happen.
I... I was careless...
I felt like something was off,
but I didn't expect this!
She said she had superhuman strength,
so I didn't question it,
but emergency exits usually open outward.
It's easier for a crowd of people to escape that way.
It seemed strange to me that she
punched it open from the outside.
And it wasn't an allergy
stopping her from saving the cat.
It's just that the one with superhuman strength
is the one holding me down right now.
Which means the necromancer isn't Shinji, but...
Shinji can't die, you know?
He can't, he couldn't,
and I won't ever let him.
It was you all along!
I'm sure of it now.
Shinji is already dead.
I couldn't feel anyone else's presence
or hear anyone else's breathing in her room.
And his hands are as cold as ice.
Let's not make a fuss.
It's really late.
I'm sorry, Nana.
Did that hurt?
You know, Shinji's always been short-tempered.
He's always thought he was super smart.
Well, he actually is, but he has too much of an ego.
He'd lose it over getting only 98% on a test.
He'd go all, "why didn't I get 100%?!"
I remember him tearing up his test at school once.
Isn't that adorable?
But he's always been so kind to me.
That day I had so much fun too.
We went to town in the evening,
and had crêpes from a street stall...
Shinji didn't like it,
but we held hands the whole time.
The movie was good too.
They had just built the cinema.
I remember buying drinks together.
Oh, but Shinji's such a little kid, he got melon soda.
And then something funny happened.
We sat down already before the movie started.
The person on my right spilled his drink
when he was putting it down.
It ended up all over my skirt.
But he didn't even want to apologize,
so Shinji lost his temper
and bent over me towards him...
But his melon soda was between us,
so that spilled on my skirt too.
I laughed so much, you know!
Are you listening?
Oh, sorry. I was in the middle of my story.
It was a really scary horror movie.
I'd been clinging to Shinji from the very beginning.
He claimed he wasn't scared, but he was shaking.
But then, I think it was about
when the credits started,
the fire alarm went off and everyone panicked.
EXIT
Everyone was pushing each other towards the exit,
and some even jumped over the rows of seats...
That's how we got separated.
I got out first and waited for him outside
for what felt like forever.
I was hoping for him to be safe the whole time.
But then,
when I saw him, he was being
carried away on a stretcher.
They said he'd suffocated.
His uniform had always been
too big for his short stature.
The collar must've made things even worse.
He helped everyone escape using his Talent,
but he was too late to escape himself.
Isn't that just tragic?
It was you controlling Tsunekichi
during the funeral too, wasn't it?
I mean...
I wanted everyone to know
how awesome Shinji is, after all!
We're madly in love, and he can't
do anything without me by his side!
I wanted everyone to remember that!
She's insane.
Yuuka.
How long do you need her held down?
Oh, sorry, I forgot.
Remember, she came to my room
and stuck that needle in my neck.
I know, I know!
He did mention it was possible
to look through the corpse's eyes.
But then she looked all innocent saving the cat,
so I was sure it must've been
some misunderstanding.
I mean, that's why we decided to wait
and see if she'd come for you at night.
Her being here means she
really wanted to kill me, right?
She did say my girlfriend would follow soon after me.
She's not right in the head.
I know, right?!
It's her, not us, right?!
It's like she has a split personality.
I did put on an act myself,
claiming I could hear Tsunekichi's thoughts,
but Yuuka's constantly playing out
a ridiculous puppet show.
Careful.
She still had more needles.
Thanks, Shinji.
Well, that's it, Nana.
I'm sorry, but this is the end.
The end?
There was always something off about this island.
I didn't really care as long as I could be with Shinji,
but then you had to come and attack us.
I'll have you explain what you were trying to do
in front of the whole class.
What's wrong?
When Kyouya made a huge deal
out of Tsunekichi's death,
you seemed so desperate to stop him...
Did you kill him, too?
And Nakajima and Shibusawa are missing,
so could it be that...
Yes, it's exactly what you're thinking.
But you know...
I may be a murderer,
but I don't use the dead as my toys!
They
all
were
gi
ven
a
gift
The
call
of
a
po
wer
with
in
Be
cause
of
that
one
sin
We
brand
them
as
mon
stro
si
ties
As
if
by
a
whim
of
the
gods
Or
may
be
some
mis
chief
of
time
What
they
all
had
thought
was
a
gift
Brought
with
it
u
nique
a
go
ny
This
was
n't
what
I
hoped
would
be
come
But
what
good
would
strug
gl
ing
have
done
When
it
was
clear
that
I
ne
ver
would
be
loved?
So
who
should
I
di
rect
this
bit
ter
rage
at?
So
who
should
I
di
rect
this
bit
ter
rage
at?
Was
my
life
all
a
lie?
Have
you
been
on
my
side?
What
if
you
be
ing
there
helped
sur
face
all
my
doubts?
There
might
still
be
a
chance
May
be
a
chance
that
I
may
be
could
see
that
I've
been
mis
guid
ed
all
a
long
May
be
a
chance
that
I
may
be
could
see
that
I've
been
mis
guid
ed
all
a
long
I
could
leave
the
world
way
that
it
is
I
could
leave
the
world
way
that
it
is
Next Episode: Necromancer, Part 2
"Necromancer, Part 2".