Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
Therefore, the so-called
Talented are no longer
human. They are the
enemies of humanity.
The following is a list
of grave incidents they
have caused in the past.
As I'm drifting through an eternity
As
I'm
drift
ing
through
The souls of fragile beings crashing over me
The
souls
of
fra
gile
be
ings
crash
ing
o
ver
me
The heavens fracture
The
hea
vens
frac
ture
But clouds mask the broken sky
But
clouds
mask
the
bro
ken
sky
Using awkward circumstance to gain the upper hand
Us
ing
awk
ward
cir
cum
stance
to
gain
the
up
per
hand
I try to test the will of God
I
try
to
test
the
will
of
God
It almost felt as if I could deceive him
It
al
most
felt
as
if
I
could
de
ceive
him
When I found you at the end of my eternal search
When
I
found
search
I also found my lost tears
I
al
so
found
my
lost
tears
Kill all the enemies
of humanity.
Though I lie
Though
I
lie
To others
To
o
thers
Time after time
Time
af
ter
time
I don't need deceit to keep you
I
don't
need
de
ceit
to
keep
you
Smiling and pure
Smi
l
ing
and
pure
My one "talent" is my mercilessness
My
one
"
ta
lent
less
ness
I weave a tangled web of destiny and death
I
weave
a
tan
gled
death
My sins dispassionate and dull
My
sins
dis
pas
sion
ate
and
dull
Hidden deep down inside my soul
Hid
den
deep
down
in
side
my
soul
Sudden showers voice their assent
Sud
den
sho
wers
voice
their
as
sent
And mute the screams of those who meet their end
And
mute
the
screams
of
those
who
meet
their
end
The heavens warp but
The
hea
vens
warp
but
The clouds mask the broken sky
The
clouds
mask
the
bro
ken
sky
Some time ago, the first
enemy of humanity appeared.
It destroyed a city, slaughtering anyone it could find.
However, it was neither an alien nor a demon,
but rather a human who had
awakened to a special Talent.
Since then, children with Talents
started slowly appearing all over the world.
Humanity's laws and ethics proved ineffective
against those with magic-like powers.
Grave incidents became increasingly frequent.
The government established
an agency to handle the Talented.
They devised a plan to win them over
by incorporating them into the military,
forming a unit of Talented individuals
with the authority to enforce the law.
However, all attempts at cooperation
quickly ended in failure.
The Talented, having become drunk with power,
or agitated after being treated like lab rats,
sought to disrupt the power structure in a revolution.
After five years of bloodshed, humanity won the war.
As decades passed, the nation
and its people's attitudes changed.
Today, the state officially acknowledges
the existence of the Talented,
and keeps them isolated by sending them to
government-run schools called "training facilities".
Those gathered at these facilities
spend their days training non-stop
to fight the so-called "enemies of humanity".
Or at least that's what most people believe.
Hiiragi Nana.
You are to covertly eliminate the enemies
of humanity nesting on that island.
Your mission is top secret.
Failure is not an option.
Can you handle it?
If you're compromised and
the Talented start conspiring against us,
then the entire world,
not to mention our nation, will fall.
We, the Talentless, will be ruled by the Talented.
In other words, it will spell the end of humanity.
Can you handle it?
Can you?
Nana.
Episode 2: Back in Time
Hey, Moguo.
You seen Nanao around?
He was all high and mighty about being the leader,
and now he doesn't even show up?
Actually, you know what?
I never thought he'd have
the guts to do what he did.
Did something happen to him?
I can't, I really can't!
You'll be fine.
Get a move on, Michiru.
Come on, this is essential
training for waterfront battles!
No way, I can't!
Take it seriously! This pond is really deep!
Sorry, man!
I can't swim, you know! Jeez!
What's the point of this exercise, sir?
Why would you freeze the pond?
How long will it take to melt?
I would give it about three or four days.
This pond is supposedly five meters deep,
but in defiance of the laws of physics,
he froze it completely solid.
So much for training.
There's no need for it.
Did you not see my feat?
The enemies of humanity
are powerless against my Talent!
In other words, these people are the real threat.
You little...!
What are you showing off for?!
It's like giving a nuke to a toddler.
Anyone who acquires such power
without effort inevitably becomes arrogant.
Give someone a gun, and they'll want to shoot it.
If we allow mentally immature children
to have these Talents, there's no telling
what would happen to the world.
For peace...
The Committee was indeed correct.
Hiiragi, could you break this up?
Sure thing!
So that humanity may live in peace,
I must kill them all.
Hey, Koori Seiya!
Can you freeze anything?
Well, yeah.
Could you freeze this desk too?
Easily.
Does that mean you could even
freeze me if you wanted to?
Be that your wish,
I could freeze such a beautiful maiden like you in
an icy coffin, preserving your beauty for all eternity!
He's lying.
Lying always makes people nervous.
Their bodies often convey it unconsciously.
Why didn't you just freeze
Moguo the other day, then?
W-Well...
That wouldn't have been fair.
His tell is quite obvious.
It's probably safe to assume
he cannot freeze people at will.
I see.
On another note, I wonder if Nakajima is sick.
Absent the day after he became our leader...
Wouldn't you agree that it's a little irresponsible?
The class still believes that Nakajima is just sick.
I must act before things escalate.
Say that again! I dare you!
Nanao's the leader, you say?!
Calm down...
Uh, no...
His blood's been boiling all day.
I'm your boss!
Who's the leader, you ask?
Who even cares?
Sh-Shibusawa...
Moguo, you should know what my Talent is.
Y-You... screwed with time again?
You should know there are
two types of people I hate:
slow eaters, and people who
are noisy during mealtime.
Y-Yeah, I do.
You're the strongest of us all, Shibusawa!
So long as you understand.
Let's keep it friendly.
He messed with time?
Rumor has it he can freeze time.
Speaking of bosses, what happened to Nakajima?
You okay?
That was close.
Who knows...
I hate to admit it, but he might
actually be the strongest student here.
Shibusawa Youhei
Estimated kill count
Over 800,000
Shibusawa Youhei
Estimated kill count
Over 800,000
Shibusawa Youhei
Estimated kill count
Over 800,000
Shibusawa Youhei
Estimated kill count
Over 800,000
Shibusawa Youhei
Estimated kill count
Over 800,000
Shibusawa Youhei
Estimated kill count
Over 800,000
Shibusawa Youhei
Estimated kill count
Over 800,000
Shibusawa Youhei
Estimated kill count
Over 800,000
How's your meal, Shibusawa?
Hope you don't mind me joining in!
Hiiragi Nana, I hate people
who are noisy during meals.
Well, you're quite a noisy eater yourself, Shibusawa!
Do you need something?
Actually, yes!
I'm super curious what kind of person
the rumored strongest student is!
Strongest? Oh, please.
Everyone bullies me, just like Nakajima.
I almost got pushed into the pond this morning.
Oh, you have pickles!
Can I have one?
Um... What just...
That was my Talent.
I can freeze time.
Try not to tell anyone, though.
But freezing time isn't
exactly what your Talent is, is it?
I'm quite a blabbermouth, you know.
Is it okay if I say out loud what your Talent really is?
You're right.
I don't actually freeze time.
All I can do is go back in time.
I change the past, and its effects
are simply reflected in the present.
You're the first student to see through me.
I guess you really can read minds.
Yay, I got it right!
That's kinda hard to believe, but it checks out.
I definitely saw the cup of water
fall off the table just a moment ago.
But there's not a single drop of water
on his clothes or on the floor.
If Shibusawa truly could freeze time
and move freely while doing so,
it's hard to believe he'd be able to gather up
all the water scattered in the air.
What's more, during that fight,
while it was possible for him to
hit Moguo while time was frozen,
I couldn't figure out why he'd go through
the effort of fixing the boy's tie.
So Shibusawa didn't actually freeze time.
Instead, he went back to before the cup fell
and caught it, creating a present
in which it never fell.
In Moguo's case, he went back to
before Moguo grabbed the boy by his collar,
and punched Moguo instead.
I'm really impressed, Hiiragi Nana!
Huh?
You'll prove a valuable ally.
Let's rebuild this world together!
This world is rife with inequality and discrimination!
However, don't you think that
with my Talent to change the past,
I could exorcise all the evil from this world?
Wouldn't one wrong step mess up
the entire course of history?
I don't make mistakes.
Because I can change the past,
I am infallible and thus the only one
capable of defining what justice is.
Makes sense!
His Talent has completely warped his worldview.
I hate people who leave even a single grain of rice!
Be sure to remember that!
I'll keep that in mind.
This is a problem, though.
If he were to witness me in the act
of carrying out my mission in the past...
Could you use your Talent to
investigate Nakajima's disappearance?
And you are...?
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone about your Talent.
I don't care. Even if you do,
no one's a match for me anyway.
Nakajima's disappearance, you say?
Isn't he just sick?
Apparently he didn't contact the school.
Maybe he's just laid up in bed with a cold?
Definitely not.
As far as I can tell,
he didn't return to his room yesterday.
Nakajima's room is next to mine.
The walls in the dorms are thin,
and yet I didn't hear a single sound last night.
I saw he didn't come to school either,
so I went back to the dorm to
knock on his door, but got no answer.
You're Hiiragi, right?
It seems you've been pretty close
with Nakajima ever since you arrived.
That's true.
And yesterday, the two of you
left school together, correct?
Right.
Where were you
and what were you doing?
Dining Hall
Answer, please.
You might be the last person to have seen Nakajima.
Let me think...
I simply congratulated him on becoming the leader.
Was he acting strange?
No, not at all.
It was more like a weight
had been lifted off his chest,
and he was all excited about
fighting the enemies of humanity.
Did you two go back to
the dorms together afterwards?
Is it safe for me to just lie here?
He might be using his Talent to investigate me.
Um, Onodera...
Kyouya is fine.
You can call me Nana, then.
I've been meaning to ask...
What are you doing to my hair?
I'm sorry. I just get the urge to touch things like this.
My little sister used to wear twintails as well.
You're sorry, but you're still...
Wait. Your sister?
I feel compelled to grab onto loose ends.
Excuse me?!
S-So you think something happened to Nakajima?
I mean, he is missing.
I need to shift the suspicion away from me.
C-Could it be the enemies of humanity?
I've definitely heard the rumors.
I heard they want to take us out
before we can hone our Talents.
People say they're already among us,
disguised as humans!
Disguised as humans...
What's wrong, Hiiragi?
N-Nothing.
Kyouya, surely you're not...
What is it?
It's just... I heard this strange thought.
You know, I can read people's minds.
What are you playing at?
Kyouya,
I've been wondering why you skipped morning classes,
and it turns out you care a lot about Nakajima.
Even though you were distancing yourself
from everyone since day one...
Nah, that's not it.
I was just curious because of all the hype
yesterday about him becoming the leader.
Are you sure that's the only reason?
Did you find something from reading his mind?
Why did you come to talk to us all of a sudden?
I simply thought I'd try to make some friends.
You think he might be an enemy in disguise?
I might be getting the wrong idea.
I just got a bit scared, since I heard
a thought in an unfamiliar voice.
Well, we'd better be extra careful around him.
Okay, I should be able to avoid
any more questions for now.
But I'm sure this has got you
worried about Nakajima, right?
It has!
Should we look into it?
You'll help me?
Of course.
Any friend of yours is a friend of mine, Hiiragi.
Let's investigate his disappearance together.
Thank you!
I'll go take a look at the past.
What did you see?
It does seem like Nakajima never
returned to the dorm yesterday.
Are you all right?
It must be really tiring for you to travel to the past.
Indeed. I used to be very frail,
but I've trained a lot for my Talent.
There must be some other limitations to it.
Otherwise he would've already
exposed me as Nakajima's killer.
You can go back in time to where
you're standing just by thinking about it?
Yeah.
That means I have to kill him
without giving him a chance to resist.
Otherwise, he could just travel
back to the past and kill me instead.
How far back can you travel?
A day at most.
The further back I go, the more exhausting it is.
If I go back more than twelve hours, it gets to
the point where I feel nauseous when I arrive.
I appreciate your help.
I don't get it, though.
He went back in time,
so why didn't he just follow Nakajima's every move?
I'll take another look.
Someone saw me last time.
Someone saw him...
How did it go this time?
Hiiragi, you went towards the shore
with Nakajima yesterday after school?
Yeah, what about it?
Nothing. I'm gonna try following you.
After celebrating at the seaside yesterday,
Nakajima and I parted ways.
That's right, but it doesn't
look like he returned to the dorms.
This is bad.
Hiiragi, you can read minds, right?
It's not very reliable.
I guess that's why you notice me every time.
Being seen in the past
sends you back to the present?
I can't stay if our eyes meet
and they register my presence.
I see.
It's not that easy to change the past, then.
But if he keeps this up...
Why don't we continue tomorrow?
We can't.
24 hours is my absolute limit.
The longer we take,
the further we get from the truth.
But...
I must do what I can for justice.
Besides, shouldn't you be worried
about Nakajima as well, Hiiragi?
You're all cheerful, but I assume
that's not how you really feel.
Actually, do you happen to remember
what time you went to the cliffs?
What's wrong?
Were you two doing something there
that you wouldn't want anyone to see?
I think it was around 6 PM.
I'm not suspicious of you or anything, Hiiragi.
I know!
Please, go take a look!
Excuse me then.
All I can do is trust myself.
Did you figure anything out?
You really are such good friends.
You even held hands.
Then right after that...
you noticed me.
Our eyes met.
I was trying to hide in the bushes.
Whoopsie.
He's right. My memories were just overwritten.
I was paying the utmost attention
to my surroundings at that time.
I noticed him, made sure he was gone,
and then I killed Nakajima.
I have a mission.
I cannot allow myself to slip up and let anyone
witness me in the act of carrying it out.
If I do, I won't be able to survive
in this den of monsters.
I'm a little relieved, though.
Please forgive me for doubting you.
Of course!
I could totally see an enemy of humanity
masquerading as a transfer student.
I'd really like to continue,
but I guess we should call it a day.
You're right. Thank you for all your help!
Why did you keep that to yourself?!
I'm sorry!
I didn't know if I could trust you!
Fair enough. I did suspect you as well.
It's this way.
This is where Nakajima was attacked by an enemy!
What happened here?
After we held hands at the cliffs,
we ended up in these woods
while trying to escape from the enemy.
And then...
the enemy ate Nakajima, leaving nothing behind...
I was so scared I couldn't do anything.
But...
You can change the past, Shibusawa.
That means you can save Nakajima, right?
In the past, where you're standing right now,
Nakajima is being torn to pieces!
Could you maybe call out to us and somehow
create a way to change the past?!
We're running out of time!
I beg you...
All right.
I'll see what I can do.
Thank you!
I'll be right back,
and I'll bring Nakajima with me.
Last night, the pond hadn't been frozen yet.
Not only can he not swim,
but going back in time
exhausts him to the point of nausea.
He almost certainly drowned.
However, no one noticed his body,
and Seiya froze the pond, just like I remember.
They
all
were
gi
ven
a
gift
The
call
of
a
po
wer
with
in
Be
cause
of
that
one
sin
We
brand
them
as
mon
stro
si
ties
As
if
by
a
whim
of
the
gods
Or
may
be
some
mis
chief
of
time
What
they
all
had
thought
was
a
gift
Brought
with
it
u
nique
a
go
ny
This
was
n't
what
I
hoped
would
be
come
But
what
good
would
strug
gl
ing
have
done
When
it
was
clear
that
I
ne
ver
would
be
loved?
So
who
should
I
di
rect
this
bit
ter
rage
at?
So
who
should
I
di
rect
this
bit
ter
rage
at?
Was
my
life
all
a
lie?
Have
you
been
on
my
side?
What
if
you
be
ing
there
helped
sur
face
all
my
doubts?
There
might
still
be
a
chance
May
be
a
chance
that
I
may
be
could
see
that
I've
been
mis
guid
ed
all
a
long
May
be
a
chance
that
I
may
be
could
see
that
I've
been
mis
guid
ed
all
a
long
I
could
leave
the
world
way
that
it
is
I
could
leave
the
world
way
that
it
is
Next Episode: The Talented vs. The Talentless
"The Talented vs. The Talentless".