Oh dear, Nana...
Did you forget you were supposed to clean up your room?
B-But I did clean up!
This wasn't me, it was...
We may owe your father a lot, but I hope you're
not expecting us to spoil you like he did.
I'm sorry.
Good grief. I sure hope you locked
all the doors and windows, at least.
After your family was murdered...
I'm not having that happen here!
B-But it wasn't my fault... it wasn't...
It wasn't me...
It was your fault.
You killed them.
Don't run away from it.
Um...
There's something that's been on my mind lately.
I wanted to ask you a question, Nanna.
But first, please let me apologize.
I panicked and lied to you this morning.
I was scared you'd get upset again
if I spoke without thinking it through first.
You see,
the reason I went to Kyouya was because
I got myself confused from all this overthinking...
Oh, but I didn't tell him anything!
I realized he'd figure out it was about you
if I explained enough to get advice.
Did she actually manage to find out
something suspicious about me?
Nanna, could you try and remember it clearly?
Um...
That morning!
When you discovered that
your parents had passed away!
Huh?
Please think back to that morning.
You said when you left your room, you thought
it seemed strangely quiet downstairs, right?
Didn't you step on something then?
Do you remember any pain in your foot?
Not really.
I-It's very important!
I don't remember anything like—
Yes!
It wasn't your fault, after all!
You said your room was so messy
it was impossible not to step on things, right?
You were playing games until late at night,
and game pieces were scattered all over the floor.
But when I woke up in the morning,
everything had been put away.
Th-That means... that...
Your parents cleaned your room
while you were asleep!
W-Wait! I was in a shock from my parents' deaths.
Maybe I didn't notice I'd stepped on something.
Um... But wouldn't that be the other way around?
You weren't in shock until after you left your room
and saw your parents' bodies downstairs.
Even then, it doesn't necessarily
mean they locked the window too!
Didn't they always tell you to lock it, though?
Would they really forget to check after
going to the trouble of cleaning your room?
We're talking about your parents here,
so they must've been very kind people.
I'm sure they would've done it themselves,
making sure not to wake you up.
So...
I-It's plausible.
But...
But even then...
It doesn't change the fact that
I was careless and lacked discipline.
But their deaths weren't your fault!
I've read about this before,
how when something bad happens to children, they tend to think that it was all their fault.
Please think it through.
You were only having fun, Nanna.
Who killed your parents?
It wasn't you, was it?
This is why Michiru's seemed
deep in thought all this time?
She wanted to make me feel better?
She thought so hard about it...
A-And yet...
I thought she'd betrayed me...
You don't have to suffer anymore.
Everything's alright now.
No matter what happens,
I'll always be on your side, Nanna.
Because we're friends.
F-Friends?
But that's...
The supply ship's coming tomorrow,
so there'll be stalls in the schoolyard.
Let's go check them out together.
Can I?
Can someone like me be friends with you?
Friends...
Michiru and I are...
friends?
Episode 13: Revival
What's wrong? You're spacing out.
Nothing. I'm just going to the bathroom real quick.
Michiru is my friend... so...
If I got her a present,
would she be happy?
You're acting strange, my dear.
Fallen head-over-heels for some fellow?
Wh-What are you on about?!
I'm thinking about exposing the culprit soon,
so I'd like your help.
What kind of help?
I still haven't figured out the motive.
All Items
100¥
Anime
Study
Society
For now, I think we should detain them for interrogation.
That's rather crude...
Have you found proof, at least?
Not yet.
At first I thought the motive was Ishii being flirty with other girls.
But as I kept asking around,
I realized there was more to it than that.
The animal cruelty that started around the same time bothers me, too.
Well, first you really need to find proof.
If you approach the culprit carelessly,
it could end in disaster.
Fine.
But...
You realize that not knowing their motive also means
we don't know who they might target next, right?
I couldn't get a smartphone,
since they're first-come first-serve.
Does it really matter?
We can see each other any time.
You're even nicer than usual today, Nanna.
Michiru...
I got this... for you.
Huh? Really?!
You've been studying really hard, so...
I'm so happy! I'll treasure it forever!
I also have something for you, Nanna.
A pillow?
I wasn't sure what to get you,
but I've always wondered when you even sleep, so...
Oh, and I've read, actually,
that the best way to forget about unpleasant things is to get some good rest.
Thank you!
This will make me think about you
every time I go to sleep.
Th-That's actually kinda embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
I yelled at you and got you all worried about me
because of something from so long ago...
You can tell me about anything.
I'll also be open with you.
I hope... the fight against
the enemies of humanity ends soon.
This should be plenty of proof.
I wonder what Michiru's doing right now.
Didn't you say we wouldn't see each other for a while?
Don't you know that cats walk their own paths?
I don't think you're cute enough to be comparing yourself to a cat.
Even cats are capable of feeling gratitude.
Especially towards kind girls
who heal their friends' wounds.
So you're here about Michiru?
It's already late,
yet I spotted her walking towards the beach alone.
I tried turning into Moguo and calling out to her.
She said that someone wanted to talk to her in secret.
Who?!
She dodged that question.
She's certainly one of those people who keep secrets absolutely secret.
Where was she going?!
An abandoned house on the beach, apparently.
Why are you telling me about this?
To persuade you, obviously.
If you swear that from now on
you'll do everything I say,
I could solve all your problems for you, you know?
You might still make it if you hurry.
You'll find the place by looking
for a tall pine tree on the beach.
I've got a terrible feeling about this.
I don't know why, but Michiru
must've been summoned by the killer.
And if that's the case,
I can't be sure I'll be able to do anything
even if I make it in time.
I don't even know their Talent.
I should get everyone—
No, I don't have the time to explain.
Kyouya!
I'm sure he won't need too much convincing.
Good evening, Inukai.
I started out with cats and dogs, actually.
Since they're cute, you know.
Whenever everyone thinks something's cute,
don't you just get the urge to defile it?
Wh-What...
You said you had something important to talk about?
Yeah.
I saw the cat I hurt the other day
walking around perfectly fine.
I figured you must've healed it.
And then I remembered that you're pretty cute, too.
It'd be really terrible to cut up
such a nice person, right?
But... when I mock and trample
the things that everyone calls cute,
I really feel like I'm my own person.
Like I'm expressing myself.
Yes?
It's me.
M-Mr. Tsuruoka?
I'd like a situation report.
E-Everything is going well, sir!
Your breathing is unsteady.
Are you chasing the enemy?
Hiiragi?
Y-Yes, sir!
You'll be paid handsomely
if you complete your mission.
You mentioned you wanted to use that money
to fund education for children
who lost their parents like you?
The salary you're currently earning is being sent
to your relatives' bank accounts, as requested.
How respectable of you, considering they kept shuffling you around after your parents got killed.
You deserve plenty of praise.
Th-Thank you very much, sir!
Do what you need to do. That's all.
call ended
Right...
Friends?
Am I delusional?
One enemy will kill another.
This is pretty convenient.
I should let the culprit roam freely.
I don't care what happens to Michiru.
I've always liked games of tag!
Both humans and animals wet themselves and run when you corner them.
Even cute things have a dirty side to them!
Huh?
Is it already over?
N-Nanna will come save me.
Hiiragi, you mean?
I don't think she will.
If I had to guess, anyway.
I sense something... filthy about her.
As if she's constantly lying, you know?
I-I won't stand for this!
You can make fun of anything you want,
but Nanna is... I won't let you say
another bad thing about her!
Ah, you're so beautiful right now.
Well, you can die now.
I'm sorry...
It's all my fault that
this is happening to you, Michiru.
I didn't care enough and
settled on Sorano as the culprit.
But... there were other suspects
I should've paid more attention to.
And I should've been more wary,
in case they were the true culprit,
especially since we didn't know their motive.
The killer pretended he was listening to Moguo's lecture on his knees,
but he actually left his body there
while his soul carried out the murder.
The fact that he skipped opening the bathroom door, but still flushed the toilet,
means he can both move through walls
and interact with objects.
And just like he's doing now,
he can also use sharp knives.
He probably opened Ishii's window
so he could keep listening to Moguo's lecture.
Having heard all of it meant he'd have a perfect alibi.
And he could return to his body
if someone asked him a question.
Ishii was probably surprised
by the window suddenly opening,
so he used that moment of confusion
to cut his throat in one clean stroke.
That's my theory.
Then, using Moguo's shouting as cover,
he made a mess of the room
to shift suspicion onto Sorano.
Am I correct,
Tsurumigawa Rentarou?!
Not that it really matters,
but I've been wondering why you didn't say anything despite being able to read minds.
I've sensed something filthy
about you this entire time.
Show me your back! I'll heal it!
Absolutely... not!
Could you maybe move?
Inukai's the one I wanna kill.
I'll buy you enough time to escape.
N-Nice knife you have there.
Where did you find it?
It was lying around this deserted house.
Isn't it nice? It's my favorite.
I clean and sharpen it every day.
But you can't do anything without a weapon.
You just think you're strong because you have one.
You're such a child.
I don't like the way you speak.
You really are filthy, Hiiragi.
Whatever. Kill me if you want.
Don't you like cutting throats of the weak?
Y-You little...
Run, now!
B-But...
But...
I have a plan!
I prepared a trap in advance!
He can't follow you without killing me first!
What? What are you talking about?
But... Nanna...
You can't die, Nanna...
Hurry up already, you stupid dog!
"Friends"? Like Hell!
I've been looking down on you this entire time!
I've always just thought of you as a useful dog!
Do you even realize how many times I've used you?!
Do you understand now?
I'm the same as him!
I hate hypocrites like you!
What's this about a trap?
Did I really scare you that much?
Don't you need to go after Michiru?
Get talking!
I guess I should've...
Normally I'd just let you roam freely,
and once you became a nuisance, I'd prepare a plan,
then I'd take my time setting up a trap,
and wait for the right opportunity...
If it weren't for Michiru...
Y-You... You lied?!
You lied, didn't you?!
You trash!
C-Can't breathe!
Ah, Kyouya...
Took you long enough.
H-How...
How dare you...
interrupt me?!
I searched all over for you.
Didn't expect you to lock yourself up in the school bathroom.
Someone summoned Inukai?
I'm pretty sure it's Tsurumigawa Rentarou.
I heard a few of his thoughts,
and I think he's our culprit.
There's a lot I want to say,
but let's save Inukai first.
I have a favor to ask of you about that.
I know. He can leave his body.
We don't know how far his soul can go,
but we have little chance of winning against something that can pass through walls.
We need to find his physical body.
I knew you'd understand.
It'd be nice if his physical body was simply near the beach,
but it's possible he's sending his soul there
from somewhere far away.
So you want to split up.
I'll hurry to the beach and save Michiru.
No. I should be the one to—
Actually, I'm not sure which job
is the more dangerous one.
Right.
If you try to capture his body,
he might attack you instead in order to protect himself.
Shouldn't we get help from the others, too?
I'm not sure whether
they'd agree quickly enough.
A lot of people might not want to get involved
after all the recent deaths.
There's no way
we have time to deal with that.
I think they'd listen
if you were the one to ask, but...
Well, I can see you're in a hurry.
Yes. That's why I'm asking you for help.
I-I mean that you're quick to understand, that's all!
I'm glad you don't hate me.
I'll be on my way.
Don't do anything too crazy.
All you need to do is escape with Inukai once you find her.
Good grief.
What have I done?
I threw my mission out the window,
confronted an irrelevant Talented without a plan,
and ended up in this pitiful state.
Actually,
if you consider all the things I've done,
this kind of death suits me quite well.
I'm cold.
I'm so cold.
Mom,
Dad...
I'm sorry.
But you know what?
I finally made... my first friend.
Her hair is always all over the place,
and she's kinda like a dog...
Yeah...
Her name is Michiru, and—
Huh?
What is she doing?
It's okay. I can do this.
N-No way.
I can't speak.
I can feel the life returning to her body!
S-Stop... Stop!
You just fainted the other day!
I'll save you, no matter what!
Because you're a good person, Nanna!
No, stop! I'm not a good person at all!
Hitomin, help me!
I'm scared to do this alone.
I'm scared...
But!
Just a bit more...
Just a little more, and...
Give me my Nanna back, please!
They
all
were
gi
ven
a
gift
No... way.
The
call
of
a
po
wer
with
in
Nanna!
Be
cause
of
that
one
sin
We
brand
them
as
mon
stro
si
ties
As
if
by
a
whim
of
the
gods
Or
may
be
some
mis
chief
of
time
What
they
all
had
thought
was
a
gift
Brought
with
it
u
nique
a
go
ny
This
was
n't
what
I
hoped
would
be
come
But
what
good
would
strug
gl
ing
have
done
When
it
was
clear
that
I
ne
ver
would
be
loved?
So
who
should
I
di
rect
this
bit
ter
rage
at?
Was
my
life
all
a
lie?
Had
you
been
on
my
side?
What
if
you
be
ing
there
helped
sur
face
all
my
doubts?
There
might
have
been
a
chance
May
be
a
chance
that
I
may
be
could
see
that
I'd
been
mis
guid
ed
all
a
long
May
be
a
chance
that
I
may
be
could
see
that
I'd
been
mis
guid
ed
all
a
long
No... No!
I'd
have
left
the
world
way
that
it
was
No...
No!