You know what?
I foresaw this the day you transferred, Nana.
Isn't that, like, crazy?
I figured out what he's after.
He hasn't made a huge deal out of it yet
despite having these photos, which means...
U-Um...
It's super crazy that our new leader's behind all this.
P-Please wait!
I'd like to clear this up.
I'll do anything.
I don't want these photos
making everyone unnecessarily anxious!
I know, right? You'll do anything, right?
I was right. He wanted to threaten me using these.
I'm just super bored on this stupid island.
It's very likely he doesn't have any friends,
so no one would believe him
if he tried to expose Nakajima's death.
Actually, I've never gotten any photos
of the enemies of humanity.
Seriously, what are we even doing on this island?
All this leader stuff is such a joke.
Kyouya would be over the moon if he heard this.
Wait, could you be an enemy of humanity, Nana?
Is that why you're trying to kill me?
I can still salvage this.
I'll get rid of him, then dispose of the photos.
I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but no, I'm not an enemy,
and I have no idea what all these photos are about.
What can I do for you to believe me?
You see, I don't have a girlfriend...
As I'm drifting through an eternity
As
I'm
drift
ing
through
The souls of fragile beings crashing over me
The
souls
of
fra
gile
be
ings
crash
ing
o
ver
me
The heavens fracture
The
hea
vens
frac
ture
But clouds mask the broken sky
But
clouds
mask
the
bro
ken
sky
Using awkward circumstance to gain the upper hand
Us
ing
awk
ward
cir
cum
stance
to
gain
the
up
per
hand
I try to test the will of God
I
try
to
test
the
will
of
God
It almost felt as if I could deceive him
It
al
most
felt
as
if
I
could
de
ceive
him
When I found you at the end of my eternal search
When
I
found
search
I also found my lost tears
I
al
so
found
my
lost
tears
Kill all the enemies
of humanity.
Though I lie
Though
I
lie
To others
To
o
thers
Time after time
Time
af
ter
time
I don't need deceit to keep you
I
don't
need
de
ceit
to
keep
you
Smiling and pure
Smi
l
ing
and
pure
My one "talent" is my mercilessness
My
one
"
ta
lent
less
ness
I weave a tangled web of destiny and death
I
weave
a
tan
gled
death
My sins dispassionate and dull
My
sins
dis
pas
sion
ate
and
dull
Hidden deep down inside my soul
Hid
den
deep
down
in
side
my
soul
Sudden showers voice their assent
Sud
den
sho
wers
voice
their
as
sent
And mute the screams of those who meet their end
And
mute
the
screams
of
those
who
meet
their
end
The heavens warp but
The
hea
vens
warp
but
The clouds mask the broken sky
The
clouds
mask
the
bro
ken
sky
Wow, this feels good.
Episode 5: The Talented vs. The Talentless, Part 2
Tsunekichi...
Don't you want to use your incredible Talent
to help the world in some way?
I hate hard-working people, you know.
No matter how hard you try,
the future won't change, after all.
But you could tell someone
if they're in danger, right?
That's what I mean.
Imagine someone's about to die
and you tell them that.
You feel me?
It's like a doctor telling a patient
they have an incurable disease, right?
Oh, that was great. I'm so clever!
I should just give him what he deserves.
Maybe I should have you
clean my ears naked tomorrow.
I could kill him right here and now, but...
Ow!
Nana, dear, do you wanna kill me?!
I'm sorry, did it hurt?
I'm telling you, the future
from the photos is already decided.
I was still alive in the photo I showed you.
Which means I can't be killed no matter what
until that happens at 10PM.
It's this whole fate thing, get me?
So if I tried to kill you now,
you say this "fate" entity
will come into play and cause me to fail?
I admit it's late at night.
The dorm walls are thin,
so making too much noise would be unwise.
Oh, but you know what?
We actually don't know what happens
after you assault me, no?
Maybe I'll end up killing you instead?
Or do you manage to kill me after all?
You know what? I think it's best to stay inside
until I can see how this plays out.
I think I'll be going back to my room.
I told you we're staying in here!
Do you not understand the position you're in?
Starting tomorrow, you'll have to
entertain me as my girlfriend, you see.
I understand. I'll stay here, I'm sorry.
Perfect. 'Night!
So that's the camera, huh?
So he takes photos of his precognitive dreams.
He probably can't choose
what he sees about the future.
If he could proactively predict the future,
he'd try to learn what happens after I assault him.
This is bad.
I thought it might be some kind of magic tool,
but it's a regular instant-print camera.
That means it's entirely
Tsunekichi's Talent that predicts the future.
If this is just a normal device, the evidence of me
killing Nakajima is probably still in there as well.
I'll need to get rid of this camera too.
Is it really true that the
predicted future never changes?
I really don't like this whole "fate" concept.
Morning, Nana, cutie.
You didn't attempt to kill me during the night?
Please, that's not funny.
Well, either way, it'd have been pointless.
I'm totally super safe until this happens, after all.
Has the future in your photos
really never changed?
My! Are you getting scared?
It'll be fine, don't worry.
Let's both avoid that shed for a while.
But if the future can't change,
we'll end up there no matter what...
Yeah, and my point is that
we should have fun until then, dear.
Since we don't know when
this is gonna happen, you see.
Judging by the phase of the moon,
it could be tonight at the earliest.
Now, would my girlfriend be so kind
as to clean up my room, perhaps?
What now?
If Kyouya or another student
saw me in that situation...
Nana, cutie, you're hiding something, aren't you?
Huh?
You see, I always get five premonitions per night,
and the last one's sometimes real juicy.
Like the one with Nakajima.
Five premonitions?
Yeah. I guess it's kinda
the Talent's limitation or whatever,
but I get glimpses of five situations.
What?
But you see, when I woke up,
there were only four photos there.
And all four of them were
really kinda whatever, so...
Time for a pat-down!
I sure get why you wouldn't want me to see this!
No, I'm sure it's not what it looks like...
Why did you hide it, hm?
I didn't want any more
unnecessary misunderstandings!
Believe me, please!
I don't want to die either!
Why would I assault you
knowing that I'm going to die?
The future is absolute.
Logic doesn't matter here!
I believe we can change it if we try!
I don't want to think we humans
are powerless against fate.
You're human too. I'm sure you
don't want to kill me either, right?
Okay, how about something like this?
Now that we've learned that I won't die,
I'm gonna be waiting for you at the gym shed tonight.
If nothing happens at 10,
I'll believe what you're saying.
I promise nothing will!
Not at 10, at least.
I'll clean up the room,
so feel free to go take a shower!
Will you? Thanks!
Let's change the future right away.
Silly! The enemies of humanity are no match for me!
True!
Yeah!
What unlucky timing.
If I attack Tsunekichi now,
the people in the hallway might hear something.
I had this thought in the shower, actually...
Killing you seems like it wouldn't
work out too well for me, right?
But wouldn't it actually count as self-defense?
Y-You call it self-defense,
but in the photo, my clothes were
all messed up, as if you'd assaulted me...
I'm entitled to a little bonus, aren't I?
You're such a cutie after all.
I won't let scum like him kill me.
In any case, I'm totally excited for tonight now.
Would it be okay for me to leave now?
I'd like to take a shower as well.
You're gonna be all clean for me, huh?
I'll be waiting at 10, then!
And if you don't come, I might let the photos
circulate around the class...
Hatadaira Tsunekichi
Estimated kill count
Over 500,000
Hatadaira Tsunekichi
Estimated kill count
Over 500,000
Hatadaira Tsunekichi
Estimated kill count
Over 500,000
Hatadaira Tsunekichi
Estimated kill count
Over 500,000
Hatadaira Tsunekichi
Estimated kill count
Over 500,000
Hatadaira Tsunekichi
Estimated kill count
Over 500,000
Hatadaira Tsunekichi
Estimated kill count
Over 500,000
Hatadaira Tsunekichi
Estimated kill count
Over 500,000
Hatadaira Tsunekichi
Estimated kill count
Over 500,000
Any moment now.
You can't change the future!
Tsunekichi most likely believes
that he won't be assaulted until 10.
Which is why I made sure
his watch is 10 minutes behind!
Wh—
Isn't this too early?!
That's what you expected to hear, right?
Try as you might...
But it's all pointless!
No! Stop!
I already fixed the time on my watch.
You really thought I was this stupid?
I do actually pay close attention to the time.
And even if I hadn't noticed,
we'd have still ended up like in the photo regardless!
Actual time doesn't matter at all.
We'll be fighting to the death
as soon as my watch shows 10 PM!
I have to admit, I'm shaken.
You sure pulled a nice little trick.
I don't know why, but you're really eager
to kill me after all, aren't you?
Then I don't need to hold back, do I?
You're all mine now!
No, really, I'm shaken.
Dropping my poisoned needles was one thing,
but the real surprise here
was someone as stupid as you
noticing that watch trick.
I guess I have no choice but to believe you.
The future really always goes as the photos show,
no matter how much you struggle against it.
Wh-What... did you...
You know how we fought a moment ago?
My needles were lying on the floor
where you pinned me down.
I absolutely hate how ideal of a coincidence that is.
But I guess that's to be expected
if the future cannot change.
Huh? Why am I dying, though?
The photo showed you were the one fated to die...
You enemies of humanity might not understand,
but I believe that what you call fate
can be molded by human hands.
That's why I didn't accept your "absolute future".
I wasn't going to give in until the very end.
What?
Look.
You were so careful about
staying inside and all that,
so I had to figure out how
to get you to somewhere empty.
Since you can predict the future,
you'd just stay put and avoid taking any risks
until you were sure of your victory.
E-Exactly. The future cannot be changed.
And that photo...
Was simply a selfie I took
with your camera last night.
It was a trap I prepared to lure you in.
I thought you'd notice it was a normal photo
and not one of your premonitions,
so I was trying to figure out when to show it to you,
but then you went and searched me.
Did you believe it was real
because I pretended to panic?
This is the real one.
But the real problem...
is this.
What are you doing, Hiiragi?
I-I hadn't seen you since last night, Nanna...
I wanted to give you the notes you asked for...
Y-You know, with everyone's Talents...
Y-You weren't in your room tonight either,
so I thought something might've happened
and asked Kyouya for help...
Hiiragi?
I can explain later!
Michiru, you need to save Tsunekichi!
O-Okay!
I have to see what they say first...
I asked around the dorm while looking for you.
From what I heard, Hatadaira Tsunekichi,
who's lying on the floor here,
has apparently been saying
truly perplexing things all day.
Fire Extinguisher
Nana is my girlfriend now.
What's with this dipshit?
Let him dream.
Fire Extinguisher
I figured something had happened between you two,
so we went to his room to check.
So they knew we'd be here
because they saw that photo.
It seems Tsunekichi's Talent
let him predict the future.
This couldn't be worse.
So...
Could you maybe explain this?
If he saw that photo of me...
I-I...
Wait... he saw this photo?
I can still talk my way out of this...
I don't think I can do anything...
Inukai is a really kind girl.
As soon as she saw this photo,
she ran looking for you.
I didn't know where to find you,
but Kyouya helped with that.
Wait, does that mean...?
Um, was there anything else?
What else?
Other photos. Did you find any other ones,
besides the one where I got killed?
No.
Though I think I glimpsed one where
you had soba noodles all over your head.
He really didn't see it.
Why do you ask?
Were there any you wouldn't want anyone to see?
Perfect. Then I can do this.
To tell you the truth, I was being threatened.
At first, he came to me for advice, because he
had a premonition of getting attacked by an enemy,
but then he showed me a few other photos...
What kind of photos?
I wonder if they were picturing the future...
They were photos of, uh... me in the bathtub...
He told me to listen or he'd show them to everyone.
That's awful!
That explains why you were making sure
I didn't see any such photos, I see.
Not just that,
but it also stops him from looking
any further, decent man as he is.
So? He attacked you and you killed him?
P-Please, scary jokes like that aren't funny at all!
I didn't do anything!
She couldn't have! There's no wounds or anything...
Maybe Tsunekichi had some sort of illness?
It might've been the enemies of humanity.
I think I noticed them somewhere close...
But there're no external wounds?
Weren't the enemies using spears
or harpoons or whatever?
I think the textbooks mentioned ones
that could curse people, too...
Is that so?
In any case,
I'd like to thank you for coming to my rescue.
I'll tell everyone about Tsunekichi tomorrow.
Also... Please don't hold
what happened against him.
Nanna...
They suddenly appear and disappear
with no sound or trace.
They kill using something sharp,
then cause an instant mysterious death.
Enemies of humanity sure are something.
A time traveler,
an immortal,
and a prophet...
You really think you have room to talk?
I'll stay with him for a little longer.
There's something I'd like to try.
Okay then.
I need to retrieve the photos as soon as possible.
I was lucky that Kyouya didn't see these.
I guess that's part of this "fate"
Tsunekichi spoke about.
My, Hiiragi.
I thought you'd be resting in your room?
I spent last night in this room,
so I'm here to retrieve my things.
But what are you doing here, Kyouya?
Don't worry. I didn't come to look
for your naked photos.
Looking at the body, I started thinking...
I don't see anything...
What are you looking for?
Ah, right.
Remember how we wondered
if Tsunekichi was chronically ill?
I thought he might have
some medication in his room.
So you don't think it was the
enemies of humanity who killed him.
I'd like to think it was.
So I'm trying to confirm that theory
by ruling out any other possibilities.
So brazen of him.
Actually, I wanted your opinion on something.
This is a photo of one of
Tsunekichi's premonitions, right?
I think so.
But it was Tsunekichi who died, not you.
Isn't that strange?
Oh, just that?
Tsunekichi apparently kept boasting
about how his premonitions always come true.
"Fate's such a massive troll, am I right?"
Something like that.
Huh? What's a troll?
It's slang for someone who's mean to people online...
Oh, I see.
I'm not really familiar with internet jargon.
I see...
I think this means that unlike Tsunekichi believed,
the future actually can be changed.
I agree.
The protagonists always
change the future in comics.
I think we really do get along well, Kyouya.
But it could also be that this photo
isn't something Tsunekichi foresaw.
Just a thought.
What? How did he...?
Something really bothers me about this photo.
It looks like you were killed
by being strangled with a rope,
but if you look closely,
the rope is double-wrapped.
Double-wrapped?
In cases of murder, unlike suicide,
the rope is usually only wrapped around once.
It's because the victim usually
struggles as you're trying to wrap it.
Why go to the effort, right?
But you can't say that it never happens, right?
It's just interesting, that's all.
He's just guessing, but I really need
to pay attention around him.
He seizes onto my smallest mistakes.
If this photo isn't a premonition...
It's possible that Hiiragi took this photo herself.
What for?
Probably to kill Tsunekichi.
If someone who believes the future
in the photos is absolute saw that,
they'd let their guard down.
Actually, where's Michiru?
Ah, apparently you'd really inspired her,
so she was going to put
a little bit more effort into the body.
I see...
What's this about?
Guess I'll check on her in a bit.
What really happened between her and Tsunekichi?
I could've gotten more of the
full picture if I saw the other photos...
Guess I was too late.
And this time I don't know how he was killed...
One's missing... Did I leave it in Tsunekichi's room?
No, I checked every nook and cranny.
Which means...
No!
It still doesn't work...
I want to practice a lot more so that
I can help people like Nanna does...
Huh?
What's this?
Michiru.
What do you have there?
They
all
were
gi
ven
a
gift
The
call
of
a
po
wer
with
in
Be
cause
of
that
one
sin
We
brand
them
as
mon
stro
si
ties
As
if
by
a
whim
of
the
gods
Or
may
be
some
mis
chief
of
time
What
they
all
had
thought
was
a
gift
Brought
with
it
u
nique
a
go
ny
This
was
n't
what
I
hoped
would
be
come
But
what
good
would
strug
gl
ing
have
done
When
it
was
clear
that
I
ne
ver
would
be
loved?
So
who
should
I
di
rect
this
bit
ter
rage
at?
So
who
should
I
di
rect
this
bit
ter
rage
at?
Was
my
life
all
a
lie?
Have
you
been
on
my
side?
What
if
you
be
ing
there
helped
sur
face
all
my
doubts?
There
might
still
be
a
chance
May
be
a
chance
that
I
may
be
could
see
that
I've
been
mis
guid
ed
all
a
long
May
be
a
chance
that
I
may
be
could
see
that
I've
been
mis
guid
ed
all
a
long
I
could
leave
the
world
way
that
it
is
I
could
leave
the
world
way
that
it
is
Next Episode: Necromancer
"Necromancer".