I may be a murderer,
but I don't use the dead as my toys!
Huh...
So that's the real you.
Wow, so scary.
Struggle all you want, though.
You won't win against all of us.
I don't have to.
I'll simply explain that I was on patrol.
Excuse me?
You think that's gonna fly?
Shinji and I both saw everything!
You tried to kill him!
Shinji is dead.
You're just controlling him.
But everyone thinks he's alive!
I'll explain your situation.
If you're not a necromancer, and instead possess
superhuman strength as you claim,
then you'll have to prove that to them,
but you can't, can you?
What do you think will happen then?
People trust in each other, not in objective truths.
Between me, the leader of the class,
and you, a mad necromancer who plays
with her boyfriend's corpse every night,
who do you think they'll choose to side with?
Still, she did take my poison needles from me.
My apparent lack of motive won't help me
if Kyouya gets his hands on my weapon...
But let me propose an alternative.
As I'm drifting through an eternity
As
I'm
drift
ing
through
The souls of fragile beings crashing over me
The
souls
of
fra
gile
be
ings
crash
ing
o
ver
me
The heavens fracture
The
hea
vens
frac
ture
But clouds mask the broken sky
But
clouds
mask
the
bro
ken
sky
Using awkward circumstance to gain the upper hand
Us
ing
awk
ward
cir
cum
stance
to
gain
the
up
per
hand
I try to test the will of God
I
try
to
test
the
will
of
God
It almost felt as if I could deceive him
It
al
most
felt
as
if
I
could
de
ceive
him
When I found you at the end of my eternal search
When
I
found
search
I also found my lost tears
I
al
so
found
my
lost
tears
Kill all the enemies
of humanity.
Though I lie
Though
I
lie
To others
To
o
thers
Time after time
Time
af
ter
time
I don't need deceit to keep you
I
don't
need
de
ceit
to
keep
you
Smiling and pure
Smi
l
ing
and
pure
My one "talent" is my mercilessness
My
one
"
ta
lent
less
ness
I weave a tangled web of destiny and death
I
weave
a
tan
gled
death
My sins dispassionate and dull
My
sins
dis
pas
sion
ate
and
dull
Hidden deep down inside my soul
Hid
den
deep
down
in
side
my
soul
Sudden showers voice their assent
Sud
den
sho
wers
voice
their
as
sent
And mute the screams of those who meet their end
And
mute
the
screams
of
those
who
meet
their
end
The heavens warp but
The
hea
vens
warp
but
The clouds mask the broken sky
The
clouds
mask
the
bro
ken
sky
You don't want anyone to learn
that Shinji is actually dead, do you?
Episode 7: Necromancer, Part 2
Who'd have guessed our supposed necromancer
was actually a corpse
being controlled by someone else?
What are you getting at?
I'll keep your secret.
I'll also leave you and Shinji alone.
You're funny.
Did you forget I have the upper hand here?
I'll make it up to you, of course.
I'll admit I've lost this time, after all.
Let me apologize by telling you
what you most want to know.
What I want to know?
Yeah. What Shinji is thinking about you.
I can read the minds of the dead as well.
I got her.
If you release me,
I'll focus and try to hear his thoughts.
How does that sound?
I can tell from the way she acts
that she's a hopeless romantic.
Don't you want to hear it?
A message from the afterlife from the boy you liked?
Thank you very much.
I'll give it a try, then.
Got anything?
He's telling you to kill me.
You're so stupid, Yuuka.
It's exactly as she says.
If you want to hear my thoughts,
you just need to kill her.
Your necromancy lets you use
the Talents of the dead.
You're right.
I just need to kill her!
That way my secrets will be safe as well.
She followed me here just as I expected.
But the real battle begins now.
There she is!
Where did she go?
This way!
I'd rather get rid of Yuuka herself,
but Shinji's protecting her, which is annoying.
It'd be nice if I could take him out,
but I'm not sure how...
Tsunekichi's necklace was under the bed.
Why did Yuuka have it?
It's a guess, but...
I suppose I could test it.
She went in here, didn't she?
Stay on your guard.
You brought it just in case, right?
Yeah.
I won't let her escape.
That's a pretty necklace you have there.
What's inside the pendant? Ashes?
Considering you wear it even in bed,
it must be insanely important to you.
To perform necromancy,
you need a keepsake...
Well, something the person had while alive.
Tsunekichi's necklace serves that purpose.
I see.
You stole his necklace before the funeral
so you could control his corpse
and get a chance to show Shinji off to the class.
I almost feel bad for the guy.
You're not one to talk, Nana.
So?
What happens if I steal that necklace from you?
Try it if you think you can.
I thought her voice was coming from over here...
Shinji!
Ow...
Damn it.
We need to hurry before the sun rises.
Yuuka needs to defend herself
while controlling Shinji.
If I can keep surprising her in the dark,
I'll get lucky eventually.
Something's a bit off.
I know I'm leaving footprints,
but how is she able to follow
straight after me in this darkness?
Wh-What?!
The hell was that?!
I told you!
This island is super weird!
I only found out thanks to my Talent,
but there's tons of corpses
buried in these mountains!
Judging by their memories,
they all died horrible deaths.
There's someone who used to be a teacher,
and there's Talented students...
And this one kid had this Talent,
I guess you could call it night vision?
I can see just as clearly as in daylight.
What does this mean?
This island has been used to isolate
enemies of humanity for a while now,
but did they get into fights amongst themselves?
Or could it be that I had a predecessor?
The Committee never mentioned anything like that!
Aren't they scary?
Maybe I should've restored their bodies
completely, like I did with Shinji...
Now, let's play a little game of tag.
I don't have time for any distractions right now!
Now that I think about it,
it wasn't just Tsunekichi's necklace under the bed.
There were other strange objects as well.
Don't tell me they were all
belongings of the zombies...
I'm definitely in trouble.
She can see far better than I can,
and there're so many zombies.
It's nearly impossible for me to attack Yuu—
Damn it!
Whoa, she's got some grit.
I managed to lose them.
I guess it's an abandoned shed...
It's broken.
Which means it can only be locked from the outside...
Shinji doesn't come to school during the day.
When I sneaked into his room,
it was excessively dark in there.
I have very little to go on.
The supernatural Talents
of the enemies of humanity
can't be explained logically in the first place.
I can't confirm it,
but if I manage to hide until the sun rises,
there's a chance...
Hide?
I can't let myself do that.
Me losing here would mean accepting
the Talented ruling over the Talentless.
If I don't have proof,
I need to acquire it, not run away!
Let's go.
Found you!
She tried to barricade herself, huh?
What is this, a zombie movie?
Listen, Nana,
you know Shinji could tear down
this shack like a straw hut, right?
How about you try breaking in, then?
You set up some trap, didn't you?
My, whatever shall I do?
It'll be dawn before long...
I don't want Shinji to get hurt by your tricks, either.
Got a problem with dawn?
Maybe you should hurry up, then.
You didn't check under the bed, did you?
You're already under attack.
Oh my.
I'm out of time.
The sun...
Yeah, exactly.
Though if I completely block out the sunlight,
I can move them a little
and see a bit through their eyes.
You kinda impressed me.
Telling me to hurry up when you should've
been desperately cowering in fear...
You sure are tough.
It kept me cautious.
You're not attacking me?
I'm wounded all over.
And the door's unlocked.
No way am I gonna attack you right now!
I don't have anyone to protect me right now.
Doesn't it make more sense for me
to lock you in here and wait for night to fall?
All the tools you could use to escape are outside.
You put a lot of effort into reinforcing the shed,
but turns out it backfired.
Guess I'm gonna take a shower and get to class.
Damn you!
Sorry to wake you up,
but have you seen Hiiragi?
Nana, you mean?
Dunno where she is,
but we were chatting until late last night!
What about?
Just having a little girls' night in, why?
No reason.
If nothing happened, that's fine.
Your necklace is about to fall off.
The clasp is broken wide open.
R-Really? Thanks!
By the way, what's a girls' night in?
Huh? Well...
I need to get out of here fast.
Once the sun sets,
the zombies might start moving again.
Let's see, how's our little Nana doing?
Be careful.
She might jump out at you.
It'll be most dangerous
right as we open the door, yeah.
Shinji, if you could?
Nana?
Did you give up?
She's not here.
Maybe under the bed?
Is there anywhere else she could hide?
You did lock the door, right?
Wouldn't that lock break
if she threw herself at the door?
Well...
I guess we could check that.
And?
No dice, I think.
Even on adrenaline, I don't think
she'd have the strength.
There's bars on the window too.
Maybe she dug a hole in the floor?
Oh, I know!
I almost fell for it!
She didn't escape at all.
Then where is she?
I mean, look, she's been lying there
waiting for her chance this whole time!
Right, Nana?
Huh?
Wh-What's the deal?
I don't know.
So she escaped after all?
Mobilize all the corpses and search the area.
I don't understand.
Maybe she was lying about reading minds,
and she actually has some other Talent?
What do you think, Shinji?
I'll kill her.
I did nothing wrong.
She was the one who wanted to kill me.
She wanted to rip me and Shinji apart.
What a lovely morning, isn't it, Yuuka?
S-Stop it!
What do you want that thing for?!
I just need this pendant to control Shinji!
I found it weird how readily
you talked about your weakness.
I'm guessing you really do need a keepsake,
something that belonged to the deceased,
to perform necromancy.
It's a fact that Tsunekichi's corpse moved,
and liars tend to mix some truth into their lies.
But I'm sharper than you think.
Your necklace would fall off too easily in a fight.
If it was important, you'd keep it maintained,
so you'd have repaired the broken clasp by now.
On top of that, last night, when I tried to steal it,
you protected your back pocket
instead of the necklace.
Your body moved instinctively when in danger.
I didn't expect it to be such a stupid thing, though.
I don't want to fight in front of the dorms.
If you want this back, you should follow me.
Take Shinji with you. And hurry up.
What's wrong?
The sun is up, you can't control your corpses.
What choice do you have but to obey?
What are you gonna do to us?
You still don't understand, do you?
Unlike when you pretended to be asleep
to ambush me, I have the upper hand right now.
What kind of Talent did you use?
Talent?
How did you escape from the shed?
The door was locked,
and there were bars on the window.
I just walked out through the door.
What? But I couldn't break the lock
no matter how hard I shoved it!
I set everything up beforehand,
trying to up my chances even just a little bit.
Prepared what?
I did see you doing something before I got there...
I wasn't reinforcing the door
to barricade myself in the shed.
You even said it yourself,
the shed could easily be destroyed
by Shinji or a few zombies.
You knew...
What did you do, then?
What did you risk getting caught for?
I actually wanted you to find me.
I wanted you to believe I was running scared,
trying to use whatever tools I could find
to keep the zombies out.
You'd never think that I was actually rushing
to remove the screws from the lock, would you?
You locked the door, convinced that
there was no escape from the shed,
but by that point, the hasp wasn't
even screwed into the doorframe.
It was just taped onto it.
There was practically nothing preventing the door from opening.
All it took was a little push from the inside,
and the door swung open, hasp and all.
You used tape to cover that up?
To hide that there were no screws in the lock?
Yeah, though I did wait until classes started,
in case you were still around.
Once I left the shed, I used the tools
I'd left outside to reinstall the hasp.
I stayed in the mountains for a while,
and returned to the dorms
once it started getting dark.
H-Hold on a sec...
Are you telling me you expected me
to lock you in the shed in the first place?
I didn't want to run away.
I wanted to confirm whether the zombies
would stop moving when dawn broke.
If I stayed at the shed, with its hasp on the outside,
there was a good chance I'd end up locked in
once it came to a confrontation.
And I figured I could pretend to be
trapped inside if I played things right.
Once you found it empty,
you'd probably get anxious and panic,
so I suspected you'd exhaust yourself
searching the mountains all night.
Back in the shed,
I was only worried about two things.
One, you could've broken into the shed
before morning came.
Two, I didn't know whether the zombies
really couldn't move during the day or not.
Those were the only things I couldn't be sure of.
You put yourself at risk
just to confirm your theories?
The conditions for controlling the corpses,
and my weaknesses...
B-But...
I get that you wanted to know my limits,
but what if I hadn't come back
to the dorms this morning?
What if I'd come back at night
while I could control Shinji?
You might be terrifying in the dark,
but during the day you're as good as Talentless,
and you have to protect those keepsakes.
So I had to be ready for the right moment,
whenever it came.
N-No matter how long?
I-I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
I'll do anything you say!
I won't tell anyone about you,
and I'll do anything you ask of me!
So please!
Give that...
Give Shinji back to me!
Do you have my needle case?
Y-Yeah.
Throw it at my feet.
No!
I like cats. I don't need another dog.
Y-You're so cruel...
How could you?!
I mean, I did try to kill you,
but you'd attacked us first!
I was scared!
I didn't need anything more than to be with Shinji!
I really didn't!
I don't really care at this point,
so you don't have to answer this, but...
Where did you put your drink?
What?!
The drink you bought at the theater.
Where did you put it during the movie?
In the cupholder, where else?!
And that's a lie.
The person on your right
spilled their drink onto your skirt.
Shinji got mad, leaned over you from your left,
and spilled his soda onto you as well.
That means the person on your right
used the cupholder on their left,
and the person on your left
used the cupholder on their right.
That leaves you with nowhere to put yours.
I guess I didn't really remember...
I must've been holding it
in my hands the whole time.
Well, not like it matters,
but you also said you were clinging
to Shinji in fear the whole time.
That aside, why were you out on a date
in your uniforms when it wasn't a school day?
Didn't you say he'd suffocated because
the collar made it harder to breathe?
So during the fire, he was wearing
his school uniform, which has a high collar.
N-No.
The date was... uh, it was a weekday!
We were on our way back from school.
I see. I didn't bother checking,
but didn't you get crêpes from a street stall?
I'm guessing you'll tell me your town
has those on weekdays as well.
Wh-What are you getting at?
I didn't expect your keepsake of Shinji
to be a piece of a torn-up test.
What a surprise.
I thought it'd be something more romantic,
like a jacket button or something.
I'd almost assumed it was
another fake, just like the necklace.
But it was real.
Your best keepsake of him was some piece of trash.
It's hard to believe from
a childhood friend, a girlfriend.
But it was real.
N-No, it's not like...
You're still denying it,
you stalker creep?!
Why did you swap your Talents
and show them off to people like that?
Why did you come up with the fake necklace,
and why were you so desperate
to keep Shinji's death a secret?
No! I... It's not like that! It's not what you think!
What kind of secret were you
this desperate to protect?
No! I didn't kill him!
I only started the fire!
It was all her fault!
I did nothing wrong...
It's because my Shinji was dating that stupid girl...
They ate crêpes together...
She was clumsy enough to spill her drink onto him...
I just wanted to free my Shinji from her clutches.
I thought her death would free him...
I did want another keepsake of him,
but he hated me, so I couldn't get close...
I should've stolen more from him.
Then none of this would've happened...
Why did I only pretend to throw this away?
If it turned out all my guesses were off the mark,
Sasaki Yuuka
Estimated kill count
Over 500,000
and Yuuka had really been a good person...
Did I intend to spare her?
Yeah, no.
They
all
were
gi
ven
a
gift
The
call
of
a
po
wer
with
in
Be
cause
of
that
one
sin
We
brand
them
as
mon
stro
si
ties
As
if
by
a
whim
of
the
gods
Or
may
be
some
mis
chief
of
time
What
they
all
had
thought
was
a
gift
Brought
with
it
u
nique
a
go
ny
This
was
n't
what
I
hoped
would
be
come
But
what
good
would
strug
gl
ing
have
done
When
it
was
clear
that
I
ne
ver
would
be
loved?
So
who
should
I
di
rect
this
bit
ter
rage
at?
So
who
should
I
di
rect
this
bit
ter
rage
at?
Was
my
life
all
a
lie?
Have
you
been
on
my
side?
What
if
you
be
ing
there
helped
sur
face
all
my
doubts?
There
might
still
be
a
chance
May
be
a
chance
that
I
may
be
could
see
that
I've
been
mis
guid
ed
all
a
long
May
be
a
chance
that
I
may
be
could
see
that
I've
been
mis
guid
ed
all
a
long
I
could
leave
the
world
way
that
it
is
I
could
leave
the
world
way
that
it
is
Next Episode: The Talented vs. The Talentless, Part 3
"The Talented vs. The Talentless, Part 3".