As I'm drifting through an eternity
As
I'm
drift
ing
through
The souls of fragile beings crashing over me
The
souls
of
fra
gile
be
ings
crash
ing
o
ver
me
The heavens fracture
The
hea
vens
frac
ture
But clouds mask the broken sky
But
clouds
mask
the
bro
ken
sky
Using awkward circumstance to gain the upper hand
Us
ing
awk
ward
cir
cum
stance
to
gain
the
up
per
hand
I try to test the will of God
I
try
to
test
the
will
of
God
It almost felt as if I could deceive him
It
al
most
felt
as
if
I
could
de
ceive
him
When I found you at the end of my eternal search
When
I
found
search
I also found my lost tears
I
al
so
found
my
lost
tears
Kill all the enemies
of humanity.
Though I lie
Though
I
lie
To others
To
o
thers
Time after time
Time
af
ter
time
I don't need deceit to keep you
I
don't
need
de
ceit
to
keep
you
Smiling and pure
Smi
l
ing
and
pure
My one "talent" is my mercilessness
My
one
"
ta
lent
less
ness
I weave a tangled web of destiny and death
I
weave
a
tan
gled
death
My sins dispassionate and dull
My
sins
dis
pas
sion
ate
and
dull
Hidden deep down inside my soul
Hid
den
deep
down
in
side
my
soul
Sudden showers voice their assent
Sud
den
sho
wers
voice
their
as
sent
And mute the screams of those who meet their end
And
mute
the
screams
of
those
who
meet
their
end
The heavens warp but
The
hea
vens
warp
but
The clouds mask the broken sky
The
clouds
mask
the
bro
ken
sky
Stupid rain.
Episode 3: The Talented vs. The Talentless
It's really coming down hard.
We're in the rainy season all right.
I've eliminated two enemies in a row, but...
I wonder what's up with Nanao, though.
Shibusawa isn't here either.
I need to proceed with the utmost caution.
If they realize that there's a killer in the class,
it'll become much more difficult for me to act.
Say, don't you think he's kinda suspicious?
Onodera Kyouya, you mean?
He's quite the enigma.
You've heard the rumors that enemies
have already infiltrated the school, right?
Say, sweetie.
How do I look today?
Try guessing what I'm thinking right now.
Well...
If there's anything I can tell you right now, Seiya,
it's that your girlfriend's sitting right over there,
so you shouldn't have me
up against the wall like this.
H-How did you figure that out?
That's crazy, Nana!
I keep telling you I can read—
It's been raining really hard all morning,
but for some reason, only your right side is soaked.
Huh?
Meanwhile, only the girl's left side is soaked.
Perhaps you two shared an umbrella
while walking to school.
Just a hunch.
This guy again?
Seaweed?!
Hey, Kyouya!
Do you want to eat lunch with me?
I'm not hungry.
It's an unused janitor's closet.
It's warm.
He goes out of his way to heat up milk for a cat?
He seemed quite grumpy at first,
but now I'm not sure what to make of him.
Hey, Kyouya.
I've been meaning to tell you since this morning,
but you've got something on your head.
Oh right, sorry.
Guess I should've taken care of that.
Hiiragi Nana.
Are you free today, my dear?
"Dear"?
Be my friend.
Excuse me?
Come in.
I-Is it really okay?
No need to be shy.
It's possible to get a rough idea of someone's
personality based on how their room looks.
Until 21st
What is this place?
We're playing games?
Don't like them?
No, it's just so sudden...
Also, this console is pretty retro.
I guess. Sorry about that.
That's just what I prefer.
I thought we could play games
together since we're friends.
Th-Thanks for being so considerate.
There's a dress-up doll on the shelf.
Would you rather play with that?
I'm fine, thank you.
Um, Kyouya...
Isn't there something you wanted to talk about?
You have a lot of friends, my dear.
It's strange considering you just transferred.
Is it really?
I just try to get along with everyone.
You see, I want friends too.
How can I make some?
Um...
Generally, you'd try to find
mutual hobbies, you know, common interests,
or open up to each other...
Hm, I see...
People often tell me that
I'm quite difficult to approach.
Do you agree?
Well, I would say you're kinda scary.
You can come across as a bit of a D-bag.
What did you just say?
D-bag?
Well, I mean...
People usually don't just force others
into visiting their rooms!
That's not what I'm asking.
What's a "D-bag"?
Excuse me?
What does it mean?
Uh, how do I explain it...
It's like, someone who's kinda overbearing,
or maybe even a bit sadistic...
Or someone who's arrogant.
Huh, so there's a word for that.
Thanks, that's helpful.
I don't get him.
What's his deal?
I always end up completely fixated on
whatever catches my attention.
Is that why you're so invested in
figuring out what happened to Nakajima?
Yeah, that's what's mainly on my mind right now.
Actually, why's that?
It's been on my mind as well...
You see, I have a little sister.
She came to this island before I did.
So she's Talented too.
I haven't heard from her since.
She came here to receive her training
and has been missing since.
I came here thinking there'd be
something more to this island.
Then Nakajima suddenly went missing.
The school isn't really doing much to find him either.
Maybe they don't want to cause a commotion?
I thought the Talented were
supposed to be national treasures.
I imagined this school to be kind of like the army,
but there doesn't seem to be
any serious training going on,
and the students are pretty much just let loose.
Is this really going to prepare us to face
these enemies of humanity they're talking about?
Wait, that comic...
The Humanity
Girl
It's quite old. You know it?
The Humanity
Girl
Yeah, it's one of my favorites!
Oh, we have a common interest.
I've always loved the protagonist!
She delivers justice by beating up
the enemies of humanity!
I know, right?
I like how she has a darker side, too.
Remember when she had a friend
who became an enemy?
It totally made me cry when she had to kill her.
She'll do anything for her mission!
No one else would've been able to do that!
I'm so glad! I didn't expect you
to be a fan too, Kyouya!
Then...
Then?
The Humanity
Girl
You'll understand if I kill you.
The Humanity
Girl
I'll try to avoid being a D-bag from now on.
Sure, see you.
Actually, there's something
that's been bothering me.
That's Nakajima's watch.
Ring any bells?
Why does he have Nakajima's watch?
Sorry to be a D-bag again,
but come with me.
Um...
What are you doing?
Whenever I'm trying to figure something out,
I have to fiddle with something.
It needs to be silky and nice to the touch.
I see...
Could I...
Please don't do it again!
Sorry.
By the way, what were you doing
on the evening of the 13th, my dear?
The 13th?
It's the day after we transferred here.
Nakajima has been absent since the 14th,
which means the 13th is
likely the day he went missing.
What was I doing again?
Nakajima and I left school together.
Why the evening specifically?
I don't have friends or anything to do,
so for the past few days,
I've been exploring the island.
That's when I came across
this rope barrier, which had been torn.
And at the bottom of the cliff, I found this.
It's Nakajima's.
It caught my attention since it seemed like
something too expensive for a student to have.
He sure is observant.
This watch is broken,
and the hands are pointing at exactly 6:10.
If it broke in the evening rather than the morning,
I thought you might have an idea
about what happened, my dear.
No, I don't...
We parted ways right here that day.
But I don't think it was suicide.
What makes you say that?
Earlier that day, when he protected
everyone from Moguo's fireball...
That was so incredible.
It's possible he was pushed off into the ocean
but used the last of his strength
to leave his watch behind.
Just a hunch.
What makes you think that?
Because it's a really nice watch.
I assume it was a gift from someone dear to him.
Maybe he wanted to let someone who realizes
the value of this watch know that he's dead.
Makes sense.
It could be an enemy of humanity's doing.
Probably.
They must've infiltrated the island already.
However, if the textbooks are correct,
they should have ferocious fangs.
Why would they bother pushing someone off a cliff?
It's like they wanted to hide the body.
Well, the enemies are rumored to be intelligent.
It's all just rumors, meaning
no actual research has been done.
And yet we have this nice little training school.
He's even more dangerous than Nakajima.
I'm thinking about reporting
what happened to Nakajima to the school.
What do you think?
Wouldn't that create a huge commotion?
True, and I'm not sure they'll believe me.
That's why I want your help, since you're so popular.
So that's why you approached me
and wanted to be friends.
Please, don't take it that way.
I genuinely want to be friends.
Then, as a gesture of good faith...
Tell me what your Talent is.
It's really nothing special.
Oh please.
My dear, can't you read minds?
Just listen closely to find out what my Talent is.
He thinks I'm lying?
It's not that I think you're lying or anything.
You have no reason to kill Nakajima.
P-Please don't say such scary things.
In any case,
I wanted to let you know that there's monsters
on this island, like a good friend would.
Thank you. You really are a good friend.
Onodera Kyouya
Estimated kill count:
Unknown
Check Talent
I understand that I must infiltrate the island,
but I'd like to know about the enemies' Talents.
Onodera Kyouya
Talent Type: Physical
If I know what kind of Talent each student possesses,
it'll be much easier for me to carry out my mission.
We have records from when
they were recruited to the island.
We also have a sort of Talent database,
and we've calculated estimated
kill counts based on their Talents.
But don't take it at face value.
You can never be sure how far their Talents go.
There are those whose Talents
develop as they mature.
In one instance, we attempted to dispose of a Talented
individual who could control microbes inside their body,
but they unleashed a lethal dose of
a virus into the atmosphere,
so we had no choice but to
drop a fuel-air explosive onto a town.
When we tried publicly rounding them up for execution,
it backfired and we were conspired against.
After years of trial and error,
sending in someone like you
proved to be the most effective method.
You must confirm for yourself
what the enemies' Talents are.
Onodera Kyouya
Talent Type: Physical
He went down such a tall cliff to pick up the watch,
which means he probably has
superhuman-level physical abilities.
But for most Talented, their abilities
come at a price, or with some limitations.
For example, becoming exhausted after using them,
or being able to freeze objects, but not people.
Until 21st
I suppose I'll set my trap tomorrow.
I'll make you reveal your Talent.
Staff Room
What? Nakajima was attacked
by an enemy of humanity?!
Yes, unfortunately.
This watch is all we found.
Please contact his parents on the mainland.
Wait a moment.
I believe you were told this when you came here,
but let me remind you it's impossible
to contact the outside world until graduation.
What should we do then, sir?
Uh, I wonder... Wh-What should we do?
It's probably better if we don't mention anything
to the other students just yet.
Oh, of course!
It'd only create unnecessary chaos.
What can we even do?!
For now, I'll ask my superiors about this.
The faculty are completely unaware.
It doesn't seem like the school will be much help.
I feel bad for Nakajima.
Speaking of Nakajima,
I wonder how the kitty's doing.
What?
I heard that he was taking care of one.
I've never seen it myself, though.
I hope it's not starving...
Actually—
I need to go to the bathroom!
I'll see you after school!
She's quite the carefree gal.
Nakajima is dead, but she doesn't look sad.
Is it just an act?
There's something off about this island.
Expiration date (unopened):
"Training" in name only.
Students left to their own devices.
No contact with the outside world.
They all talk about the enemies of
humanity, but do they really exist?
First my sister disappears on this island,
and now Nakajima is dead.
There's someone here who's up to no good.
That much I'm sure of.
Looks like the cat's not here.
Oh well. It'll probably drink this if I leave it out.
No one knows the secret behind this island.
It wouldn't occur to anyone
that the Talented gathered here
are being eliminated in secret by a Talentless.
That's why those who try to uncover the truth
and those who voice their concerns
need to be disposed of with the highest priority.
Right now, I have an overwhelming advantage.
Even as the murders continue,
no one will think I could have a motive.
Let's assume there's a monster
lurking on this island, trying to kill us.
If its goal is to kill,
I have an overwhelming advantage.
His room was a huge mess,
so it seemed strange to me
that his bathroom was so clean.
He double-bags his trash, which implies
he's very concerned about the smell.
Until 21st
The tomatoes on his desk had a label
with the expiry date attached to them.
It's probably because it's hard to tell
from their appearance if they've gone bad.
In other words, Kyouya probably won't notice...
I thought I left the window open yesterday.
Even if the room was full of gas,
Kyouya wouldn't be able to smell it.
Now, show me.
What's your Talent?
Kyouya!
He's not moving.
It said his Talent was a physical type,
so I thought he'd break through a window
or a wall to escape before the fire spread...
Hang in there! I'll bring water! Wait, no, someone—
How are you the first one here?
He's unscathed?
How were you able to tell it was me in the flames?
I'm sorry.
It's just a bit unsettling.
I can't help but wonder...
You're... okay?
You're my friend, my dear.
It's not inconceivable that you heard
my thoughts from afar and came running.
You bringing up the cat back in the hallway
doesn't necessarily mean you knew
that I'd been feeding it during lunch breaks.
It could've been a coincidence, right?
I want to know, though, why do you
look like you've just seen a ghost?
You can read minds, but you didn't know?
I'm immortal.
Since we're friends, I'll let you in on a secret.
I have no sense of smell,
but that has nothing to do with my Talent.
I've been that way since birth.
My immortality does come at a price, though.
I'm thinking clearly about it right now.
I'll let you be the only one who knows
about it, since you can read minds.
Thank you! I got the message.
I hope we'll continue to be good friends.
I'll find out what it is no matter what.
They
all
were
gi
ven
a
gift
The
call
of
a
po
wer
with
in
Be
cause
of
that
one
sin
We
brand
them
as
mon
stro
si
ties
As
if
by
a
whim
of
the
gods
Or
may
be
some
mis
chief
of
time
What
they
all
had
thought
was
a
gift
Brought
with
it
u
nique
a
go
ny
This
was
n't
what
I
hoped
would
be
come
But
what
good
would
strug
gl
ing
have
done
When
it
was
clear
that
I
ne
ver
would
be
loved?
So
who
should
I
di
rect
this
bit
ter
rage
at?
So
who
should
I
di
rect
this
bit
ter
rage
at?
Was
my
life
all
a
lie?
Have
you
been
on
my
side?
What
if
you
be
ing
there
helped
sur
face
all
my
doubts?
There
might
still
be
a
chance
May
be
a
chance
that
I
may
be
could
see
that
I've
been
mis
guid
ed
all
a
long
May
be
a
chance
that
I
may
be
could
see
that
I've
been
mis
guid
ed
all
a
long
I
could
leave
the
world
way
that
it
is
I
could
leave
the
world
way
that
it
is
Next Episode: Healing
"Healing".