Though the spring sunshine may
herald the coming of summer,
some can only let out a cold, wintry breath,
trapped in the dark as they are.
How can they be offered salvation?
How can they be afforded the
warm touch of a gentle melody?
Tell me how, Haruta.
Ru
Ha
Ka
Chi
BLOSSOM
into
the
scent
of
rain
until
I
was
breathless
Straight
ahead
chased
the
rainbow
in
the
distance
Will
I
ever
reach
Countless
colours
merge
together
to
become
harmony
suddenly
born
strange
song
with
building
a
bridge
of
echoes
to
far
away
could
make
our
own
rainbow
from
here,
where
we've
come
then
the
colours
in
it
would
be
ours,
ours
only
million
nameless
hues
tion
would
form
its
gradient
rainbow
Let's
not
fear
the
pain
and
push
open
the
door
bathe
in
the
light
of
youth
THE CLOTH CUBE
The Concert Band
Needs you!
I'm Homura Chika,
The Concert Band
Needs you!
a cute girl in the first year of high school,
and a wonderful flutist.
The Concert Band
Needs you!
Huh?!
The Concert Band
Needs you!
Okay, that part was a lie. I only picked up
the flute once I started high school.
I'm a beginner with a mere
month and a half of experience.
This is still too hard for you, huh?
Don't worry!
Your playing is nice and loud.
Be a good girl and hand out
these flyers, Chika-chan.
You're nothing if not loud, so there's that.
What was that for?
Good morning.
Has anyone asked to join?
Nobody yet.
But we've had a few stop to listen to us.
We have a chance, then.
Yes.
Let's take it one more time from the top.
Right.
We are the Concert Band!
Please consider joining us!
Here you go!
We are the Concert Band!
Please take one.
We can put on fun
performances together—
Knock it off!
Narushima Miyoko, Class 1-3.
You know of her?
Somewhat.
She's an outstanding talent
I want in our band at all costs.
In junior high, she played the oboe
on stage at Fumon Hall.
What's more,
her band only had twenty-three members—
an exceptionally low number.
Despite that, their debut performance
earned them silver in the competition.
Huh? Twenty-three is an
exceptionally low number?
What are you talking about?
Of course it is.
The All-Japan Concert Band Competition
is divided into two categories:
Category A, which allows
a max of fifty-five members,
Category A
55 members
Category B
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
55 members
Category B
30 members
and Category B, which allows a max of thirty.
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
55 members
Category B
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
55 members
Category B
Category A
30 members
Category B
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
55 members
Category B
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
National
Regional
Prefectural
Local
Category A
55 members
Local
Category B
30 members
National
Regional
Prefectural
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
National
Regional
Prefectural
Category A
55 members
Category B
30 members
National
Regional
Prefectural
Category A
55 members
Prefectural
Category B
30 members
National
Regional
Prefectural
Category A
National
Regional
Prefectural
Category A
55 members
Prefectural
Category B
30 members
National
Regional
Prefectural
Category B
30 members
National
Regional
Prefectural
National
Regional
Category B
30 members
Prefectural
Regional
But Category B only goes up to the regional level.
You can't participate in the All-Japans
at Fumon Hall that way.
Just how many people will we have
to recruit before the competition?
It's not like we can compete this year regardless.
We'd have a hard time even
in Category B with our roster.
Would you like to listen to
Narushima-san's performance?
This is your place?
Yeah. I live alone in this apartment complex.
What? Really?
Instead of having my own room,
I got an old apartment.
I split the rent with my parents.
Talk about living in comfort.
You remember my older sisters, right?
Minami-san, Tsumugi-san, and Fuyuna-san...
That place is hell.
Come in.
Thanks for having me!
Wait, isn't this a bad idea?
Should I really just waltz into the
apartment of a boy who lives alone?
I have zero interest in you,
for your information.
I know.
This was at last year's junior high All-Japans.
Wow.
But don't you think she has
a problematic personality?
What are you saying?
If we're going to cover for your mistakes,
we need as many good performers as we can get.
Figures.
I want us to take part next year.
I want to help Kusakabe-sensei take the stage
at Fumon Hall as a conductor.
Yeah...
We need her skills to achieve that.
I'm done with concert bands, sorry.
And that's a crying shame, isn't it?
I'm sure your oboe must be
sobbing its heart out.
Yeah! It's crying so much it's got
its own, even smaller violin!
Chika-chan, you're way off.
In so many ways.
Take your comedy act elsewhere.
Please! Help us out here!
We have every intention of
making it worth your while.
Tell us what you want.
For you to go away.
Other than that.
I'm thirsty.
Grilled Chicken Centre
Where are we supposed to find
domestic pineapple juice?!
Here it is!
Chika-chan, money!
Just you wait, Princess Kaguya!
Grilled Chicken Centre
Here you go, Narushima-san.
Hey, you said you wanted this!
Sorry.
It's our bad for disturbing
your peaceful school life.
Going to the market was something
we decided on our own accord,
and while Chika-chan has absorbed the cost
of the juice, she doesn't hold it against you.
How much was it?
How much?
Quite a lot.
After all, it was expensive
domestic pineapple juice.
But you nearly bought
domestic kiwi fruit juice.
I love kiwi fruit.
Did you know the kiwi fruit is in the
genus Actinidia, just like cat powder?
Really? Maybe my cat will like it, then.
So how much was it?
I don't care about the money.
Sorry. I apologise.
If we want you to join the concert band,
we should just come out and say it.
You're annoying me.
The way she's acting,
we won't get along even if she does join.
Something's not right.
Don't you sense anything?
Not really.
Thought as much.
"He who would the daughter win,
must with the mother first begin."
What? No way!
But Koromin said so!
That's just out of the question, right?
Right!
You're Nishikawa Mayu-san, right?
Y-Yes.
Do you have a moment?
Sorry to make you come here.
Don't be!
You were friends with Narushima-san, right?
I noticed you two walking home together in April.
You've had your eye on her for that long?
Narushima-san moved here recently,
so she doesn't have any friends from junior high.
Going by roll numbers,
you would've ended up sitting behind her.
You struck up conversation first, right?
A lot of people become friends that way.
Wow! Just who are you, Kamijou-kun?
A moron.
But I bet you couldn't handle her
control-freak nature after a while.
You shouldn't let it bother you.
That's how oboe players are fated to be.
The oboe changes its tune drastically
based on its player's quirks.
It's a very sensitive instrument.
So the longer one plays it,
the more of a control freak they become.
Is that so?
Are you serious?
But you know what?
That's proof that she's given the oboe her all.
We would love to have her as a bandmate.
But Miyo-chan won't...
You know why she quit the oboe, don't you?
I was there when she played
at All-Japans last year.
After all the programs had ended,
a scream rang across the auditorium.
And she was nowhere to be seen
during the awards ceremony.
Does that have anything to do
with why she quit?
Miyo-chan's little brother
passed away that day.
BLOSSOM
Miyo-chan's little brother had
been in hospital for a long time.
His condition took a
sudden turn for the worse.
Their parents were at the venue as well,
so there was nobody by his side at the end.
So she felt guilty and quit the oboe?
Yeah.
Have you ever gone to hang out?
At Narushima-san's place.
Such a lovely aroma.
Could it be beef stew?
Yes?
It's Nishikawa.
Oh, welcome!
Just one moment!
Long time no see.
Help yourselves.
Sorry for showing up without notice.
Don't be.
It's been such a long time since
any of Miyoko's friends stopped by.
Um, where's Miyo-chan?
I'm sorry. I called for her, but...
Oh, it's our fault for dropping in
without telling her.
We have plenty of time,
so we'll wait as long as it takes.
I even brought along
my own chopsticks, just in case.
And Chika-chan was interested
in some of that beef—
What was that for?
Miyo-chan...
You can drink that in my room.
The coffee.
Sorry, Miyo-chan.
This is a bother, isn't it?
That should go without saying.
Drink your coffee and go home.
Don't you know?
Haruta once spent five hours
on one cup of coffee at a café
just so he could finish reading
eighty-three volumes of Patalliro!
You have five minutes.
She says we have five minutes, Haruta.
It's like a little museum of sorts.
I'm lucky I got to see this.
Solitaire
What do you mean?
Tower of Hanoi
Solitaire
Cast Puzzles
Tower of Hanoi
Solitaire
Cast Puzzles
Tower of Hanoi
Solitaire
Cast Puzzles
These are all puzzles.
Solitaire
Tower of Hanoi
Cast Puzzles
Solitaire
Tower of Hanoi
Cast Puzzles
Solitaire
Tower of Hanoi
Cast Puzzles
Solitaire
Tower of Hanoi
Cast Puzzles
Solitaire
Tower of Hanoi
Cast Puzzles
Solitaire
Tower of Hanoi
Cast Puzzles
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
All the classics are in here.
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Mastermind
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Rubik's Cubes
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Rubik's Cubes
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Rubik's Cubes
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Rubik's Cubes
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Rubik's Cubes
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Rubik's Cubes
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Rubik's Cubes
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Rubik's Cubes
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Rubik's Cubes
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Rubik's Cubes
15 Puzzles
Tangrams
Rubik's Cubes
And the pictures on the wall
are all trompe l'oeils.
I doubt you collected all of this.
Why is that?
These books are the Bibles for puzzle buffs.
Their author, Dudeney, was a genius
whose talents manifested at the age of nine.
Looking at this "exhibit",
I find it hard to believe you touch them often.
I bet they all belonged
to your little brother.
So what?
It's fantastic.
He must've admired Dudeney,
who was already known as a genius at his age.
Look, he signed all the items he made himself.
His devotion to puzzles was truly praiseworthy.
As serious as his illness may have been.
What is with you?
Everything you have here is the mark
your brother left on the world.
They're truly precious,
and not for show.
Did you actually solve all of them?
I'm not surprised.
You couldn't have.
Not in your current state.
That should go without saying.
Haruta!
Because you're carrying a burden that you
can never lighten, and you're doing it alone.
And what could you possibly do?
We can help shoulder it together with you.
We can try to solve any puzzle that you can't.
At the very least, you won't be the only one
suffering due to the puzzles in this room.
Get out.
Get out!
Sorry.
I've listened to Miyo-chan's
All-Japans performance.
Were you at the venue as well?
No, I listened to the recording.
Satoshi-kun had asked
Mr. and Mrs. Narushima.
He told them to watch over
Miyo-chan on stage
and record her performance for him,
or else he'd hate them forever.
Oh...
Nobody was in the wrong.
It was just a perfect storm of bad luck.
So it was nobody's fault.
Miyo-chan?
Try to solve this by yourselves.
A Rubik's cube?
All of its faces are white.
Out of all the puzzles Satoshi left behind,
this is the only one I just can't solve.
Is this scrambled?
"Scrambled"?
It's when a puzzle is jumbled up
and ready to solve.
He said it was.
And the solution?
He didn't show me.
If we solve this,
will you seriously consider
joining the concert band?
You have until after school on Friday.
Got it.
You can't do it.
That cube is impossible to solve.
It's the punishment that Satoshi left me.
Music Prep Room
Monday
Wow!
The issue is this one.
Why the gloves?
I don't want to get her
treasured memento dirty.
Memento...
Tuesday
Maybe it sounds different somewhere?
Or maybe there's a
subtle colour difference?
The smell, maybe?
It smells weird!
Let me see that.
You're right.
Wednesday
Yeah, I think it's oil paint.
I knew it.
So he painted a regular Rubik's cube
white using oil paint?
Yeah.
It looked like one of Narushima-san's
parents is an oil painter.
How do you know?
You got distracted by food and let something
important slip by unnoticed, like always.
Hey, I noticed the smell!
Is there anything else you've noticed?
Even the slightest of details could help.
This doesn't have Satoshi-kun's
signature on it anywhere.
Thursday
Music Prep Room
Give it up and go
apologise to Narushima.
Tell her you couldn't solve it,
but you want her to join anyway.
We have till tomorrow.
But if we don't know what the solution is,
how are we supposed to solve it?
Still, there's bound to be a right answer,
as long as it's a puzzle.
Kusakabe-sensei...
So this is the Rubik's cube
everyone's talking about.
Yes.
The person who can tell us its answer
is no longer in this world.
If its creator knew that they'd be gone
by the time it was solved,
they must've left some way
to prove when that had happened.
On this cube?
This cube is probably made so that the proof
will show up by itself when it's solved.
Proof of solution
Show up by itself
Satoshi-kun's signature missing
Oil paint
I think the steps that need to be taken to
find that proof are the crux of this puzzle.
Steps that need to be taken
Crux of the puzzle
This is no punishment.
Con amore.
Connor Moray?
It's a musical term.
It means "with love".
This is a puzzle that was made with love.
Friday
Did you solve it?
We're going to solve it now.
And you'll solve it with us.
You called this cube a punishment, didn't you?
That's right.
Satoshi couldn't make friends
because he was ill.
Puzzles were his source of
self-esteem and emotional support.
He would make puzzles,
and I would solve them.
That's how it was for years...
Until I joined the concert band in junior high.
I was having so much fun
that I left him all alone.
So this unsolvable puzzle
is a message from him to me.
Saying he wants to cause me trouble,
and that he won't forgive me.
You're right.
This cube is a message from Satoshi-kun.
Let's begin.
Right now, this cube is in a scrambled state,
and all six sides are white.
This is the start line.
But no matter how much you turn it,
you'll always go back to square one.
Do you know why Satoshi-kun
didn't tell you what the solution was?
Because he wanted you to take a
step forward from this scrambled state.
But that's impossible.
Chika-chan, Nishikawa-san.
Wh-What are you doing?
Forgive me, Miyo-chan.
I'll be done in three minutes.
Trust me.
What do you think you're doing?
Stop it!
Hey, do you hear me?!
Please, no!
Let go! Let me go!
All done.
Why would you do this?
It's time for you to move on, Narushima-san.
Shut up.
Are you going to use your sorrow
as a shield for the rest of your life?
It's only been a year since
Satoshi died, you know.
It's already been one whole year.
A year in our lives is more significant
than a year in the life of an adult.
Haruta!
Stay away!
This cube is a message
that Satoshi-kun left for you!
No matter what happens,
never stop in your tracks.
Keep moving forward.
He wants you to paint this
pure-white world in your own colours.
And this is the first step.
Take a good look.
Your little brother sends his best wishes.
Satoshi...
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
Any signature on that cube
could only have been under the white.
So I thought about how to strip it off.
The squares that were written on
had linen applied on them
and were coated with zinc white.
The other squares also had linen applied
but were coated in a different white paint.
When you paint over zinc white
using an oil-based paint,
it will peel off.
But the paint needs to dry
before that happens.
It usually takes an entire day.
Yes. I'd already painted over it
in white yesterday,
so that it would conveniently
peel off in front of Narushima-san.
Impressive.
I couldn't have done it
without Homura-san's hints.
There's that goody-two-shoes act again.
What will Narushima-san do now?
That's for her to decide.
A promise is a promise.
Oh, come on.
world
is
still
grey,
but
it's
star
ting
to
chan
words
hang
in
the
air,
pat
ches
of
color,
hi
ra
drif
ting
thro
ugh
the
world
hide
my
heart
in
doubt
tries
to
figure
out
whe
ther
to
say
'yes'
or
'no'
Some
times
we
lose
each
other
in
our
fanta
sies,
tired
to
walk
clear
of
them,
lody
won't
stop
now
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
You've
solved it,
Onee-chan
fuzzy
trian
gle
is
a
circle
of
love,
tur
ning
on
ward
What
ever
for
mula
we
try,
can't
solve
it
an
shin
ease?
An
xious?
mony
might
seem
cont
radic
tory,
will
keep
gui
ding
ards
a
new
future
look
for
the
answer
days
that
are
to
come
Where am I supposed to take
my first step towards?
Why is Maren in the drama club?
Challenge accepted.
Yes, I call it...
EXIT GAME
"Exit Game"?