Nemurin here!
Are we already past the half-way mark?
That was quick.
It feels like it was only yesterday
that I started doing these previews.
It hasn't been long since I was deleted either, right?
I wanted to visit a lot more dreams!
Without further ado,
here's the preview for next week's episode!
Next Episode
Next week: Hardgore Alice vs Calamity Mary!
Truly devilish magic approaches.
What's the truth behind Alice's magic?
After a long decisive battle,
who will be left standing?!
Episode 07: Up Your Friendship!
Up Your Friendship!
Look forward to it!
Will that do?
This is the first time
I've worked properly, so I'm tired.
I can skip work next week, right?
Well then, goodnight!