I lovehate you, lovehate you, baby, yeah!
Hacka Doll
The Animation
You won't find anything ordinary around here!
You have so much information at your fingertips!
Don't be shy and don't run away!
Bang! Bang! Just leave it to us!
C'mon, just be true to your feelings
and let yourself be taken with the flow!
This freedom is finally letting me see
that there are so many choices in front of me
Which one do I pick? Won't you help me choose?
Let's keep touching today, baby!
How do you want to feel?
I can be in the minority or the majority
They're both just as fun to me!
Let's keep touching today, baby!
So won't you softly touch me, baby?
I just can't wait to be with you!
I lovehate you, lovehate you, baby, yeah!
Squid Black Light General Hospital
Hey. Glad you came.
You guys are the ones that
can advance anything, right?
Yup! We're Hacka Dolls!
Well, the reason I summoned you is because...
We want you guys to fight monsters
for us while we're in the hospital.
We got a little carried
away in the movie version.
The founder took it too seriously.
She blew away a building with her bare hands.
I can't hold a candle to her!
So that's why we need your help.
For today, hang out at the embankment
on Third, and they'll show up.
Um... Who exactly will show up?
Who else? The monsters of course!
Praying for your speedy recovery.
The Neighborhood Big Friend Association
We can sense that sort of thing.
Praying for your speedy recovery.
The Neighborhood Big Friend Association
Okay, get out there and be
Magical Girl Lovely Hurt!
Okay! We'll do our best!
Episode 12: "Magical Girl Lovely Hurt♥"
I can't believe we get to help Lovely Hurt!
A gorilla, right?
That was a gorilla, wasn't it?
We're so lucky to get a big gig like
this in our second-to-last episode.
That said, will the monsters really show up here?
A scream?!
What the?!
Today, just like any other day,
we'll stare at the girls walking
down the street for no reason.
We'll wave at them.
We'll greet them with smiles.
And we'll create incidents!
Mama!
Don't look at them.
It's the evil monsters!
They really did show up...
We need to transform, guys!
Yes!
Stop right there!
Who's there?!
Blazing in the sun, Hacka Drive!
Lovely #1!
Swaying in the breeze, Hacka Rhythm!
Lovely #2!
Exuding the sweet fragrance
of the ocean, Hacka Romance!
Lovely #3!
Together, we are...
Magical Girl Lovely Hurt!
Magical Girl
Whoa! It's Lovely Hurt!
Kick the bad guys' butts!
You seem a bit different,
but there you are, Lovely Hurt!
Victory to the swiftest! Here I come!
Bring it on!
Ouch!
Don't dodge it! Elbow him!
Quit slacking!
Grab him from behind and throw him!
What's wrong?
Come at me with your usual
focus on physical blows!
Ouchies!
He doesn't fly away when punched,
like they do on TV!
What are you doing?!
Use Lovely Folding Chair
to beat him to a bloody pulp!
Get out your Lovely Bar, moron!
#1!
You won't get away with that!
No!
Looks like you're having
an off-day, Lovely Hurt!
I'll defeat you swiftly so I'll have
time to stop by the cleaners afterward!
Hold it!
Nothing can be seen
in a world of darkness.
However!
If you close your eyes,
you can see a tiny bit of light.
I call that light "hope"!
Who the hell are you?!
I need not tell the likes of you!
#4, what are you doing?
Manami
Akino
Saori
Last night was wonderful!
Sakako
I am a substitute for the heroes
who hurt themselves in the movie!
Manami
Akino
Saori
Last night was wonderful!
Sakako
Manami
Akino
Saori
Last night was wonderful!
Sakako
Manami
Akino
Saori
Last night was wonderful!
Sakako
Manami
Akino
Saori
Last night was wonderful!
Sakako
Heroes just keep coming to
thwart me, one after another...
At this rate,
I'll never be able to make
this a happy and healthy town!
Huh? You weren't going
for world domination?
Stop your whining!
All right! I'll just have to crush you!
And now the final blow!
Idiot! What are you doing?!
Look what you did to our town!
Put it back!
Huh? That's easier said than done...
What? Why does it always end like this?!
Something is seriously wrong here!
So this is the end... How regrettable.
Mister Monster...
I wanted to clean up this town.
I wanted this town to be a safe place
for all the little children who live here.
I wanted everyone here to smile.
However!
Those impetuous magical girls,
those transforming heroes, always attack me!
We were only trying to make
this town a better place!
Poor guy.
I understand!
Right!
Mister Monster, we were wrong about you.
We thought you were the bad guy.
We'll help you clean up this town!
You'll really help me?
Yes!
You can count on the Hacka Dolls!
Starting today, we'll collaborate
with the evil monsters!
It's the start of a new group!
New costumes!
Hacka... Dolls!
All for love! All for you!
New costumes to commemorate the founding of a new group
These new wrestlers motto is to make this town a clean and beautiful place
Your innocent smile will power me up
Your tears will clear up like the sky
We'll make a vow for peace to the setting sun
It's a little embarrassing,
Don't miss this battle of historic proportions!
Lovely Hurt vs. Captain Evil Monster
but you can leave world peace to us!