Takamatsu, your report, please.
At once.
According to the Armory's reports,
our emergency ammunition stocks will soon be depleted.
Before conducting our next combat operation, we should be sure to refill.
We've got a new recruit as well,
so we'll need new guns too, right?
Good point.
Understood! Our next operation will be to drop into the Guild.
D-Drop?
What's wrong, Otonashi?
I guess I'm just... not good with heights.
What are you talking about?
We're not dropping from the sky.
We're descending underground.
Oh, underground, huh?
Wait, underground?!
We call it the Guild.
It's deep underground.
We have allies there who make weapons for us.
So, it's there to keep Angel from finding out?
Correct.
If the Guild was seized, our source of ordinance would disappear,
and we'd lose any chance of success along with it.
Yeah?
It's me.
We're coming tonight.
Deactivate the traps for me.
Roger. Tonight, it is. See you then.
Okay.
We'll take everyone currently present here.
Oh? But what about Noda?
That idiot's probably goofing off somewhere again.
All right, let's go.
Here we go...
Okay, let's get moving.
Come on, don't just stand there. Let's go.
I-In here?
So this is the entrance, huh?
It's been a while since we've
visited the Guild, hasn't it?
It sure is dark.
Hey, someone's here!
Oh... It's just a moron.
Otonashi, huh? I refuse to accept you yet.
Why'd he pick here to lie in wait?
Noda attaches great significance to situations.
That's a little cryptic...
I don't really want you to accept me, either.
You scumbag... This won't end like bef—
Defensive positions!
The traps aren't deactivated?!
What's going on?
Exactly what you're seeing.
The road to the Guild is filled with anti-Angel traps.
And by the looks of it, they're all still armed.
Which means...
I wonder if we forgot to deactivate them?
No way. That's like asking to be annihilated.
That's not it. The Guild must have rearmed the traps themselves.
But why?
There's only one possibility.
Angel is here!
In here?!
Just wild heaven.
How negligent.
So wait, these Guild guys are doing this even though they know we're here?
It seems you still don't understand...
No matter what might happen, we aren't going to die.
Although, we'll certainly taste the pain of it...
I'd prefer to avoid that...
But if the Guild's location
is discovered and overtaken,
our weapons, ammo, and everything else will cease to function.
After that, how would you suggest we fight against Angel?
The Guild's decision was correct.
Are we going to pursue Angel?
Even with all the traps armed?
The traps will handle Angel somehow... let's retreat!
The traps will do little more
than slow down her advance.
We'll chase her.
Advance!
So, uh, what kind of traps
are set up here anyway?
All kinds, my friend. Look forward to 'em.
Watch out, it's coming!
Huh? What is?
Run for it!
Fool, we're crazy...
In here! Hurry!
That was Takamatsu's voice...
It got him.
Everyone but Takamatsu appears unhurt.
Let's continue.
Is it really right of us not to help him?
It's not like he'll die.
He'll make it out on his own, eventually.
Really?
Up you go.
Ah, thanks.
You saved me back there.
No need for thanks.
To tell the truth, I've grown to like you.
You coming onto me?
No way, man!
Will it open?
Not at all.
I forgot about this one!
This trap seals off all of the exits!
Don't forget something that important!
How foolish.
What's about to come is really dangerous!
Avoid it!
Get down!
What the?
What happens if you touch them?
You'll be split in two by the sharpest object imaginable.
Second wave incoming!
What do I do?
You evade it!
Third wave incoming!
What was the third wave, again?
It's an X pattern!
So what do I do with this one?!
Just do something!
Open up already!
Don't look!
You really don't wanna see.
What's going on?
It's open! Let's go!
So the sacrifice this time was Matsushita, huh?
With a body like that, it's no surprise.
The man needs to go on a diet.
He saw something pretty nasty.
Poor guy, right in front of him.
I'm glad that you managed to make it.
By the way, even when you're chopped up like that, you'll still recover.
The trap's firing up!
I forgot about this one! It's a falling ceiling trap!
I told you not to forget
important things like that!
TK!
Hurry up! Go now and you'll make it!
Hold on to each other and get out of here!
Thanks.
See ya!
Appreciate it.
Sorry.
Even TK sacrificed himself...
You guys sacrificed him.
Like I said, he'll be fine eventually.
Don't sweat the small stuff.
We'll make sure his sacrifice isn't in vain.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
Something's...
I forgot about this one!
L-Like I told you, don't forget important things like that!
Too heavy...
I can't hold on...
Otonashi and I can drop down.
Hang on! Don't just make these decisions yourself!
Losing everyone here would be a terrible idea.
You don't need to tell me that!
Hurry up and climb, everyone!
Otonashi, can you make it?
I don't have much choice!
You're quite the sadist.
Shut it! I'm climbing!
What are you doing?
Don't stop, just keep climbing!
But where do I grab on to?!
I really don't care!
Just grab wherever you want!
Hurry up already...
I am.
You're gonna fall if you grab there.
I guess so.
Whoa, what's this? She smells great...
Not good.
I need to climb.
Hey, why are you looking at me?
I can't help it!
H-Hurry up and climb up already.
Y-Yeah...
Ah! You can't grab there!
Idiot!
Uh, well, Hinata was...
He sacrificed himself.
I see...
We're down to four, now.
Hah. You've got some nerve.
Being one of the last remaining as the new guy.
Sure, whatever.
You'll definitely be next.
An inundation trap, huh?
This guy can't even swim?
The exit's this way. Come on!
Here.
Thanks.
Yuri! Over here!
Shiina.
Let's go.
Huh? What's that doing here?
That's...
The puppy's gonna get swept away!
Shiina! No!
I messed up. It was just a toy!
Even Shiina was caught up in one of the traps!
That was a trap for Angel, too?!
Wait... she couldn't tell at a glance?
She has a weakness for cute things.
Wow. That's an unexpectedly adorable trait.
But she'll be fine too, won't she?
You're the only one left, huh?
Seems that way...
If we were a real unit, we'd have been completely wiped out by now.
I'm a terrible leader.
There wasn't much we could do about it.
These are anti-Angel traps after all.
If they can't even stop us, what good are they?
Um...
Should we take a break?
Sure. We need to dry our clothes out, anyway.
I'm amazed that you're able to lead a group like that.
Why were you chosen as the leader?
Because I was the first to resist.
That's the only reason.
Against Angel?
Yeah.
I had siblings...
Huh?
I'm talking about what you don't have. Memories.
From before you came here? When you were alive?
Yeah.
Including me, four siblings.
I was the eldest daughter,
and had two younger sisters,
and one younger brother.
My parents were fairly successful in
their work lives, so we were quite well-off.
We were surrounded by nature,
so it was almost like living in a villa.
It was during summer vacation.
In the afternoon, when my parents were out,
some men I'd never seen before were in the house.
Even though it was the middle of summer,
they were wearing stifling-looking balaclavas.
I knew they'd come to do something bad.
I was the eldest, so I knew that
I had to protect my younger siblings.
But hey, there's no way that would happen, right?
Of course, the guys were after our valuables,
but they couldn't find them.
Because of that, they started indiscriminately destroying windows and televisions out of rage.
After that, they came up with something diabolical to do with us siblings...
Little girl, you're the eldest, right?
Your parents must've told you where the valuables are, right?
Like, "if there's an earthquake, grab these and run,"
or "if robbers come, give them these and ask them to leave."
I'm sure your parents must've told you something, right?
I don't know...
I don't know anything about that!
Well then, go and look.
If we don't like what you find, you'll be saying goodbye to these kids, one by one.
We'll give you ten minutes for each of them.
Use those ten minutes to find
something worthwhile.
I started searching the house frantically.
My head was pounding like it was about to split.
I was nauseous. I was ready to faint.
My siblings' lives were on the line.
I had to find something!
But I had no idea what sort of valuables
they were looking for.
Ah, it's time! I have to hurry up and find something!
I'll bring the biggest-looking thing here.
Heavy.
I'm sure this is worth a lot!
I have to get it downstairs!
By the time the police arrived, thirty minutes had passed.
The only one alive... was me.
All alone.
It's not that I care if I'm reincarnated as a water flea, or anything.
It's just that if God exists, I want to fight him.
I mean... it's just too much.
He doesn't intervene when bad things happen...
That afternoon, I truly thought I was a responsible older sister.
Everything I wanted to protect was
taken from me in just thirty minutes...
Don't you think that's just ridiculous?
Don't you find a life like that totally unforgivable?
You're strong, Yuri.
If I had memories like that,
I'd only want to sit back and disappear.
But you're fighting, Yuri.
That's right.
Hey, can I ask you something?
What?
Why did you die, Yuri?
Oh...
Don't be stupid. It wasn't suicide or anything.
Someone who commited suicide wouldn't fight back like this.
Besides, there are no suicide victims in this world.
Now let's get going.
I'll protect you.
This is the Guild?!
It's Yurippe!
She's here!
She's okay!
So these guys make weapons in this place?
You managed to make it past all of the traps, Yurippe?
We should have known you would.
More importantly, where's Angel?
Her advance was halted not long ago,
but it seems that she's begun to move again.
There it is again!
She's close.
Yurippe...
We're abandoning this place.
What?
Are you serious, Yurippe?
Think about it! Are you fine with not being able to make weapons anymore?
Places and tools aren't important.
Memories are.
Have you guys forgotten that?
N-No...
What do you mean, Yuri?
In this world, nothing with a soul can be given life.
Only objects of form alone.
As long as you know the composition and structure of the object,
that's essentially all you need.
You can even make things out of mud.
However, we eventually prioritized efficiency,
and all we do now is make replicas in this factory.
Chaa.
This guy's a high-schooler, too?
In the past, we used to create objects using just the shape and memory of them, no?
Well then, let's head to the Old Guild.
It's been lying dormant for quite some time.
There's nothing there, but...
There's a mountain's worth of earth to make things from over there.
We should be able to get back to the surface from there, too.
What about this place?
We'll blow it up.
Otherwise, Angel could reach the Old Guild from here.
It's the only place we have left to return to.
Even so...
She's right above us!
The only things you need to bring with you
are your memories, and your pride as a craftsman.
That is all.
Right guys?
Yeah!
All right! Prepare the explosives!
Let's see some teamwork!
Yeah!
There are no traps left. Hurry!
Yuri, where are you going?
To buy us time!
Oh, you came. Aren't you afraid?
There was nothing I could do if I'd stayed down there.
She's here...
Let's do this!
Guard Skill: Distortion.
She's responding too quickly!
Incredible. She can keep up with her in close combat?
Load shell!
Is it okay to fire with her up there?
Just do it!
Heave! Heave!
Hurry it up!
Guard Skill: Delay.
Damn it!
Otonashi!
Get outta the way, you two!
Guys! You get things done when you need to!
Something like that doesn't look easy to make!
Otonashi, this way!
Let's do it!
All hands, brace for impact!
Fire!
Did it work?
The cannon blew up, huh?
Damn it. I guess you can't make
things you don't understand...
Don't randomly make thigns!
Angel's recovering!
You guys!
Do something with these!
Shell squad, hurry up!
All members accounted for!
Got it. Time to blow this place to pieces.
You sure?
Do it.
Here goes!
How many years has it been?
This place really is empty...
What a joke.
If you tear down the walls,
you'll have all the earth you need.
What a crappy nesting place.
I'm counting on you to make a new one.
Right.
Okay, let's get started, you guys!
Yeah!
Hey morons, you awake?
We tore down the Guild, and blew up Angel.
Hurry to the Old Guild, and let everyone know.
We'll replenish our arms as fast as we can, before Angel can recover.
All members, to the Old Guild.
I repeat: Hurry up, morons.
I saved her without even thinking twice.
What am I doing?
It's just that if God exists, I want to fight him.
I mean... it's just too much.
It's too terrible.
You really are amazing.
So this is why everyone follows you.
You truly are a leader.
Why's the new song a ballad?
Please, call me Christ.
...I couldn't sing the song I wanted to.
Angel's residence.
You guys were really fired up.
Another one that's great is Alchemy! Alchemy is...
No memories!
Then, what happened?
I was just starting to change
my opinion of you guys, too!
Angel has appeared.
The worst case scenario.
...That's as far as you go.
I said, don't touch that!