You being a member of an organization
from the dark side like GROUP
meant that we wouldn't be able to find you
through our regular information networks.
That's why we decided to use Shiokishi,
who's at the core of Academy City.
Etzali,
we're here to kill you.
Is that...
Yes. An original Grimoire.
This should normally be able to
take out celestial bodies in one hit,
but apparently the rabbit bones
I used were of low quality.
What did you do?
What did you do to Tochtli?!
Rabbit bones.
Do I really have to spell it out for you?
Isn't it fun watching her?
She probably has fewer than half of her bones left.
Tecpatl!
That's it.
That's how our people fight.
Let us show each other the pinnacle of our intellect
in this battle for control over the Aztecs.
K-Kinuhata!
So I assume you don't mind being killed here.
Of course not.
I'm not so intolerant as to
take offense at such delusions.
DRAGON
If I'm not mistaken, Kihara Amata
broke through your reflective wall
by pulling back his fist a moment before contact.
And...
Kakine Teitoku used a material
that doesn't exist in this world.
Oh, well.
I suppose basing my actions on outliers
wasn't going to work out.
You're small fry.
You may have some decent skill,
but you just follow a scheming old fart's orders.
And you're the descendant of people who
considered themselves on the side of justice?
Does that bastard Shiokishi
look like a righteous person to you?
Are you doing the righteous
thing by being his lapdog?
Don't make me laugh.
It's true that righteousness is constantly
used as a pretext by those in power.
But will entrusting everything to evil
solve every last one of the world's problems?
All evil like yours does is scrounge
for crumbs that righteousness dropped.
You shithead.
The moment you consider those mere leftovers,
your righteousness is already a farce.
How would a villain like you know
what a righteous person should be?
I do know.
So vividly, it makes me almost
flip out every time I recall it.
Really?
But regardless, you'll never meet
that righteous person again.
Because you'll die here.
Your electrode was modified
to be controllable remotely.
Once you're isolated from the MISAKA Network,
you lose all ability to fight.
This is my righteousness.
This is how I continue to fight
for what I consider righteous,
despite living in the world of the despicable.
What?!
You're super-experienced in fighting espers and
endowed with the eye to spot their weaknesses.
However, it seems you failed to understand
that I'm a human super-struggling to survive.
Oh, right.
I'm almost invincible in close combat,
but what I'm worst at is dealing with
super-precise, long-distance attacks.
Compared to a firepower freak like you,
Sunazara Chimitsu was a lot harder to deal with.
Liquid nitrogen?!
You replenished the nitrogen.
The Grimoire is pouring into my head.
But I don't care.
Even if it's the end of me...
The difference in experience shows, Etzali.
You should know that to use
one of these as a weapon,
you need to take measures to prevent
the back-flow of information.
Which means you haven't actually
read your original Grimoire.
How?!
Don't you know?
An original Grimoire sides with the one
who's most willing to propagate its knowledge.
A transcription of the stone tablets!
You hadn't really engaged the knowledge
of the original Grimoire.
Did you really think it would
allow itself to be used like that?
H-How?!
This is a jamming device.
What?!
Broad-spectrum electromagnetic jamming would
interfere with my connection
to the MISAKA Network.
So I analyzed the signal you used before
and calculated targeted jamming for it.
That's how evil does things.
You and I are exactly the same.
And I'm definitely not righteous.
So you, who use the same methods,
are also a tried and true villain.
Don't you think you went a bit overboard?
I get that you're super-proud of your guns,
but calling a Six Wings assault chopper too?
What are you talking about?
Huh?
If I could bring an assault chopper,
I'd definitely be shooting at you
from beyond your effective range.
So what in the world was that?
Is there someone else who's super-after us?
Wait!
Hamazura! Super-run away!
I think they're after you!
What?
Let's go, Hamazura!
B-But Kinuhata's still—
Quickly!
Damn it!
What's the super-meaning of this?
Do you know that Aleister has
set some kind of plan in motion?
Elements like Kamijou Touma and Accelerator
are nothing but outliers within the margin of error.
That's why they can easily be
incorporated as keystones of the plan.
However, Hamazura Shiage is different.
That Level 0 was an element that should
have been killed in the dark side's conflicts.
A Level 0 with no power or role to play,
Hamazura Shiage is trying
to take fate into his own hands,
and gain a new value that even
Aleister himself cannot assess.
He might even threaten Aleister's plan.
Academy City has turned all
its attention to killing Hamazura.
Do you think that man is worth all that?
DRAGON?
Have you figured out anything about it?
I really hope you're not trying to play dumb.
I'd feel much better if I really didn't know,
but unfortunately I do.
It's something that human eyes shouldn't see.
What is this DRAGON? Where is it?
Don't be silly.
DRAGON is everywhere.
Like right behind you right now.
What?
A dragon?
I suppose one could call it that.
Although "angel" is also applicable.
But if you want to express what I am more precisely,
you will need to use another name.
I am the one who once gave an eccentric
sorcerer by the name of Crowley
all the knowledge that he needed.
A Certain Magical Index
I am Aiwass.
Takitsubo!
Hamazura!
Run!
Otherwise they'll just catch us both.
S-So...
Hamazura!
Shut up.
Someone...
Please...
Don't worry about me, Hamazura.
I'll buy you some time.
Don't be stupid!
Please come!
A gallant hero that can save her!
Please!
Hey! We're alive, Takitsubo!
I don't know who helped us, but we're alive!
Hamazura!
No!
Don't get yourself killed by these pathetic goons.
You'd ruin my plans to butcher you into little pieces.
You appear bewildered.
Is it so incomprehensible that I'd appear before you?
What are you?
Why are you hiding behind the codename DRAGON?
Do I have to begin explaining from there?
I'm nothing special, really.
I'm just a gyhufwe aygjewfw.
I'm just a fwegyhu wewaygjf.
I'm just a wfhygue gjfweway.
I'm just a hufwegy ygjfwewa.
I'm just a wegyhuf awewfjgy.
I'm just a egyhufw gyawewfj.
I'm just a hufwegy ewfjgyaw.
What?
How inconvenient.
Apparently such a simple concept
cannot even be expressed in this world.
Do you know about Fuse Kazakiri?
What?
That's an artificial form of
what you would call an "angel".
It is a clump of AIM Diffusion Fields,
as well as something like a production
line used to give me, Aiwass, a form.
So, I appeared here out of curiosity,
but what shall I do now?
What would you like to do?
Would you like to destroy Aleister's ambitions
using information gained from me?
Are you seriously offering that?
It's no problem for me if Aleister's plan fails.
I can easily wait another 10,000, or even
100,000 years for another opportunity to hufwegy.
100,000 years for another opportunity to wegyhuf.
I can easily wait another 10,000, or even
100,000 years for another opportunity to fwehugy.
100,000 years for another opportunity to hwegufy.
I can easily wait another 10,000, or even
100,000 years for another opportunity to egyhufw.
No, to manifest.
I can tell you that Aleister's undertaking
is already beginning to come apart at the seams.
What?!
The cracks are slowly starting to widen.
If things continue this way, the cornerstone
of his plan, Last Order, will inevitably break down.
Bring it on!
I don't care if you're a clump of
AIM Diffusion Fields, or an angel, or whatever.
But if you're planning to hurt that kid,
I won't hold back!
Dear me.
My mistake.
That Aleister. He has affixed
something to the afguyas virus.
something to the afyasgu virus.
That Aleister. He has affixed
something to the yasafgu virus.
something to the aasfguy virus.
That Aleister. He has affixed
something to the yasafgu virus.
I'm terribly sorry.
Please do something about these yhuilaf
autonomous wings if you want to uylihozq me.
Please do something about these ilafyhu
autonomous wings if you want to hozquyli me.
Please do something about these ylafhui
autonomous wings if you want to louyzihq me.
Please do something about these layhuif
autonomous wings if you want to hlizqouy me.
Please do something about these yafhuil
autonomous wings if you want to hozuyliq me.
Please do something about these yhlafui
autonomous wings if you want to uhozqyli me.
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
Do as your will dictates.
Adhere to your Law.
Was that all?
All I had to do was mention
Last Order to provoke you.
You said that you're manifesting
using AIM Diffusion Fields.
And in order to control them,
you stuffed a virus into that kid,
creating this Fuse Kazakiri thing.
In that case...
So you did think this through.
You reconfigured all of the units
in the MISAKA Network.
But do you realize what that means?
You're cutting off your own lifeline.
Shut the hell up!
Very well.
Then show me your Law.
Why are you still alive?!
Hamazura!
You're quick to run as usual,
but are you sure that's what you want to do?
What about your beloved Takitsubo?
Which part should I fry first?
Should I make this little face sizzle?
Don't go playing the tragic heroine here.
You're not some damsel in distress.
Don't you have power you can use to fight?
Just run away if you're scared of the Body Crystals.
But Hamazura will be burnt to a crisp if you do.
Because you left him to die.
That's more like it!
Hurry up and take it!
It's your greatest weapon after all.
Hamazura.
Mugino!
What was that, Hamazura?
Who are you trying to protect?
What? If you finish her off yourself, problem solved?
Mugino Shizuri!
Apparently killing you just once wasn't enough!
No, it wasn't.
Not by a long shot!
What do you take me for, Hamazura?!
A smoke screen? Are you a ninja now?!
I-I did it!
Hamazura!
Did you think those mass-produced munitions
would be enough to take out Rank 4, Meltdowner?
Hamazura.
Is this an atmospheric entry test chamber?
It's really annoying actually.
Neither I, nor Kakine Teitoku, are allowed to die.
The General Superintendent
is so hellbent on reusing us,
the Level 5 espers, even to the point
where my body's become like this.
Say, Hamazura,
why did I become such a horrible monster?
Mugino...
Was that what you were hoping to hear?!
Hamazura!
What are you trembling about?
Can't I at least have some nice
enjoyable screams out of you?
I'll mix you in with some molten iron,
then cool you off to make a modern art piece!
What?
Warning: Initiating experiment.
Hamazura!
Is it all over?
Aleister is such a worrywart.
Apparently my barrier is built
more sturdily than I thought.
Go to hell.
I'm sorry, I know you fought
to the best of your ability,
but apparently I have the ability to transform.
Hamazura!
Listen to me!
Super-get out of there right now!
Kinuhata?
Another Academy City
military unit is heading your way.
Take Takitsubo and get away super-quickly!
Huh? But where can I go?
Aleister, could it be that you
are infatuated with them?
Those who try to walk straight ahead,
led by the emotions coming from inside,
rather than doing what they are told.
Those who try to walk the right path,
despite being tortured by the heavy crimes
they have committed in the past.
I'll save this kid's life!
Those who can become heroes
for the people they love,
despite nobody choosing them
and having no notable talents.
All of them, no matter how many
times they are beaten down,
are able to stand back up on their own.
They appear to possess what you are lacking.
Thus, it would not be surprising
if you were infatuated with them.
After all, back then, you could only
crumble down and lament.
Aiwass, I will use anything and anyone that is useful.
That also includes you.
Also, allow me to say this.
There's no guarantee that your
absolute superiority will continue forever.
The matter of the child is difficult.
She will definitely fall apart eventually.
If you do not want to lament her fate,
try walking a path different
than any that has existed before.
Go to Russia.
More precisely, to the Elizalina Alliance
of Independent Nations.
Remember the term Index Librorum Prohibitorum.
It is crucial to your predicament.
Go to Russia?
What's the matter, Hamazura?
Nothing.
Don't ever leave me.
I won't.
I'll never leave you.
Damn it, I'll never let go of you!
I'm coming!
Next Time
Academy City and Russia.
Everything is about to be engulfed.
By what?
Needless to say, it's the start of World War III.
Next time: "Alliance of Independent Nations".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.