"For any long-distance relationship to last,
the partners need to always
be thinking of each other."
"How to Steal Him"!
Love Trickery
Compilation
How to Steal Him!
Findings of love researcher professor Holon Neurospec
A Stronger Feminine Appeal Can
Overwrite His Memories
"A Stronger Feminine Appeal
Can Overwrite His Memories"
Th-The sexy fallen-angel maid!
Was that a perfectly-executed boobs-based plan,
combining heart, technique, and physique?!
The Priestess is truly a fearsome rival!
I may no longer have any chance of—
It's the new costume I'd heard about!
The revealing Great Spirit maid costume!
I can't possibly wear that!
Among the major events in October,
I think the ball at the
Queen's House would be optimal.
Although the guests there
may be somewhat unrefined.
Um, Knight Leader,
don't such evening parties and balls
tend to feature romance?
You came to me asking for instruction
on proper behavior in Britain.
Are you not investigating the
possibility of marrying nobility?
Where in the world did you hear such a thing?
That's odd.
Was the sexy fallen-angel
maid costume a false rumor?
That reaction is rather unladylike.
Ahem.
But anyway, what's the situation at the Eurotunnel?
Its restoration is looking grim.
I heard that relations with France
are becoming strained.
The British Parliament is
having a hard time suppressing the military,
who are pushing for a preemptive strike on France.
On our side, some domestic groups
are also exploiting the disturbance
to make worrying moves.
We have enemies both outside and inside.
We both have a lot to deal with.
A Certain Magical Index
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
Carrying a ticking time bomb
The Earth keeps on turning, so hurry up!
No one can pretend it's not their business anymore
Suddenly common sense is out the door
Opposing fates fail to reach each other
Drenched in the rain of resentment
But why? Fear and doubt keep building up heavy in my heart
My racing heart is flooded with ambition
Ready!
Everyone that's drawn to this place
Has gone beyond the meaning and color of desire
My heart wants to stay strong
I feel it deep inside me
With all my soul, this one thing
Dive into a heart
Sky Bus 365
I-I went and said some crazy stuff.
I know that you've lost your memories.
I can fight too.
I can help you!
Oh, hey, Sparky.
What are you doing here?
N-Nothing. What do you care?
Just my usual thing, you know.
No, I mean...
What about you? Are you doing better now?
I guess.
So you really found out.
I'd love it if you wouldn't tell others about it.
O-Okay.
And look, I know you have a thing
with the vending machines,
but try to avoid doing high kicks
in front of people while wearing a skirt.
Okay.
You're awfully meek today.
What am I doing?
Why am I feeling all warm and fuzzy inside?
H-Hey...
Fuzzy!
Nothing fuzzy about it!
What was up with Misaka?
Wait, could there be any chance
that Index has also gone haywire?
The aftermath of the explosion in
the Eurotunnel connecting Britain and France
Index is her usual self.
is now also affecting air traffic.
Furthermore—
Touma, what's for dinner?
I ran into some trouble,
so it's instant noodles.
What trouble?
Wait a moment, it's almost ready.
Wh-What was that sound?!
Oh, that was just—
Touma!
You're such a klutz.
Here! I saved one for you.
Wh-What's up, Tsuchimikado?
Hey there, Kamiyan!
Do you have some time? I have a long story for you.
A miracle is happening before my eyes.
So please keep it short.
Huh? All right then, I will.
Get to Britain now.
What?
A sleeping gas grenade?
Beef or fish? Beef or fish?
All right, I get it, you're looking forward
to the meal! Keep quiet already!
Beef or—
So why do I have to go to Britain, anyway?
Um, it says that there was some huge
magic-related trouble in Britain,
so the government has officially summoned you.
And I have to go with you, or something.
By the way, Touma,
when does the plane food arrive?
I guess in about nine hours.
The tickets were cheaper
because there's only one meal.
What?!
Remember that it's still better than
what Tsuchimikado had prepared!
To assist in alleviating the crisis caused by
the explosion in the Eurotunnel,
Isn't this Britain?
this flight will be taking on goods
that need to be transported to Britain.
They said it's France. Now that I think about it,
they mentioned this on the news.
That man in work clothes
over there is eating a sandwich!
Not fair! I want to have one too!
C-Cut it out.
Mister?
Yes?
Is something the matter?
I-I'm fine.
By the way, is an airplane really
the best way to ship daily necessities?
They're mostly importing things
that cannot be procured domestically.
I think the containers for this flight
included some liquid food.
Liquid food?
I don't know what the sickness is called,
but I was told that they're special foodstuffs
for people who cannot eat regular food.
Foodstuffs... Food... Airplane food... Plane meal...
Beef or fish!
Beef or fish! Beef or fish!
You have to pick one or the other!
Beef or fish! Beef or fish! Beef or fish!
I-I'll bring your meal right away!
Damn! The free seats got taken up
by people waiting on cancellations.
Beef or fish! Beef or fish!
What do I do?
Are we there yet?
Sure is taking a while.
Huh?
Maybe I should close it.
You saw it, didn't you?
Captain, we have an emergency.
A terrorist?!
Air traffic control informed us that a member
of a French anti-Britain organization
is aboard this plane.
He said that unless we accept his demands, he'll bring down the plane in a fireball.
Seriously?
The terrorist's demand is
the destruction of the customer management
system maintained by the major airlines.
They want to bring down all British air traffic.
The blood you saw was that of my colleague.
We think that the terrorist did it.
Don't tell me you think I'm the terrorist.
I hadn't thought things out that far.
Can you find the terrorist by yourselves?
Wouldn't you like all the help you can get?
I can help.
We don't want people to start panicking.
We can't have an amateur messing things up.
Are you prepared to take the lives
of 500 passengers in your hands?
Throw him in there.
Damn it!
Where did Touma go?
Shit! Why is the connector broken?!
Now I can't inject the program to disrupt
the emergency landing stabilizer.
Emergency landing?
What are you doing?
It's a knife made of animal bone.
The airport's metal detectors can't catch it.
Stand up. I'll stab you if you don't do what I say.
A Certain Magical Index
Get in, if you don't want to get stabbed.
Index?!
Damn it!
Stop!
Index!
You again!
What in the world happened here?!
He even attacked a passenger.
Damn! What's he trying to achieve here?!
The emergency landing stabilizer.
What?
That's what Index thinks she heard the man say.
This plane has a system that uses sensors
to detect the impact of a belly landing
and automatically shuts down all engines.
And what if that triggered at the wrong time?
The plane would crash.
I understand what happened.
It's unfortunate that we could not prevent it,
but the important thing is that
you weren't seriously injured.
It pains me to say it, but I'll have to have
you stay away from the rest of the passengers.
I have a duty to preserve the lives of all passengers.
To hell with that!
Preserve the lives of all passengers?
Look what happened when
I listened to you and did nothing!
My friend got attacked!
Are you telling us to just sit
and wait for him to come back?!
The witnesses are the ones in most danger!
Where?
Where is he?
Damn it!
If only he was doing something obviously suspicious!
Okay.
What? What happened?
What's going on?
Did we lose altitude?
N-No, the alarm was triggered
by the manual switch in the back.
C-Captain! We have an emergency!
What is it this time?!
I don't know!
Damn it! What's happening?!
What in the world is going on here?!
The fuel supply meter shouldn't
be going down this quick!
There must be a hole in the tank!
We won't make it to the airport like this.
We need to be prepared to land on a highway.
Captain! What are your orders?
Damn it! I'm coming.
Seems like the illusion you people
cast is starting to take effect.
Making a gauge look wrong is a trivial matter.
So instead of the airport,
you're going to make them land on a highway
in a rural area with few buildings around?
Oh, my, would you prefer it exploded
over a city or a residential area?
Do we know which roads they could use?
Of the highways located
between London and Scotland,
the sections around Kendal
and Carlisle seem most likely.
Close all highways in that area.
Block all roads with entrance ramps.
I don't mind speeding things up,
but what if the plane breaks up while still in the air?
If that happens, we need to at least retrieve
our young Index Librorum Prohibitorum.
We can find a way to get
one person safely to the ground.
I mean this from the bottom of my heart:
you should die young.
What's going on?
We're losing altitude?
Oh, shit!
Gain altitude!
If you don't want me to start killing passengers,
take the plane back up!
I can't!
We won't make it to Edinburgh airport.
Not only that,
the engines are in danger of exploding!
You shithead! I'll kill you!
Listen! You have three minutes.
If you don't restore our altitude by then,
I'm going to start killing passengers!
That's odd.
What is?
The plane raised its altitude.
It looks like they decided
against the emergency landing.
Archbishop, we have an emergency.
We've detected large-scale jamming
from the direction of Scotland.
Jamming?
A third party is interfering with our illusion spell.
Interference from within Britain?
This failure is on you, Archbishop.
I know that.
I want you to make sure we've
covered our bases with Sky Bus 365.
What do you need?
I'll need a transport plane.
We're back to cruising altitude?
There you are!
You knew you had that coming.
We're safely back on course
to land at Edinburgh airport.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
What's wrong, Touma?
Why did he wait so long to act?
He likely wanted to cause problems
in the airspace above Britain.
If he'd done it earlier,
he'd have had much more time to negotiate,
and maybe Britain would have given in.
Anyway, it's all over now.
Why worry about it?
Why did he wait until the final hour of the flight?
There's more of them!
In the hold!
He was waiting for the cargo to be loaded in Paris.
He was waiting for his backup who
got on board with the cargo in Paris!
He was trying to play it safe.
Is there only one entrance?
Y-Yes.
Whoever's helping the terrorist
probably has a weapon.
If we're going in, the most dangerous
moment is when we open the door.
But there's no other way in.
Can't I go through that duct?
What? This isn't a movie!
It's not wide enough!
No, it's fine.
What do you mean, Touma?
The free drinks included
bottles of coffee and tea, right?
Can you bring me some?
And make sure to heat them up as much as you can.
The negotiations must have failed.
Worst comes to worst,
I'll at least take this plane down!
Tea?
Hi there, terrorist!
You know about thermal expansion, right?
I'll take this plane down!
My homeland of France suffered enormous
damage from the Eurotunnel explosion.
So we have to make them suffer just as much!
We'll seal off their air routes
in addition to their land routes!
Is there really a reason to quarrel over
whether Britain or France is to blame?!
There's liquid food in these containers!
It's cargo that France is sending as help to Britain!
Isn't that the relationship
between France and Britain?!
Every country has its fools!
Even if they're spread out
among the virtuous population,
we can't allow them to have their way!
Stop!
Geez, you're still such an amateur.
It's another ten minutes to Edinburgh airport.
He'll probably survive.
Geez. You are the one in charge
of managing that girl.
You should be prepared to make such tough calls.
Hang in there.
Breaking news.
Passenger flight Sky Bus 365
has landed safely at Edinburgh airport.
So that plane managed to land safely.
But that's all because they brought out a stealth
transport plane that uses Academy City tech.
I guess Britain is done for.
M-My body is all ticklish
after absorbing so much magic.
It's time to stay sharp.
We're about to destroy the entire
framework that Britain is built on.
When I least expect it, you're gone
And loneliness hits me hard in the chest
In the night filled with signs I look up at the stars
I bite my lip and pray
Every time the dawn comes I run to you
You try to hide behind a smile that you're covered in wounds
But I notice, because I'm not a child
I'll protect you even if I have to make an enemy of the entire world
This strength comes from the light you've given me
I don't want to just wait for a miracle
I want to start a revolution that changes who the two of us are
And this is the night before it starts
Next Time
Numerous threads intertwine
around a special mystic artifact.
The true goal of the sorcerers,
what they call New Light, is revealed.
Next time: "The Maze of Great Britain".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.