Awful news! The bread place
out front is completely sold out!
And the cafeteria's packed!
They beat us to everything.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault for asking
the teacher a stupid question.
At this rate, we'll have to go into afternoon
classes before we can sate our hunger.
We can't do it!
We're still growing, so we need our calories!
We can't last until after school!
What do we do?
Sounds like we'll have to leave campus.
But...
Shall we?
We have no choice.
All right, we're breaking out!
Let's make a run to the convenience store!
Yeah!
We need to send out a small group.
If we all try to get out at once,
there's no way the teachers won't notice.
Speed is of utmost importance here.
Yeah,
if we get there and all the boxed lunches
are sold out, it'll all have been for nothing.
Team A, escape failed.
Team B, all caught!
You're our last hope.
Damn it! We're the only ones left!
Shit! It's Saigo!
So he gets to be fancy and eat out?
Don't get distracted, Kamiyan!
If we get caught here, the entire class goes hungry!
Shit!
Sorry, we won't forget you.
Huh?
Hey!
What was that for, Tsuchimikado?!
No!
Kamiyan, let's split up!
O-Okay!
And of course he comes after me!
Huh?!
I won't allow it!
Wha— Wait, Itsuwa!
Huh?
A Certain Magical Index
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
Carrying a ticking time bomb
The Earth keeps on turning, so hurry up!
No one can pretend it's not their business anymore
Suddenly common sense is out the door
Opposing fates fail to reach each other
Drenched in the rain of resentment
But why? Fear and doubt keep building up heavy in my heart
My racing heart is flooded with ambition
Ready!
Everyone that's drawn to this place
Has gone beyond the meaning and color of desire
My heart wants to stay strong
I feel it deep inside me
With all my soul, this one thing
Dive into a heart
The Third Layer
I'm really sorry!
I thought he was an assassin
from the Catholic Church.
I-It's fine.
Saigo is a strongman of a teacher, famous for
catching a giant boulder with his bare hands.
He'll be back on his feet in no time.
I'm really sorry for how useless I am.
Actually, you were very helpful.
Huh?
So why are you here, anyway?
Oh, uh...
What are you doing?
Do you remember the name Acqua of the Rear?
Yeah, that's one of the
God's Right Seat people, right?
He showed up after I fought that other one, Vento.
So, Acqua sent letters of challenge to both
the Church of England and Academy City.
Letters of challenge?
It said he'd be tracking you down within
a few days and pulveriz— I mean, attacking you.
Wait, why me?
What do you mean "why"?!
It's because you foiled far too many of the
Roman Catholic Church's darkest secret plans!
You're giving me too much credit.
I'm just a high-school student.
The Front, the Left, and now the Rear?
Why is everyone going after me?
Don't they have anything
better to do with their time?
I have information that Acqua of the Rear
also possesses the powers of a saint.
A saint?
But no need to worry!
If Acqua comes after you, we'll protect you!
So what did you come here for?
I came to be your personal bodyguard, of course!
24/7 protection!
I wish Itsuwa would stop being
all business and go on the offense.
I know, right?
I think she's unaware of her own weapons.
What weapons are you talking about?
I'm talking about...
the Itsuwa Hidden Huge Boobs Theory!
Do you have any evidence
for that hypothesis, acting Pope?
It's really irresponsible to just say random stuff.
Remember those horse race predictions you made?
According to the analysis of the data from the
Grand Itsuwa Massage Operation I once conducted,
her shoulders contained no less than 40 knots.
However, if you calculate the strain on her
shoulders due to clothing and equipment,
it's not possible to account for more than 37!
S-So, you mean...
Exactly.
That difference is the proof for the
Itsuwa Hidden Huge Boobs Theory.
Really?!
And to demonstrate that theory in its fullest,
we need a new stratagem.
But Itsuwa is a notorious late bloomer, you know.
And that's why I prepared this plan.
I call it the Grand Field Sniper's Free Kick Operation!
I can't believe he's lost his memory.
And when did that happen?
What the hell?
Right on!
Nice timing!
You people...
I already have enough issues on my mind!
I don't need you to add this weird stuff on top!
They're gone?
A-Are you all right?
Yeah, more or less.
Why you...
Oh, it's Misaka.
How long are you going to take
advantage of those maternal lumps?
An enemy!
Don't! In fact, let's split!
Hey!
Hold on right there!
Touma!
Why is Itsuwa from the Amakusa
Church standing beside you?
Well, um, you see, how should I put it?
Basically, God's Right—
Look, I'm Acqua's target,
so can you please not tell Index?
Itsuwa?
Yes! I-I understand!
Oh, sorry! Did I squeeze your neck?
N-No.
Fine.
Jerk.
What in the world is going on here?
Is some unbelievable power trying
to raise Index's rage to its critical point?!
U-Um, Index?
I'm not quite sure what's going on,
but please come and bite
my head before you explode!
If you can dish it out in smaller portions,
I think my skull might not crack.
Oh, yeah! I have a present for the kitty!
Top grade bonito!
Did you buy groceries? When did you manage to?
Even if I'm your bodyguard,
I'd still feel awkward freeloading off you.
I'll help out around the house.
Wh-What happened, Touma?
Why did the whole feel of the
situation suddenly change?
Try to find the reasons within you.
Who has been leaving all the work to poor Kamijou
and has never even thought of offering to help?
Well, I'm sorry about that...
Wait! That still doesn't change the situation!
The pots and pans are in here.
The spices are in there.
Okay!
I have no idea why she's so eager,
but I'm just grateful she's here!
And to think that I got away from Index's
interrogation without head damage, that's so—
The sight of a girl cooking...
Why does your face look like that
of a lamb who's just witnessed a miracle?!
Wait! Those fish cakes still aren't ready!
Hearing that isn't enough to stop my mouth!
Don't disrupt
a man's dream!
Behold!
That is the correct way
to stay at someone else's place!
Index, why are you always doing nothing
but eating, sleeping, and watching TV?
Oh, wait!
The rerun of Magical Powered
Kanamin Integral is about to start!
Go and clean the bathtub, right now!
Yes, sir.
The smell.
I can smell it!
Come on! Not another weirdo!
That miso soup you're making!
You're using dried scallop powder
as your secret ingredient, aren't you?!
H-How did you know?!
It's a secret not even my mother knows!
Thank you.
This taste!
I have to go!
Wait, why are you taking away the white stew?
I'm going to make a true
miso soup right now, damn it!
What?
I was fine with the stew you already made.
Hm, I feel like I've heard that voice before.
Well, um...
You shouldn't worry about such weirdos.
Please explain to me how you broke
the tub using a sponge and detergent.
I was just scrubbing it like you told me to!
No, you didn't!
You just poured loads of undiluted detergent
into the heater's inlet, didn't you?!
Huh? Don't you put detergent in to clean it?
Now the water heater's burned out
and you almost caused a fire!
U-Uh...
May I suggest using a public
bathhouse as a change of mood?
A Certain Magical Index
Bathhouse?
Thanks for even renting a bike for us.
Don't worry about it.
I received abundant funds for this mission.
Touma!
I feel like there is some ulterior motive
to this seat distribution.
What? It's not like that at all!
I was just being chivalrous
and let you have the good seat.
Academy City is pretty empty at night.
And on such a well-maintained road,
you've just gotta cut loose!
Stupid Itsuwa! Don't cut loose with us riding!
Touma, look!
An enormous jungle gym!
District 22 is mostly underground,
so they can use the surface for power generation.
The underground town uses a lot of electricity,
which is why the entire district
is covered with lots of generators.
So which layer is that spa resort on?
Um,
I was told it's on the third one.
Touma, what are these layers? Is it a cake?
It's not about food.
It's like floors.
District 22 is split into ten underground layers.
This is the exit for the third layer.
The ceiling of the third layer is all one big screen.
It shows the night sky in real time.
Are we really underground?
There's a river, and forests too!
Academy City never ceases to amaze me.
There it is!
Over there!
Oh, man, it's so annoying!
How can that idiot do such things
while I worry about him?
One adult.
Collect all the stamps to
Collect all the stamps to get
a Gekota strap after your bath!
But really, how many times are
you going to make me come here?
Collect all the stamps to get
a Gekota strap after your bath!
I'm not making much progress with those stamps.
Maybe I should take Kuroko
with me and get twice as many.
Milady!
No! No! No! No!
I'd better collect them on my own.
What?
What are you doing here?!
Hush!
Be quiet at the bath.
Don't bring the towel in!
Okay.
You!
You're the girl that idiot clung to
when he got hit by the soccer ball!
No!
I... Um... No...
Th-That was an accident.
It's just that my chest happened
to be in the right place.
What do you mean an accident where
your chest happened to be in the right place?
I wonder if those girls know
about that idiot's amnesia.
Did Touma do something to you?!
Now that I think of it,
it's not like I'm his... anything...
N-N-No, he...
Touma did do something, huh?!
Were you scared? Are you all right?
And why do I have to be so bothered
by that idiot in the first place?!
N-No, it was just a matter of bad timing...
He's always going around grabbing onto girls!
N-No, we actually get along quite well!
Man, how could this be any more of a pain?
Hey, the short-haired girl is sinking!
We have to help her!
Hold up your guest key here
Cold
Hot
That's hot.
Maybe I should've gotten a cold one.
Did you come out to enjoy the night wind?
I totally forgot that we're underground.
Would you like to walk around for a bit?
Sure.
Wait, where's Index?
She was running around
the all-you-can-eat food stalls.
I see.
I guess she won't get lost then.
This is a good opportunity.
The mood seems to be set.
What do you think, acting Pope?
You mean about the
Grand Evening Date Operation?
About Acqua of the Rear.
We received the report about
him from Academy City, but...
It's a bit hard to believe, isn't it?
It's weird that three of the four
top God's Right Seat members
would put schemes in motion
just for Kamijou Touma.
I have the feeling he's hiding something from us.
In other words, if we're serious
about guarding Kamijou Touma...
Yes, it might be necessary to dig that out too.
All the people are gone!
They sure got us.
By the way, where are the others
from the Amakusa Church?
Well, I think they're nearby,
on the lookout for trouble.
It would've been a lot more reassuring
if the Priestess was with us.
Is Kanzaki really that powerful?
O-Of course she is!
She's a Saint! There's fewer than
twenty of them in the whole world!
When the Priestess is with us,
any trouble gets resolved in a flash.
Oh, really?
Well, she was powerful enough
to fight that "Power of God" Archangel.
Sh-She fought an Archangel?!
I know I shouldn't let my guard down, but...
Itsuwa, is something wrong?
N-No! It's nothing. All good.
I was just wondering why
there aren't any people around.
Even though the night view is so pretty.
Yeah, you're right,
but Academy City's like this at night.
But wait, there's really absolutely
no people or cars at all.
Itsuwa!
I sent my proclamation.
Surely you could have chosen
a different course of action.
Is this the choice you decided to bet
your lives on after careful consideration?
That's...
Tatemiya's amulet.
Tell me honestly,
was there really no better option?
Acqua!
Itsuwa!
I came to remove the root cause of
the mayhem spreading throughout this world.
Are you sure you have the time
to worry about others?
Your entire organization stood
together against me and lost.
Do you think you alone stand
a chance of defeating me?
I have my pride!
Itsuwa!
Your right arm.
Give it to me, and I'll allow you to live.
Shove off!
I see. In that case,
I'll have you learn a bit more about reality.
Kamijou!
Keep it together!
I'll use my healing magic on you!
It's not working.
Are you done?
In that case, I'll just pulverize you with him.
Thank you, Itsuwa.
Your healing magic
brought me back some energy.
Wait!
I admire your courage.
You have one day.
If within that time you cut off
your arm and present it to me,
I'll let you live.
You have one day.
When I least expect it, you're gone
And loneliness hits me hard in the chest
In the night filled with signs I look up at the stars
I bite my lip and pray
Every time the dawn comes I run to you
You try to hide behind a smile that you're covered in wounds
But I notice, because I'm not a child
I'll protect you even if I have to make an enemy of the entire world
This strength comes from the light you've given me
I don't want to just wait for a miracle
I want to start a revolution that changes who the two of us are
And this is the night before it starts
Next Time
The power of the Saint shook the ground
and reverberated throughout the layer.
With everything taken from her, and at the end
of her strength, Itsuwa makes one final attack.
Next time: "Saint Destroyer".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.