"Are you okay?"
asks Misaka as Misaka tries
to understand the situation.
Thank goodness.
The damned thing worked.
It really worked.
This world is cold, ruthless,
and filled to the brink with malice.
But if you take the initiative,
after many, many, many struggles,
you will see the light.
And it looks like this world isn't so cruel
as to take away that one ray of light.
I hate to rain on your touching reunion,
but I don't think we're quite
on track for a happily ever after.
The light is converging on that lump in the sky.
It won't be pretty if that
gets unleashed on the Earth.
Fucking assholes!
Wha—?!
Misaka Worst,
I'm going to stop that thing.
Can you protect this kid?
Well, it's all the same job.
"Where are you going?"
asks Misaka as Misaka tries to pose a question.
"You're not going to leave, right?"
says Misaka as Misaka tries to get a confirmation.
Don't worry.
I'll finish this up quickly.
"No! I don't want us to be apart!"
says Misaka as Misaka tries to plea.
Yeah.
I've always wanted us to be together.
I see now.
This is what it feels like when
you're fighting to protect something.
A Certain Magical Index
The Son of God
Another light appeared!
What in the world is happening?!
Are you really up there, Kamijou Touma?
What's going on?
I should have gained more than enough power.
At least enough destructive power to disrupt
the strategic situation down on the surface,
and give the last push I need to reach victory.
Are you done?
This is where
your illusion dies!
What?!
The malice that was enveloping
the Earth is declining!
Why?!
Warning. Chapter 88, verse 1.
Irregularities in main unit
encountered during search operation.
The effects of strong external stimuli have
led to serious deterioration of search efficiency.
What have the Anglicans done?
Misfortune!
I just need to buy five, maybe ten seconds.
In that time, I can forcefully override
the settings of the Index Librorum Prohibitorum.
I don't care if the high load ends up
burning away the 103,000 books.
I'm going to defeat the enemy I'm facing!
I'm using the full extent of the miracle and blessing
of the son of God to bring this phenomenon about,
but this fool isn't even fazed.
Fortune and misfortune mean nothing to him!
He has the power to overcome such vague concepts!
If you think what you're doing
is the only way to save anyone,
I'll destroy that illusion first!
Sorry, Sasha and I have already
used an escape pod to evacuate.
You should hurry up and get one too.
The Star of Bethlehem has already began to fall.
So this is the end of the line.
Get up, we're leaving.
The escape pods are probably useless at this point.
At most we'd be able to activate
one of the single-person ones.
There's no chance to save more than one of us.
Seems that way.
Are you sure?
I'm a pathetic man who doesn't
even know how big this world is.
Oh yeah?
Go and find out, then.
Misaka!
Hey, could we land somewhere?
"The intense vibration occurring inside the fortress
makes it impossible to approach it any closer"
explains Misaka.
"Even if it were possible to land,
the likelihood of then being able to take off—"
All right.
Try to keep it as steady as possible.
I'm going to pull that dork out directly.
No! Stay away, Misaka!
Shut up already!
You have no other way to get out, do you?!
Not yet.
"The vibrations of the fortress have
reached a critical level," reports Misaka.
"Getting any closer is likely to result in a crash."
I'll use his buttons, his belt buckle,
and whatever else is there
to pull him up with magnetism!
Touma.
Index?
Why didn't you get out?
Well, there's your mystic artifact,
and I also need to take care of the fortress itself.
Sorry.
I've been hiding something
from you this whole time.
But I didn't know if it was
really the right thing to do.
I did something horrible to you.
I've been deceiving you all this time.
There's no guarantee that I'll be able
to make it out of the Star of Bethlehem.
So I'm going to tell you while I still have the chance.
My...
My memories—
That's okay.
That doesn't matter any more.
I don't care as long as the Touma
I know comes back to me.
I'll come back no matter what.
I'll come back to apologize to you directly,
rather than through an artifact.
50.9 MHz.
That's the frequency that this speaker receives.
Tell that to the people of the Church of England.
I need help.
Can they tell me how to minimize the damage
from the fall of the Star of Bethlehem?
I can't do that.
I can't go back through my own will.
Yeah, I thought so.
Head on back, I'll be there soon.
Okay.
A Certain Magical Index
Touma...
So I can change where this thing falls by destroying
some of the mystic artifacts that make it float?
There are twenty of them in different places.
If you destroy numbers 3, 9, and 13,
it should fall at the edge of the Arctic Ocean.
Got it!
Tell me something. Index's consciousness
was with you on the Star of Bethlehem.
Couldn't have you resolved this problem
by relying on her knowledge?
I couldn't stand to let Index
suffer in that state any longer.
We've confirmed the destruction of artifact 3.
That's weird. What's that huge thing?
Telesma?!
What's that doing there?!
Misha Kreutzev is advancing
towards the Arctic Ocean!
We've detected a telesma line connecting them.
They're obviously inducing
interference in each other.
What?!
Is this some new ability?
No, Misha is likely trying to replenish its body.
What do you mean?
Misha Kreutzev's element is water.
If it makes use of the special symbolism
of the ice of the polar cap,
its power will grow even more immense.
But if it tries to output power too forcefully,
there's a possibility that the body
that Misha is composed of
would explode,
releasing a massive amount of telesma.
How do we stop it?!
Our entire organization might not
be enough to stop even the former Misha.
The Star of Bethlehem is deviating
from its projected trajectory!
What?!
Is that Touma's doing?!
Yeah, this world might fall to ruin one day.
But that end doesn't need to be this tragic.
Fighting to prevent that is right!
Damn it! I can't find anything.
We need to find something to use as
a bargaining chip with Academy City.
Hamazura, we need to get out of here.
They'll be coming after us.
I know, just give me a little more time.
We can use my blood as insurance.
It contains the DNA map of the Rank 4 esper.
If each of us has it, we can deter them.
You'd do that?
Dear me,
you sure caused us a lot of problems.
Who are you?
A colleague.
Perhaps even our chains
of command overlap somewhere.
What would they like to say?
"It’s always like this with you."
I'm relieved I was able to secure our
top-priority objective, Takitsubo Rikou.
Takitsubo is your top priority?!
Didn't you notice what she did?
When you were fighting the masked squad,
Takitsubo Rikou exerted influence on
the personal reality of Mugino Shizuri.
What?!
It was already recorded in the Parameter List.
She's only the eighth known case of this rare ability.
If it continues developing,
she may become able to provide all
the functions of Academy City by herself,
becoming an Academy Entity of sorts.
Wait a minute!
You're telling me you knew that from the start?
Are you saying that no matter
how much effort we put in,
we were always doomed to fail?!
Takitsubo and I chose this path on our own.
But you, Hamazura,
perhaps you just needed to be
given an equal opportunity.
Mugino?
I didn't expect to hear that from you.
Did you gain the ability to empathize
with the weak or something?
Shut up!
It's fine.
We're ITEM.
And we don't regret that.
So it's all good.
You still kicking, Hamazura?
Thanks, Digurv!
You saved my life.
How?!
We aren't in Academy City.
Even a Level 0 like me managed to survive
by relying on the help of others.
Reinforcements will arrive soon.
The battle's outlook hasn't changed!
I know that.
You mentioned something interesting just now.
The Parameter List, was it?
Tell me everything you know.
I'll show you how cruel a human can be,
armed with the excuse
of defending someone they love.
This is the retrieval team.
We've secured the target.
We're heading for the rendezvous point.
What happened to the kids?
Another squad has them.
Then pledge this to me.
Never again use the kid or the Sisters
as a shield, or give them orders.
Never again play with any of their lives.
And don't hand off your
dirty work to people like me.
It seems you don't understand your position.
What? I think you're the ones
who don't understand the situation.
W-We turned the switch off, right?
Yes, it should be off.
Let's check just in case.
This isn't a negotiation, a suggestion, or a deal.
It's a triumphant return, you shithead.
Wh-What?! You?!
Aleister Crowley?!
It appears people do
recognize me once I leave my tube.
Why?!
Even if you can't tell how valuable it is,
you were too obsessed with that right hand.
You were supposed to see it merely as a hand
that destroys supernatural abilities.
But you caught a glimpse of what's beyond that.
I can't allow that.
What's beyond that?
I'm sure you understand.
Your plan was outdated and badly constructed,
but how is its goal different than a world enveloped
by a single type of power, that of Academy City?
I see now.
Apparently I was getting close to
the truth of this world in my own way.
Looking at your face,
I can feel how pointless my actions were.
That's not the face of a person
who would really save the world.
Back then, in that place,
that man was standing where nobody could reach.
A futile effort.
He wasn't concerned with
whether it was futile or not!
He just couldn't let the world be trampled over!
Thinking you could explain that right hand
and Kamijou using mere Christianity,
that in itself was your downfall.
We've detected something!
This wavelength is that of
the golden sorcerer, Aleister Crowley!
It looks like he did show up there.
This is where things start,
Board Chairman Aleister.
You look like you're enjoying yourself.
Yes, I find it amusing.
More precisely, I'm joyous that the
amusing times are going to last longer.
He did a good job.
Rather than eliminating me, he did something
more like transferring me to a different domain.
I think it would be good if you
learned more about humans.
If you underestimate them, they'll stab you
in the heart when you least expect it.
What are you saying?
If weak humans are really capable
of accomplishing such a feat,
don't you think that would itself be
an extremely interesting precedent?
Well, it looks like he's not dead.
I'm sure you don't want it all to end
with one defeat after another.
Tell us what you saw and heard.
Who are you?
I'm Ollerus.
A long time ago, I was supposed
to become a God of Magic.
But Othinus the One-Eyed
took that position from me.
Now I'm just a pitiful sorcerer.
After careful examination of the
conditions suggested by Academy City,
we have agreed to participate in talks.
As of this moment,
we declare all military action suspended.
I sincerely hope that this decision we all arrived at,
will be recorded as correct in the history
books of the peaceful world of the future.
You may think of yourself as a rather misfortunate fellow,
but it seems the devil's luck is with you,
Kamijou Touma.