Chapter 8, verse 25.
Commencing elimination of persons
who may hinder remote access operations.
Innocentius!
Chapter 10, verse 3.
Detected effects of a spell.
Determined that halting all
life activity of enemy elements
is the most effective resolution to the situation.
Chapter 11, verse 2.
Effective destructive force confirmed.
Determined that pressing
with a sequence of attacks
and not allowing for time to recover
is the optimal course of action.
A Certain Magical Index
If it gets so hard that your head feels like it's going to burst
Then admit you've had enough and let go of the steering wheel
But then you'll just be waiting for salvation among the doubts and strife
Heaven's Killer
The sound of imminent destruction
Surely one day we'll look back on this with a smile
I'm understanding more and more
I can hear it!
Now listen to me roar!
Wake up and believe in me, in you, and in the end of the world
My fingertips point towards the future
So break out and believe in me, in you, and in the Hand's true power
I'll hold it tight in my palm
And embrace the wind of loneliness
But my belief is that one day
We can bring about a pure and innocent world
Fuze Kazakiri
Shit!
Th-Third question:
What in the world just happened?
Kazakiri Hyouka?!
What's she doing here?
F-Fourth question:
What in the world is that?
Oh, that's Kazakiri Hyouka.
She's a friend.
A friend?
Well, I have no idea why she's here,
but it's clear what I have to do.
hboreturnfbyuo
ReturnvnfrLocation.Correctcoord.ujHeaven.
Originalproper.qNaEPlace.
Powers of different formats
are being forcefully mixed together.
Return.rbjyNecessary.
jwnPerform...hlvfkadoperation.
afhjdFiamma.ghkjUtilize.nbmerInterests.
Contact.beqPlan.bfmfghCollaboration.
If you would dare to hurt my dear friends for that,
I'll do everything in my power to stop you!
alnsDamage.ngbksngDisregard.rngoPriority.
ngslgnReturn.ehjgadfCorrect.anfaLocation.nagfajll
Obstacle.tndEvil.hnkSynonymous.ghoaJudgment.gnalagtAll.
angflaCapture.
GHOdfgaNecessary.GognHfInformation.
HfongGParchment.AngotAhgObtain.
It must be able to sense the parchment.
What're we gonna do now?
This seems like more trouble than a hurricane.
There's only one difference between
a natural disaster and a man-made one.
If it's man-made, you have an enemy you can kill.
It's nice to have a clear target.
Otherwise you just pile up a lot of
annoying anger with nobody to direct it at.
I'm leaving you to watch the kid in the back.
Make sure she's safe.
That's a bit of a tall order.
Misaka is really bad at that sort of thing.
Lucky for you, I still have some use for you.
You have leeway to make dumbass jokes
like that without being killed on the spot.
Yes, that's how Misaka likes it.
The Russian military is going
to use a biological weapon?
Are you sure, Hamazura?
Yeah.
They want to prevent Academy City
from seizing their nuclear silos.
It's not safe to stay here.
What do we do?
Do we call the Academy City troops stationed nearby?
No, if there's any significant movement,
the military might decide to release it sooner.
We'll go deal with it.
Then I'll come with you.
And who's going to protect the people
of the village if something happens to me?
Let's go, Hamazura.
Yeah.
Hamazura!
Don't get yourself killed.
I won't.
See you.
Good luck.
Thanks!
Oh, so it works on these ones.
You manipulated my wings made up
of AIM diffusion field aggregates.
Who are you?
I'm surprised a monster like you
is capable of normal conversation.
Did you get lured here by this thing too?
Crude bastard.
Is it trying to introduce itself, or something?
Uhm—
I'll deal with you later.
I feel like that other monster is more likely
to hold the key to saving that kid.
You two may be monsters,
but you're nowhere near as bad as Aiwass.
anGHahConfiguration.AnghoOePreparation.
FhtSDComplete.AZxJHSe
AFGoFaghfoaCommand.ZNmmGh"Sweep."
ghHotuDrop.
That shithead!
What the hell was that?!
And it looks ready to do that attack again, damn it.
I can't afford to die here.
Not until I tear apart every single one
of the absurdities binding that kid!
I don't care if you can be beaten or not!
As long as I have a reason to, I'll crush you!
Secondwaveattack.nahgfReady.
Thirtyseconds.YonghSweep.WnHtRedrop.
Secondwave.HOgnphAttack.PlhkHyNkg
Is that all you've got?
If nobody stops me,
my purge is going to envelop the world.
Long time no see, Acqua.
Do you still want to call yourself
part of God's Right Seat?
Or are you back to being a mere mercenary?
I would accept either one,
as long as it's a position from
which I can stop your tyranny.
How would you do that?
I'm sure you're aware of the reason this war started.
I pulled the trigger,
but no bullet would fire if there were no gunpowder.
Still, is that any reason to unleash
the power of an archangel on the people?
Are you going to stop me?
In the end, you have to rely
on violence to solve problems.
However, you're not powerful
enough to stop an archangel.
I'll grant you the right to resist,
but the smart thing to do
would be to stand back and watch.
Is it now?
Then let me present a way to deal
with this that doesn't use violence.
What did you do?
No, it can't be...
Have you forgotten?
I'm Acqua of the Rear.
A member of God's Right Seat,
the darkest side of the Roman Catholic Church.
And I'm the one in control of Archangel Gabriel.
You'd do such a thing?!
You'd absorb its telesma into your body?!
It's clear as day what will happen to Gabriel
if I absorb a massive amount
of its water-elemental telesma.
You're insane.
But it's not impossible.
The nun from the Russian Church,
who you're trying to make use of, has managed it.
Nonsense!
You don't have her extensive
training and innate tolerance.
That's not what I'm talking about.
If someone else can do it, then I can too.
That's all.
All right.
Do it then.
But are you aware that what
you're doing is basically suicide?
About half of its telesma has been drained,
but the remainder is still more than enough.
You're sacrificing your life in vain.
Kill him, Misha Kreutzev.
A Certain Magical Index
That bastard!
Misha Kreutzev only appeared after
the Star of Bethlehem was in place.
If Fiamma could control an archangel,
he wouldn't need to start World War III to achieve his goals.
But he didn't start using it until this thing appeared.
He must need the Star of Bethlehem in order
to summon and maintain the archangel.
That makes things easy.
There's probably something in here
that's keeping Misha around.
I just need to break whatever
that is with my right hand!
I still have things I need to do!
It's building up energy!
Oh no, it's going to explode!
I don't care if I don't belong here!
What do you really want to do?
It doesn't matter if it's hubris,
choose whatever makes you stand proud!
He's right!
I want to protect her!
I don't want to lose her!
I don't even want to entertain the thought!
To protect this one illusion of mine,
I'm going to fight any reality that stands in my way!
Hold me up!
I'm satisfied with my choice.
Removing archangel Gabriel from the picture
will have a huge effect on the war.
You were relying too much on that power, Fiamma.
You forgot that the people can join forces
to stand against a powerful foe.
You've lost sight of the option to entrust
the battle to someone who shares your goals.
And so had I.
I'll die, taking the archangel with me.
And I'm satisfied with that.
Because I know it ensures that people
in the distant future will be able to smile.
Shit!
Hang in there!
What the hell happened here?!
Takitsubo! Can you treat his wounds?
Don't bother.
I'm beyond help now.
Keep quiet!
Leave me and go.
I've fulfilled my goal.
Bringing me along would only slow you down.
And what about the people
who are waiting for you?!
I'm sure this isn't the first time
you've played the hero!
And people like you always
have others relying on them!
Do you really fight so that you can laugh
at the tearful faces of the people waiting for you?
Stand up, hero!
Stand up!
I see how it is now.
That damned shithead!
I've obtained the information from
the parchment via Gabriel's perception abilities.
All that's left is...
Sasha!
You've been causing trouble.
You made me move up the schedule for the ritual.
And you think I'll just let you do what you want?
A human has defeated an archangel!
The scales have clearly tipped in our favor!
Don't you worry about it.
The archangel had done its job the moment
it made the night sky into what I wanted.
Raising the lone Star of Bethlehem
in an imperfect sky filled with telesma
is part of the ritual to reset the four elements.
What do you mean? What are you trying to do?
This is a mere means to an end.
The important thing is this Right Arm.
Everything revolves around it.
By controlling all four elements—
fire, water, wind, earth—I'll gain vast power.
If only there were no warping in the
alignment of the elements in the world,
the proper power could have perfect
control over the proper world.
Now, let me show you what the proper power is!
Damn it, there's too many of them.
Hamazura, I think they'll use a timer
to release the biological weapon.
We should wait for them to leave.
Good call.
Hamazura, don't do anything stupid.
Okay.
Shit! They saw us!
What now?
An Academy City plane?
Hey, there! I know you're hiding in among the trees.
If you're a good samaritan, you have my admiration.
After all, I'm basically the same.
Someone from Academy City?
We also know about the Kremlin Report.
We're going to roast that
biological weapon real well.
Takitsubo! Where are you?
Say something!
Takitsubo!
A Certain Magical Index
Fear never loosens its grip on me
But I hold back my tears
It's a lonely battle in this never-ending night
I wonder where you went
Just as the courage I was relying on was breaking down
I heard a voice calling me from afar
Your smile, so sincere it's almost awkward,
Makes the lonely night turn into day
Spread throughout the whole world
Are hope-filled lights
As they connect, the future smiles upon us
I feel like this sad journey is
Coming to an end
Your voice will be what changes me
I'm not alone
May this never-ending song shine brightly
"Have you calmed down?"
asks Misaka.
Yeah. This is far beyond just a bad situation.
I don't want to think about what would happen
if they detonated a nuke that high.
Can you tell where they'd launch the missile from?
"According to the radio chatter,
it's a location about 70 kilometers from here,"
answers Misaka.
Should I just take it from them?
Can you drive a car?
Next Time
The power of the Right Arm and the knowledge
of the Index Librorum Prohibitorum.
Having mastered both, Fiamma unleashes
a series of attacks that pin me down.
Is he after the power to save the world?
Next time: "Index".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.