For Your Safety
Please steer clear
of this area during
construction.
We apologize for
the inconvenience.
You came alone, huh?
So, how much do you want?
All of it.
I want everything you have.
Huh?
You have the money for it?
No.
What?!
I don't have any money.
But I'm telling you to give me all the drugs you have.
Who the hell do you think you are?!
Hey!
You little—
You think you can get away from us?
Uh...
I would suggest you reconsider.
Who the hell are you?!
My name is Boogiepop. For now. I guess.
Great job, Masaki.
You wouldn't believe how stuffy this thing is.
But all the rumors say that's how he dresses.
He must have it rough trying
to fight in this getup all the time.
You're a hero, Masaki.
Thanks to you,
we saved more than a hundred people from
ever coming into contact with these drugs.
It's quite noble.
Noble, huh?
Oh?
Your hand...
Huh? My hand?
It'll be fine.
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
Can
you
see
the
mean
ing
in
side
your
self?
New Messages
Can
you
see
the
mean
ing
in
your
dark
ness?
New Messages
Oh,
where
are
you
now?
Boogiepop and Others
Have
you
gone
a
way?
Boogiepop and Others
Here
now,
is
it
just
a
look
like?
All
of
the
world
is
slow
ly
chang
from
here
Yesterday I had the strangest dream
A voice from the dark was calling out to me
When I turned around, all I could see
Was the presence of an unfading
ma
bo
ro
shi
Illusion
Can
you
see
the
mean
ing
in
side
your
self?
A voice laughs suddenly, then disappears
Why do we meet, and why do we then part
And never know the reasons why?
mean
ing
in
your
dark
ness?
The repeating reflection in the shadows
Within that nothingness,
Searching for something unknown, he walks on
Before I knew it, two weeks had already passed
since we started having me play Boogiepop.
School's going to start soon.
What should we do then?
I mean, we can't keep this up forever,
right?
Y-You want me to wear that?
You'll wear it when you appear.
How was that?
Was that overdoing it for a groper?
You're truly amazing, Masaki.
I don't think I like using you as bait, though.
I still have no idea why
Orihata wants me to do this.
I'm kinda glad that today was a bust.
Getting attacked every day would be scary.
So, what now? Do you want to keep doing this?
Masaki.
What's up?
Isn't there anything you want me to do for you?
I'll do whatever you want.
Listen to anything you say.
Anything for you, Masaki.
I know it hardly makes up for this. But...
If it would make you happy, I'll do anything at all.
In that case... How about we keep
playing Boogiepop a little longer?
Are you sure?
Yeah. I'm starting to have
fun with it, so let's keep going.
You really are an idiot, Masaki.
Guess I am.
See you next time.
Hey, Masaki.
Do you—
Did you say something?
No, never mind.
Well, good night.
Good night.
Yes. This is Orihata.
Camille?
Yes.
That bastard still hasn't fallen into the trap?
Not yet, no.
Guess he's not quite dumb enough to come
out of the woodwork for some impostor.
Whatever.
We'll use Masaki Taniguchi
for another purpose, then.
Cut ties with him for now.
I'm willing to sterilize this
whole area if that's what it takes.
Await further orders.
Over.
Yes, this is Sasahara.
I put the drugs in the usual coin locker.
Put them in the drinks you serve
at that fast food job of yours.
Understood. Executing command.
What?
Periodic report.
Yeah?
70% of the spiked cream has been sold.
However, there are no visible changes
in the ones who purchased it.
All right. Begin stage two on everyone
who bought the spiked cream,
whether they showed results or not.
Understood.
Urgent report.
What've you got?!
Apparently, he's been frequently
appearing near the expressway overpass.
That's just the fake I've got walking around!
Anything else?
Rumors say a figure matching his description
was spotted on the roof of Twin City.
I know that already! Do your fucking
homework before you call me, dammit!
Boogiepop, you son of a bitch.
I'll destroy you! I don't care
if I have to level the whole city!
But what he said keeps running through my mind.
The reemergence of the Imaginator
is my primary concern at the moment.
If I can figure out what the hell
this Imaginator is, I might be able to—
Any time I feel really depressed,
I pay a visit to my secret place.
Listen.
Keep your distance from him
until I figure out what's going on.
I first met Jin when I was five.
You have some nerve asking
for favors after being gone so long.
Stop it already.
You left the family of your own accord.
Why on earth should I lend you any money?
Uncle is right, Father.
There's no way he'd let you
borrow money just like that.
Let's go home.
Y-Yeah, you're right...
He was my first love,
but I had no idea what to say to him.
At the time, I thought I'd never see him again.
But then, when I was nine,
our paths crossed again in a way
I would never have imagined.
You don't need any money?
No. I'm sorry about my behavior before.
But I'm no longer in need of money.
Then what are you here for?
Kouji, do you have any interest in paintings?
Paintings?
I'm talking about real masterpieces.
That's the type of work I'm doing now.
You've become an art dealer?
But a trade like that requires an incredibly
discerning eye. Otherwise you're just asking to fail.
I'm not concerned.
The boy is handling that side of things.
Jin is?
He's a genius. He's already received
countless awards for his art.
I see. Do you want to be a painter
when you're older, Jin?
It's my dream.
It happened later that night.
What were you doing out here?
Sorry. I didn't mean to frighten you.
I was just hoping it would snow.
Snow?
Yeah. It looked like it might snow tonight.
Do you like snow?
I do. It probably seems childish, huh.
Shortly afterward, my uncle passed away,
leaving Jin all alone.
It's still not clear how he died,
but there were no signs he had been poisoned,
so the cause of death was declared undetermined.
He's such a good boy. They should just adopt him.
But he declined the offer, didn't he?
I couldn't help but be relieved that we could stay
cousins instead of becoming brother and sister.
But he still...
Jin...
Oh, is that what your man is called?
Student Identification Card
This card certifies that the following individual
is a student registered with this institution.
Year:  2
Name: Kinukawa Kotoe
Birthdate:
Shinyou Academy High School Division   Principal
Kotoe Kinukawa, age seventeen, eh?
Student Identification Card
This card certifies that the following individual
is a student registered with this institution.
Year:  2
Name: Kinukawa Kotoe
Birthdate:
Shinyou Academy High School Division   Principal
Student Identification Card
This card certifies that the following individual
is a student registered with this institution.
Year:  2
Name: Kinukawa Kotoe
Birthdate:
Shinyou Academy High School Division   Principal
Student Identification Card
This card certifies that the following individual
is a student registered with this institution.
Year:  2
Name: Kinukawa Kotoe
Kinukawa?
The Ladder
Ferris Wheel
Bathrooms
Rest Area
Kinukawa Industries
No wonder she had the master key.
Perfect. She'll be the ideal tool for
finding out more about this Imaginator.
Kotoe
Kinukawa
Hey, can I ask you something?
Huh?
You ever hear the name "Imaginator" before?
Hey, how do you know that name?
Where the hell is that bastard?
Ah, so it's a person?
I'm asking the questions here!
Some good friends of mine got all screwed up
by that so-called Imaginator fuck!
Screwed up?
Could you elaborate a bit more on that?
I'm prepared to compensate
you for your cooperation.
Who the hell are you?
I'm definitely no friend of the Imaginator's,
I can tell you that much.
I didn't see anything myself.
I just know a guy who was in the wrong place
at the wrong time and saw the freak in action.
You're talking like this guy witnessed
some supernatural phenomenon.
That's 'cause it was.
God knows how,
but he said this freak took on a whole
gang by himself and sent them all flying.
Flying?
Yeah. But he didn't throw a single punch.
And the ones he got...
They turned on the others.
Sounds more like a monster than a person.
Yeah, well... I don't exactly understand it either.
So what happened to the guys he attacked?
What do you mean?
You said he messed them up somehow.
Right.
I did run into one of them once.
A guy named Tsuyoshi.
We were never really buddies,
but when I got his attention...
The bastard looked over at me and grinned.
And what's so weird about that?
He's never been that kind of guy.
At the time,
I hadn't heard about the Imaginator yet.
He just seemed like a totally different person.
I see...
So the Imaginator is capable
of doing something to people
that draws them to its own side.
Something like that.
What did its voice sound like?
Voice?
Your friend heard it call itself by name.
Isn't that how you found out?
Yeah. He said it sounded like some cocky asshole.
Like some dude with a god complex.
But your friend never saw his face?
Nope.
Come to think of it...
What?
He did mention something about
a figure in white... like a white shadow.
What happened? Did that ring a bell?
Damn it! I can't access it!
H-Hey...
Never mind. It's nothing.
Just who are you, anyhow?
What are you looking into this Imaginator for?
Don't you want to avenge your friends?
And how the hell would I do that?
Get a group together with this.
Once you do, we're hunting the Imaginator down.
H-How the hell'd you get all this money?
Please. This is pocket change.
Hey, Masaki.
What's up?
You've been going out a lot lately.
Oh, have I?
You come home late, too.
What've you been up to?
Oh, nothing much.
What are these calluses?
I've just been practicing karate.
I'd been slacking off since I came to Japan.
Didn't Mr. Sakakibara warn you
about getting a big head?
You'll be the one who ends up hurt.
I know. I'm not, I promise.
I just have a lot of stuff on my mind.
It would be nice if that were all.
Café Tristan
Oh? So that's your boyfriend?
I'm almost impressed.
Masaki, I...
Is this a friend of yours?
She's... my upperclassman at school.
The name's Kotoe Kinukawa. Charmed, I'm sure.
Likewise.
Oh my. No hesitation at all
when a girl offers her hand?
You must be experienced with the ladies.
Seriously, who are you?
I'm Orihata's friend. Same as you.
Right, Mister Boogiepop?
Kinukawa knows about what we're doing.
I sure do. And I'd just love to lend you a hand.
Why would you?
Do I really need a reason to do the right thing?
You should totally keep at it, Taniguchi.
She came to talk to me about it.
You don't actually want to do it anymore, do you?
Orihata, come with me for a sec.
Oh, don't mind little old me.
I wouldn't want to come between you.
I'll pay your tab. Please take your time.
Masaki, I...
What did she do to you?
Nothing...
What was up with that girl's attitude?
Is she blackmailing you?
It's nothing like that. Really.
Then what the hell is going on?
She sure wasn't acting like she was your friend.
If you're in some kind of trouble, I can—
She saw the costume.
Costume?
Yes. Her father is the landlord of my apartment,
so...
Wait, so she's Kinukawa
as in Kinukawa Enterprises?
Yes.
But why would a well-off girl like her—
Well...
How convenient that you live smack in
the middle of Kotoe Kinukawa's territory.
This can be home base for my Imaginator hunt.
Imaginator?
I've already got men prepared
to hunt the Imaginator down.
You'll be their overseer.
B-But won't Masaki be...
I told you, we're done with that dumb kid.
What?
Don't tell me you're afraid
he won't love you anymore!
But the Touwa Organization explicitly
instructed me not to let anyone hate me...
So...
What?!
You think you've got any right
to get picky about men now?
Just so you know, I'm no run-of-the-mill terminal.
I'm a copy.
How many guys have you bent over
for since you left the facility?
I...
You were their project to see whether synthetic
humans could interbreed with normal ones,
but you didn't get knocked up even once.
Correct.
And yet a successful terminal like me
doesn't get to have anything down there!
Why the hell does a failure
like you get to have all the fun?!
What bullshit!
Listen and listen good, Camille.
Before we cut the kid loose,
see if you can crossbreed with him.
If I do, will you let Masaki go?
Huh? Yeah, sure.
Thank goodness.
Masaki won't have to be Boogiepop anymore.
Masaki... whatever happens, I have to save you.
I'm sorry. I...
You can't tell me?
This is all my fault.
Let's stop doing this Boogiepop thing.
Good idea.
Yes.
You don't need to put yourself in
the line of fire anymore. I'll do it alone.
Huh?
What do you mean, Masaki?
Just what I said. I'm going to keep going on my own.
But why? You didn't want to do it in the first place.
So what? You didn't want to do it either, did you?
Why not just be honest with me about how you felt?
I...
I never liked putting you in danger
to lure out criminals anyway.
But I thought this was
what you wanted to do! So I...
Why... Why are you...
I'd better get going.
Masaki!
Wait.
Please, let me go!
Excellent work, Camille.
New orders.
For whatever reason, he's going to
continue being Boogiepop on his own.
I came here to get you
to reconsider telling him to stop.
Lucky for us he's touched in the head.
What do you mean?
It won't be long now before Boogiepop's
corpse is discovered in some alley.
So "cutting him loose" meant—
Yeah. Then everyone will know the true
identity of the legendary Boogiepop
as just some pathetic, heartbroken idiot!
No! You can't!
I'll make a report to the
Touwa Organization about Boogiepop...
Do you actually think you have anything
to do with the Touwa Organization any more?
The Touwa Organization has—Axis has—
already long since abandoned you!
Got that through your head?
You're nothing but a tool for me, Spooky E!
M-Masaki...
I'm such an idiot!
I know she might seem calm,
but that girl is incredibly unstable.
I never thought too deeply about why
Orihata would want to do any of this.
Huh. Strict parents?
I don't have those.
There had to be more to it than that.
But I was having too much fun to question it.
Push
Button
Before
Crossing,
Even
Bicycles.
So until I figure that out, I'm going to keep going.
Sorry, Nagi. I won't be coming home for a while.
Discernment whited out
The illusion keeps warping
I call out to that presence
And its resonance replies
Flashbacks come ever faster
Still searching for this feeling
I'm overflowing
But don't stop me now
When Man Kills Man
The Scream Inside
Where the Killer's Mind Changes
Imaginator
Looping around again
Through this looking glass
I see an unfamiliar self there
Smiling back at me with a heart of ice
Mirror, mirror, mirror
Now there's no going back
Wavering in the shadows
Oh, won't someone free me
From this web of lies?