Can
you
see
the
mean
ing
in
side
your
self?
New Messages
Can
you
see
the
mean
ing
in
your
dark
ness?
New Messages
Oh,
where
are
you
now?
Boogiepop and Others
Have
you
gone
a
way?
Boogiepop and Others
Here
now,
is
it
just
a
look
like?
All
of
the
world
is
slow
ly
chang
from
here
Yesterday I had the strangest dream
A voice from the dark was calling out to me
When I turned around, all I could see
Was the presence of an unfading
ma
bo
ro
shi
Illusion
Can
you
see
the
mean
ing
in
side
your
self?
A voice laughs suddenly, then disappears
Why do we meet, and why do we then part
And never know the reasons why?
mean
ing
in
your
dark
ness?
The repeating reflection in the shadows
Within that nothingness,
Searching for something unknown, he walks on
Habara! Habara!
Are you all right?
Y-Yeah, I'm fine.
It looks like the earthquake is over.
What happened to me?
You started shouting about something,
and then you just collapsed.
I see...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Anyway, Habara...
I found another trapdoor.
It's right here.
Hey, wake up!
Isn't she the girl from earlier?
The one you laughed at.
Hey, you awake?
Who are you?
I'm Kentarou Habara. He's Shirou Tanaka.
Sakiko Michimoto...
Did you see the King of Distortion too, Michimoto?
The King of Distortion...
Did you guys wake me up?
What did he look like?
Did you learn anything about who he really is?
What's the point of asking me that?
We're gonna take him out!
But first we need to know more about him.
Take him out?
What did the King of Distortion say to you?
Pretty much the same thing he said to you, I bet.
Then why...
Habara, I got the hatch open. It wasn't locked.
Great.
Well, it's fine if you don't believe me.
Just sit tight and we'll be back.
Is there anything down here?
It's the same as the other room. Nothing useful.
Should we go back?
Yes.
I won't let you interfere.
I don't care why you're doing this.
I won't let you stop the King of Distortion!
Hold on!
I'm going back! I have to go back!
Hey!
Dammit, it's stuck shut!
What the hell is her deal?
Hey, you over there!
Don't stand so close. It could be dangerous.
Whoa, what's happening?
Wh-What the...
Good day, ladies and gentlemen.
Have you solved the riddle yet?
No, the fact that you're still hearing this music
means that you have yet to reach me.
I don't know how many people
are inside the Moon Temple right now,
but allow me to address those of you on the outside.
There is no way into the Moon Temple.
It would be wisest not to even try.
That's Kyouichirou Teratsuki's voice.
I knew it. He has to be the King of Distortion.
Furthermore, to those inside the building,
I imagine you might be concerned about
the noise you heard before the music started.
What you heard was the sound of
every air duct in the building being sealed shut.
As you may have guessed, this means
that your oxygen supply has been cut off.
I don't know exactly how long you have,
but if you don't act quickly,
you'll all die of suffocation.
Are you serious?!
Now, then. I wish you all luck.
Do your best.
Shit! You've gotta be kidding me.
Does he actually intend to kill everyone here?
Please calm down, Habara.
It's not as simple as he made it sound.
But—
Closing all the air ducts wouldn't be enough
to cut off the air flow to the entire building.
He's just trying to scare us.
What's he got to gain from scaring us?
Just think, what would most people do
after hearing that and being sent into a panic?
They'd run.
But the exits are—
Yes. They're all blocked.
So that leaves... up!
That's right.
Fearing for their lives, most people will try to go up.
His intention is probably to draw people to him.
What a sicko. This really is just a game to him.
I guess the first thing we have
to do is find a way out of here.
Agreed. Let's go.
I'm beginning to think she had pretty good taste.
She? Who do you mean?
That girl who was in love with you.
She knew how to pick 'em.
Oh... is that right?
What's going on here?
Are you just trying to kill everyone
who's been trapped in here?
That's it?
Who knows? What do you think?
If I knew, I wouldn't be asking you!
It's not like you to care so much,
Miss President.
This is how it should be.
You were awfully brave back then, too.
You were there, and so was Masami Saotome...
If only Shirou Tanaka could join us,
our little class reunion would be complete.
What are you getting at?
Nagi Kirima might even come save you again.
I'm sure not counting on it.
Is something bothering you, President?
I figured it out, Saotome.
You figured what out?
I know what I left with you.
I figured out why the King of Distortion
appeared to me as Masami Saotome.
The real reason.
Miyashita...
You called?
M-Miyashita?
Wh-What are you doing here?
Hey, are you really satisfied
just standing around out here?
Wouldn't you rather go inside?
Y-You're...
You're the King of Distortion.
If you want in, follow me.
H-Hey!
What on Earth is happening?
This is a dream world inhabited
solely by the two of us.
Everyone else is having their realities
shifted a teeny bit, that's all.
Shifted?
Hey, what are you doing?
What the hell?
This is the staff entrance.
Hey, Takeda.
Catch me if you can.
W-Wait!
Habara!
Here?
Yes. This spot makes a slightly different sound.
There's got to be an inspection
hatch or something like that—
We'd better hurry.
Yeah.
I can't go back.
Isn't there any way back to you, Hinako?
I wish everything would just fall apart.
Boogiepop...
Did you... save me?
I wonder, did I?
U-Um... You're the, uh...
Precisely. My name is Boogiepop.
It seems that you're already familiar with me.
Are you the real Boogiepop?
I'm not sure. Is there anything in this
world that can truly be called real?
That's not what I mean.
What I want to ask is... Do you actually... um...
Do I actually kill people?
Indeed I do.
Isn't that why people like you
came to call me the Reaper?
Why do you kill people?
It is my job.
The ones I kill tend to be enemies of the world.
How do you choose your targets?
I wouldn't say that I choose them.
Much of the time,
the ones I am to kill appear
in front of me of their own accord.
Are you saying they ask to be killed?
I think I understand how they feel.
I might disagree.
No human truly wants to be killed.
That's not true!
I know there are people who hate their lives
so much that they genuinely want to be killed!
Those are simply people who have made a choice
between experiencing death or continuing on
after their reason for living has died.
What does that mean?
To earn the right to ask for death,
one must first have truly lived.
Have you...
truly earned that right?
But I'm terrible!
I'm an awful, unforgivable person!
Is that really grounds for deserving death?
Obviously!
The rest of the world would be
better off without terrible people in it!
Does that mean you want to see a world
in which only good people have the right to live?
Yes... Someplace without people like me...
Where Hina can live out her whole life peacefully.
She was...
She was a much, much better person than I was...
But for some reason I'm the only one who's still...
Was your King of Distortion kind to you?
Yes... She said I had to change all this pain into gold.
What does that mean?
I-I didn't really get it either, but...
I felt like I had to do it anyway.
I'd do anything to live there with Hina!
She is a part of you.
Any kindness she might have showed
came from within you.
I'm sure that, much like myself,
the King of Distortion has no body of its own.
What you saw was an externalized version
of the distortion inside your heart.
It sounds to me as though you've been distorting
your own kindness all this time.
That's no simple task, to be sure.
This distortion has no doubt been
causing you pain for a very long time.
But at the same time,
the mere fact that you felt so much pain
serves to prove what a kind person you really are.
She appeared to you in order to show you that.
Haven't you already done what she asked?
If those feelings of yours aren't gold already,
then there cannot be anything
in this world that truly glitters.
My oh my.
I suppose it won't be so easy
to bring this to a conclusion.
Has he been controlling
the Moon Temple from here?
I don't think so. This is awfully
fancy-looking for a control room.
So maybe it's...
First things first. I'm gonna see if I can
figure out how to open the front doors.
Hello. You've done very well to make it this far.
Whether there's one person
in this room or several, I don't know,
but I wish to congratulate you
on making it to this point.
Kyouichirou Teratsuki.
As you may have already realized, the Moon Temple
was built for the sole purpose
of luring you here at this moment.
Ah, yes. I should probably explain a few things.
Have you ever felt like the world
has its own sort of flow?
You might also think of it as fate
or as a set of patterns or trends.
But have you thought about what that flow really is?
Humans have been trying to find
the answer since the dawn of time.
Even today, they're searching for it.
The concept of evolution was born
from that search as well.
With evolution, something of a
directionality or a flow can be observed.
So, naturally, the question arises,
"Is that flow still flowing on, even now?"
And if so, is there some way to predict
in which direction it will flow next?
But now we've arrived at God's doorstep.
And yet, there has never been a point
in human history where someone with power
wasn't trying to step across that threshold.
But in this age, there are no obvious
rulers or figures of authority.
What the hell is he talking about?
All that exists is a system.
For simplicity's sake,
we'll call this system the Touwa Organization.
This organization is my employer
as well as my creator.
That's right. I am a synthetic human
created by the Touwa Organization.
My job is to manipulate the economy
in whatever way the Organization desires.
But my role is almost at an end.
I've become a bit too powerful for their liking,
so it won't be long before they dispose of me.
But before my time is up, I wanted to have
a little fun at the Touwa Organization's expense.
That's why I had the Moon Temple built.
I have full confidence that once I die,
this building will be made into a public spectacle.
Perhaps you are one of those who came to see it.
Or maybe you're one of the event staff.
Regardless, I'm sure you never
expected to be caught up
in something like this.
But here you are.
As a matter of fact, you were meant to come here.
You were trapped inside this building
and rendered unconscious with sleeping gas.
But what's important is the fact that you awakened
and came all the way here.
There are people in this world capable
of understanding things better left unknown,
of finding their way to places
they should be unable to reach.
It is these individuals that the
Touwa Organization is most wary of.
I'm sure you see what this means.
You have the potential to become
an enemy to the Touwa Organization.
That is what I wanted to tell you.
I constructed the Moon Temple
solely to deliver this message.
It took every last yen of what remained
of Kyouichirou Teratsuki's fortune.
All for the sake of warning you to be careful.
The password to release the Moon Temple
from its current lockdown will be...
Stairway to Heaven.
I'll leave it at that.
If you type that in, everything will unlock.
Furthermore, all of the data
in this room will be erased.
Listen carefully. You are a possibility.
I cannot even begin to guess
at the true potential you hold.
I'm sure that even you yourself
aren't fully aware of it yet.
What matters is how you plan
to develop that possibility
and what you use it to do from here on out.
I wish you the best.
Ah, it's you, Eugene?
I'm sure you'll have no problem
making me disappear.
What the hell was that?
I see.
That explains a lot.
Huh? What are you talking about, Shirou?
That was a bunch of nonsense!
How so?
Come on! It didn't explain anything!
The only things that made any sense are that
we're trapped in here, and that we were put to sleep.
Why? Why didn't he say a single word
about the King of Distortion?
Stumbling blind in a whiteout
The illusion keeps warping
I call out to that presence
And its resonance replies
Flashbacks come ever faster
Still searching for a way out
I'm overflowing
But don't stop me now
When Man Kills Man
The Scream Inside
Where the Killer's Mind Changes
Imaginator
Looping around again
Through this looking glass
I see an unfamiliar self there
Smiling back at me with a heart of ice
Now there's no going back
Wavering in the shadows
Oh, won't someone free me
From this web of lies?