I'll kill you. I'll kill you. I'll kill you. I'll kill you.
I'll kill you. I'll kill you. I'll kill you. I'll kill you...
Can
you
see
the
mean
ing
in
side
your
self?
New Messages
Can
you
see
the
mean
ing
in
your
dark
ness?
New Messages
Oh,
where
are
you
now?
Boogiepop and Others
Have
you
gone
a
way?
Boogiepop and Others
Here
now,
is
it
just
a
look
like?
All
of
the
world
is
slow
ly
chang
from
here
Yesterday I had the strangest dream
A voice from the dark was calling out to me
When I turned around, all I could see
Was the presence of an unfading
ma
bo
ro
shi
Illusion
Can
you
see
the
mean
ing
in
side
your
self?
A voice laughs suddenly, then disappears
Why do we meet, and why do we then part
And never know the reasons why?
mean
ing
in
your
dark
ness?
The repeating reflection in the shadows
Within that nothingness,
Searching for something unknown, he walks on
I see.
So you feel certain that people are saying
horrible things about you behind your back.
Do you feel like you're being followed?
You think I'm lying, don't you?
No, I haven't determined anything yet.
Doctor, will you hear me out?
Of course.
I've come to realize that our world
is harboring a terrifying evil.
Since this evil knows that I'm aware of it,
it goes around telling everyone I know the most
vile lies about me to undermine my credibility.
As you'd expect, it's made my life a living hell.
And how did you come to this realization?
It's obvious. I hear messages through the TV and
radio all the time about how he's coming to get me.
I see.
That must be quite the ordeal.
It really is.
Long time no see.
Oh, Dr. Kisugi.
I'm glad to see you doing so much better.
And you're the same as ever, Doctor.
Thank you.
But I have to say,
I have no idea how you were cured.
It's truly remarkable.
You still think it was all in my head, right?
To be perfectly honest, I do.
I'm actually starting to think the same thing.
So do you have some idea as to why?
Well, I met someone not too long ago.
And after I met him, I felt like a weight
had been lifted off my shoulders.
I'm wondering if that's what actually cured me.
I-I see. So who is this person?
A man?
He was a weirdo.
I haven't seen him again since then.
Not that I haven't looked.
But I get the feeling I won't find him.
It's just a hunch, but...
Maybe it was love.
Am I wrong?
Who knows? I'm not really sure myself.
I wonder what my dad would say.
He'd probably tell you that first love bears no fruit.
You should forget about him.
Yeah, you're probably right. But still...
Hey, Dr. Kisugi. Why did you decide
to become a psychiatrist?
Huh?
I have no idea what I want to do with my life.
How did you decide on your career?
I wonder. Maybe I ended up here
because I'm a coward.
What do you mean?
Performing an analysis of the mind often
requires deconstructing indescribable fears.
I've been a huge coward ever since I was a child,
and I always wondered where that
cowardice came from. Why does fear exist?
After years spent pursuing an answer
to that question, I ended up here.
Then, if—
Miss Nagi Kirima, please come to window three.
Damn, that's me.
See you around, Doc.
Right. See you later, Nagi.
I was right. She hasn't realized a thing.
That one moment set everything in motion.
Right after that incident, Nagi Kirima,
who had an incurable illness,
made a miraculous recovery.
My ensuing experiments on rats
induced regenerative abilities
that rendered them basically immortal.
Just as I thought. There's no other
word for this than evolution.
I wonder what would happen if
I injected this into one of my patients...
As if. I could never do that.
But what if instead...
We have breaking news regarding
the recent string of murders.
Found in Hinoki Park:
Mutilated Corpse of
High School Girl (16)
Corpse of local student (16) discovered by a man jogging in the park
The body of a teenage girl, believed to be
another victim, was discovered last night.
The excessive mutilation of the body,
including the jaw being pried open,
matches the MO in the
three-month string of serial killings
involving grotesque corpses left in random locations.
BREAKING
New Victim's Body Discovered As
Serial Murder Spree Continues
Female Students Targeted By Killer
New Victim's Body Discovered As
Serial Murder Spree Continues
Female Students Targeted By Killer
This makes five victims.
Just like the other four,
she had her lower jaw pried open
and her brain sucked out.
Yes, the killer seems to have extreme
superstitious beliefs regarding the brain.
Can you expand on that?
The killer has disassembled the skull
of each victim with extreme care.
This could be an attempt at a ritual,
possibly even something occult.
What is it?
Oh, nothing. I just thought he looked good on TV.
Bet they love him for these guest spots.
What's your take on these murders, Dr. Kisugi?
Even specialists shouldn't make hasty
assessments of such extreme cases.
That's what the director would say.
BREAKING
New Victim's Body Discovered As
Serial Murder Spree Continues
Female Students Targeted By Killer
New Victim's Body Discovered As
Serial Murder Spree Continues
Female Students Targeted By Killer
Superstitious beliefs regarding the brain, huh?
But to be able to disassemble a skull,
the killer must have some
really specialized knowledge.
Sounds like a real nutcase.
Maybe the dissection itself is the goal.
Like, the killer takes pleasure in
the act of disassembling the skulls.
What do you think?
I haven't a clue.
But if the killer turns out to be
someone in the medical field,
it'll cause no end of trouble.
That would be some commotion.
Like kicking a snakes' nest.
Wh-What?
You mean "a hornets' nest," right?
Oh, is that how the saying goes?
Y-Yes. I'm pretty sure it is.
You must not care for snakes.
N-No, that's not why...
Do you have some trauma involving snakes?
N-No, I just think they're kind of creepy...
Some philosophers believe snakes
are a metaphor for the male sex organ.
Wasn't one of them Freud?
L-Like I said, that's not it! I don't have...
Are you all right? You're starting to look pale.
N-No, I'm fine.
I might just be overtired.
Too sweet to even be worthwhile.
His fear will remain unpalatable
no matter how much I scare him.
I suppose men just lack depth.
Someone! Someone, please help me!
Save me!
This must be a dream! It has to be!
Well, I can't blame you for feeling worn out.
There's been a lot of upheaval here recently
after the sudden dismissal of that veteran nurse.
Oh, you mean what the director did?
It does feel like he's been causing quite a stir lately.
I wonder if someone caught wind
of some dirty secret of his.
This isn't enough.
Not enough, not enough, not enough, not enough,
not enough, not enough,
not enough, not enough, not enough...
How are we feeling tonight, Mr. Shinokita?
Have you had any visitors?
Oh, just as I thought...
No one's come to see you.
I hear that kind nurse who
was taking care of you quit, too.
Do you feel lonely, Mr. Shinokita?
You worked yourself to the bone for your family,
with nothing to show for it but
a divorce and a demotion at work.
And to top it all off, all those years of drinking
with clients have ruined your health.
Who knows how much longer your company
will allow you to remain on sick leave?
How are you going to pay your
hospital bills once your disability runs out?
If I'd given you that drug,
maybe I could have cured you.
Look at me!
I haven't used enough discretion lately,
so while I lay low,
I'll have to settle for messing with you.
Yes, just like that! More! Fear me more!
From the bottom of your heart!
Well? Impressive, isn't it?
Look what else I can do!
It's all thanks to that drug.
Juuust kidding. It's all a magic trick.
Just a little sleight of hand.
Oh, dear me. Again?
Watch out, Mr. Shinokita.
If you go crazy, you'll end up in my ward.
And I'm going to have even more
fun with you when you do.
Not enough. It's not enough.
I need more, more, more, more, more, more,
more, more, more, more, more, more, more!
Help me...
Help me... Please...
Please...
Something with even greater destructive power.
What I desire is absolute fear!
As I thought, women's fear
tastes far better than men's.
A stronger will improves the taste as well.
But don't you think you're
both equally to blame here?
He's a college student, though...
That doesn't matter.
Let's go talk to him in person.
Yes. And the fearlessness of youth
is the perfect conduit to a strong will.
If I could have her...
It'll be fine.
Next up, we have breaking news
about the string of grisly murders.
NEW VICTIM'S BODY DISCOVERED AS SERIAL MURDER SPREE CONTINUES
My, how awful. To think the killer
only targets young girls.
NEW VICTIM'S BODY DISCOVERED AS SERIAL MURDER SPREE CONTINUES
The DNA from the body of the victim
found the other day at Hinoki Park
NEW VICTIM'S BODY DISCOVERED AS SERIAL MURDER SPREE CONTINUES
You be careful, too, Makiko.
matched that of a local teenage girl
previously reported missing.
NEW VICTIM'S BODY DISCOVERED AS SERIAL MURDER SPREE CONTINUES
I know.
But it would seem...
SCHOOLGIRL'S REMAINS FOUND IN PUBLIC PARK
BIZARRE DEATH
I left too obvious of a clue.
SCHOOLGIRL'S REMAINS FOUND IN PUBLIC PARK
BIZARRE DEATH
At this rate, they're definitely going to catch me.
SCHOOLGIRL'S REMAINS FOUND IN PUBLIC PARK
BIZARRE DEATH
Before I kill her, I need to find someone I can frame.
Otherwise, it's only a matter of time before
whoever produced this drug catches on to me.
But if they were able to develop
something like this in secret,
they must be a huge organization
with an enormous reach.
As I am now, I bet I could turn the tables
and take advantage of them.
All I need is to know their weakness.
Oh? Are you afraid of me?
Yes. Individuals gather together.
They become a community,
which will inevitably develop a weak point.
This holds true even at the national level.
I do wonder... what would a whole
nation writhing in fear taste like?
How have you been? Any changes to report?
You've been kind to me, Doctor,
so I just wanted to let you know.
The world is coming to an end.
Oh, dear. That's awful.
Yes, it really is awful.
You remember the terrifying
evil I mentioned before?
It's finally going to make its move.
I see. That is a problem.
Can't we ask it to stop?
I don't think we can.
Then what should we do?
There's nothing we can do.
There's nothing we can do
but give up and await our doom,
cowering in fear.
Are you afraid?
I should be very afraid.
That sounds rough.
It really is.
You're free to enter now, miss.
Touka Miyashita
File
Edit
Chart
Entry
Calendar
Memo
Examinations
Other
A split personality?
Yes. The personality of a very strange man
is residing in my daughter's mind.
But Mrs. Miyashita, it takes a professional
to diagnose dissociative identity disorder—
But it's true!
That strange man dwelling
inside her nearly killed me!
Mom...
Don't interrupt me!
May I speak with your daughter in private
in order to understand what happened?
She's always like that these days.
Is that because you have DID?
I guess so...
I don't really understand it, though.
So you aren't conscious of it?
Right...
By the way, do you get along
well with your mom and dad?
W-Well, I...
While I don't think it's the only reason,
many cases of DID are linked
to instability in the home.
Well, I guess there isn't much I can say.
Would you be willing to try something for me?
Try what?
Try and roleplay as this so-called other personality.
What?
Your mother called it the
personality of a strange man.
Try imagining yourself as someone like that.
I-I'm not sure how to do that.
This is a form of hypnotherapy.
If you truly have DID,
the other personality may emerge
while you're acting.
I-Is that how it works?
Just give it your best shot.
How would this man behave?
O-Okay—I mean... Y-You got it, lady.
Yes, that's it. Just relax and keep going.
'Kay...
So, what kind of man are you?
Um...
Your mother said you were strange,
so you must be the eccentric type.
You're free to think of me as either
a man or a woman. I don't mind.
Oh, so your gender is ambiguous? That's unusual.
So, why exactly are you inside Touka?
I'm not sure of that myself, as of yet.
You're not?
I feel bad that I've become a burden
on the Miyashita family,
but there isn't much I can do about that.
What I do know is that I have a mission.
I see. So there's something that you need to do?
I'm meant to avert threats to this world.
Threats to this world?
An enemy of the world has appeared nearby.
If nothing is done,
it will mean the destruction of the world.
I see you operate on a large scale.
I wouldn't say that.
Threats to the world can be found anywhere.
Really? Then they must not be all that scary.
Of course they aren't. Not to you.
What's that supposed to mean?
Because you are an enemy of the world.
Her weakness... disappeared?
An enemy, you say?
Yes, an enemy.
But you're nothing unique.
Every human has the potential
to become an enemy of the world.
Humans are like fuses.
It only takes the slightest spark to
provoke them into inducing an explosion.
They can shake the world to its foundation
without sparing a thought for the consequences.
I suppose I could be described as
a natural predator of beings like that.
You said all humans,
but I believe most people are normal.
It's because they're normal
that they turn out that way.
What do you mean?
Say you were to encounter something truly unique.
If you possess a strong sense of self,
you can deal with it calmly.
But a truly normal person
would be at risk of losing to the current
and being swept away by a tide of emotions.
And they end up on the most dangerous
type of rampage there is.
Isn't that a form of normalcy bias?
Who knows?
It's just that those who are content
with being normal have no resistance.
And the world isn't as stable
as they'd like to think it is.
Disaster can strike at any time.
Yes. People who wish to knock down the walls
supporting this world have no shortage of chances.
What an exquisite song. It's quite beautiful.
Yes. Not a single wasted note.
And not a single trace of fear.
Whatever do you mean?
There's too much fear in this world.
So much it sickens me.
How wonderful it would be if fear were
to disappear completely from this world.
I see. So that's your aim.
Does that still make me an enemy of the world?
There are many facets to everything.
And just as many different,
equally valid interpretations.
For example, the world would certainly
be free of fear if all life were to die.
I see.
So, what would you do if you found
one of these enemies you speak of?
I would kill them.
That's a terrifying thing to say.
What choice do I have?
That seems to be the only thing I'm good for.
So you would show no mercy?
Correct.
Nor would those who become my enemies desire it.
You're saying your enemies will want a proper duel.
Don't you agree?
What would happen if I just
killed this girl here and now?
If I gave in to my desires
and killed everyone in this hospital?
D-Did you figure anything out?
It's hard to say yet.
I'll need to reevaluate the situation
once things have calmed down at home.
I see...
No. Now is not the time.
Touka.
You should try not to let this get to you.
Yes, ma'am.
Until next time.
Okay.
Thank you very much.
When I die, I'd like to be
sent off with a song like this.
Much better this than some dreary requiem.
Stumbling blind in a whiteout
The illusion keeps warping
I call out to that presence
And its resonance replies
Flashbacks come ever faster
Still searching for a way out
I'm overflowing
But don't stop me now
When Man Kills Man
The Scream Inside
Where the Killer's Mind Changes
Imaginator
Looping around again
Through this looking glass
I see an unfamiliar self there
Smiling back at me with a heart of ice
Now there's no going back
Wavering in the shadows
Oh, won't someone free me
From this web of lies?