Maybe this project's BOM is a bit excessive.
But now all that's left to install are
the memories of another 10,031 deaths.
Mm-hmm. Our research is almost complete, Hirumi.
I can't stay like this. I wasn't useful in the slightest.
Adonai.
Just lay her down here.
She's all right.
Her life force doesn't appear
to be particularly disrupted.
You can heal people as well?
No, I'm just checking their condition.
Even knowing that,
I can only perform regular first-aid.
I'm sure we all would've died if you hadn't shown up.
Th-Thank you.
Tch.
I couldn't do anything. Anything at all.
Everything reflects the darkness
A Certain Scientific Accelerator
The pitch-black town is coated
In light from countless windows
It shines across the barren streets
I sneer at all the shadows
As I remain constricted
By the chain wrapped around my neck
Everything reflects the darkness
When it's inside of my hand
Shadow is the light
I will bear the burden
Of the hell that's in my past
These bloodstained memories I bear
Though they haunt my mind
Fighting dark with darkness
I will still destroy all of
These shadows cast in days gone by
I'll never change
Everything reflects the darkness
When it's inside of my hand
Time Limit
Download
What the hell are you doing?
I doubt they'll be returning any favors.
I'm sure they've seen
the error of their ways after all that.
Like hell they did.
That mindset would've
eventually gotten them killed.
You really are amazing.
You use your power to snatch
people from death's embrace.
I was just crushing some annoying bugs.
You weren't!
What?
I can tell just by looking at them.
You hurt them, but you never once tried to kill them.
You act rough and defiant,
but you end up saving people.
At least, that's how it's starting to seem to me.
That's just your own delusion.
You really are the only one I can count on!
What?
U-Umm... W-Would you
become my m-master?
What?
In the Rosenthal family,
when a master takes on an apprentice,
the apprentice offers something red from
a garment or piece of equipment on their person.
It symbolizes entrusting one's flesh and blood.
By giving it volume and form,
we emphasize that symbology even further.
Go give that to the Anti-Skill lady
on the floor over there or something.
Huh? Don't be like that, please!
Please become my master!
I want to learn from your strength!
Huotou, you ask him for me too!
Understood.
Executing your instruction, Adonai.
Accelerator, I implore you
to become Adonai's master.
Please consider my request.
Wait, where the hell are your clothes?
Oh, she didn't have any time.
Pursuing the enemy was urgent,
so she didn't have time to sort out proper gear.
You have a point,
this doesn't provide adequate defense.
Oh, I know!
I can just give Huotou my equipment!
That'll increase her defensive—
That would introduce room for concern
about your defensive capabilities.
May I suggest borrowing Accelerator's clothing?
Good idea!
Master wouldn't need to rely
on his clothing for protection.
Then, if you don't mind.
If you don't mind.
Hey, Master, wait!
I implore you to become Adonai's master.
You don't even have to do any teaching!
I'll learn on my own, so become my master!
I once again implore you to become Adonai's master.
Apprenticeships are an extremely effective custom!
I repeat, I strongly implore you
to become Adonai's master.
Please, I'm begging you!
I really need you to become my master!
Please!
Tch.
Shut it already.
Please!
The entire world is in danger if we leave them—
I don't give a shit about the world.
Leave me alone, or I'll shut you up for good.
I have to stop Hirumi, no matter what!
But I can't stop her in my current state.
I need strength. A lot of it.
Please!
What a selfish little kid.
What happened here?
Tch.
Hey, you're bleeding.
Misaka proposes getting first aid.
Huotou concurs.
W-Wai—
Come on, keep still.
Come on.
Master, wait!
I don't give a shit about what you want,
but I hate that guy.
Hishigata, was it?
I'm going to find him and
flatten his ass like a pancake.
I'll come with you, then!
Sure. Have fun.
What?
What is that?!
That's a Rosenthal-style magic circle.
This is Taotie.
Taotie?
It's a Si Xiong charm that's
far more powerful than Huotou.
Get back, everyone! It's after me! I'll—
You get back too.
This is perfect.
He came right to me.
I didn't even have to go and find him.
Wait! We don't even know
what kind of ability he's boosted!
We need to be careful—
Master!
Accelerator!
Looks like a substitution ability. Replace?
Are you all right?
Tch.
Did you think bringing another one along would
help you stand a chance, you fucking coward?
Huh? Nothing to say today?
Stay out of this.
A woman?
Hirumi?
Stop this already!
Give back Hirumi!
Are you okay, Adonai?
You got a death wish?
What's going on?
Tch.
Another corpse's ability?
They brought along three of them.
Let her go!
So she's what you were after!
You make some pretty clever moves, don't you?
See you later, Esty!
You think you can get away?!
Can you follow them, Huotou?
That would be difficult to execute.
Given the size of this fire,
over 70% of my body would suffer from burns
and my mobility would drop below 50%.
Even if we caught up, the probability
of stopping something that massive—
Forget it!
Calm down!
There is a possibility of success, Adonai.
Should I execute the command?
I retract my command.
A Certain Scientific Accelerator
Right. Will we get reinforcements?
Roger.
We'll stand by.
I'm certain I saw your corpse, Hitokawa Hasami.
NAME: Hitokawa Hasami
Why are you still alive?
She's not.
NAME: Hitokawa Hasami
Hitokawa Hasami is dead.
Her body is just being controlled by a pseudo-soul.
NAME: Hitokawa Hasami
A pseudo-soul?
A man-made spirit-like entity.
We of the Rosenthal family
have made our livelihoods
practicing necromancy for generations.
You control corpses?
You don't believe me?
I have no clue how it works,
but I'm not going to deny it.
There's a dead person moving around
right in front of me, after all.
So, what do those huge
military robots have to do with you?
I have to stop them.
That's amazing, Hirumi!
I didn't know you could do that!
Yeah, me neither!
That said, I can't be too happy about it.
You can't go sending those coffins
out without permission. Hmm?
You caught one of the Sisters!
Nice work, Hirumi!
You're the best, you really are!
All right, leave the rest to me. Mm-hmm.
Huh, what's that?
I see how it is.
So that girl was inside the robot
because it used necromancy to operate?
That's right.
I built it with Hishigata.
Hishigata Mikihiko, huh?
Address
Date of Birth
Associated
Groups
Name
Address
Date of Birth
Associated
Groups
Notes
Name
Address
Date of Birth
Associated
Groups
Notes
Date of Birth
Associated
Groups
Name
Address
Date of Birth
Associated
Groups
Notes
So he's the one behind this string of incidents.
Wait, does that mean those robots
just now were also using necromancy?
Those are even more dangerous.
They use the evil spirits of the Numbers.
The Numbers' evil spirits?
Qiong Qi, Hundun, and Taotie.
They're special pseudo-souls my family has honed
ever since the fifth head, Nathan, created them.
They're stronger than her?
I'm already plenty surprised at how strong she is.
Corpses that have the Numbers'
charms planted on them
can exhibit power far greater
than the body originally could have.
But any ordinary caster would
have trouble controlling them.
Qiong Qi
And Hishigata isn't even a necromancer.
Hundun
It would be extremely dangerous to leave him be.
Taotie
They once destroyed an entire town
when the practitioner lost control!
I see how it is.
That's pretty troublesome.
Hey, if it isn't Accelerator! Mm-hmm.
So someone else is driving these hunks of junk now?
Calling them hunks of junk is a bit mean.
These three are different from
the prototype you destroyed earlier.
They have pseudo-souls that boost their abilities
to be equivalent to Level 5s. Mm-hmm.
Even the rank-one esper of Academy City won't—
Give me a break.
Tell me where you're hiding already,
you dumbass shut-in.
I'll tear you to pieces.
You're pretty confident, aren't you?
I could've sworn Qiong Qi here'd
given you a lot of trouble just now.
Why don't you try and destroy it?
Weaklings are all bark!
Come on, psychokinesis is way
more versatile than your power!
At the end of the day,
your vector manipulation needs a medium to work.
If you can't make direct contact, then you're
no different from any other natural phenomenon.
I don't give a shit about psychokinesis or whatever.
If there's any kind of force
at play then there's a vector.
Don't get the wrong idea.
It doesn't matter how many pieces
of Level-5 junk you send my way.
I'm the rank-one esper.
Wow, that's amazing!
The low-level espers I've been
experimenting on were absolute trash!
I'd love to put him in a coffin!
We'd definitely see something awesome! Mm-hmm!
Hey, Miki.
Yeah, Hirumi, I know.
We've got to finish our mission first. Mm-hmm.
I wonder what I should crush next.
An arm? The other leg?
Huh? I thought this was a one-on-one.
Oh, sorry about that.
You're really a low priority,
but I've been having so much fun,
I just can't stop myself from having a go at you.
Anyway, I need to finish what I came for.
Who said you could go?!
Bad luck!
There's a prime ability inside Hundun called
Stealth Hide. It dulls the senses of anyone nearby.
The coffin boosts the ability,
so it completely inhibits all perception.
Isn't it amazing?
But man, she really does look alive.
That was my mistake.
Both Hishigata and I believed that.
Even though I knew all along.
I have to put an end to this.
Don't think you could leave that up to Anti-Skill?
I started all this myself,
and I've even dragged my master into it.
I can't bear the thought
of leaving it to even more people.
Why are there so many kids in Academy City
trying to do everything themselves?
Sorry, Huotou.
Can you come with me for just a bit longer?
Understood, Adonai.
Sorry, Hitokawa.
This will really be the last time I do this.
Once this is all over,
I'll never use necromancy again.
I'm almost done copying over
the memories of the 10,031 deaths.
Hirumi, you'll gain the perfect ability once
I download the formula to use this data, won't you.
If I'm being picky, I would've preferred
the data from Last Order, the host Sister.
Yeah, sorry about that.
I didn't think DA would be that useless.
Hey, Hirumi, I was saving that avocado one!
Oh, sorry!
This guy really doesn't give up.
Running around like a headless chicken
won't help you catch Hundun.
Then can you tell me why they're following me?
Should I spoil it?
It's obviously because I'm heading
right towards your pile of junk!
Nothing's completely invisible.
As long as it physically exists,
the air will move when it does.
Tracing that back tells me exactly where it is.
Well this is a surprise.
My ability is also pretty versatile, wouldn't you say?
Yeah! You really are amazing!
How about I give you that Sister back
without even a scratch as a reward?
What?
You're a strange one. Mm-hmm.
These clones are a dime a dozen, but you're getting
so worked up trying to rescue just one of them.
And she's just one of the leftovers of the 10,031
clones you spent your days slaughtering, isn't she?
I saw the records.
Level 6 Shift, was it?
Please don't tell me you're trying to play the hero
by saving one after you mowed
down ten thousand of them.
I don't even get why you care.
Weren't they just
lab rats made for you to kill in the first place?
What the hell...
are you rambling about?
It's just that...
I've decided to...
snap every single bone in your body!
You say some pretty scary things.
Well, I guess negotiations have broken down.
I'll be using this lab rat in an experiment
the way it was meant to be used!
Keep talking!
Not that I plan to let you have the time to!
Wow, that's some impressive firepower. Mm-hmm.
We're probably in trouble
if we don't try to run for real.
Aren't you going to go after
those three robots, Adonai?
We'd only get in Master's way.
I'm going to do what I know how to.
Man, he seems pretty angry for some reason.
He's going to catch up to us at this rate.
Will it finish in time?
I'm not sure! Mm-hmm!
I have to stop
Hishigata and Hirumi.
This all happened because I came to this city.
Hiding in my shell
Holding in all the emotions that I feel
Shackling my mind
But the shackles laugh at me, I find
Swallowing the pain
Savoring the rotten taste because I know that
Worse flavors lie in my future
Someone, take this cup
I'll keep repressing my feelings
Just run away from the torment
I know that I am to blame for
All your suffering
This mind has lost its sense of
Anger and jealousy
Never again to empathize
As I desperately struggle ahead
Possessed by my fears and doubts
Why can't I just live a decent life?
I'm fed up with my past, yet I can't let go
I can't forgive myself
Don't I still deserve to suffer?
That's the question nagging at my heart
As it rots
Next Time
Hirumi
Friend