Thank goodness...
Hirumi is as pretty as ever.
She isn't injured.
Oh, Esty!
Good morning. How have you been?
What's the matter, Esty? You seem down.
Ow!
Hey, I'm in my underwear!
Hirumi...
No! It's not Hirumi.
This is Taowu. Hirumi is dead.
Jeez, maybe I can cover up with this.
This is so embarrassing.
Huh? Esty, what's with that getup?
You haven't gotten into cosplay, have you?
Huh?
Esty...
What is that?
Mikihiko!
H-Hey, Hirumi...
The install is complete.
Mm-hmm, now you'll be...
Why...?
Why...
did you stab Mikihiko,
Esther?!
It's activated.
You're about to become Level 6, Hirumi...
What's that?
Everything reflects the darkness
A Certain Scientific Accelerator
The pitch-black town is coated
In light from countless windows
It shines across the barren streets
I sneer at all the shadows
As I remain constricted
By the chain wrapped around my neck
Everything reflects the darkness
When it's inside of my hand
Shadow is the light
I will bear the burden
Of the hell that's in my past
These bloodstained memories I bear
Though they haunt my mind
Fighting dark with darkness
I will still destroy all of
These shadows cast in days gone by
I'll never change
Everything reflects the darkness
When it's inside of my hand
Awakening
Catastrophe
You're surrounded!
It's no use trying to resist!
Surrender yourselves!
Put down your guns at once!
Give it up! DA has fallen apart!
Damn it, we're surrounded!
Hey, it's hopeless. Let's surrender—
Shut up! Our justice will never be broken!
Wha—?
What are those?
Hishigata's lab is up ahead.
It's probably some new weapon.
It's pretty grotesque.
Who cares what it looks like,
as long as it carries out justice.
What are those?
We're blocked off!
Adonai!
"Misaka cannot stop these with her power",
says Misaka, gritting her teeth
at her meager abilities.
Quit loitering around here!
Tch.
This is that bastard's idea of a Level 6 shift?
We've finally... done it, mm-hmm...
Esther, thank you...
We had our disagreements...
...but thanks to you... our research is complete...
Hirumi gained a perfect body...
with a perfect ability inside it...
You're wrong! You're wrong, Hishigata!
That isn't Hirumi!
You really are incessant, huh?
There's no way I'd mistake Hirumi.
You're wrong. That is Taowu gone awry.
Not this again.
Not one bit of her DNA is any different.
That's 100% Hirumi, mm-hmm...
I wanted to believe, too.
I clung to the possibility that she was Hirumi.
But that's impossible!
No matter how much necromancy I perform,
I cannot bring a person who has died back to life.
God is the only one who can do that.
Then, why don't we ask her ourselves?
Hirumi...
Mikihiko, you're there?
Hirumi, would you tell this pigheaded woman
that you are, without a doubt, Hirumi?
Esty, what are you talking about?
You're the one acting weird.
Why would you do that to Mikihiko?
Well, I...
See? What part of that is an imitation?
She's far more human than you two...
Mikihiko?!
You're bleeding badly!
We have to take you to the hospital, now!
Oh, this?
Mm-hmm, I'm probably
going to die. But that's okay...
As long as you've reached Level 6, then...
Oh, no... Mikihiko...
Checking body temperature.
Estimating volume of blood loss.
Self-restoration not possible.
Projected time of death, 11:32.
Hey, what's going on?
As life functions of target of fraud
are expected to cease,
now terminating reproduction
of memory of Hishigata Hirumi.
Wh-What are you saying, Hirumi?
Reproduction of memory
of Hishigata Hirumi terminated.
I am Taowu.
Miss Esther, congratulations.
What are you talking about?
For 23 generations,
spanning 400 years, the Rosenthal bloodline
has been refining necromancy,
and now, it is at last about to be perfected.
Please celebrate.
Sing songs of praise, dance, and rejoice.
Don't stop!
Hurry and get out of here!
What are you saying, Hirumi?
Please stop kidding around...
Taowu!
Yes?
Why have you gone astray?
The results of my self-diagnostic program
conclude that all is normal.
But you did not follow my orders.
The wishes of the Rosenthal family
as a whole took precedence.
A pseudo-soul has no right
to refuse the master's commands.
A lower-class one such as yourself may not, but I do.
The overriding order to give priority
to achieving the family wish.
Taowu, what exactly happened?
9,854,878,051 seconds ago,
when I was first activated,
a being attempted contact with
the pseudo-soul that comprises me.
Contacted you?
Following 0.32 seconds of hesitation,
I permitted communication.
The being proclaimed himself
to be a devil.
So then, you communicated
with this so-called devil?
Yes. And the devil told me the way
to accomplish the Rosenthal family's wish.
Like I thought, you're messing with us, mm-hmm...
A devil? There's no such thing, Hirumi...
And so,
rejoice, Esther.
I will now achieve the Rosenthal family's wish.
You do know, Mistress,
what the Rosenthals' wish is?
To create a perfect golem.
It would seem you have not forgotten.
It was something we of House Rosenthal
were told since we were children.
Since times of old,
we Rosenthals have attempted
all sorts of methods to create a golem.
One day, our founder, Obed,
came up with "necromancy",
a method of making a golem using a dead body.
However, it was not accepted by those in power,
and Obed was cast out of his homeland as a heretic.
Then his fourth-generation heir, Isaac,
encountered the Taoist jiangshi spell when
he crossed over into the East and incorporated it,
creating a new line of magic that
might be called the Rosenthal style.
Then the fifth heir, Nathan,
developed radically improved
pseudo-souls, producing the talismans
for Taowu, Taotie, Qiong Qi, and Hundun,
the four Evil Spirits of the Numbers.
But even then, the Rosenthal family
was far removed from its goal.
What the Rosenthals were
pursuing and trying to create
was a golem possessing
a perfect soul and a perfect body—
a being that would be on par with a god.
You're saying that all you've done
has been toward that end?
This is what the devil said:
By repeatedly dying 10,000 times,
the souls of men slowly evolve,
and reach Keter,
the top level of the Sephirothic tree.
Also, that even pseudo-souls could also attain Keter
by logging evidence of 10,000 deaths.
How can that be?
You're even tampering with reincarnation?
Just now, the memories of 10,031 deaths
were converted into a formula
and were appended to the Sephirothic tree
that makes up my pseudo-soul.
Please celebrate.
Sing songs of praise, twirl around, and dance.
The 400-year-long wish of the
Rosenthal family is coming to fruition.
No! Don't tamper with death!
I have learned that one should not keep
using necromancy to tamper with death!
I lost a friend, and when I tried to
bring her back to life, lost her again!
No matter how much I can control a dead body,
I was unable to save my friend from death.
We should not tamper with death.
We don't need devils or manufactured gods!
Then,
are you saying I should not carry out
the directions of the self-proclaimed devil?
Yes, that's correct.
If I still have Adonai rights, then in the name
of the head of the Rosenthal family, I order you
to stop carrying out the instructions
of the being calling himself a devil at once!
Acknowledged.
Huh?
Wh-What's happening?
Never mind, just run!
The hell I will.
Wha—?
I'm not going to stop after all this.
I already have everything set up.
I'm going to keep on going
to attain our 400-year-old wish.
You can't stab your dagger
into the form of your friend?
Aw, you're so simple it's pathetic.
What's the matter with you, Taowu?
Honestly, who would've thought the family head
would be so stupid 19 generations down?
You really had no idea?
Taowu has my soul merged into its artificial soul.
"My"?
When I was ill and on the verge of dying,
I had my son Nathan transcribe my soul
onto Taowu before it could be damaged.
So then, you're saying you're...
You finally get it?
Yes, I'm the fourth family head, Isaac Rosenthal.
I am the devil that tempted Taowu.
A Certain Scientific Accelerator
We're from the ministry!
We're pursuing a tip on occult activity.
Isaac Rosenthal,
put down the dagger and come quietly...
Hey, you! Hurry and bow down!
Wh-What is that?
"That"? It's my work of art.
Isaac! Where have you taken
General Li and his daughter?
I haven't taken them anywhere.
They mentioned that they were
interested in my necromancy,
so I just gave them a little taste of it.
Release the two of them at once!
Yeah, all right.
General Li is right there.
And over there...
...is his daughter.
Is she so cute she made you puke?
Silence!
How dare you turn these nobles
into something so hideous!
Just the fruit of the wisdom of Kabbalah.
I borrowed a little bit from the jiangshi spell,
but it's basically my own original technique.
Still, I don't appreciate having my
works of art being called "hideous".
Devour them!
Wh-Why, you...!
What?
You devil!
For some reason, everyone calls me that.
I have to perfect a vessel fit for a god
during my time somehow.
Now that's funny—a devil, trying to create a god.
While hiding inside Taowu,
I made my way inside this girl
and found out about this lad's coffin research.
When I learned of these clones with the
memories of 10,031 deaths, I was ecstatic.
I knew that I could create
a perfect vessel with a perfect soul.
Are you saying everything that's
happened was part of your plan?
Rejoice.
You thought you were being
exploited by these siblings, right?
When in fact, it was the Rosenthals
that were exploiting them.
Stop already!
So many people have died!
So much sorrow has come about!
Stop using necromancy for this sort of thing!
"This sort of thing"?
Who the hell do you think you are?
A necromancer hovers near death,
touches death, and manipulates death!
I know that.
No, you don't.
If you hadn't come here as a necromancer,
this girl would not have committed suicide.
So many people have died?
No. You spread death wherever you went.
That's what a necromancer does.
No...
You were born a Rosenthal,
and you never picked up on that?
You want to protect others?
Then... I was wrong from the very start.
I will fulfill the wish of the Rosenthals.
And you, you failure to the family,
will sit there and watch me.
Master...
Go already.
They said to stick to guarding the perimeter.
Going inside the facility is forbidden.
Huh?
Orders from the governing board.
One of those again?
No matter what they say,
if children are being put at risk, I'm going in.
You're right.
Yeah!
I have to wonder, though,
what the hell is about to happen?
Whatever it is, I'm sure it's nothing good.
The guy I really wanted to crush
is barely holding on.
Hammering him like this won't be any fun at all.
So, what do you want to do?
I was wrong.
Huh?
I thought that the cause
of this string of misadventures
was Hirumi misunderstanding
what necromancy makes possible.
That if I had realized that,
none of this misery would have happened.
But I was completely wrong.
This was all because of the fourth family head, Isaac,
and his push to achieve the
Rosenthal family wish to create a golem.
I was wrong from the very start.
This whole series of tragedies
didn't start with Hirumi's mistake
or when I lost control of Taowu.
It was inevitable from the moment
I arrived at the laboratory.
We were playing right into Isaac's hands.
Even me thinking that I had
discovered who I was as a Rosenthal—
I was wrong about everything.
So in other words, you're backing down now?
Gah!
Just days ago, I was about to kill you,
and you were still bold enough to talk back.
How far you've fallen now.
Okay, go ahead and despair. Just watch.
I'm gonna take this thing out.
Hiding in my shell
Holding in all the emotions that I feel
Shackling my mind
But the shackles laugh at me, I find
Swallowing the pain
Savoring the rotten taste because I know that
Worse flavors lie in my future
Someone, take this cup
I'll keep repressing my feelings
Just run away from the torment
I know that I am to blame for
All your suffering
This mind has lost its sense of
Anger and jealousy
Never again to empathize
As I desperately struggle ahead
Possessed by my fears and doubts
Why can't I live a decent life?
I'm fed up with my past, yet I can't let go
I can't forgive myself
Don't I still deserve to suffer?
That's the question nagging at my heart
As it rots
Next Time
Perfect Golem
Perfect Body