Summer Memories.
Candy House
This way.
Fun House
Daddy!
Hibiki?
Thank goodness!
Don't wander off like that.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for bringing Hibiki back.
Thanks!
No need to thank me.
Instead...
Our story is starting, now let's walk together
so that these miraculous days never end.
Yes! Let's go now.
After our boundless dreams.
When I lay out the map of my future,
my heart starts throbbing, telling me to make my move.
Sometimes I'll inevitably end up
shedding a few tears,
but let's keep our eyes on the future.
The curiosity that's driving me
right at this moment is still a mystery,
but I do know that I want to find out the answers with you.
Our story is starting, now let's walk together
so that these miraculous days never end.
Yes! Let's go now.
Our harmony resounds throughout the world.
We'll never forget to wear our smiles
with everything that makes this moment shine.
Yes! Go my way.
We'll keep dreaming on and on.
Hanayashiro
It's so exciting to come to
a theme park with everyone!
It is!
Inoue, do you not like theme parks?
Well, I wouldn't say that, exactly...
Oh, right, there's a haunted house here.
After all you've been through with Amami,
you're still scared of the fake stuff?
Shut up!
Entrance
Hanayashiro
Theme park!
She's really psyched.
It looks so fun!
Huh? Um...
Shh. Don't make eye contact.
Hey!
You got us the tickets, right, Amami?
Oh, yes.
Someone my dad works with gave them to us.
He told me this theme park
holds memories for us.
Hello!
Hello, hello, hello.
Knock it off!
Her patience ran out!
Why are you here, Yamada's brother?!
Oh, I had nothing to do, so I tagged along.
No one invited you!
Stuff like that is what
makes my brother so great!
That wasn't a compliment!
By the way, everyone.
Why aren't you more lightly dressed?
How can you say that so casually?!
But it's summer!
And you're high school girls!
You've gotta do the things
you shouldn't while you're still...
young!
She's about to do something she shouldn't!
Now, now, now...
Let's all just have fun here together.
Yeah, sure. We don't really have
time to waste on him, anyway.
We did invite an actual special guest, after all.
That's right. Look!
Ta-da!
I did agree to do this...
Bound Soul?
Well, it's just an audio and video feed, though.
And while we were at it,
we asked the roll-call samurai
and the gal ghost to help.
Roll-call Samurai
and Gal Ghost
We're all going to a theme park.
Let the other ghosts know.
I think quite a few of them are here.
Huh?
Greetings.
Hey, girlie.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because knowing you, you'd just
stress out and make a fuss over
both the living and the dead.
It was just a little surprise.
Someone's a lot more
surprised than you, though.
Don't worry! They're all people you know...
That's not the problem!
Blank.
Yoshida Yoshiki has three days until the deadline
for his self-written comic manuscript...
Yet he's plagued with writer's block.
The white page seems to expand into eternity
as the blinding sunlight reflects off its surface...
Summer is here!
This so-called theme park is quite a strange place.
What's the matter? You spooked?
M-Most assuredly not!
There's nothing to worry about. This is a fun place.
The roll-call samurai's totally spooked.
You think he'll freak out in the haunted house,
even though he's a ghost?
Barbarian cavalry!
That's what he's scared of?
You dork!
They're just machines.
You're so behind the times, samurai.
Hanayashiro
What is this?! That's how they work now?!
Quick, put in some money!
Um, okay...
Look at all the options!
This is so cool!
One more, one more!
They're mass-producing ghost stickers?!
Looks like you're the one
who's behind the times now!
Get outta the shot!
Hey, wanna ride that?
Yeah!
Roller Coaster
Oh, this is—
Don't say it.
I get it! A ghost is riding with you!
I said not to say it!
If you can't deal with this much,
how will you handle that?
Wow! Everyone's riding with us?
Roller Coaster
What a weirdo! She's screaming
before the ride's even started!
That was fun!
It made me a little dizzy, though.
Someone untangle me!
House of Mirrors
If someone lifts their skirt here,
I'll get a 360-degree panty shot!
Whoops...
Dead end?
Hello?
My name is Mary.
I've got a 360-degree view of you in here.
Lady Amami's riding with the Bound Soul...
Should I tilt it downward some more?
No, this is fine. I can see the view well.
Still, you do have some unusual friends,
inviting ghosts to a theme park.
Yes. They really surprised me.
Do you come here often?
Apparently, I did when I was a little girl,
but I don't really remember it.
I see.
Oh, right. She said she'd come along, too.
What? Who?
It sounded fun, so here I am.
I'm glad to have you!
Haunted         House
It's finally time for the haunted house!
Let's make sure we're all set.
Tissues for Inoue, check!
Tissues, check!
Protective charms, check!
Um...
Then let's head in!
I wonder what kinds of ghosts will pop out.
Stop scaring me...
With a big group like this, though...
It might not be that scary.
Oh, come on...
That was scarier than any ghost.
Our true enemy is one of our own.
You scare way too easily, Inoue.
I wanna go home...
Wow, they did a good job with this.
To spend your entire existence sticking
your neck out and scaring people...
Noritama?
Six...
Seven...
Eight... Nine...
I'm missing one!
Um, here!
Plastic
It's an unbreakable plate for lunch boxes.
Please take it!
She fixed the problem!
Why are you sticking right behind me?
Hey, we're in a haunted house, after all.
Hey, she looks like you!
She does not.
It's the Flame-Haired Messiah!
Look, look, look!
I don't look like that, you idiot!
The Last   Room
Well, this is the last room
of the haunted house, but...
The thing that's surprised me most of all so far is...
Amami only getting scared by the fake ghosts.
Man, what a blast!
We're just getting started, bro!
By the way, Amami, you said this
place held memories for you.
Yep! We totally are!
Where to next?
Somewhere really explosive!
Oh, right.
I don't remember it too well myself,
but I got lost here when I was little, and...
Oh, is he lost?
That was timely.
Okay!
I'll go find a staff member!
You can stay here and play with us while we wait.
Have we met before?
Yes... Yes, I understand.
House of Mirrors
We've found the parents. I'll take him there now.
That's great.
Thanks for coming back.
He must've felt so helpless,
being lost and all alone.
All alone?
What is it?
Candy House
Thank you!
No need to thank me.
Instead...
Come back with your friends and play with me.
Seriously, what is it?
Oh, it's nothing.
I came back with my friends to play.
This Way
Haunted House
Let the panda take your picture!
Memorial Photos
Hanayashiro
Everyone line up!
Roll-call Samurai, let Gal come in closer!
Everyone squeeze towards the middle.
And Hanako's getting covered up.
Ogawa, if you'll kneel down...
Huh?
Hanayashiro
Okay!
We're all ready.
P-P-Panda! I'm a panda!
Hanayashiro
Everyone say, "Panda drank some water!"
Click!
Hanayashiro
Dad, I'm home.
Welcome back, Hibiki.
Good evening!
Hello, everyone!
Time for today's big climax!
A sleepover at Amami's house!
U-Um, the boys...
Don't mind us.
We'll sleep in the yard!
Uh, going home isn't an option?
Nope!
How could I miss the chance
to have a summer sleepover
with a bunch of young high school gir—
Bro!
Thanks for having us!
You're welcome to stay over,
but are you sure our house will do?
Of course!
Are you cool with this?
Frankly, I think this place'll be
way scarier than a haunted house.
O-Of course. Sleeping over at
a friend's house is perfectly normal.
Inoue!
Seriously, stop being so dramatic!
Wanna do something?
How about a word game?
Sounds good!
It... It does?
Okay! I'll start then!
Umbrella!
Aquatic snail!
Level Five.
East Asian Law.
Winking.
Girls' Bathroom.
Mt. Kilimanjaro.
Oil Candle.
Extremely late at night.
This is our complete theme
park group, and then some.
While I'm in here doing this,
other students are probably out
enjoying their summer to the fullest.
Like going to theme parks,
and maybe even having sleepovers afterward?
I'm so jealous...
No, I swore to dedicate my youth to manga!
I have to finish in time for the summer event
so the whole world can witness its greatness!
I'll try for real next year.
Um, everyone...
What should we have for dinner?
Oh, I'll help you cook!
Me too.
I know! Make Inoue's grandma's fried eggs!
Don't decide for everyone!
That was great!
Sure was!
I never thought I'd get to eat a dinner
made by beautiful high school girls.
I'm deeply moved!
Get back out in the yard!
Actually, the gal ghost's mother
taught me the recipes for all of these.
Wow, they're really delicious.
Please, it was nothing.
Cut it out!
Your fried eggs were great, too, Inoue.
I-It was really noffing thpethia—
That came out totally wrong!
Well, now that dinner's done,
wanna go for another summer favorite
and light some fireworks?
I brought my yukata! What about you all?
Mine's ready!
You told me to bring mine, so I did.
Yeah, got mine.
High school girls in yukatas?
Hang on, let me get my camera—
Forget the yard! Just go home!
This one.
No, this one!
By the way...
Don't the ghosts always come to
whoever's sleeping in the middle?
Don't say stuff like that!
Sheesh! Let's just go to sleep!
Okay.
Until she said that, I'd forgotten
this place was packed with ghosts.
Honestly, don't scare me...
Can't sleep?
D-Don't worry about me.
I'll get sleepy eventually.
Um...
Wh-What?
My dad told me
that when I was little, and I couldn't sleep,
he would always hold my hand like this.
Amami...
I can't sleep like this.
S-Sorry!
I'm so nervous, my hands are shaking...
What are you guys doing?
Try counting sheep?
Should I warm up some milk?
Everyone?
You're all awake?
Stretching can also help.
They say light exercise helps, too.
Did you bring your wooden sword to bed?
It's to protect myself from that idiot.
How about a lullaby?
Or have the ghosts scare her silly until she faints!
A-Anything but that!
Just kidding.
Well, we can always pull an all-nighter together.
We might have to.
That could be fun, too.
Thank you, everyone.
What are you thanking us for?
Yeah, she's the one who should be...
Unbelievable.
I was all set to stay up all night.
Too bad.
I hope we'll all continue to spend our days
together, one by one, just like this.
I-I'm sorry, Inoue!
I held your hand all night...
What the heck? Darn it, now I'm blushing, too!
Girl on girl?
Aaaaaaaaw, yeah baby!
Wow!
Mysterious fluffballs!
Wow! Wow! Wow!
We won't tell the adults!
Have you noticed it? Do you feel it?
See with the mind's eye.
I want to get possessed and be loved.
An after-school sensation.
Common sense means nothing to high-school girls
with a "que sera, sera" attitude.
Out of our way, ghosts!
Abracadablovelove!
Wow! Wow!
You should join us too!
Smile! Smile! Smile!
Let's have a blast!
We only have one chance to be young,
so we should enjoy it to the fullest.
Evil spirits, vengeful spirits, all welcome.
Yeah!
Nothing's impossible in this world.
There are all sorts of strange events and phantoms.
Yeah!
Come what may, we'll never back down.
What does it mean to be ordinary?
Yeah?
If only the gods know the answer,
Yeah!
they can keep it to themselves!
After all...
Ignorance is bliss.