K & C Pharmaceutical Corporation
Japan
The target appears to be heading south.
Footprints were found 400 meters south of here.
All vehicles are searching the area.
We will keep you updated
as more information comes in.
Director...
Our surveillance cameras alone
can't cover it any further.
Make use of government and police cameras, too.
Damn it!
This is too slow...
Way too slow!
The target may have left the
research facility's surveillance area.
It may take time for street-
surveillance cameras to find her.
If the situation changes, contact me immediately.
Over.
Roger that.
Director...
Could the target have possibly jumped even farther?
Why do you think I've been limiting
her calorie intake during meals?
We'll certainly get some good data today.
I want to see how far the Queen
can go on that meager amount.
Yes! Here we go!
Ugh... Not again.
This is why I requested a bigger budget!
Target located on the national highway,
500 meters southeast.
Since it's a street-surveillance camera,
this is the best it can do.
All vehicles, create a perimeter
around the target's current location.
Car #4, proceed directly to the point.
She may have one more jump in her,
but she won't get very far.
Yes! Analysis complete!
Sending coordinates!
Car #4 here.
Minnie C is heading toward the target.
Roger that.
You can wait where you are.
So cold...
Is this how all of the outside world is?
Where do you think you're going,
Red Queen?
Don't come near me!
Stop being stubborn,
and return to where it is nice and warm.
No!
Everyone is waiting for you.
Open!
You see?
You have already exhausted your energy.
Wonderland is the only place you belong.
Who's there?
I see.
#106.
She appears to be resisting.
That's the Red Queen for you.
I'm impressed she had that much power left in her.
Not quite.
Huh?
This is
someone else?
Jump.
Visualize the largest town you can.
Go there and cause as much commotion as you can.
Who are you?
We'll meet again.
What the...?
What happened?
I don't know!
Perhaps a lightning strike.
We'll switch to another channel and restart it.
Lightning?
All right! Success!
Restoring visuals.
Where's the target?
No sight of her.
Nothing here, either.
Tachibana here.
Capture of the Red Queen has failed.
Someone interfered.
Who was it?
I don't know.
A female ability-user I have never seen.
She told the Red Queen
to go to a large town and cause a commotion.
To all vehicles.
All cars, except #4,
expand search to the metropolitan area.
Roger that.
Do whatever you can to pick up her trail.
All vehicles have changed course.
They're heading south, toward the metro area.
Director, further pursuit is impossible.
Why?
The bridge...
The bridge... is gone.
All vehicles, return to the research facility.
Minnie C, as soon as you arrive, report in detail.
Over.
Go to a large town and cause a commotion, huh?
Alice,
having drifted in space for a long time,
began to feel a bit dizzy.
When she found out she was
capable of walking again,
she felt relieved.
"If I can get to the top of that hill,"
thought Alice,
"I'll have a much better view of the garden."
The Red Queen Escapes
Sorry to wake you so early.
If you're tired, you can get a bit more rest.
Okay.
Target located.
She's in Shinjuku.
Cameras spotted her at 4:57 AM.
Send the footage of the target to me.
Roger that.
New Message
QXE
Indeed,
that certainly is a large town...
Here is your order.
Truly, you do fantastic work!
I was right to ask you for this, Kashimura.
Is that so?
That's a lot.
It's to thank you.
Consider it a token of my gratitude.
I accepted this job because
it was a personal request.
I won't get buddy-buddy with you people.
Hey, old man!
Who do you think you're address—
Shut up!
Sorry about that.
He can be a bit hot-headed.
I'll accept my fee and nothing more.
Kashimura...
You really are a strange one, aren't you?
Thank you for coming!
Sawaki Industries
COMPREHENSIVE & SUPERIOR INFORMATION
FREE INFORMATION DESK
Welcome.
Oh, Kashimura...
Haven't seen you in a while.
Cigarettes. The usual.
You really should quit smoking.
It'll kill you someday!
Shut it.
Hey, uh, you know...
I'm kinda worried about that girl.
Would you take her to the cops?
She's been there for like three hours.
A child shouldn't be in Kabuki Town.
Call them yourself.
I called, but they wouldn't do anything.
They don't trust foreigners.
DONATION BOX
Your Cooperation Is Appreciated
Check Screen and Touch to Continue
Are you 20 or older?
I Am 20 or Older
After verifying your age, you may still be asked for ID
Ask the owner to, then.
I can't!
DONATION BOX
Your Cooperation Is Appreciated
The owner hates cops.
Also, he's been stealing donation money.
DONATION BOX
Your Cooperation Is Appreciated
He's totally crooked.
Hey, little girl.
You aren't supposed to touch the merchandise.
If you're lost, why don't I take you home?
Have you and I met before?
Kashimura Zouroku.
Born June 19, 1943.
One granddaughter named Sanae.
She's been at training camp for her
high school club since yesterday.
But I don't know what "club"
and "training camp" mean.
Guess I was wrong.
But you don't seem like a bad person.
Hey, you!
How would you like to make a deal with me?
A deal?
If you agree, I'll grant any wish you desire!
What the heck is this?
Something out of a comic book?
Sorry, but I don't know much
about that kind of stuff.
Huh?
I... I get it.
You're making fun of me, right?
I'm not making fun of you.
I just have no clue what you're saying.
Forget it!
What on earth was that?
She disappeared, Kashimura!
Hey, what's going on?
LAND FOR SALE
No idea.
This is bad.
My power's weakening.
I'll have to go with the guy from before...
Thank you for your patronage.
Hey, you...
You really won't make a deal with me?
How did you get in this car?
Don't worry about that.
What's your name, little girl?
Where is your home?
I have no home.
C-Come on!
Make a deal with me.
If you do, I'll grant any wish you desire.
Is this the attitude you take when
you ask someone for something?
If you have something to say,
have the right attitude—
Hesitate, and you'll die.
What?
Look ahead.
What was that all about?
Just get out of here!
It'll come back!
Damn it!
I missed...
Hey, Sis, don't you think this is going a bit far—
Shoot, Yonaga!
But...
Don't argue!
Right now!
O-Okay...
No need for mercy.
I-I'll have to try my best to miss.
Just shoot right into it!
What the heck is that?
The sisters who followed me.
The younger can call a bow,
while the older can call anything with a chain.
Like the wrecking ball before, and that bike, too.
There's no chain on a bike.
Yes, there is.
The bike chain!
Don't slow down just yet.
They'll be back on us again soon!
Ow...
Hey, why did you stop?
Get out.
You know those two girls, right?
Don't drag a stranger into your problems.
I don't need that.
I think I like you.
Darn it!
We're too conspicuous...
I missed again!
Yonaga, hurry up and shoot again!
O-Open.
T-Try to miss.
Try to miss...
Wh-What the hell are you doing?
I'll drive!
Hey! Stop!
P-Please stop, Sana!
You did it, Yonaga!
Sana...
What was that?
Should we call the police?
No, I'd say an ambulance.
What the hell is going on?
Foreigners?
Are they filming a movie?
Was that CG?
You can't escape now, Red Queen!
They ordered you to follow me here,
you knuckleheaded sisters?
Kn-Knuckleheaded?!
Calm down, Sis.
Sana, let's return to the research facility.
I... I know they conduct some unpleasant tests...
B-But we can't live in the outside world!
That's a lie!
I won't be fooled anymore,
and I'm done being a lab rat.
I'll crush that place with my own two hands.
S-Sana...
You don't know anything about the outside world!
Yonaga, shoot her!
Huh?
I won't go back.
Sana!
Sana...
I'm sorry!
You think that pointing that
dangerous thing at people is all right?
Wh-What are you doing—
That's what I'd like to know.
Ow, ow...
What are you doing, and in the middle of the city?
Do you know how many
people could have been hurt
by one wrong move in your
nonsensical game of tag?
Take a good look at what you've done!
Do you think you're playing a video game?!
Well?!
And as for you two!
Y-Yes?
Do you two have a beef with me or something?
N-No...
N-Not at all...
Listen to me.
This world has boundaries you must respect.
I don't know what you three have been through,
but old folks and children walk around these parts.
Your actions could have killed someone.
Listen up.
The police will be here soon.
You're gonna have to step up
and atone for what you've done.
What do you say?
Y-Yes, sir!
Yotsuya Police Station
Okay, why don't you two give me your names?
Now, will you tell me your name?
I don't mind telling you, but...
Are you hungry?
You expect me to believe that nonsense?!
Plenty of witnesses were at the scene.
Aren't they telling you the same "nonsense" I am?
All right, why don't you explain these?
These show you leaving Sawaki's office.
That incident is somehow connected, isn't it?
You think mobsters can produce
wrecking balls from thin air?
I'm asking the questions here!
I was only there to deliver an order.
And that exchange caused all this, didn't it?!
Sergeant...
May I have a moment?
What is it?
What?
Was that cream puff good?
Uh-huh.
Then, will you tell me now?
The older twin's name is Asahi,
and the younger is Yonaga.
And what's your name?
The older twin's name is Asahi,
and the younger is Yonaga.
And what's your name?
The older twin's name is Asahi,
and the younger is Yonaga.
And what's your name?
Can you slow it just as she disappears?
Yes, sir.
That's impossible!
It's true.
She disappeared right before my eyes.
The footage hasn't been altered in any way.
What about the twins?
There was a man calling himself their sponsor, so...
You sent them with him?
Well...
They may be children, but you know
how much trouble they caused!
I was following orders from the higher-ups.
What?
I was told not to pursue this case further.
You're free to go.
You're being released due to lack of evidence.
Your car's in the lot out back.
You want me to drive a wrecked car?
It's definitely my car, but the repairs were done fast.
Is this a free service?
We just came out and found it this way.
You found it this way?
That's right...
The car and crash scene have
been completely restored!
I'm the one who wants to ask
what the hell happened, and how.
Wrong way on a one-way street,
ignoring a red light,
speeding, property damage...
Normally, we'd hold you overnight
to get the story out of you.
But there's no evidence at all.
Image Data Not Found.
Huh?
That's weird...
Image Data Not Found.
We checked all the security
cameras in that area, too.
Image Data Not Found.
But nothing was on them.
Why are the pictures gone?
Several reports were filed.
Image Data Not Found.
Isn't this crazy?
Huge accident
Image Data Not Found.
Isn't this crazy?
Huge accident
Image Data Not Found.
Isn't this crazy?
Huge accident
There's no picture...
Isn't this crazy?
Huge accident
There's no picture...
Isn't this crazy?
Huge accident
There's no picture...
Isn't this crazy?
Huge accident
There's no picture...
Isn't this crazy?
Huge accident
There's no picture...
Isn't this crazy?
Huge accident
There's no picture...
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
Huge accident
There's no picture...
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
There's no picture...
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
There's no picture...
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
There's no picture...
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
There's no picture...
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
There's no picture...
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
I'm serious!
There's no picture...
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
I'm serious!
There's no picture...
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
I'm serious!
There's no picture...
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
I'm serious!
There's no picture...
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
I'm serious!
There's no picture...
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
I'm serious!
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
I'm serious!
I saw it, too!
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
I'm serious!
I saw it, too!
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
I'm serious!
I saw it, too!
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
I'm serious!
I saw it, too!
Seems fake...
Huh? It was there
a second ago!
I'm serious!
I saw it, too!
Seems fake...
a second ago!
I'm serious!
I saw it, too!
Seems fake...
a second ago!
I'm serious!
I saw it, too!
Seems fake...
a second ago!
I'm serious!
I saw it, too!
Seems fake...
Huh? What the...
And many witnesses were on the scene.
You sure you uploaded it?
I did!
shinjuku wrecking ball girl accident
But we didn't even find skid marks.
Huh? Why isn't anything coming up?
Nothing at the parking lot you said was destroyed,
and no giant hole in the road.
That's impossible.
It means you've been exonerated.
Also...
Forget what happened today.
Got that?
Your fine's been dropped.
Just go home.
Is he the man who was with the Red Queen?
Yes.
Kashimura Zouroku
What should we do?
Keep the old man, Kashimura,
under surveillance, too?
No.
Judging from the circumstances,
he just seems to be caught up in this mess.
For the time being, let's prioritize
the Red Queen's capture.
Feel free to eat all you like.
NEW CARS
OLD CARS
BUY
SELL
SUZUKI
Huh? Are you serious?
Yeah.
All right, let me take a look...
Do you really want to get
rid of this car, Kashimura?
Yeah.
But you took such good care of it.
I see no reason to scrap it.
Some weird stuff happened.
Be careful with it.
Right...
Hey, it's me.
Sorry.
I ran into a little trouble.
Sorry, but you two need
to take care of things today.
Give me a call if something comes up.
After I grab some food in Shinjuku, I'll head home.
Welcome!
Beer, mutton stir-fry, and fried bread.
Coming up.
And I'll be using the ashtray.
Help yourself.
Your beer.
Thanks.
Don't they have cream puffs?
You pop up when and where you like, huh?
Where'd you come from this time?
Can I drink some of this?
This isn't for kids to drink.
Hey, bring me some orange juice.
Okay, you got it!
Well?
What do you want?
This is no place for a kid to hang around.
I don't want any more trouble.
Dreams of Alice.
More comic book stuff?
That's what we're called.
You can think of us as people
with supernatural abilities.
I don't know how such a thing comes to be, exactly.
But by using these visions called
"Mirror Gates" as intermediaries,
we have the ability to materialize
any one thing we imagine.
Chains, bows, arrows...
Some people can fix things, too.
And that's the power you used to drive my car.
That's right!
It was my first time driving,
but it wasn't yours, so I—
Here's your orange juice.
And mutton stir-fry,
with Chinese onions, and fried bread.
Are you done talking?
If you are, then please go home.
My food will get cold.
I-I'm not done...
I've decided that I like you!
I'm going to make you my servant,
Kashimura Zouroku!
You'd better be happy!
Don't stand on the chair.
And keep your voice down in the restaurant!
Yes, sir.
Have you eaten anything yet?
Huh?
In the convenience store, you were staring at food.
When did you last eat?
A-About three days ago...
I'm fine.
This long is nothing.
Hey!
I need to place another order.
Sure!
C-Can I really eat this?
I don't have any money.
Well, I do.
Wow, check that out!
Is she training for an eating contest or something?
So good! So good!
I didn't know food was this
good in the outside world!
How many servings are you gonna eat?
I can't help it!
Activating the Mirror Gate takes
a tremendous amount of energy.
It makes me hungry.
Come to think of it, those twins were eating, too.
Hold your chopsticks right!
Chopsticks?
You mean these things?
You don't know how to use them?
Lay off.
It's my first time outside the research facility.
Earlier, you said something about making a deal.
What do you want me to do?
Thank you very much!
I want
to crush the research facility.
Research facility?
There are many other Dreams of Alice, just like me.
They're locked up there,
and awful things are done to them.
But even though I escaped,
I couldn't do anything alone.
I want your help.
When I looked inside your head,
I saw that you're a good person.
I want to help my friends!
Please!
Asano Beer
Shanghai Home Cooking
Shanghai Xiaochi
Thank you very much!
Come with me.
We're going somewhere else.
It's too bright...
Don't just stand there. We'll get separated.
Remember what I told you?
This is no place for a kid to hang around.
R-Right!
Hey, Bro! How about visiting our cabaret club?
Hey, what kind of shop is that?
When he said "Bro," did he mean you?
Just shut up and walk.
Hey, wouldn't it be easier in your car?
The car creeped me out, so I got rid of it.
Creeped you out? Why's that?
Would you just stop talking?
Hanazono Shrine
What's your name?
Did you not hear me?
You told me to stop talking.
Well, now you can.
What's your name?
Sana.
And your last name?
I don't know.
I don't remember anything
before the research facility.
I don't even know where I came from.
And "Sana" is just the name
that Asahi and Yonaga gave me.
Asahi and Yonaga?
The twins who chased us.
They were the only ones who called me by name.
Yay! I got "very good luck"!
Ugh, I got "very bad luck."
Wow, I've never seen that before!
Easy for you to say.
It'll be fine.
I got "very good luck," so we can share half of each!
Only for a little while.
For a little while,
I'll give you food and a place to stay.
But during that time, you'll help me with my work.
"He who does not work, neither shall he eat."
Okay, that's fine!
I knew you were a good—
Show some respect for your elders!
Don't get the wrong idea.
I won't baby you!
And one other thing.
Don't use that weird power again.
Why not?
With that, I can do anything.
You don't want me to grant your wish?
Earlier, you said you looked inside my head, right?
Y-Yeah...
So what?
And you knew that I have a granddaughter, too.
See? Amazing, right?
And you really don't understand what that means?
You said you can do anything
you can imagine, right?
Y-Yeah...
Then try using that power right here.
Here?
You can, right?
Create chains or a wrecking ball or whatever.
You'd cover this whole place in blood.
You get it?
Someone with a power like that
mentioned a family member
I hadn't even spoken of,
and demanded that I make a deal.
You blackmailed me.
I... I didn't mean to...
Even if you didn't,
some people may see it differently.
I have no interest in any deals or wishes.
The only people anyone needs to
think about are those within reach.
Listen up!
I hate crooked stuff!
Listen.
That research facility and its experiments
are problems for grown-ups to solve.
First, you need to fix that
twisted temperament of yours.
If you value your friends,
they're all you need to think about.
What?
Nothing.
You really don't know how to talk to people at all...
Yes, it's me.
Understood...
I'll head that way with the data now.
Yes, see you soon.
I'm sleepy...
Not much longer. Hang in there.
'Kay...
This Wonderland created by the Red Queen
is underneath the research facility.
It's these children's playground, brought to life
by randomly rewriting this space.
She made this?
I can't believe it...
Next, please look at this.
What are those things?
Are they alive?
Of course they are.
She made them from her favorite picture books.
The cause of this is unclear.
The space inside is intricately warped
to be many thousands of times
the size it originally was.
And it's still growing.
Is there anything here you do understand?
I can only say we're studying it now.
So what will you do, then?
There are two problems.
The first is that the one possessing
this immense power is a child.
If she remains in the outside world
in a psychologically unstable state,
the existence of the research facility
could become public knowledge.
And the other is that the loss of the Red Queen,
a valuable sample of this ability,
is a massive detriment for us...
no, for the country itself.
And what do you intend to do?
Her capture will be conducted in secrecy.
But if an accident should bring
this incident into public awareness...
Coercion?
I would like you to recognize the search
for the Red Queen as a state of emergency
as soon as possible.
Hey.
Hey, wake up.
Are we there?
Not yet.
Follow me.
Here we are.
This is your house?
Where I work.
Thanks to you, I didn't get any work done today.
So I had to let the youngins handle it.
But I've gotta check how the prep is going, at least.
Come in and wait a bit.
Hey, is this...
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
For bouquet
For
Friday's
Event
Wow...
Well, I'm a florist.
A florist.
I specialize in arrangements
for events and gifts, though.
Events?
Gifts?
Th-This flower is...
Um...
You know...
What is it?
Uh...
It's called... block?
No, that's wrong. What was it?
Th-This flower is called ph-phlox.
In the language of flowers...
Uh...
Take care, sir!
Y-Yeah.
Why is Sawaki all dressed up today?
Well, you know...  For this.
Huh?
He's gonna cut off a finger?
You numbskull, it's for his girlfriend.
His once-in-a-lifetime proposal.
And he's bringing her a flower
arrangement by Kashimura.
What?
So, that old guy this afternoon
really was a florist?
Kashimura Floral
H
Sorry about running so late.
Where are we going?
Home.
We have to walk more?
You aren't even walking.
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Kashimura
Zouroku
Sanae
Don't space out there.
Head upstairs.
Take off your shoes.
No one's using this room right now.
It's a little dusty, but you'll have to make do.
Turn in for the night.
I'll get you some fresh clothes.
Clothes?
They're my granddaughter's,
so they'll be big on you,
but you can—
Zouroku...
Cream puff...
Hidden beneath this scab
Are a great many things all working in unison
So please hold on just a little bit longer
Because I'll change myself starting from there
When do I start
To truly become myself?
Let's go meet the people who deserve my affection
We'll find them scattered across the world
I want to learn so much about them
One person, another person, more and more people
Three, four, five, six, the number rises and rises
Finding out the truth
Can sometimes be painful, but...
The world will keep moving
On and on, forever and ever
Even far into the future
Remaining unchanged
Next Episode
Dreams of Alice
Dreams of Alice.