What are you saying?
I'm not human, you know.
I'll cause a lot of trouble for you.
For Sanae, too.
So what?
No matter what you are,
in tough times, you should be with others.
You left because you wanted
to see what was outside, right?
Then do that.
Don't go back on your word.
I hate crooked stuff, you know.
Y-You must be an idiot!
I see.
Sorry I'm late.
I'm here to save you.
I'm Cabinet Information Research Office
Secret Service agent Ichijou Shizuku.
We'll be taking you two with us!
Mirror, mirror, on the wall
I want to change this world
The streetlight brightens up the night
And brings forth a sea of light
That reaches far into the distance
I dream upon a restless star
As I wait for the night to end
So I can continue searching for the future
The curtains covering a new stage
slowly part
as I wake up
Wonder drive! Let's start running now!
Wonder drive! To the world ahead of us!
Uncertainty, hesitation, and confusion
Just throw it all away!
Wonder drive! Keep charging along this path
Replace that clock's rhythm with your own
We are walking along a road
No one has yet dreamed of
Mirror, mirror, on the wall
I want to change this world
A Home to Return to
Um, I will now read back your order.
Three stewed Hamburg steak B meals,
four mozzarella pizzas, two mushroom risottos,
three herb and chicken salads,
and three orders of focaccia.
Is that correct?
Yes, and the drink bar for four, please.
Drink bar for four.
Okay. Thank you for your order.
Yes?
What?!
Yes, the container holding
the Red Queen has been stolen.
I believe the thief possessed a Dream of Alice.
Surely not the one from before...
I strongly suggest that you retreat,
former Second Lieutenant Minnie C. Tachibana.
I will not let you have her.
The Red Queen is my last...
Operation 3-1.
#590, operation 1-8.
Different types of cards?!
#51!
#15!
That should stop her for a while.
Is either one of you hurt?
You are just the best, Ichijou!
God, you're so awesome...
I wish I could've seen you
kicking ass from down below!
voice
Quiet, Yamada.
What's happening around us?
Oh, right. Sorry.
No sign of the enemy within
one kilometer of the target ship.
The Mirror Gate is still responding. Please be careful.
Just count on Yamada Noriko's special,
voice
new and improved, pan-global,
Ichijou-detection system!
voice
Refrain from saying useless things.
The annoying girl is Yamada,
the team director of technology.
voice
I don't understand it all, but...
She takes base station data from
geostationary satellites and cell phones
to form a system that locates Dreams
of Alice, or more specifically, Ichijou...
Really, she's just my stalker.
Sta...
She always shows up at my destinations before I do.
At first, I wondered whose agent she was.
How rude!
Call me your unwelcome little sister.
Or at least your fan!
She's the best hacker around, but she's also like this.
It did take a while to enable it
to detect anyone other than her,
so locating the escort was delayed.
I'm sorry that you had to go through
something so terrifying, Sana.
Now, let's get you home.
voice
Ma'am! Incoming!
#12!
Operation 3-6.
#21.
They can turn invisible, just as our intel said.
Both of you, stay behind me.
#576 through #580.
Operation 2-4. Add paralysis attribute.
I remember now.
The day of the typhoon,
you were the one who got in my way.
Just what are you?
How are you able to use so many types of cards?
Everyone should be restricted to one.
Perhaps it's just talent?
But... But this is all I have!
#12!
Darling,
please lend me just a bit more strength.
Yamada!
Y-Yes, Ma'am!
Don't bring the helicopter any closer.
Stand by overhead!
Get too close, and you'll be knocked down.
voice
Sana.
Can you hear me? This is Ichijou.
Oh...
voice
Take this. #66.
Use that to replenish your energy.
voice
What is this?
It's candy.
It's very sweet, so eat it slowly.
There's water, too.
voice
I'm going to find a way to stop that woman.
When you get your powers back, take Kashimura and escape.
voice
Do you remember the helicopter that was above?
If you can reach it,
the scary people won't follow anymore.
You'll win!
Okay, got it.
Hey...
It'll be okay.
You said it'll be okay, so it'll be okay.
I see.
I'll be the one to save you this time!
Hey, I can't open this.
You open it.
At eight o'clock!
No... ten o'clock...
The second row of containers!
No, wait...
Um, I mean...
voice
Calm down, Yamada.
I'm sorry, but there's still a large margin of error.
voice
I know!
If I tell myself you're the target, my motivation
and accuracy will exponentially increase!
voice
That's enough of that!
#381!
voice
She stays hidden,
while the invisible arms strike with precision.
Where is she?
Ma'am!
Yamada... Where is she?
Oh, right!
Stay calm...
I found her!
At three o'clock, the seventh row of containers!
I'm such a genius!
This is
the end for you.
I really don't like it
when I have to get serious.
#1!
There it is!
#2!
#3!
I hate using the single digits.
I can't pull punches with them.
Just what are you?!
All right!
Let's do it!
#12.
Operation 1-8.
Stay out
of our way!
Didn't I tell you...
I can't pull punches?
Former Second Lieutenant Minnie C. Tachibana,
you are under immediate arrest for abduction
of a minor, assault, and actual bodily harm.
This is a magical storeroom
that some maid in a cartoon used.
It showed up one night,
after I'd fallen asleep with the TV on.
666 weapons and 13 grimoires are stored inside.
I'm basically a human weapon.
Ridiculous, isn't it?
I don't believe
these are things that appear for
the purpose of granting our wishes.
I'm out of energy...
How long have I been alone?
Long ago, I realized that the
gears had slipped off-track.
But still, I am unable to stop.
What am I to do?
To think that I must... go on living.
Tomorrow, the next day, and even beyond that.
I am sorry, darling...
I'm sorry that I am still alive.
I'm so sorry!
Hey, Zouroku.
What?
I think I'm going to cause more trouble for people,
just by existing in the outside world.
Even if I don't,
I'll probably still make lots of mistakes.
I don't know why I was made this way, in this form,
but someone made me.
Within this world,
someone wanted me to
do something in human form.
You know, Zouroku...
I want to be human!
Or if not human, I want to be something more real.
I don't know how to say it, but...
I want to learn lots more!
About humans, about you and Sanae,
and about how much there is to this world.
I want to eat lots of delicious things!
By doing that,
I want to become something more real.
And one day, I want to find out why I was made,
and why I'm not human—
I'm hungry.
Someday, you'll understand it all.
Yeah!
And my hair...
I can do it myself, but I want Sanae to do it for me.
Ask her when we get back.
Okay!
That's a nice view...
Pretty amazing.
Isn't it?
I can do anything!
Thank you very much.
Yes, that's right. The situation's changed.
Dispose of all data relating to Dreams of Alice.
And until you hear from me again...
Kitou Kouichi, correct?
That's right.
Oh, pardon me...
I'm with the Yotsuya police.
voice
I'm really sorry about this, old man.
Given the commotion this ended up causing,
life will probably be noisy for a while.
You might as well give up.
Hmph!
Well, on that note...
Where are you now?
I don't know.
I'm in the sky.
voice
Well, that's fine.
Just try not to let people see you or take pictures.
voice
It'd make my life hell.
Hear that, Sana?
voice
B-But it wasn't me...
This wasn't on purpose!
voice
I guess it's fine every now and then.
Not every day you get to fly around in the sky.
What the hell?
It grosses me out when you're in a good mood.
Does it?
Well, it happens sometimes.
After all, I got another granddaughter today.
Sanae will be happy, too.
You idiot!
H-Hey, Zouroku.
Um...
I'm sorry I knocked over those vases today.
You should say those things sooner.
Yeah...
Let's go home.
Okay.
And that was how our family
gained a new member today.
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Ichijou and the others said
the scary organization that had held Sana prisoner
was dismantled shortly after that.
And after the incident, the people opposing
Naitou and his team quietened down.
Grandpa complained that the way
Naitou had used him disgusted him.
The military lady who took Sana
returned to her own country due to a...
protection agreement or something?
Oh, welcome back, Sanae.
Thanks, Sana.
Going to water the flowers?
Yep, that's my job.
When the soil's dry, give them water.
Looks like you don't need water too badly today.
That's because it rained a little bit yesterday.
I see!
She's so adorable!
Prune the wilted blossoms...
There.
This looks great!
Okay, let's eat.
Yeah.
By the way... Lately, you seem
to have more stamina, huh?
Let's all go somewhere to play soon.
Okay!
What's "play"?
Where are we going?
Maybe a theme park or a zoo!
I bet you've never been to a zoo, right?
Or an aquarium...
Aqua... What is that?
Or a hot spring.
Hot spring?
What's a hot spring?
Oh, hot springs are great.
They're paradise!
Paradise?
Is that amazing?
For now, let's just eat.
Time to eat.
Time to eat!
Sounds like they're having a great time.
It sure does.
So peaceful.
So little to do...
I wish we'd have another incident.
That's rather rash, you know.
Hidden beneath this scab
Are a great many things all working in unison
So please hold on just a little bit longer
Because I'll change myself starting from there
When do I start
To truly become myself?
Let's go meet the people who deserve my affection
We'll find them scattered across the world
I want to learn so much about them
One person, another person, more and more people
Three, four, five, six, the number rises and rises
Finding out the truth
Can sometimes be painful, but...
The world will keep moving
On and on, forever and ever
Even far into the future
Remaining unchanged