K-Kuroko,
is this... some joke you're pulling?
What are you talking about?
Uiharu? Saten?
Why do you know our names?
Have you mentioned us to her, Shirai?
No. We are not acquainted.
I don't know why you know about us,
but if you require assistance, we may help
as members of Judgment.
No,
never mind.
You crossed a line there, Shokuhou.
You went after my friends.
This isn't
just a prank anymore.
If I show them our dorm rooms
and our photo albums,
they'll understand that their
memories were tampered with.
But
would they cooperate,
if I'm still "just a stranger" to them?
Getting them involved now might be a bad idea.
Miss Misaka?
We should get ready for the next event.
Why would she go this far?
She already had me cornered.
What can I do now?
I feel your heart beat on beyond the hands of time
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Believing that our bond will last until the end
The fervor to protect you growing day by day
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they'll never fade
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they’ll never fade
In the fragile, tender kindness of your bright eyes
There's a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
There’s a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
All the wonderful times that we spent side by side
Will live within my memories eternally
As my mind overflowed thinking of you
More than I could ever hope to explain
I turned the pain of the loss that I felt
To power I'd never known
To power I’d never known
And I keep rushing into the light
No one can stop this phase
Now that we're hand in hand
Now that we’re hand in hand
I etched a vow into the fabric of my mind
So I can keep you safe whatever perils come
I take your hand in my own and never let it go
The time that I have spent just standing by your side
Is all that I have ever wanted to recall
Until at last the day comes when I see you smile
Know that I’m never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
Know that I'm never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
You're in great shape, Kongou.
Even the commentators praised your performance.
How very discerning of them!
What was all that about?
I think we should've talked to her a little more.
That is but your admiration
for the famous speaking.
She seemed like she wanted something, though.
Shirai, Saten, and Uiharu, good day!
Hello, Kongou!
How are you doing, Shirai?
I took first place in the event
in which I participated in your stead!
Wait, what are you sulking about?
You know the Railgun at our school?
She bothered me with some nonsense earlier.
She ran up to us then started asking
if we are pulling a prank on her.
Thank you for your continued
efforts in the events, though.
S-Sure...
Uiharu.
Excuse us.
Right.
Goodbye.
Did she have a fight with Miss Misaka?
They usually seem to get along so well...
You were going to take part in this many events?
And all of them pair events too!
Pair events?
The next pair event is the balloon sandwich!
Each pair has to carry their balloon
to the goal together without using their hands!
They are disqualified if the balloon pops!
I don't have time for this...
I have to get out of here and look for her.
Misaka,
shall I inflate the balloon?
Please.
Darling,
let us hold each other in love's embrace!
We're disqualified if the balloon pops!
Kuroko kept running wild
so we could barely practice.
I didn't think we were on such close terms.
I had no idea you had a twin sister.
Huh?
Was it your sister who joined us
for the Balloon Hunter yesterday?
Kongou, you noticed it wasn't me?!
Oh, my.
I have a good eye for people.
How do I put it? She had a different air to her.
Kongou, please help me!
Tokiwadai's really strong!
No surprises there, really.
Congratulations.
Thanks...
That...
That is abusing your powers
beyond a line, Shokuhou Misaki!
Keep it down, Kongou!
She kidnaps your sister,
not to mention manipulating
your friends' memories.
This is a disgrace upon Tokiwadai.
I shall help you.
I will look for your sister.
You should keep Shokuhou's lackeys busy.
I'm so sorry to get you involved
in a private matter like this.
Just watch your back, and don't get in too deep.
It's really scary how you can
never tell what's on that girl's mind.
If you find a clue, just let me know
and I'll handle the rest.
No.
You should not trust anything I tell you.
But why?
I could already be brainwashed by her too.
You should consider the possibility
that everything I tell you is a lie.
But...
But then you couldn't trust anyone, right?
That is why I will bring you
your sister, not information.
This might come off strangely after saying all that,
but trust me and wait.
Kongou...
Congratulations on your win.
Just as expected.
Thanks.
She did not turn Misaka's friends into her enemies.
She likely did not feel that to be necessary.
If she is after her sister,
then she must have just been trying to stall.
And she didn't think it needed
to work for long, either.
I should hurry.
Don't get into trouble, Kongou.
It's one thing to help me search,
but she shouldn't put herself in danger.
Miss Misaka!
Your phone.
Damn, does she suspect something?
It is the Gekota model from Lovely Mitten, right?
Yeah...
Actually...
What?! Pyonko?!
I saw the strap on your bag,
so I wondered if you were a fan too.
So that's why...
I have long wished to have a good chat with you.
I really wish it was not considered so childish.
Mothers of small children
keep giving me weird looks about it.
Right?
When something new's on sale,
I can never line up early because of the dorm rules.
That reminds me,
did you see the new local-edition series?
I feel they are not taking us Gekoers seriously.
They don't respect the original franchise enough.
This goes even deeper than I thought...
They should learn from the limited
edition that came out this year.
I couldn't get that yet.
I haven't seen it in online auctions either.
Really? I have two, one to display
and one to keep in mint condition.
Two?!
If you do well in your events today,
I'll give you the unopened one.
Rea—
What an advanced trap.
I very definitely took out Misaka Mikoto.
With those nano-devices injected,
there's no way she could move.
Catching her was your job.
I bet she was taken to some hospital or something.
I guess that should work as well.
I've got another job for you, Baba.
Another?
The targets are Misaka Mikoto's clones.
The Sisters.
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Trust
Misaka said that she last saw her sister around here.
Which means Shokuhou Misaki
likely contacted her here as well.
This does not feel right.
According to Misaka, her sister does not
have the power to block Mental Out.
She could just manipulate her
into going to some abandoned place.
Why use such a contrived way then,
transporting her by ambulance?
EXIT
exit
So perhaps she was taken down not by Mental Out,
but something Shokuhou Misaki
was not expecting either.
Then I might find some clues here.
This is...
that character Misaka is so enamored with.
What's that?
H-Hey, you!
Don't bully the weak!
You shall be fine now.
I can understand if you are worried,
but I do not have the time to assist...
I really do not have the time for this!
I should take it to Judgment.
Oh?
Kongou?
Are you in a hurry? What hap—
Perfect! Could you take care of this cat please?
Oh?
That is Miss Misaka's cat, right?
Is it?
I am not entirely sure,
but it appears to be the cat that was
with her before the Balloon Hunter event.
Balloon Hunter?
Then it was her sister.
She had a sister?
I... do not have time to explain in detail.
Misaka asked me to look for her missing little sister.
Missing?
I found this cat where I suspect
her sister got into trouble.
The scope of this is beyond me,
but I have a friend from the swimming club
who can read animals' minds.
She might be able to talk to this cat as well.
My!
Look, Mommy! Doggy robots!
Really.
The things you see in Academy City.
Nagatenjouki is running away with this.
Wow.
These strawberry-flavored fried noodles are great.
Let's go again today!
That girl in pink is so cute!
That may be a clue to where Misaka's sister is!
A Tokiwadai student. "Misaka". "Sister".
Let me call her.
Wait here, please!
Very well!
I would not have guessed this kitten might be a lead.
The psychometrist isn't close enough to Misaka
for Shokuhou to lay a hand on her.
I brought your sister, as I promised!
Thank you, Kongou!
You're a hero!
Not a chance!
Excuse me.
Y-Yes? How may I help you?
May I have a moment?
I am actually quite busy at the—
This is about Misaka Mikoto's sister.
I'd rather not discuss it in
a crowded place like this. Shall we?
Starlight Games limited edition?
I bet she knows already, but let's show her anyway.
Wait, show who?
Kongou?
And... who's that?
Do you call her a "little sister" after the Sisters?
Or did she introduce her as her real sister?
Whichever.
You see, I was told to take this
"little sister" to safety as well.
Would you mind if we exchanged intelligence?
That is a wonderful proposal indeed,
and I will be happy to oblige as soon as you explain
who exactly you are and what
you want from Misaka's sister.
I feared you'd say that.
Could you perhaps let that go
and just fill me in on your lead?
Otherwise,
A robot?!
I'll drug you and force you to speak.
You just keep your distance, please!
He was suspicious from the moment he appeared,
so I assumed he was working for Shokuhou Misaki,
but if he is looking for her sister,
then perhaps he is with a different faction?
I came along hoping I could
get something out of him.
In any case, he has clearly made an enemy
of Miss Misaka.
Look! Look!
I need an excuse to get away from here.
All right, while we wait for the
next competition to start, we should—
My balloon!
This is it!
Thank you, big girl!
Miss Misaka, watch out!
Ah, I accidentally got on!
I can't get off now!
There, that was just an accident,
so it's not my fault, right?
Misaka, please get off at the next station.
I'm out of the telepath's range. Now—
Are you hurt?
Yes, we caught up. She is fine.
We will get off at the next station.
I see, of course you catch up to
a moving train in that situation. Why not.
We'll take a train back, or call a taxi.
Sorry for the trouble.
You're not going anywhere.
I looked up your powers after that event.
You can create air currents
around points you've touched.
But there is nothing here to use it on.
Guess why I led you here?
Just give up and spill the beans.
Then I won't have to hurt you.
Otherwise...
What?!
There seem to be two points you've failed
to grasp about my ability, Aero Hand.
First, I can create pressure
at any point I touch.
It's coming from the ground?!
Second...
The parabolic antenna?
If I build up enough pressure,
it can lift heavy machinery to the stratosphere.
There is nothing I can not blow away!
If I break something, I can just pay for it.
Maybe you should give up now?
That power level is definitely
beyond my expectations.
Great Dane-types aren't enough.
I just need a little opening, though...
Kongou is not here.
Are you sure this was the place?
Y-Yes.
I asked her to wait here...
So sorry. I called you all the way here...
No problem! Call me again when you find her.
Later!
Where did she go?
Oh?
Saten!
We keep running into each other!
Did you see Kongou?
Why am I feeling dizzy?
You seriously ran in to protect the cat?
Just give up.
I injected you with nano-devices
that rob you of control over your body.
It's rare stuff, so I'd rather not have used it.
If I could at least...
have gotten this kitten to Misaka...
Are you doing this for Misaka Mikoto
without receiving anything in return?
For some stranger?
That's what got you in this shit. What a laugh.
She's a mean bitch though.
Fast-talking you into getting involved in this.
Level Fives are all assholes.
Watch...
your words...
She... Misaka... does not use people like that.
I am... doing this... of my own will.
Not that... someone like you... would understand.
Bugger off!
Who the fuck do you think you're talking to?
In the end you're just a useless piece of shit!
You rotten piece of trash!
All Misaka Mikoto's got is trash like this?
Oh, wait.
I can't kill her before I question her.
The more primitive they are,
the easier they annoy me.
Great Dane-types, get her.
Kongou!
This is horrible.
Did you do this to her?
What if I did?
Who cares what I do to trash?
What?
She was working for Misaka Mikoto.
She was second-tier shit
the moment she obeyed someone else.
Not only that, she couldn't even
finish her mission. Not even third-tier.
Absolute trash.
You—
Saten, I am terribly sorry.
Please take Kongou and that kitten
to somewhere safe.
But...
We must protect that kitten,
or Kongou's efforts will have been in vain.
Besides...
He humiliated our friend.
You are not the only one here
with something to be angry about.
Do you know, can you recall, about the promise that we made so long ago
After it's done, wonder if I will fade away into the dark
I know we've gone well past the point of no return to living righteously
But I still feel just a little freed
I need to reach through to the world that lies beyond that lingering memory
As I fall into a slumber
Flashing back to that day
Fighting to hold back the tears that I can't bear to shed
I'm doing whatever it takes just to fight through to my destiny
I could never just believe that fates are predecided
Yet, somehow, people still find their meaning
As they struggle through this story without a name
In this cruel world of suffering
I find myself just trying to bring back those days again
They can't come back
Next Time
Awatsuki, this is the first time
I've felt such a strong impulse.
Hell Breaks Loose
Indeed, me as well.
You abused Kongou so much.
We must have a word with you.
Yes!
For a high-school student,
you speak like a delusional child!