Area B! Report!
Everything in order.
Stay on guard duty.
What a gig.
They've got this many security robots,
and then hire private security like us as well.
There must be one hell of a VIP coming.
What's the deal? A malfunction?
Wait, that's my tablet!
If he's here, I bet Kihara Gensei
will be in the VIP room.
Hey! I'm talking to you!
According to the map,
straight through here is the shortest route.
Call it brute force,
but I can't let Shokuhou get there first.
I feel your heart beat on beyond the hands of time
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Believing that our bond will last until the end
The fervor to protect you growing day by day
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they'll never fade
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they’ll never fade
In the fragile, tender kindness of your bright eyes
There's a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
There’s a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
All the wonderful times that we spent side by side
Will live within my memories eternally
As my mind overflowed thinking of you
More than I could ever hope to explain
I turned the pain of the loss that I felt
To power I'd never known
To power I’d never known
And I keep rushing into the light
No one can stop this phase
Now that we're hand in hand
Now that we’re hand in hand
I etched a vow into the fabric of my mind
So I can keep you safe whatever perils come
I take your hand in my own and never let it go
The time that I have spent just standing by your side
Is all that I have ever wanted to recall
Until at last the day comes when I see you smile
Know that I’m never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
Know that I'm never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
She's just as brutish as ever.
Can't she act with some more elegance?
Hurry! It's Area B!
Wait!
There's someone here too!
Stop right there!
I don't know how you got in,
but trespassers here are to be detained.
We'll shoot if you get any closer.
Whatever. Shoot!
What's wrong? Can't you hear your orders?!
You may shoot.
Wh-What?!
We've been waiting for you.
Well done.
Let me tweak his memories just a tiny bit.
Okay boys, sit.
Seal every exit from the building.
Don't let even a single ant out of here.
Capture Kihara Gensei no matter what.
Yes ma'am!
A metal that can turn into a liquid?
Did you find anything?
There was an initiative working on that a while ago,
and a bunch of companies did research on it,
but only two of them are still around.
Yes, but neither of those have records
of theft or loss of the material.
Of course, we cannot exclude
the possibility of an inside job.
Shirai, I've sent you the search
results from the student records.
I will look at it right away.
Oh? There's an abandoned factory in District 7.
Her! I found her!
KOUZAKU MITORI
Kirigaoka Attached
Junior High (Dropout)
Liquid Shadow - Considerable Ability
Can control liquids with specific gravity greater than 20.
Any difference from the user's appearance
causes inaccuracies in precise movements.
This means the controlled liquid must maintain a human form.
This humanoid lacks senses other than hearing and touch.
Ability range impossible to measure.
Assumed to be capable of free control
even from hundreds of kilometers.
||||||||||||||||||||||||||
|||||||||||||||||||||||||||||||||||||
Kouzaku Mitori.
Kirigaoka Attached Junior High, third year.
Dropped out.
Oh?
||||||||||||||||||||||||||||
Liquid Shadow - Considerable Ability
Can control liquids with specific gravity greater than 20.
Any difference from the user's appearance
causes inaccuracies in precise movements.
This means the controlled liquid must maintain a human form.
This humanoid lacks senses other than hearing and touch.
Ability range impossible to measure.
Assumed to be capable of free control
even from hundreds of kilometers.
Part of her file is sealed?
Why would that be?
I checked in Anti-Skill's database.
She was part of a failed terrorist attack
14 months ago and was sent to the Reformatory.
But she still kidnapped you. Did she escape, then?
Judgment would've been sent
the wanted notice if that'd happened.
Are you sure it's her?
She was wearing a dark hood,
so I cannot be 100% certain,
|||||||||||||||||
||||||||||||||||||||||||||||||
KOUZAKU MITORI
Kirigaoka Attached
Junior High (Dropout)
Liquid Shadow - Considerable Ability
Can control liquids with specific gravity greater than 20.
Any difference from the user's appearance
causes inaccuracies in precise movements.
This means the controlled liquid must maintain a human form.
This humanoid lacks senses other than hearing and touch.
Ability range impossible to measure.
Assumed to be capable of free control
but I feel that the darkness
behind her stare is the same.
Then we could go and ask at the
student records administration center.
They might tell us something.
You're right.
Then...
Oh, wait, what do we do about Misuzu?
Konori knows about her. It shouldn't be an issue.
What'll you do, Saten?
You can't get entrance approval at the center
without being a Judgment member.
Really?
Then I'll pass.
Just gonna kill time.
Oh, right, we're in the middle of the Starlight Games.
So much has been going on, I almost forgot.
Good Luck Charm
Anyone around!
We're doing a scavenger hunt.
Good Luck Charm
Could someone lend me a good luck charm?
No one? Of course not...
Good Luck Charm
In Academy City, where science rules all,
of course I had to get this.
Such misfortune!
A charm...
Good Luck
Mom gave me one when I left for Academy City,
but it means a lot to me.
Can't just let some stranger borrow it.
Sorry, spiky head!
Such misfortune!
Takoyaki
Here you go!
Excuse me! Do you have a good luck charm?
I don't, sorry...
Sorry for bothering you...
He's still at it? We've come a pretty long way.
He must be dead last at this point.
But in the scavenger hunt,
you don't get points if you give up,
but you do get some just for managing to finish.
He's not giving up. Trying so hard.
Good Luck
Charm
Anyone have a good luck charm?
Good Luck
Good L
Good
Goo
He looks like a nice guy, too...
I'm sure he wouldn't throw it away.
Excuse me, would anyone happen
to have a good luck charm?
Hey!
I've got one.
Really? Would you let me borrow it?
Yeah.
Good Luck
You're my savior!
Whoops. I can't erase the blessing.
Uh... It may be a bit old,
but it's very important to me.
Of course. I'll be sure to return it
as soon as the race is over.
But I can't just make you wait here until then...
Then how about we meet
over there an hour from now?
Sure, that sounds all right!
If something comes up,
please bring it to Judgment's 177th branch.
All right,
uh...
I'm Saten.
I'm Kamijou Touma.
Thanks! I'll bring it back for sure!
See ya!
Wait, was that abandoned factory around here?
NO  ENTRY
Shinohara  Liq
Shinohara  Liquid  Material  Factory
What?! Kouzaku Mitori is already deceased?
Huh?
Excuse me?
Is this certain?
She was definitely reported as dead.
Two months ago in the Reformatory.
Cause of death: heart failure.
I must have mistaken her for the attacker.
But this seems fishy.
Huh?
This timestamp indicates that she was
incinerated right after they found her body.
Indeed. They would've had no time
to perform an autopsy on her.
Maybe they never did.
What do you mean?
Maybe they wanted to hide something,
so they disposed of the proof before
the true cause of death could be found.
Or maybe it's all a ruse and she's still alive.
Do you have a basis for those assertions?
None at all!
I just love conspiracy theories!
She'd get along with Saten.
For sure.
I've heard a rumor about this.
Apparently, children held in the Reformatory
sometimes disappear suddenly, without a trace.
Even if the guards report it, no one investigates,
and those in charge act as if nothing happened.
And it's always the high-level espers
and smart students who go missing.
What if Academy City struck deals
with them and freed them in secret?
Having them dead on paper
might be more convenient.
Crazy, right?
Well, or so they say.
It's just a rumor.
Kouzaku Mitori
A Certain Scientific Railgun
In the end we got no certain information.
But if we assume that it really was
Kouzaku Mitori who kidnapped you,
that would mean someone powerful
enough to fake her death is involved.
But why would someone that
powerful go after Misuzu and me?
Judging by the circumstances,
she was probably after Misaka Mikoto.
But we have no way to guess her reason.
Why, I wonder?
Misaka piqued your interest after all.
Wh-What do you mean?!
I was speaking as a member of Judgment!
I am d-definitely not interested in her at all!
Sure, she was wonderfully dignified the other day, bu—
Shit... What the hell is going on?!
Why are my teammates ambushing me?
Hey!
Are you all right?
What's going on?
Stay away!
What are you doing?! Are you the insider?!
That's you, traitor!
What'd you call me?
That's her ability for you.
They can't tell who's friend or foe.
Without reliable cooperation or communication,
they've been thrown into disarray.
This should be the floor with the VIP rooms.
Kihara Gensei's room should be—
What are you doing here?
You're with team Q.
This area is team D's.
Oh, uh...
We heard there was an emergency,
so I was sent as backup.
The guests have already evacuated.
You should accompany them.
Come on.
Roger.
I could knock him out here,
but if Gensei's this way,
I should have him guide me there.
She's suspicious.
Team Q shouldn't be on duty now.
She didn't react to the secret code phrase either.
As soon as we turn that corner,
I'll pump her full of lead.
News to you?
I don't need your help detecting
a piece of metal like that.
What a lovely outfit!
Shut it.
Unlike you I can't waltz around in gym clothes
showing everyone my face.
More importantly, where's Gensei?
I'm putting plenty of manpower into the search.
Sure hope he hasn't escaped.
I have every escape route covered,
from the underground tunnels to the rooftop heliport.
Speak of the devil.
They caught Gensei.
NO  ENTRY
shinohara  liquid  material  factory
And of course, there's nothing here.
It's just slowly turning into a ruin.
I hoped they might be reusing the old machinery...
People?!
That cosplay bitch sure treats people like shit.
I'd say she pays well enough to make up for it.
What are they doing here?
The power's on?
It's closing!
Close call!
Wait, why did I come in here?!
It's not opening. I'd need one of those cards.
Wh-What now?
Call Uiharu?
What's she even cosplaying as?
Maybe a nurse?
Crap!
Maybe this place—
Don't turn around.
O-Okay!
What are you doing here?
U-Uh... W-Well...
I got lost!
Forget everything you've seen. Shut up and run.
O-Okay! Right away!
Bingo! Why do I always have
to be right about this stuff?
Um, I can't get out of here on my own.
I told you not to turn around, moron!
What just happened?
What are you doing? Why'd you let her get away?
The plan or whatever's already
in the final phase, isn't it?
I figured it doesn't make a difference at this point.
But there's no reason to let her live either.
Hey!
Did something happen?
An intruder.
She ran away. Catch her.
R-Roger!
So stupid, coming in here without thinking.
What is it, Professor?
Listen, Xochitl.
I just got in touch with the Board of Directors
to ask their opinion on this matter.
Let me sum it up for you.
What?
Stop it! Let go!
I said let me go!
Such a lively little mouse.
What do we do with this kid?
Make her spill why she snuck in here.
Once she talks, dispose of her however you like.
I've got something to attend—
Wait!
Oh?
What now? Betrayal?
Or do you know that little rat behind you?
I don't care what happens to this fool.
But you're the one who betrayed us, Kouzaku.
The secret organization I belong to, MEMBER,
is supposed to answer directly
to the Board of Directors.
We of course assumed that you
were handing us orders from them too.
However,
the Professor started doubting it and confirmed
that this job has nothing to do with the Board.
You conspired with whoever's giving you orders
and used your middleman position to trick Baba and me.
Correct?
Personally I don't care whose orders they are.
But treason calls for punishment.
Oh? If we fought here it'd just
turn into a one-sided slaughter.
I wonder.
You might fancy yourself out of reach,
but you don't know all my spells either.
I'm 90% sure she's bluffing.
But her ability is definitely not
something you'd see in Academy City.
She might pull out something unexpected.
I can't afford to fail here.
Meh, fine. I'll leave.
Just one warning before our heartfelt goodbye.
If you have a home,
you should leave Academy City right away.
If you want to live, anyway.
I have no home.
And there is someone here I must pursue,
even if it costs me my life.
What a romantic.
H-Hey!
Thank you so much for helping me!
Oh?
We met yesterday, right?
Was this your thanks for—
No means to protect yourself,
and not ready to face death.
Don't just dive thoughtlessly
into the underworld without preparing.
Come on.
I'll see you out.
Okay!
Where did you find him?
He was hiding in the safe room.
Is that Kihara Gensei?
Should I remove the tape?
No need for that.
I'll ask his brain directly.
What are you doing?!
A disguise?!
Hey, Shokuhou! What's going on?
Shokuhou?
You want me to play your double?
I have an affair I must attend to.
But—
Just do some small talk at the forum.
Right...
Now, if you're reading his memories,
you know what's going on.
If you're over there,
that means you aren't at that place right now.
Um...
Can they protect the Exterior without you,
Shokuhou Misaki?
Why?
How does Gensei know?
Hey! Shokuhou!
At least explain!
Go! As fast as you can!
Ouch!
You're awake?
This is a certain building in District 2.
"Did you rescue me?"
—asks Misaka in an expression of gratitude.
This is but a part of my job.
Nothing to be grateful for.
She fell asleep again.
Oh my.
I hoped I finally had a decent task for a change,
but it seems things aren't working out well.
Do you know, can you recall, about the promise that we made so long ago
After it's done, wonder if I will fade away into the dark
I know we've gone well past the point of no return to living righteously
But I still feel just a little freed
I need to reach through to the world that lies beyond that lingering memory
As I fall into a slumber
Flashing back to that day
Fighting to hold back the tears that I can't bear to shed
I'm doing whatever it takes just to fight through to my destiny
I could never just believe that fates are predecided
Yet, somehow, people still find their meaning
As they struggle through this story without a name
In this cruel world of suffering
I find myself just trying to bring back those days again
They can't come back
Next Time
So what's this Exterior?
Clone Dolly
You know, the legendary sword!
That's Excalibur.
Those big lights?
Chandeliers.
A dog breed?
That's terriers!
The things you use when your real hair isn't enough?
That's extensions!
Just tell me already!