Five o'clock! That's probably the real one!
Wait! Your line of fire goes—
Why
did you miss?
So that's what it really wanted.
What's wrong?
Do you want to see the city burn?
Your bluffs won't work on me.
You're not gonna do that.
Can't you go on like this?
That's a cruel thing to ask.
Are you confident that you could still
maintain your identity if one day you realized
that everything beneath
your thin layer of skin was fake?
If you think staying functional makes
a machine happy, that's mere human ego.
Is there no other way?
Merely existing in this form,
which constantly screams that it has no soul,
is unto itself an intense and unending agony.
Please.
Fine.
A Certain Scientific Railgun
I must thank you, Railgun!
Don't give me that crap!
Why do I have to do this?!
Do you feel guilty? You are far too kind.
You are doing nothing more
than disposing of a broken appliance.
You wanted to destroy yourself,
along with the airship that held
the data necessary to build another you.
And Kuriba, who could recreate it all.
Your safety mechanisms forbid suicide,
so you tried to trigger the city's
defenses by using the gas tanks.
Yes.
I should tell you that—
What happened?
Kuriba!
I was going to say that I convinced her—
You must have the devil's luck to have survived that.
No way!
This can't be!
K-Kuriba! We need to repair it! Fetch it!
Wait!
Let the Doppelganger finally rest!
That's what she wants!
What's this about?
Chief,
I'm afraid I can't take part in this project any further.
Wha—
Making subjects suffer for the fame
or profit of the scientist is not medicine.
Hold on! Can you imagine
just how much this could help—
The Doppelganger has nothing you want.
There is no soul there.
It's just an illusion born of your wishful thinking.
You—
You're not fooling me!
What?!
I'll do whatever it takes to get it back!
Are you insane?
Shut up!
Turn around!
Or you know what'll happen!
I can tell their rough positions via EM waves.
But I can't ensure Kuriba's safety without precision.
The girl with the mask is probably watching,
but the airship floated far away.
It could take them a while to get here.
No soul? Are you stupid?
It's true!
She just faking "possession"
by using artificial muscles!
You're lying!
I'm not!
She's been suffering since she realized
what a soulless, twisted being she is!
She chose herself to cease functioning!
No. It must be there.
Beyond the artificial muscles. It must be there!
If necessary, it must be disassembled—
Chief, please stop!
We shouldn't trample on the
Doppelganger's dignity any further!
Hey!
If we don't stop here, we'll end up
making even bigger mistakes!
L-Let go—
I-I didn't! You tugged at me!
I didn't meant to shoot!
Kuriba!
Hold on!
I'll call the hospital,
and send Seike and Naru there to—
No need. I'll can handle it.
Just call the hospital!
Fine.
She was shot in a bad spot. She won't—
Kuro—
She was lucky to be shot there.
She always did... have the devil's own luck...
There is a cyborg right here designed just for her.
Administer miahilin... part... can be...
Hell, why is this knowledge—
Darlin—
Kuroko.
I'm really sorry, but could you help me
carry these two to a hospital?
It's got no soul? You can't expect me
to believe that at this point!
Oh, that's it! I should just try again!
Even without Kuriba we'll eventually get it!
We can just use Child Errors to make it quicke—
You devoted your life to finding low-cost
treatments for the many people
who are beyond the reach of current medical care.
Yet once you stepped off the right path,
you couldn't stop yourself.
Human desire is really scary.
I'll be kind enough to remind
you of your original goal.
If you want to try again, then climb back up
A Certain Scientific Railgun
My Dear Friends
from below zero.
Darling? Did you get some good news?
The girl you helped me carry
got out of intensive care.
She's recovering well.
I am delighted to hear that.
It's thanks to you.
Really.
I only wanted to see you happy.
But if you are willing to show
your gratitude in other ways—
I'm not.
Oh my, you surely get along well.
Shokuhou.
Greetings, Misaka, Shirai.
Hi.
Greetings.
Oh, right—
If it's about Kuriba, I've heard already.
Glad she's getting better.
Thanks for going to the trouble.
And trouble it certainly was.
What do you mean?
Could it be that "deal" the other day
was with Shokuhou Misaki?
I, uh...
Wait, Darling, you used to just
give her the cold shoulder!
Since when do you get along?
I wouldn't go that far...
Then why did you keep it secret?!
Was it some intimate ordeal?
Why would you even suggest that?!
You are not giving an explanation!
Don't worry, Shirai.
I won't take your "Darling" from you.
I... see.
Though,
I might end up taking you from her.
Huh?
Just kidding.
Hi!
Oh?
Oh!
Hokaze, hello!
Uiharu, Saten! Greetings!
Greetings!
Come on...
Do you know each other?
We met at branch 177 the other day.
I love how you're basically
the perfect Tokiwadai lady.
Especially your drills.
You flatter me.
Allow me to introduce you!
This is Shokuhou Misaki, our queen.
Q-Queen?!
Uiharu, she's the real deal!
What do we do, Saten?!
Oh my, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you!
I'm sure we'll get along.
Cut the crap.
Oh, my.
What was that, Misaka?
Nothing.
Darling!
Now, listen. When you address Her Majesty,
there are rules that must be observed.
The world of Kuroko just faced its greatest calamity!
Quickly! We must reaffirm the strength of our bond!
There really is never a dull moment in this city.
Hey, cut that out!
Huh? Shokuhou!
All right.
We've been facing difficult
missions one after another.
Any ideas on how to improve our performance?
Sure!
Anyone else?
Why are you ignoring me?
All right, Naru.
Clearly we need a new member!
We need to fill the gaps in our skillset!
Naru said something useful!
And what would those gaps be?
Yellow!
Yellow?
What are you talking about?
Think about our name, Scavenger.
Doesn't it sound like a hero team?
So, I'm Pink! Leader is Red, of course.
I was considering Black for Seike,
but settled on Blue!
And Yakkun is White!
So we're missing Yellow!
I-I see.
Well, if you make our costumes out of paper,
S
then we could transform together, I guess?
Not a chance.
Just kidding...
I love that idea!
Let's try it now! Take your clothes off!
We should improve our moves and skills.
What? Hold on! Why me?!
Right?
Try it out on yourself!
I need it on someone else so I can adjust the design!
It's gonna be over in a flash!
Why?! You've seen me naked so many times!
No one asked you to undress!
There should be no secrets between teammates!
This is a pretty extreme interpretation of that!
Are you saying we're not friends?!
I've used quite a lot of my chemical stocks, too.
2 Minutes Later
Cut me some slack already...
You can't use your ability for
much longer than three minutes.
Aren't you about to run out of gas?
Was she after my time limit all along?
But she's the dumb one!
Naru should lose interest in about half an hour.
I'll just wait it out outside.
When did she cover the door in paper?
Did she know I'd need to stop my ability
to grab the door handle?!
Come on, Seike, let me see your little Seike!
No!
Phew.
So I was right to give you Blue rather than Black.
Stop fooling around.
Now Scavenger is even more tightly b—
You two keep quiet.
Well, good job completing that mission.
It turned out rather bigger than expected, didn't it?
I guess you know already,
but our client company has gone bankrupt.
So we're not getting paid.
Consider it an unlucky—
Hold on a second.
You expect me to just nod and thank you?
Come on.
The client is no more. There's nothing I can do.
I don't get my cut either. I'm a victim just like you.
We're putting our lives on the line.
Our circumstances are different.
Please appreciate that.
Oh?
You sure are cheeky
for a measly second-rate team.
This is no issue of second-rate
or first-rate, or even of our pay.
By accepting missions,
we take on the risk of being shelved,
demoted, or even purged.
It's just not right if a contract gets scrapped
after we complete the mission,
and all we get is "nothing I can do".
This isn't acceptable.
You need to give us a proper token of goodwill here.
Very well.
While I can't pay you,
I'll restore your rank to what it was.
Normally you'd have to succeed at several
more missions to get that, so that's your reward.
To what it was? Doesn't this merit
us becoming a named team—
Don't get ahead of yourself, kid!
Go get some sleep before your next mission!
We did it!
That's our Leader!
Now we'll get better pay next time!
Then we can by new stuff
to replace our old equipment!
What was that about?
Hmph!
Our night vision is ancient.
Our rations are past their best-by dates.
And our comms are just toys.
We don't need to replace these.
They do the job.
Plus, I like the design.
So, how are you doing?
"My test results are fine."
"However, I was instructed to avoid going outside,
so I thirst for stimuli from the outside world,"
complains Misaka, taking this
opportunity to voice her discontent.
Can't help you with that one.
But I got you the cake you like,
so why not have some and cheer—
Sister.
The trends of the world
change every day, you know.
That is no longer the most
popular cake at that shop.
What?!
But I'll accept it nonetheless.
Can't you just say thanks?
Hey!
Oh my.
Are you not that one kitten?
Kongou?
Misaka! What a coincidence!
What are you doing here?
Don't tell me you still need treatment.
No, I just had some paperwork to deal with.
But more importantly,
is this the person you were looking for?
Oh...
Yeah,
my little sister.
Oh, that's splendid!
This is Kongou. I've told you about her, remember?
She's the one who helped
a lot when you went missing.
You even suffered grievous wounds for me.
Thank you very much.
It was nothing worth mentioning.
I am so glad to see you well.
Is there a name I can use?
Name?
It's pending.
Pending? That is a unique name...
It seems to like it.
Oh, is that the kitten's name?
Can I know yours, then?
Me?
"I'm Misaka 10032,"
I answer concisely.
Ten...
Mind if I call you Tennie?
Well—
Yes, I'm fine with that.
You are?!
Isn't that Tokiwadai's uniform you're wearing?
Yes, but only for cosplay purposes.
Cos... play?
"That aside. What should I call you?"
I ask, changing the topic gracefully.
M-Me?
Well, since I'm calling you Tennie,
how about you call me M-Minnie?
Wow! Is this the sea?
Yeah. Close enough.
That's sloppy! Careful what you teach her!
Remember, we told you it's an aquarium.
Ah!
The big version of what you do in your jar!
Not exactly...
Will this really be enough?
Getting out of Academy City can be tricky,
but with my ability it's really no big deal.
I'd rather not take her on a long trip
until she's fully recovered.
Let's take it slow.
If you say so.
Mii! Misaki! Is that a dolphin?
I think that's a tuna.
Tuna? I know that from a book!
It's tender and delicious!
What book is that, even?
Huh?!
H-Hey!
Ouch!
Doppelganger?
Is this a dream? Or am I crossing
the Acheron and seeing my guilt—
It's a dream.
Are you giving me a chance to apologize?
An apology?
I didn't try to kill you out of resentment.
It was merely a necessary condition.
Though accepting casualties as a necessary condition
may be a thought pattern affected by you.
You knew well the chaos Indian poker could cause.
Yet to save your mother, you went ahead with it.
Even your own life was among
the potential acceptable casualties.
You are fundamentally incapable
of achieving anything any other way.
But you shouldn't think
that makes you a bad person.
Don't lose the ability to achieve things
for fear you might hurt someone.
That would lead to the dull life of a symbiont.
Symbiont?
So, I already looked over the cyborg
implant designs you completed for your mother.
I found three areas for improvement.
Huh?
While this design will work initially,
it may not last beyond ten years.
Huh?
I am better at simulations, after all. So first—
So...
You met the Doppelganger in your dream?
Yes. It's weird.
That shouldn't happen just from
replacing a few of my organs.
What does that mean?
At first I thought it was just
my guilt producing hallucinations.
That matches up perfectly with our battle.
And ever since then, she keeps
pointing out issues with my research.
How can I get you to move on?
"Move on"? As if one could
be a ghost without a soul.
Are you done complaining?
Next we'll spend the night
going over your darkest secrets—
Stop!
Honestly, I'm afraid to go to sleep at this point.
That aside,
I'm a bit relieved.
I'm sorry.
I ended up having you shoulder
all the burden in this case.
I'm not sure if I should be telling you this,
but it seems the moment the
Doppelganger was at her happiest
was during the time when she fought you.
Well,
tell her she was quite the formidable opponent,
the next time she shows up in your dreams.
We have come for you, Darling!
I watch you as you walk off calmly beneath the morning sun
How about we go eat something nice?
And your image fades from my eyes
Actually there's this place nearby
that came up in this urban legend—
As you slowly blur into the distance
It feels as if a breeze of summer has blown us far apart
Saten!
You stepped on a land mine, Saten.
I-I'm just kidding!
And I head off on my way home
No, you are always—
Anything's fine as long as we're together.
Through these ever-sprawling deserted urban streets
As the stars fade into the brightening sky
Let's go!
The scent of twilight lingers in the air
A Certain Scientific Railgun
I wonder what we could become
And what our stories' pages might have in store
And whether these warm days might never return
Even if decades pass and we still don't meet again
I know that there's one thing I never could forget
The vow we made each other
With hand in hand so long ago
A lukewarm breeze announces
The end of summer fast approaching
I feel as if I'm taking on the warm red glow of the sky above us