Very awesome punch!
Aweso—
Now!
Wait wait wait wait hold on hold on hold on hold on!
Good luck!
Gotta give it a try!
Wait, how am I supposed to land?
Uh... th-thanks?
Though it was your fault I needed catching.
How'd it go?
It didn't work.
It seems like some weird power is flowing
into her from the outside. I can't erase it all.
It worked for a second where I touched her,
but it reverted right away.
What now, then?
We're not the only ones trying
to get her back to normal... I think?
Dunno who it is though.
I guess our only option is to keep her busy
until they manage to cut off the external influence.
They told me that me being around her
should suppress the transformation.
Hey, she changed again.
They said it'd slow her down, but not that it'd stop...
What is she even trying to do?
S-Sogiita!
That was pathetic. She caught me off guard.
A-Are you all right?
How tough are you to take that without a scratch?
This is gonna take some guts.
I know what Kihara Gensei is after.
The puppet wasn't trying
to kill me, but to capture me.
He wants some information from me.
It's obvious.
He wants the code to release the Exterior's limiter.
I feel your heart beat on beyond the hands of time
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Believing that our bond will last until the end
The fervor to protect you growing day by day
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they'll never fade
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they’ll never fade
In the fragile, tender kindness of your bright eyes
There's a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
There’s a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
All the wonderful times that we spent side by side
Will live within my memories eternally
As my mind overflowed thinking of you
More than I could ever hope to explain
I turned the pain of the loss that I felt
To power I'd never known
To power I’d never known
And I keep rushing into the light
No one can stop this phase
Now that we're hand in hand
Now that we’re hand in hand
I etched a vow into the fabric of my mind
So I can keep you safe whatever perils come
I take your hand in my own and never let it go
The time that I have spent just standing by your side
Is all that I have ever wanted to recall
Until at last the day comes when I see you smile
Know that I’m never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
Know that I'm never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
Where's the camera?
There!
If the details in the student records are correct,
Kouzaku's puppet has no eyes.
KOUZAKU MITORI
Kirigaoka Attached
Junior High (Dropout)
Liquid Shadow - Considerable Ability
Can control liquids with specific gravity greater than 20.
Any difference from the user's appearance
causes inaccuracies in precise movements.
This means the controlled liquid must maintain a human form.
This humanoid lacks senses other than hearing and touch.
Ability range impossible to measure.
Assumed to be capable of free control
even from hundreds of kilometers.
||||||||||||||||||||||||||
|||||||||||||||||||||||||||||||||||||
She uses bat-like echolocation to orient it.
It's sensitive enough to pick up
heartbeats from dozens of meters away.
The camera is only there for support.
This should work, then!
That device is designed to protect
sensitive discussions from eavesdropping.
This should blind and deafen her for a little while.
I have to use that time.
My, my.
Shokuhou, dear, you are so paranoid.
You have no records anywhere on
how to release the limiters on the Exterior.
What a waste of effort.
Just as I thought.
The Exterior's current output is probably insufficient
to precisely control Misaka while she's in that state.
That's why he wants to release the limiters.
The access codes for Exterior's
critical functions aren't recorded anywhere
outside of my own brain.
The core of the Exterior's defense is secrecy.
Hardly anyone should even be aware of its existence.
But I have a backup plan for the worst-case scenario.
Oh?
This and the surrounding buildings have
supplemental security measures that only I can activate.
Can I hope this will put him to sleep?
Multi-Skill.
While I don't have ten thousand kids like Kiyama,
I have kidnapped—I mean, invited a few
to borrow their interesting abilities.
Don't tell me you didn't expect this.
Such a creepy old fart.
But this isn't all.
If sleeping gas didn't work, let's try this!
No such luck!
Can I ask you something?
What would that be?
I thought you'd reached the conclusion that the
only one capable of reaching Level 6 was Rank 1.
Indeed, he's the only one currently capable
of reaching Level 6 in a stable manner.
Stable?
Misaka is currently being pushed towards
Level 6 by overloading her power.
According to theoretical models,
at 53% of the way there,
her mind will transform and be
transported to another dimension.
I need the limiter release codes to
keep her tied to this world beyond that point.
Then, at 100%, the moment she reaches Level 6,
the toll will be too great on both her mind and body.
I predict that she will simply disintegrate.
Misaka simply can't become a stable Level 6.
In exchange for her destruction,
for a moment, a brief, fleeting blink of time,
we will have a chance to witness the domain of God.
After that, she'll either shrivel up
like a pathetic white dwarf,
or she'll detonate like a supernova,
and open the gates to an exciting new world for us.
Either way, something is going to occur at such scale
as to erase this city from the face of the Earth.
If she's gonna blow up Academy City,
you'll obviously be caught in the mess too.
Are you supposed to be making sense?
Get caught up? You must be joking.
Bleeding-edge science demands sacrifices.
This is why I hate dealing with madmen.
It turns out using Clairvoyance
isn't as easy as I thought.
While it allows me to see through obstacles,
I have to carefully zoom in the right direction
at the right distance to find what I want.
You wasted my precious time.
Now then.
Even if I tried to read your
memories with Mental Out,
you could block the intrusion
into your brain with the same ability.
But if I cause you unbearable pain or
knock you unconscious so you can't use your ability,
that shouldn't be an issue, should it now?
I can't breathe? The air's...
You're not very fit,
so hopefully you'll pass out quickly.
Misaka is progressing as well.
Oh my!
Kamijou's interference was expected,
but now Sogiita got involved as well!
Add the unpredictable power of Rank 7
to the stimulation of the Imagine Breaker!
What an unprecedented chance
to observe a physical division by zero!
Multiplying those two by Misaka!
This is a unique chance!
I must deploy all equipment and
analysis espers to observe immediate—
O-Oh shit!
Is he insane?
That insane explanation implied that
if he fails to get the release codes from me,
the city will be saved at the cost of Misaka's life.
I'll always remember your sacrifice
for at least a week and a half!
It's one outcome to consider.
But I doubt he'll just let me get away.
I could handle him if he only had Mental Out,
but what am I even supposed to do
against a mad scientist with Multi-Skill?
My special security systems
will only buy me so much time.
Graviton panels?
Exterior
A Certain Scientific Railgun
She's not here.
It's taking too much time to search everywhere.
I need some sort of clue.
I found her!
That's Kouzaku, right?
Saten's found the suspect on a security camera!
I'll send you the details.
It's timestamped three minutes ago,
and she didn't show up on any other cameras,
so we can identify the building she's hiding in.
I'll be right there!
She's coming straight this way?
A security camera?
Come on, they only cleared their own trails?
You're sure she's not on any other cameras, right?
Yeah, nowhere else.
If she tried to move to another building,
a camera'd be bound to catch her.
She's in there.
Uiharu, lock all the cameras
in the area onto the target building!
Roger!
She should catch her easily like this.
F-Focus!
The computers will detect
and alert on any movement, right?
What's that?
What? Did you find something?
Saten, shut up for a second!
Sorry...
Look at that!
From the sewers?
Shirai, the puppet is heading
your way at high speed!
This really is the right place then.
You think she'll use the puppet
to destroy the cameras?
Indeed, she could take out a few cameras
and escape through the resulting blind spot.
But right now all the operational cameras
in the area are facing this building.
Securing a blind spot by
destroying them would take time.
I have to deal with her before that.
She's after me, not the cameras?!
Perfect.
I'll use her panic to corner her even further.
I know her ability's features and weaknesses.
The puppet is no threat—
Ouch!
What's wrong, Shirai? Did something happen?
She got me. I got hit by a counter-attack.
Are you all right?
No need to worry.
She barely scraped my side,
but the cut on my arm is deep.
And my wounds from before only just healed!
This is a precious maiden's body!
But now I can be certain that Kouzaku is here.
On one of the upper floors.
That attack hit me even though
the anti-eavesdropping device was active.
That means she was watching directly.
The vines moved in parallel,
targeting a straight line that passed through me.
I suspect she was watching from above,
unable to precisely gauge the distance,
so she had to fan her attack out.
She has nowhere to run if I corner her from below.
It's but a matter of time before I catch her.
But I have this weird feeling,
as if I've forgotten something important...
Oh, Shokuhou.
Excuse me for getting so worked up earlier.
It's a weakness of mine: if I see an unexpected
situation, I focus in on it and lose touch.
It's nearly cost me my life multiple times.
You should've dropped dead then.
I'm surprised
you came here and waited for me.
I expected you to try to run away.
You've got Clairvoyance.
I couldn't get away if I tried.
If you caught me outside, I'd be out of options
with no security to protect me.
So I came to negotiate!
Negotiate what?
I'll give you the release codes,
so let me get away.
Oh?
I thought it over,
and I really couldn't care less about Misaka.
If you say Academy City will be leveled,
then I should get out before then.
I waited for you because I didn't want
to waste time by trying to escape from you.
I see.
Just a little more.
But your offer has no merit to me.
I can't use Mental Out on you.
Without my ability I'm just a cute
and lovely and beautiful young girl.
Don't tell me you've got a fetish
for bullying such delicate maidens?
Four more steps.
How unexpected of a
shriveled-up little man like you!
Three more.
Two more.
It's a trap with extremely high-
output oscillators: the Hag's Hug.
One step on it and you're done.
The waves travel up your feet, amplifying
through your body, finally collapsing in your head.
It destroys your inner ear
and shakes up your brain good.
One more?
True, if you gave me the release codes,
I'd have no further business with you.
But there is one thing that concerns me.
You've been staring at this spot so hard
it's made me wonder if something's hiding there.
You realized!
Or not.
It's but a decoy!
The real deal is already under you!
Graviton panels.
Originally they were intended for me to use
as shortcuts, but I made them appear as the floor.
Now I just have to lock you in there—
His feet are exploding?
No, he's compressing the air under him
to turn it into a foothold.
It's what he used to suffocate me
and divert the flames.
It's the Aero Shooter ability!
I can't waste any more time on you.
You're not getting away.
Now it's my turn to—
I wonder.
This is the best of all my countless traps.
The pressure rises slowly,
so I had to time it perfectly.
See, graviton panels can be used like this too.
They were developed as temporary
footing for construction workers,
but they expand well enough
to break the arm of an old man.
Can you block my Mental Out while in so much pain?
How mean of you, hurting a fragile old man so much.
Not that this old man
has any hands in the first place.
P-Prosthetics?
I told you I've almost died
in the line of work many times.
My body is a collection of bleeding-edge tech.
Your goal was pretty easy to figure out anyway.
You kept pretending to run away, but when a person
has a plan, their goal always shows on their face.
And I'm very good at noticing that hint of hope.
So looking at you now, it's plainly obvious.
You have no other tricks
up your sleeve. Nothing at all.
The limiter release codes
are mine.
Do you know, can you recall, about the promise that we made so long ago
After it's done, wonder if I will fade away into the dark
I know we've gone well past the point of no return to living righteously
But I still feel just a little freed
I need to reach through to the world that lies beyond that lingering memory
As I fall into a slumber
Flashing back to that day
Fighting to hold back the tears that I can't bear to shed
I'm doing whatever it takes just to fight through to my destiny
I could never just believe that fates are predecided
Yet, somehow, people still find their meaning
As they struggle through this story without a name
In this cruel world of suffering
I find myself just trying to bring back those days again
They can't come back
Next Time
I should be cornering Kouzaku Mitori,
but I cannot seem to reach her.
One other than God who reaches the will of the heavens
Something feels really wrong.
But I will find her for sure!
Hmm. Shokuhou is not interrupting me this time.