You restored the erased data?
There!
Shokuhou.
A DNA computer that creates esper abilities?
Is this Shokuhou girl involved in that research?
We don't know that.
What we do know is that she
didn't want to be seen there.
Which means it's probably her hideout.
And that'll be where she's keeping her.
Kuroko.
Do you recognize this building? Any idea where it is?
I would really appreciate if you
stopped being so overly-familiar.
That building?
It closely resembles Judgment HQ in district 2.
District 2?
I'll head there then.
Sorry, but when Mom wakes up—
We'll tell her that she had a heat stroke,
and hold her here for a while on
the pretext of reissuing her visitor pass.
No need for you to worry.
Thanks!
And thank you for the intel, Saten.
S-Sure...
U-Um, Misaka?
So our memories really did get altered, right?
And that's why we don't remember you?
Don't worry about it.
Once it's all done,
I'll catch Shokuhou and drag her back here.
Sit tight and I'll take care of everything.
Technology lying hidden behind heavy defenses?!
Chasing the cutting-edge DNA computer
that creates esper abilities!
I feel your heart beat on beyond the hands of time
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Believing that our bond will last until the end
The fervor to protect you growing day by day
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they'll never fade
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they’ll never fade
In the fragile, tender kindness of your bright eyes
There's a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
There’s a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
All the wonderful times that we spent side by side
Will live within my memories eternally
As my mind overflowed thinking of you
More than I could ever hope to explain
I turned the pain of the loss that I felt
To power I'd never known
To power I’d never known
And I keep rushing into the light
No one can stop this phase
Now that we're hand in hand
Now that we’re hand in hand
I etched a vow into the fabric of my mind
So I can keep you safe whatever perils come
I take your hand in my own and never let it go
The time that I have spent just standing by your side
Is all that I have ever wanted to recall
Until at last the day comes when I see you smile
Know that I’m never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
Know that I'm never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
This is turning into such a pain in the neck.
September 19th
What's going on here?
It seems that she was taken out
by military-grade nano-devices.
It might interfere with her electric ability.
I don't know if antivirus software could cure her.
Either way, I would suggest we take her back.
I believe this is an opportunity for us.
Sheer luck though it is, we may get
a few steps ahead of our opponents.
If her life ends up in danger, I'll let Misaka know.
Really?
I'm not happy about it,
but there's nothing else we could do.
Call an ambulance.
I'll get in their heads and make them
carry her part of the way for us.
Right away.
Is that her cat?
Oh, my.
It had no collar. Probably a stray.
Either way, we've got no time
to worry about cats. Leave it.
You're right.
Hello?
What's the status on auribus oculi fideliores sunt?
That urban legends site?
It's unbelievable.
I raised security levels to the max
so no one could tail or locate me,
then some esper who can use distant water
droplets as cameras still takes a photo of me.
Why does the admin of some lame
urban legends site have such an ability?
Espers all abuse their abilities.
Look who's talking.
What was that?
You don't need to worry about that.
I'm running a program that generates
dummy pages to hide it.
No one will be able to find that site, I guarantee.
September 20th
My, would you look at that.
Someone is trying to restore the original site
by analyzing the patterns in the generated dummies.
I vaguely recall you saying you
guaranteed no one could find it?
J-Just sit back.
I prepared for this scenario.
It detects who's tampering with it.
There it is.
Judgment office 177?
And of course the Judgment girl there
had to be Misaka's friend.
That was when everything went south.
Not that I had any other choice—
which means this situation was a necessity too.
Don't you think, Misaka?
Oh,
fancy seeing you here.
Says the one who glared into every
security camera she saw on the way.
A coincidence, I'm sure.
Where is she?
As you're aware, she's in the building
from that photo on the website.
That's my most trusted hiding spot.
She's all right?
I wouldn't hurt someone
just because they look like you.
Are we done now?
Are you kidding? I've got plenty more to ask you.
If you insist...
But I'm short on time too, so you'll
have to come along if you want to chat.
Isn't there anything I could do for her?
She said she'd take care of everything,
so why worry about it?
Honestly, I have my doubts about
this memory manipulation story.
But if it's true... Wouldn't it be horrible
if your friends forgot about you?
You wouldn't mind if Uiharu and I suddenly
treated you like a complete stranger?
If you put it that way...
I'd hate it.
What are you doing?
These are the student records.
I am looking for the person
who took Uiharu hostage.
I only saw their face, so I don't know
which school she attends.
However, I can guess her ability.
She creates a lookalike out of liquid metal
that she can control remotely.
Considering that it seemed to be at least Level 3 or 4,
that limits the range of search significantly.
I see! That might help Misaka!
I am looking for the culprit of an attempted murder
strictly as a member of Judgment.
We cannot simply share the results
of investigations with civilians like that.
Uh...
However,
in an emergency situation where such disclosure
is judged to be advisable, we may do so.
What's with that smirk?
All right, I'll help look through the files too!
Hey! Don't ignore me!
We're going away from the place in the photo.
I told you I'm short on time.
If you want to talk, don't complain.
And I really don't want anyone
near that place anyway.
Don't worry. Once the dust's settled she'll be free to go.
She was injected with some nano-devices,
so I'm kinda concerned about
her immune system, though.
But there's no risk to her life.
The people looking for the Sisters
hit her with those nano-devices?
Who are they?
At first I thought they were under your command,
but they've been looking for her
even after she went missing.
And they've been questioning people,
which shouldn't be necessary for you.
Can I assume you're not on friendly terms?
Yep. And we're heading to
where their leader is right now.
It all started when I heard about an incident
I'm sure you're quite familiar with:
the Level Six Shift project.
Researchers in my facility
had been whispering about it.
That after the project broke down,
information about it started circulating underground.
Did you hear about the Level Six Shift project?
Tell me
everything about that.
They mass-produced clones
of Rank-3 Misaka Mikoto
and used them to try to make
Rank-1 Accelerator reach Level 6.
Apparently the project fell apart halfway through.
What happened to the clones?
I don't know. I'd assume they were disposed of.
Have you found out what happened
to the Sisters after the incident?
I'm sorry, but not yet.
Oh, come on. You were involved in the experiments.
That's one of the reasons why I hired you.
I was merely in charge of reinforcing security.
A different facility took custody
of the Sisters after the incident.
Don't worry.
I have a few clues that may lead to them.
Better sooner than later, if you would.
There is one thing that worries me, though.
There seems to be another organization
looking for the Sisters as well.
I see. Look into that as well, then.
And at the end of that investigation...
You found them.
The guy you ran into is just a mercenary.
From what I heard, he was told to
get rid of you and look for the Sisters.
Get rid of me?
Keep in mind that you'd derailed the Sisters project.
I figure they're scared of you.
But they got the wrong me.
It's strange that they just tried to
disable you with the nano-devices.
I'm sure you can guess why
they'd want the Sisters though.
There is one thing they could gain.
The MISAKA Network.
The network formed from the Sisters' brainwaves.
I'd really rather they didn't get to abuse
that immense computational power.
So I used my awesome ability on the clone I had
to block out any connections in the network
that could've spread an electronic virus.
Even if another of the Sisters
fell into the wrong hands,
they wouldn't be able to interfere
with the MISAKA Network.
So that's how you got a step ahead of them?
What would they want with the MISAKA Network?
Nothing good, that much I'm sure of.
After all, the mastermind behind all this is
the Level Six Shift project's greatest proponent,
Kihara Gensei.
Railgun and Mental Out
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Kihara Gensei?
I haven't met him in person,
but I've heard that name a couple of times.
He was the one behind that project?
Not just that. He uses any means necessary
in his search for the "truth".
He's responsible for the downfall of
multiple researchers and entire facilities.
He's one of the foremost
SYSTEM researchers in Academy City.
Of course he wouldn't just ask to restart the project,
but we can both guess what happened.
All that said, we're heading to where
Kihara Gensei is right now.
Can you just walk in to say hi?
Please. He's quite the slippery old man.
It took effort to find him.
Apparently he'll be going undercover
at the International Esper Research
Conference in the ninth district.
I know from reading the memories
of someone involved.
I want to use this rare chance
to put an end to all of it.
You manipulated my friends' memories.
Was that your weird way
of protecting them from danger?
They'd definitely go down like flies if they
carelessly involved themselves with that old geezer.
And even if they didn't, their unpredictable actions
could interfere with my plan.
It wouldn't end well for any of us.
Why wouldn't you talk to me, then?
Why go so far as erasing
their memories just to hide it?
I told you that Kihara's people are wary of you.
If we teamed up, they'd notice me too.
There had to be some other way!
Kongou—
I dragged her into this... and it was probably
sheer coincidence that she ran into them...
So I guess I can't really blame you for that.
But if we teamed up from the get-go
she wouldn't have ended up like that!
It's a pity she got wrecked like that.
But she did end up taking out
all those clunkers I'd have had trouble with.
What I'm saying is that you
should've let me deal with those!
Why—
What if Kihara Gensei
just didn't show up, wary of you?
What if you betrayed me
and handed me over to them?
I wouldn't—
Cooperation?
Trust?
How can you believe in such fuzzy ideas?
You believing what people told you like a good girl
is what led to the Radio Noise
and the Level Six Shift projects.
I always check the minds
of the people I cooperate with.
Their secret motives. Their earnestness.
In some cases I'll take control
of their emotions and actions.
I can't tell what's going on in your head.
It'd never even occur to me to team up with you.
The only reason I'm here with you
is to respect your friend's sacrifice,
and because now we can put an end to this
before they know we've made contact.
It seems we can never see eye to eye after all.
Just one question.
Why would a corrupt monster
like you care about the Sisters?
Sorry, but we aren't good enough
friends for me to answer that.
Anyway, we're almost there.
Misuzu?
Is this the nap room at office 177?
If your conclusion is correct, that would mean
Uiharu was under their control since yesterday.
Yeah.
They tried really hard to hide that site.
I figure they'd look into who
Uiharu was after she found it.
They got her memories,
then controlled her to fit their needs.
That'd explain why she
led us on the wrong patrol route.
Right.
But we shouldn't tell her that. She'd feel responsible.
Uiharu...
Could you tell me more about that?
Uh...
Yes.
But first, would you please brew us some tea?
Sorry to ask that of you right after you woke up.
O-Okay.
Sh-Shirai!
Your will to protect your friends is wonderful.
Uiharu isn't so weak as to crack over this.
Mind control...
I see.
I was getting in your way without even knowing it.
Once we finish this tea,
let's get back to investigating.
Uiharu, please look for suspicious
individuals in the student records.
Really? What if someone
makes me hide something again?
We have no time to have you
thoroughly checked, but we need your help.
If you're worried, then work where
we can see what you are doing.
Or do you want to go back and rest?
Not at all! I'll get ready right away!
Well played.
Let's just not tell her that our
brains were meddled with as well.
You can go back to your job now.
The conference is being held in there.
I already took care of security.
Kihara Gensei is in there?
If you promise not to interfere,
you can just sit here and watch.
You must be kidding.
It's time to put a fork in the people
who can only achieve anything by sacrificing others.
Wait! Hey!
Level Six. It's beyond what's
possible with current abilities.
Even Accelerator would've needed
the sacrifice of 20,000 clones.
Whatever Kihara Gensei is planning,
the cost will probably be greater even than that.
If such a cost is considered acceptable,
what does that make this city,
all aimed at reaching for the heavens?
Hold on.
I can't afford to get absorbed in my thoughts
while infiltrating hostile territory.
Shokuhou...
She's gone?
The road didn't branch before here.
She couldn't get lost.
She tricked me?
You got me with that nice story,
but if it's war you want—
Wait... for god's sake...! I told you... to wait up...!
Would it kill you... to listen...?!
Don't get so worked up all by yourself!
I brought you here, so we should move together!
Don't just sprint in like that!
That was more of a light jog...
W-Well, we do have different weight distribution.
I bet your air resistance is lower as well.
No wonder you can't imagine my struggle.
More like you have the fitness of a deep-sea sponge.
Excuse me?! I'm perfectly fit!
Now that I think about it,
I've never seen you in PE class.
So what, do I have to be an athlete now?
What is this, grade school?
Oh wait, is that why you have
the physique of a child?
My figure's got nothing to do with this!
What about that twinkle of yours?
What is this, a comic book?
I was born with it! Didn't your parents teach
you not to make fun of others' bodies?
Look who's talking now!
Now that I think about it,
bringing you along was definitely a mistake.
I was going to deal with this all by myself.
We don't have to go in hand-in-hand like chums.
Yeah. Having you nearby
isn't exactly reassuring for me either.
Let's split up.
Don't get in the way.
Same to you.
Uh, reporting in...
I found out that the one who
stole information from our villas
was not Misaka Mikoto,
but fifth-ranked Shokuhou Misaki.
She must've set her up to cover up the evidence
she couldn't hide with memory manipulation.
She was aware that MEMBER
was ordered not to kill Misaka Mikoto.
You just found out, Kouzaku Mitori?
You knew? You should've told me, then!
Even if I told you, your job would be the same.
You continue with the preparations as planned.
Do you know, can you recall, about the promise that we made so long ago
I guess.
Are you sure about that, though?
You can guess what Shokuhou Misaki
would want with that information.
After it's done, wonder if I will fade away into the dark
Don't worry. There's no need for concern.
I know we've gone well past the point of no return to living righteously
It's all green.
Honestly, I'm a bit worried with how well it's going.
But I still feel just a little freed
I need to reach through to the world that lies beyond that lingering memory
As I fall into a slumber
Flashing back to that day
Fighting to hold back the tears that I can't bear to shed
I'm doing whatever it takes just to fight through to my destiny
I could never just believe that fates are predecided
Yet, somehow, people still find their meaning
As they struggle through this story without a name
In this cruel world of suffering
I find myself just trying to bring back those days again
They can't come back
Next Time
I'm going in!
Kouzaku Mitori
If there are any guards, I'll knock 'em out.
If there's a wall in my way,
I'll hit it with my railgun.
Good Luck Charm
Maybe the reason my Mental Out doesn't work
on Misaka isn't because of her electro-barrier,
but because her brain is made of muscle?