You're awake?
This is a certain building in district 2.
"Did you rescue me?"
—asks Misaka in an expression of gratitude.
This is but a part of my job.
Nothing to be grateful for.
She fell asleep again.
Oh my.
I hoped I finally had a decent task for a change...
I feel your heart beat on beyond the hands of time
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Believing that our bond will last until the end
The fervor to protect you growing day by day
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they'll never fade
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they’ll never fade
In the fragile, tender kindness of your bright eyes
There's a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
There’s a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
All the wonderful times that we spent side by side
Will live within my memories eternally
As my mind overflowed thinking of you
More than I could ever hope to explain
I turned the pain of the loss that I felt
To power I'd never known
To power I’d never known
And I keep rushing into the light
No one can stop this phase
Now that we're hand in hand
Now that we’re hand in hand
I etched a vow into the fabric of my mind
So I can keep you safe whatever perils come
I take your hand in my own and never let it go
The time that I have spent just standing by your side
Is all that I have ever wanted to recall
Until at last the day comes when I see you smile
Know that I’m never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
Know that I'm never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
So Kihara Gensei's after the place
shown on that urban legends site?
That's right.
But how did he find it?
It wasn't me!
I know. You'd have to have been a time traveler.
What if he's just trying to trick you into going back?
He could find the place by tailing us there.
That's possible.
But even if he did find the place,
that wouldn't achieve anything.
Worst case—
Hey! Why are we stopping...
A traffic jam?!
What's going on?
One of the automated buses apparently
exploded and burst into flames.
Bus service is suspended while
the cause is being investigated.
The buses were a main mode of transport
for the Starlight Games spectators,
so this is causing kilometers-long traffic jams.
We're blocked in now.
I've got no choice.
Exterior.
Open overriding counter-current beyond pair 13.
Shokuhou?
The road...
Hurry through! Full speed!
Y-Yes!
Did she do this?
Controlling thousands of people,
kilometers apart, all at once?
She may have the strongest mental power
of any esper in Academy City,
but she shouldn't have such nightmare-level powers.
How did she do it?
I can't let them take over
that place before I get there.
Makuwa, what are you eating?
A melon. Isn't it obvious?
What is the food you most dislike?
Apples.
Shokuhou.
Your ability is developing well.
The Exterior will be complete soon, too.
I don't need that thing, though.
Don't be like that.
This project is important
for you as well, not just for us.
So? Can I go home now?
No. I'd like to introduce you to someone.
How are you feeling today?
Let me introduce you.
This is our prototype. We've been calling her Dolly.
A prototype?
Come on! What did I tell you about greetings?
No!
What's the big deal?
Not like you've got boobs worth looking at.
Don't look at me.
My.
Well, one less thing to explain.
She was born with a kind of illness, you see.
She can't stay alive without
the devices embedded in her.
Sorry.
Did I creep you out?
Nah. No big deal.
I know it is.
I used to have a friend.
She's called Mii.
I can't go outside,
but she came to visit me every day.
We'd chat about all kinda things.
She'd play with me, too.
But then,
she saw my scars...
and the next day she stopped coming.
Why does my body have to be like this?
It freaked out my only friend...
I wanna see her again so bad...
Clone Dolly
Laboratory #2
So?
Why'd you make me meet her?
We are gathering certain data from her.
The shock of losing her friend was apparently too great,
and her numbers are all over the place.
We'd like you to help her regain her inner peace.
That's more than I can do.
At my current level I can't erase her memories
of her friend; I could barely even modify them.
Indeed. But her facial perception...
Excuse me.
You came again, Mii!
Why do I have to babysit her?
Ugh, look what you've done...
Are you really in junior high?
Yeah!
Here.
The doctor told me I would be, anyway.
I've never been to school though, whatever that is.
Do you like school?
Hmm, hard to say...
It's easy to get shunned for my ability.
Shunned?
Uh... Hated, I guess?
Really?
I like your ability.
Here!
No. I was told not to use it.
What's it like outside the facility?
I'd like to see the ocean...
Too bad. There's no shoreline in Academy City.
The checkpoints are so strict,
getting out of the city is pretty hard.
But if you can get an excursion permit,
I'll take you to see the ocean.
Thanks a lot, Mii!
Hey!
Wh-What are you doing?
Never mind.
I don't get it.
It's going well.
Yes. Let's keep observing for now.
I'm done!
Yay! I win again!
I did it!
Hey! That's bad manners.
You always walk up to the trash to throw it out.
O-Of course!
Budding ladies throwing trash like that
goes against good manners and fine decorum!
It might be fine now, here in the facility,
but once you get outside,
the boys will be watching your every move!
You must learn how to act with dignit—
You can't do it?
E-Excuse me?! It's easy as pie!
Really?
All right, I'll show you!
I... uh, a finger hit it in the wrong place!
I-I forgot air resistance!
Oh, something went in my eye!
I'll make it the next time!
She's getting closer and closer.
Darn!
Good luck!
Concentrate! Concentrate!
It went in! Did you see that, Dolly? I can do it if—
H-Hey! Someone!
Report.
They'll be here to pick her up soon.
What a mess.
I figured it'd be sooner than later...
Get a hold of yourself...
This can't be...
Tell me...
What?
Tell me your... name...
Misaki. Shokuhou Misaki.
Misaki...
thanks for being my friend.
She's gonna be fine, right?
She'll get well and come back right away?
No. This is your farewell.
Her body's been past its natural limit for some time.
Even with the science of Academy City,
it would've been impossible
to extend her life any further.
I'm sure Dolly was aware of that as well.
Clone Dolly
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Oh, you're here again?
You're behind your curriculum. This won't do.
Oh, right, they told me to tell you.
That girl died.
What a mess.
Now it's Shokuhou acting up.
Who'd have thought she had feelings?
We could tell her that she was a clone.
If she knew she was artificial,
maybe that'd make it easier for her.
Sure.
We can try that if she doesn't improve.
Project Exterior isn't like that puppet
the higher-ups forced us to deal with.
It's the long-awaited fruit
of the Clone Dolly group's efforts.
But I have my concerns.
If Shokuhou keeps growing at this rate, one day
our mental guards won't be able to keep her out.
After that it will be nigh-impossible
to keep the goal of the project from her.
That shouldn't be a problem.
Oh?
And why would that be?
Once the Exterior is complete,
that girl will be of no use to us.
We should just get rid of her at the first chance.
That concludes our regular meeting.
Thank you all.
I figured that'd be it.
I spread my rule under the surface after that.
I brainwashed everyone on the Exterior project.
They wouldn't be able to squeal
even under extreme torture.
How did Gensei find it?
Target has passed the checkpoint.
Roger.
All units retreat!
They accepted that as a legal finish.
Good Luck
All thanks to this.
Her name was Saten, right?
We were supposed to be meeting here.
Crap.
No
Signal
No signal?
Don't bother.
There's very powerful jamming over this whole area.
By the looks of it, he wasn't bluffing.
This is weird. It's too quiet.
There don't seem to be any
automated weapons either.
Did they run away scared of Misaka?
What about the people who worked here?
Who knows?
They maintain the Exterior,
so I doubt they'd kill them.
Exterior?
I showed you earlier.
Earlier?
The Exterior is a system
that boosts and extends my ability.
Officially, anyway.
Officially?
The original goal of Project Exterior
was to enable anyone to use my ability.
What?!
Regardless of whether the
registered user is an esper or not,
they can utilize Mental Out.
That's the kind of toy it is.
Oh?
Originally Clone Dolly was a research group aimed
at creating geniuses and super-powered espers.
But once they saw what my ability could do,
they realized it could just brainwash existing ones,
and switched gears to build the Exterior instead.
I took it over and put a stop to their plans.
It takes a noble mind like mine
to control Mental Out.
It would be nothing short of dangerous
in the hands of some lowlife.
So it wasn't enough for them to amplify your ability;
they wanted to give it to others too?
Is that the "DNA computer that creates abilities"
from the urban legend site?
I wonder where those rumors come from.
It's not even a computer.
I want to keep this secret, but here I am,
showing it to you of all people.
They cut out a piece of my cerebral cortex,
cultivated it, and grew it into this giant brain.
That's what the Exterior is.
And Kihara Gensei wants to use this for something?
Probably.
But they couldn't take it away.
Not to mention how using it requires going
through a registration process that takes days.
That's right. Even if they took this place over,
it'd take a while to be useful.
Are they after that Sister after all?
But I put multiple protections
over her with my ability.
They'd need to use the Exterior to unlock those.
I can't think of any gaps in my defenses.
Your little sister was getting treated
in a room over there.
Come.
It connected?
Hello?
Finally, I got through.
I'm at the Exterior. Where are you?
On the roof. She's with me too.
Great work!
The roof! I'll be right—
No.
The attackers appeared to be
a skilled special ops team.
I was carrying her.
I doubt they'd just let me slip through.
I must assume they wanted me to take her here.
Be careful.
I'll be fine!
I've got an amazon with me whose
bust size was converted to battle skill.
No need to worry.
I wonder who that might be.
Shokuhou?
I see. If she's with you—
This wasn't part of the plan,
but one less thing to worry about.
I can't move?
What?
Hey!
Hello.
It can't be!
Keitz Nokleben
You wanted to prevent hijacking
by making registration ridiculously slow?
You're so naïve.
If I tune the giant brain to my brainwave frequency,
its power is mine without registration.
You've heard the rumors too, haven't you?
The Level Upper!
I gave the brainwave tuning instructions to Kiyama.
Getting through the layers of protection
on the Sisters will be easy for me now.
"No!"
"This shouldn't be happening!" Says Misaka as Misaka...
What's wrong?
"All the protections on 10032 have
been removed!" Says Misaka as Misaka...
As is installing a custom virus
on the MISAKA Network.
The equal and opposite forces on an object—
Is that the MISAKA Network?
No, wait...
What is this feeling?
Get going already.
What does that goopy girl want out of this?
I don't know the details.
We were following false orders.
There were some weird things
about the missions, though.
I asked her about it.
I didn't get a straight answer,
but I could guess at the truth.
There she is!
How wonderful.
But this great power is just a giant light show
if nobody's putting it to good use.
What would the most amusing thing to do with it?
What did you do to her?!
How about we use it to detonate
the sleeping powers of Aleister's little favorite
who's been hiding in the shadow of Plan A?
They're actually after Misaka Mikoto.
Let the experiment commence.
Do you know, can you recall, about the promise that we made so long ago
After it's done, wonder if I will fade away into the dark
Misaka,
can you reach the will of the heavens, Level 6?
I know we've gone well past the point of no return to living righteously
But I still feel just a little freed
I need to reach through to the world that lies beyond that lingering memory
As I fall into a slumber
Flashing back to that day
Fighting to hold back the tears that I can't bear to shed
I'm doing whatever it takes just to fight through to my destiny
I could never just believe that fates are predecided
Yet, somehow, people still find their meaning
As they struggle through this story without a name
In this cruel world of suffering
I find myself just trying to bring back those days again
They can't come back
Next Time
Just like that, Misaka's down for the count!
Join the Fray
Starting next week I'll be starring in a new show
in this slot: A Certain Scientific Mental Out!
That preview style is freaking ancient.
Are you really junior high-age?
You're supposed to be down, so stuff it!