I know you can hear me.
I made sure to leave the communication device intact.
If I ever again see a robot of yours
near me or my friends, even for an instant,
no matter where you are, I'm going to find you,
and crush you.
He ran away.
Well, any memories he had of Shokuhou
have probably been erased or altered,
so whatever.
There's no useful information in the vehicle either.
This was planned meticulously.
It was clear from the moment
he brought out that kind of robot:
this is no amateur job.
A vehicle this large can't take narrow alleys,
which limits its possible routes.
I should be able to use surveillance camera footage
to trace it back to where they're keeping her.
I feel your heart beat on beyond the hands of time
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Believing that our bond will last until the end
The fervor to protect you growing day by day
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they'll never fade
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they’ll never fade
In the fragile, tender kindness of your bright eyes
There's a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
There’s a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
All the wonderful times that we spent side by side
Will live within my memories eternally
As my mind overflowed thinking of you
More than I could ever hope to explain
I turned the pain of the loss that I felt
To power I'd never known
To power I’d never known
And I keep rushing into the light
No one can stop this phase
Now that we're hand in hand
Now that we’re hand in hand
I etched a vow into the fabric of my mind
So I can keep you safe whatever perils come
I take your hand in my own and never let it go
The time that I have spent just standing by your side
Is all that I have ever wanted to recall
Until at last the day comes when I see you smile
Know that I’m never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
Know that I'm never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
You still don't know where Misaka is?
No.
Well, we have no other options.
We'll split up in groups of three again—
I'm so sorry, but we're supposed to
take part in an event very soon.
We can't really excuse so many of us skipping out.
Oh, just great!
But we still have to search with whoever's left.
If only the Queen were here, she'd know what to do.
Are you still unable to reach her?
Not since last evening.
What queen were they talking about?
Where could she be?
It's Shokuhou Misaki from our school.
That's what her clique's members call her.
Really?
Queen?
Shokuhou Misaki was the one
who can manipulate memories, right?
Rich girls are weird.
Thank you very much.
Wannai, how is Kongou doing?
According to the doctor, she fortunately
has no wounds that would leave scars.
He said he'll send for a specialist
regarding the nano-devices.
So she's not in any immediate danger, then?
Yes, indeed.
As for what we could do to assist her...
We are sorry to bother you again.
Don't worry about it.
So you... can talk to cats?
No. My ability is psychometry.
It's its own thing, separate from telepathy.
It doesn't allow for two-way communication.
All I can do is read fragments of the qualia—
that is, the sensory experiences—of animals.
On the bright side, it lets me put together
the kinds of complex connections
that a little kitty couldn't comprehend.
I see.
You're interested in yesterday around noon, right?
Yes, that's what I've been told.
Let's see.
It's at a construction site
or a materials storage area.
There's a tall man.
I also see the back of a woman, I think.
They start talking.
"I don't care how, we just have to beat them to it."
"I have other things to worry about right now."
"What's the status on auribus oculi fideliores sunt?"
Is that Latin?
"The eyes are more trustworthy than the ears."
Maybe it's a code phrase.
Um...
It would be difficult to get any more.
The kitten was quite flustered at the time.
That's plenty. Thank you so much.
Even if we do not understand what it's about,
it may be valuable information to Misaka.
Saten, do you have your phone?
Yes, it's right here.
The situation being what it is, it's probably
a good idea to inform Misaka immediately.
Can we ask you to do that for us?
Sure.
All right, thank you for taking care of that.
We'll be in Kongou's hospital room if you need us.
Got it.
Now then...
Wait! I don't have Misaka's contact...
I do?
Checking every camera one by one
would take too much time.
They might get away before I can find them.
'''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''''
Tokiwadai Middle School wins Balloon Sandwich event!
Mikoto seems pretty dedicated.
Mom approves.
There. Everything's going to be okay.
You don't need to worry, I'm here with you.
I recognize that head.
Uiharu!
Miss Misuzu!
And who's this boy?
He got lost.
Oh, that's quite the pickle
with so many people around.
Want some help?
No need. His parents are already heading this way.
Really?
Yes.
The badge you received for
the event contains a GPS tracker,
so HQ can track any of the visitors if needed.
It's dad!
Daddy!
Make sure to stick together!
PASS
Academy City
Starlight Games School Invitee
Misaka Misuzu
I see.
I was wondering how they're
keeping an eye on so many visitors.
But of course they had a plan.
But then, if you hack that system,
it's quite easy to find any visitor you want,
mother of Misaka Mikoto.
I was thinking one hostage would suffice,
but then, I'm up against
the third-ranking Level 5 esper.
I'd feel better if I had an extra one.
What is it that you wanted
to talk about out of the blue?
Um...
I have things to do, you know.
Please get straight to the point.
Okay.
You see...
What's her condition?
Her life is not at risk.
Wannai and Awatsuki are with her.
She'll probably be fine.
I see.
Someone managed to do that to Kongou Mitsuko.
Yes.
And Misaka seemed really angry.
Perhaps she felt responsible.
Misaka Mikoto again?
I think I have a good idea of what's been happening,
but don't you think it's a bit of a stretch to conclude
that we may be acquainted with Misaka Mikoto?
That's why I said "may".
Misaka Mikoto
Miyao Eri
Mimura Ayaka
Mikihara Megumi
Masuda Makoto
After all, there's an esper at Tokiwadai
who can manipulate memories.
You think Shokuhou Misaki
manipulated our memories?
To what possible end?
Also, if that's what you think,
why haven't you called Uiharu?
Well, if my theory is correct,
telling Uiharu could be a problem.
A-Anyway,
I have to call her to relay the information,
so I'll use the opportunity to ask her.
Well, I guess we should.
As a member of Judgment,
I should investigate the situation.
Who could be calling me now?
Incoming Call
Saten Ruiko
Saten?!
Hello?
Um, is this Misaka?
My name is Saten Ruiko.
Thank you for telling me about
what happened at the hospital.
You're welcome.
So, I heard from Wannai
that you're looking for your sister.
Why are you so nervous about this?
So, we had the psychometrist
examine the black kitten.
I see.
However, I'm sorry to say this
after you went to the trouble,
but neither the description
of the man with Shokuhou,
nor the contents of their conversation ring any bells.
About that, the conversation
included a name that I know quite well.
Really?!
I also wanted to ask you more
about our relationship with you.
Could we meet up in person?
Okay, let's do that.
Can you tell me where you are?
The plaza in front of the station building
in District 10. The upper level.
Oh, that's quite close to us.
If you stay there, I can have Shirai
pick you up and bring you—
Hold on! I'm not a taxi, you know!
Are you with Kuroko?
I told you not to call me by
my first name like we're friends!
Misaka.
There's a little something I'd like to ask you about.
I'm busy at the moment.
I don't have time for weirdos like you.
Unless of course you're with
the people who hurt my friend!
Whoa, you went right into battle mode,
but how does this make you feel?
A Certain Scientific Railgun
The Eyes Are More
Trustworthy Than the Ears
Uiharu!
Let's first have you hang up and drop the phone.
Good girl.
I guess I don't need to introduce myself.
After all, you assaulted several of our villas
and rummaged through our data.
Villas?
Assaulted?
What's this about?
Non, non. There's no use denying it.
You've been investigating us,
so I'm sure you know what I want to ask.
Your clones, the Sisters.
Where are you hiding them?
We know that you obstructed
the Level 6 Shift Project.
You can't tell me you don't know what
happened to the Sisters after it was canceled.
Where are the clones left in Academy City hiding?
What's going on here?
I thought she was with Shokuhou.
We have the Dark Side's
information network on full alert,
but all leads on the Sisters turn up dead ends.
Just how good is the security
of the people you left them with?
I have no idea who you people are,
but what do you want so badly
that you'd attack my friends?
Oh, my. I really didn't expect to hear that from you.
From where I stand,
you're the weird one, able to live in a city
like this and pretend everything's fine and dandy.
I mean, I know that you've seen some things.
The inhumane plans for creating a Level 6.
The human experimentation on Child Errors.
Using negotiators to swindle people
out of their DNA maps.
Those are not just single organizations
acting on their own.
All of it can be traced back
to the higher-ups of Academy City.
You know that even this very city
is one big experiment.
That's right. You're not just one of
the random students who know nothing.
And yet, you avert your eyes from reality
and spend your days without a bother.
I'm amazed that you can act like it's nothing.
It's not that I—
Anyway.
I don't see the connection.
What does all of that have to do
with you hurting my friends?
I have nothing to tell you.
Release Uiharu.
My electricity will pierce you
before you can use that knife.
Uiharu, you say.
So you do know her, then.
You see, I saw her being friendly
with your mother, so I assumed as much.
My mother?
That's Mom!
And another...
Not even you can take
both of us out at the same time.
It shouldn't be difficult to choose between
the location of the clones and the lives of these two.
Let me ask again: Where are the Sisters?
And I'll tell you the same again:
I have nothing to tell you.
Oh, my. Might you be thinking that we're bluffing?
Or are you prepared to sacrifice one of them?
I'm going to save Uiharu.
Even if it costs me my life.
No matter what.
Is that any way to treat your mother? So cruel!
Seriously?
Oh, my. I guess the negotiations fell through.
I'm sorry, missus,
but we can't have people taking us lightly.
You can blame your daughter for abandoning you.
She had an ally in hiding?
Breathing, pulse, and body temperature are normal.
No visible external wounds.
She ran.
I'd love to give chase,
but securing the hostages is top priority.
And I can question the other one.
Uiharu is okay.
She doesn't seem to be hurt.
Please stand back!
What?
I'm with Judgment!
You're under arrest for abduction and blackmail of—
Kuroko!
Get away from her!
She's not human!
My spikes are ineffective.
Kuroko, teleport these two somewhere safe.
Zapping her with electricity didn't do much.
Can the railgun blow her away?
She melted?!
Is that liquid metal?
I guess someone was remote-
controlling it like a puppet.
But why did it suddenly fall apart?
I don't know.
If it's the ability of the other woman we saw,
maybe she went out of range.
Well, we wouldn't want Mikoto dead anyway.
Still, direct face-to-face negotiation is hard.
But she can do all kinds of stuff over a video connection.
Anyway, at least I didn't come away
empty-handed, so I guess it's fine.
Villas?
Assaulted?
What's this about?
I didn't get into it when she said it,
but she had no reason to feign innocence.
We had assumed it was her from the witness reports,
but those may have been fake.
Or maybe
the memories of the witnesses were altered.
I guess I have to look into that again.
Also...
It's not that I—
There may be hope for her yet.
All right, please explain to me what's going on.
I'm sorry, I myself have no idea who that person—
That does concern me, but first I want
to know about your actions back there.
You were acting as if you knew I was there.
You said that you'd save Uiharu,
and not your mother.
Those words were meant for me, weren't they?
Well, after I hung up the phone,
I felt Uiharu's phone getting a call by the EM waves.
I assumed it was Saten calling her
to check what's happening.
I had just given you my location,
and I knew you could make it
there in under ten seconds,
so I assumed that you were lying in wait nearby.
Thank you.
For trusting me with rescuing your friend.
Uiharu is a member of Judgment.
It's only natural to prioritize the civilian.
More importantly, I'm amazed you'd entrust
your mother's life to someone else.
She'd be mad at me if I'd
prioritized her life and not my friend's.
Plus,
I trusted that you'd be there to save my mom.
O-Of course.
It is part of my job after all.
What else—
Are you all right?
I'm sorry I made you strain yourself
when you're still hurt.
I-I'm fine!
I don't need your help!
Nonsense.
Come on, grab on to me properly.
P-Please let go of me.
I'm not into this kind of thing!
They said they're both fine and will wake up soon.
Thank goodness.
So? Wasn't there something
you wanted to talk to her about?
Oh, yeah.
So, the one who kidnapped your sister,
the person the kitten saw,
it was Shokuhou Misaki, right?
Yes, I'm fairly certain about that.
So, the thing we heard from the psychometrist,
auribus something, the phrase in Latin,
it's the same as the name of
an urban legend site I've seen.
Urban legend site?
Why would Shokuhou Misaki
concern herself with such a thing?
That site's thing was that
they don't just gather rumors,
they actually try to verify the information.
So while I was out looking
for shadow metal yesterday,
Uiharu tried to find the site,
but she said it wasn't there.
And just now when I tried looking for it,
the search results are full
of pages that look the same,
but the site I'm looking for doesn't come up.
It's impossible to completely erase
information once it's on the web,
so maybe someone created lots of dummy pages
and pushed them up in the search results,
so that people can't find the site.
That would mean that there is information
on the site that this person doesn't want known.
Exactly.
If Uiharu felt something was suspicious,
she would try to find out more.
And she has the skills to do it.
But then whoever hid the site
noticed Uiharu prying and went after her.
Assuming it was Shokuhou,
she made her erase the data.
Then she searched Uiharu's memory and
that's how she found that we were friends.
It adds up... I guess.
It's a rough theory I came up with
trying to connect the dots.
But if I'm right, then on that computer...
It's worth investigating.
She reconstructed the erased data!
There it is!
MISSION:5
llllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
Technology lying hidden behind heavy defenses?!
Chasing the cutting-edge DNA computer
that creates esper abilities!
Shokuhou!
Do you know, can you recall, about the promise that we made so long ago
After it's done, wonder if I will fade away into the dark
I know we've gone well past the point of no return to living righteously
But I still feel just a little freed
I need to reach through to the world that lies beyond that lingering memory
As I fall into a slumber
Flashing back to that day
Fighting to hold back the tears that I can't bear to shed
I'm doing whatever it takes just to fight through to my destiny
I could never just believe that fates are predecided
Yet, somehow, people still find their meaning
As they struggle through this story without a name
In this cruel world of suffering
I find myself just trying to bring back those days again
They can't come back
Next Time
Tokiwadai's Railgun.
Railgun
Railgun and Mental Out
A vexing girl who just flaunts being a Level 5.
Or so I thought.
But what was that smile?!
Why does it stir up my heart so violently?!
Isn't it because you're a perv?