Please eat your fill,
Mother.
Let's have our breakfast, too, Hibiki.
Okay, Dad.
It's your first day at your new school.
Will you be okay?
Yes.
Do you have everything?
If you have any sort of trouble...
If I have any trouble,
everyone will be there to help.
Okay, then. Be careful.
Off you go.
See you later.
I Can See Them.
She looks like a princess or something.
I wonder if I'd look like her if I let my hair down...
Oh, yeah...
I'm sorry! I'm just, uh...
What are you doing?! That's dangerous!
C'mon, let's get going.
Okay.
Seriously...
Did you hurt your foot or something?
What if something had happened to you
right there in the middle of the street?
Thank you.
He was just playing a little joke, though.
He didn't mean any harm.
Huh?
Our story is starting, now let's walk together
so that these miraculous days never end.
Yes! Let's go now.
After our boundless dreams.
When I lay out the map of my future,
my heart starts throbbing, telling me to make my move.
Sometimes I'll inevitably end up
shedding a few tears,
but let's keep our eyes on the future.
The curiosity that's driving me
right at this moment is still a mystery,
but I do know that I want to find out the answers with you.
Our story is starting, now let's walk together
so that these miraculous days never end.
Yes! Let's go now.
Our harmony resounds throughout the world.
We'll never forget to wear our smiles
with everything that makes this moment shine.
Yes! Go my way.
We'll keep dreaming on and on.
One Week Later
Caution
Slasher
Murder
Site
Come here...
Caution
QITIQXODZIZXGHX
XHGZXIZOXDQTIX
GXZOQTZIX
Come here...
Caution
Slasher
Murder
Site
S-Sorry, but I'm on my way to school.
Caution
Slasher
Murder
Site
I know.
But as a soul bound to the place of my death, this is what I do.
U-Um... I'll stop by again on my way home.
Caution
Slasher
Murder
Site
Do as you please.
You know, it's been about
a week since I last saw you.
Have you gotten used to your new school?
Yes!
Thank goodness I wasn't late!
Morning, Amami-san!
Good morning, Ogawa-san.
You too, Uehara-san.
Hey.
And you, Esumi-san.
'Sup.
Really?
Yeah!
Looks like Amami's finally warmed up to this place.
She had a lot of trouble at first.
She'd randomly start talking to thin air,
Good morning!
and then she'd skirt around invisible obstacles.
Excuse me!
Yeah. She has that thing that
lets you see spirits. A sixth sense.
I was a little creeped out by her at first, but...
Don't push me!
I guess we've just gotten used to it.
Amami-san!
Amami-san, are you all right?
Y-Yes, I'm fine.
I-I appreciate the thought,
but I can open doors myself.
Every door is automatic for her.
The ghosts must really like her.
Hey!
Good morning, Amami-sa—
P-Please wake up, Yamada-san!
Hey, new kid!
Inoue-san!
Good morning.
Don't give me that "good morning" crap!
Come on, at least say hello to her.
Sh-Shut up.
Oh, screw it!
I'm gonna give it to you straight right now.
This "sixth sense" or whatever you call it is ridiculous!
Wow, she's not wasting any time this morning.
Inoue-san hates paranormal stuff.
That said, why aren't you three bothered by any of this?
Well, it's not like we can see them.
Amami's the only one they mess with.
We're sort of used to it.
Yeah.
I swear, every last one of you is totally nuts!
Well, I don't believe any of it!
U-Um...
You're free to regard me however you like, but...
I hope you'll believe your grandma.
She's right behind you.
Nana, are you there?!
Inoue's a grandma's girl?
You can't fool me with your lies!
B-But...
Stop following empty space with your eyes!
Settle down, Inoue.
Don't bully your classmates, or else...
Or else what?
Or else your beloved grandma will hate you.
Gotcha.
Nana would never hate me!
Does she believe in ghosts or not?
Hey, look! There's a cat!
Isn't it cute?
Come to think of it, didn't you say
you could speak to cats, Amami-san?
Yes, but only a little.
Whoa, a whole gaggle of chicks in bloomers!
Can't get enough of those plump thighs!
C'mon, what's the problem?!
Don't be a prude! Lemme see!
Wow! You're very good at this.
A friend taught me how to cut them this way.
Oh, I didn't know we had such a prodigy here!
Yes, right over here.
Huh?
So, what is the person who taught you like?
Well...
She has beautiful hands, with long fingers.
Why her hands?
Wouldn't most people describe the face?
Well, actually, she hasn't found the rest of her body yet.
But I'm sure that her face is very beautiful, too.
I can't hear you!
What are you doing, Amami?
Oh, I promised a girl who lives near me that I'd give her a handkerchief.
I'm embroidering her name on this one.
Who is she?
Hanako-san. She haunts the toilet at West Gate Park.
She finally brings up a name I recognize, and yet I'm not happy. Why is that?
It's best not to think about it.
Hanako is a very common name, very common, very—
What's wrong, Amami?
C'mon, tell us what happened.
Yesterday, Hanako-san,
the girl I gave the handkerchief to...
She disappeared!
Her last words were "thank you"...
Hanako-san went to the other side!
She crossed over!
H-How long are you gonna cry in here?
She disappeared, that's all.
You'll run into her again sooner or later.
Inoue-san...
J-Just so you know,
I don't believe in ghosts, okay?
Right.
Thank you.
I'm in here!
She followed you to school!
Forget it! I'll never accept you!
The school is so creepy in the evening.
This is when you run into things
you really don't want to run into.
Why...
I-Inoue-san?
Why did it have to be the new kid?!
Um, why are you here so late?
I-I'm the class rep. I had work to do.
You're not going to tell me you're
hanging out with a ghost, are you?
How did you know?
You're not even trying to spin it?!
We were all playing hide and seek, actually,
but I can't seem to find any of them.
Who plays hide and seek with things that are invisible to begin with?!
That's what I want to say...
But I'm afraid it'll come back around to me twofold!
Hanazuka Prefectural High School
U-Um...
Inoue-san?
What is it?
We both walk the same way to the station, right?
Yeah, so?
We walk... the same way...
W-Wait for me!
Hey there, ladies. Let's see those panties—
Kitty?
Are you all right?
I... I kinda liked that...
West Gate Park
U-Um... Inoue-san!
I'd really like to walk with you.
Why? You'll be fine by yourself—
She's not fine at all!
Lately, the kids around here call for me a lot.
Kids? What kids?
What do you want to play today?
I knew it, and yet I still asked.
Inoue-san, would you like to play, too?
No way!
I-It's okay. Don't cry, kids.
I-I made them cry? I didn't mean to...
You don't have to be scared. It's okay...
I'm sorry!
I just remembered I have somewhere to go.
Huh?
I'll be right back. Please just wait here.
Wait... At a time like this?!
Wh-What are you so scared of?
I'm a lot more scared than you are!
What the heck am I doing,
out here with no one around?
I'm leavi—
Seriously, what's the deal with that new kid?
Manipulating me like that...
Will you play with us?
Why should I...
C'mon, it's past sundown already.
It's dangerous for kids to be out,
so go home before it gets dark...
O-Oh, fine.
I'll play with you for a little while.
Really?
J-Just for a little while!
We'll play for a bit, and then you're going straight home.
I thought you were kinda scary,
but you're actually nice!
Wh-What are you talking about?
She's a tsundere!
Where'd you learn that word?
Let's play hide and seek!
Tag!
Red light, green light!
Wait—Which is it?!
S-Sorry to keep you waiting!
Finally!
Where did you go?!
Oh, right!
I bought a few things.
Some yummy snacks!
Shopping, huh? Well, aren't you special?
I'm not... I'm really not...
You have no idea what I've been through.
These kids I don't even know asked me to play,
and I couldn't say no...
And then they just vanished.
Huh?
They just left without saying a word.
Kids these days are so rude.
And it'll be dark soon.
They'd better have gotten home safely.
So, why did you go out to buy snacks, anyway?
It's an offering... for the children.
If...
And I mean if the sixth sense is real,
what good is it?
All it does is scare people
and place more burdens on you.
There's nothing good about it.
Inoue-san.
What?
These offerings don't ever go away.
Huh?
Of course they don't.
You can't eat when you're dead.
Yes... You're right.
But I can see them.
I see them happily eating the offerings.
It's not a one-way street.
Everyone, alive or dead,
shares a bond through the same feelings.
And through my sixth sense,
I can confirm those bonds are real.
Ever since I was little, this power
has helped me form many bonds.
It still does.
It created a chance for me to talk with you.
It helped us grow
a little closer.
I-I'm sorry! I'm getting full of myself!
I shouldn't assume that we're on friendly terms...
Bonds, huh?
Um...
I-Is something wrong?
I was just resigning myself. Don't worry about it.
Okay then.
It's about to get really dark. Let's head home...
Amami.
Inoue-san, did you just...
Shut up! Let's just go, Amami!
Okay!
Come play with us again, okay?
Hey, did you say something?
No.
But...
I just saw another beautiful bond form.
Why'd you want to walk home with me, anyway?
W-Well...
It's love!
I-It's not! I just wanted to talk a little more...
A-Are you talking to that cat?
So it's not... um...
Oh, yeah, I can talk to cats.
And this cat isn't just an ordinary cat—
No! I don't wanna hear it!
I see 'em!
P-Please, wait!
Like I'm gonna wait just because you tell me to!
Please don't say that!
Stay away from me!
Please wait! Please!
Go away!
I said stay away!
Girl-on-girl lovin'. Heh.
Wow!
Mysterious fluffballs!
Wow! Wow! Wow!
We won't tell the adults!
Have you noticed it? Do you feel it?
See with the mind's eye.
I want to get possessed and be loved.
An after-school sensation.
Common sense means nothing to high-school girls
with a "que sera, sera" attitude.
Out of our way, ghosts!
Abracadablovelove!
Wow! Wow!
You should join us too!
Smile! Smile! Smile!
Let's have a blast!
We only have one chance to be young,
so we should enjoy it to the fullest.
Evil spirits, vengeful spirits, all welcome.
Yeah!
Nothing's impossible in this world.
There are all sorts of strange events and phantoms.
Yeah!
Come what may, we'll never back down.
What does it mean to be ordinary?
Yeah?
If only the gods know the answer,
Yeah!
they can keep it to themselves!
After all...
Ignorance is bliss.
Next Time
Good evening. I'm Amami Hibiki.
If you stay up too late, it'll be hard to wake up in the morning.
Please be careful, everyone.
I'm a bit sleep-deprived myself...
It's not that I was up late, but I just...
It's embarrassing to say, but a lot happened.
Next time on Re-Kan!:
"They're My Friends."
They're My Friends.
Make sure to watch with everyone
behind your back and above your head.