We Are All Connected.
Aizawa.
Here.
Akaishi.
Amami.
Amami?
Hey, Amami.
Here.
Is something wrong, Amami?
You've had trouble focusing lately.
I'm sorry.
Our story is starting, now let's walk together
so that these miraculous days never end.
Yes! Let's go now.
After our boundless dreams.
When I lay out the map of my future,
my heart starts throbbing, telling me to make my move.
Sometimes I'll inevitably end up
shedding a few tears,
but let's keep our eyes on the future.
The curiosity that's driving me
right at this moment is still a mystery,
but I do know that I want to find out the answers with you.
Our story is starting, now let's walk together
so that these miraculous days never end.
Yes! Let's go now.
Our harmony resounds throughout the world.
We'll never forget to wear our smiles
with everything that makes this moment shine.
Yes! Go my way.
We'll keep dreaming on and on.
I'm so hungry!
Let's have lunch together, Amami-san.
Sorry, Ogawa-san.
I need to take care of something.
Amami...
Do you think Amami-san forgot her lunch?!
Don't do it, Amami-san!
She's been doing this every day lately.
If you try to fill up on tap water,
you'll just make yourself sick!
She just wanders around the school,
like she's searching for something.
And you guys! Pick on me already!
I'm trying to lighten the mood here!
At first, I was wondering what the joke was.
Are you listening?
Hey!
Yeah...
Come on, you guys!
I guess Amami-san really did lose her sixth sense.
This must be another effect of that.
I can't capture ghosts on camera anymore,
and there are no signs of spiritual activity.
Even though the roll-call samurai and
the gal ghost are probably right up there...
It's a good thing!
Life's been too crazy with them around.
Yeah, so you say,
but I bet you're sad you can't
see your grandma anymore.
Nana's still here!
She's watching over me,
even if I can't see her!
What is it?
Nothing.
Just thinking that Inoue-san's really changed.
No kidding.
Before, she just insisted that
there was no such thing as ghosts.
That probably goes for all of us.
The school and the town seem so quiet now,
even though that's really the norm.
We'd never have realized the truth
if Amami hadn't shown us...
Reference Room
That even though we can't see them,
there are so many interesting
personalities all around us.
I think I'm pretty interesting!
It's all thanks to Amami-san.
They ignored me again...
It's thanks to Amami...
Maybe you're right.
That's why...
That forced smile on her face
somehow really bothers me.
Infirmary
Amami!
We heard Amami passed out!
Shh!
Quiet in the infirmary!
I couldn't find anything wrong.
I assume her anxiety got the best of her.
Anxiety?
Her guardian is coming to get her,
so you should all get back to class.
Let's go.
She must be anxious about you-know-what.
What else could it be?
You guys are awfully mean to me...
No peeking at a sleeping girl!
E-Everyone...
Amami?
Hey, are you okay?
Where... are you...
Come out... Say something...
Please...
We're all right here!
Not us, huh...
She can't even see them in her dreams.
Amami...
The Next
Day
Amami's out sick today?
After what happened yesterday, I'm not surprised.
Hey, why don't we all go visit her after school?
I'm in.
You'll come with us, right, Inoue-san?
Y-Yeah...
Amami
I'm sorry. I know you came all this way...
Um, may I ask why we can't see Amami?
Is she that sick?
No, the doctor said it's just a mild case of anxiety.
She's resting in her room right now.
Then why can't we...
Hibiki said...
"I can't face everyone after making
them worry about me so much."
And "I'm sorry."
What the heck?
Why? Why is she apologizing?
She's always worrying about others, even when they don't ask...
And now she says...
Don't be stupid!
Inoue-san, I'm sure Hibiki realizes that.
But now that she can't see the ghosts
who have been near her all her life...
I don't think she knows how to handle it yet.
I myself have no idea what to say to her.
She hasn't been eating well these past few days, either.
She hasn't been eating?
Not since the Star Festival.
If nothing changes, she'll just grow weaker...
Um...
We'll be going now.
Please take care of Amami.
It's really frustrating that
we can't do anything for her.
If only Amami-san could get her
sixth sense back somehow...
How are some run-of-the-mill high school kids
supposed to restore someone's sixth sense?
I'm concerned that she's not eating, too.
Yeah. That's the more pressing issue.
Oh, yeah!
Hey, Inoue!
That cousin you told us about before...
You mean Yuuki?
You and Amami cooked for him because
he was a really fussy eater, right?
What about it?
I just thought if we did the same thing,
Amami might eat for us...
No way!
I didn't even know why Yuuki was so
hung up on that dish until Amami tol—
But yeah, they're really good.
I'm so glad you like them.
They're actually...
They're very special to me...
What's wrong, Inoue-san?
Sorry, there's something I need to do.
You guys can go on ahead!
Yes?
Who's...
Oh... Inoue-san?
Why are you so out of breath?
Did you forget something?
I...
I have a favor to ask.
The Next
Day
Guess we all had the same idea.
Well, there's nothing we can do for Amami.
So all we can do now is help
with the stuff she can't do herself.
I've got the Noritama offering!
Noritama
Here!
Just like that.
Let's clean up, then.
We've got a lot more places to get to.
Where's Inoue-san?
Oh, of course!
It was your friends,
the roll-call samurai, the gal ghost,
and so many more that
gave me the push to do this.
My friends did?
I'm relieved.
You were able to connect to
so many people in my absence.
Yes.
They're all very dear to me.
But now they're gone,
all because of my selfish wish.
We're no longer connected.
Amami, get your butt out here already!
Inoue-san?!
Get that weak look off your face.
Eat some food, and get your strength back.
They...
They all looked so happy
whenever they ate their offerings.
Slasher
Murder
Site
And that, in turn, made me happy...
But...
Caution
Slasher
Murder
Site
Now...
I can only see them in my memories.
And I'm still...
Get off your high horse
and eat something!
Eat it right now!
Now chew it up!
Something told me this was probably
what you wanted to eat most right now.
The fried eggs you made for Yuuki that one time
were your mom's recipe, weren't they?
I...
When I thought of how they can't eat...
I felt it wasn't fair that only I could...
But...
It's good.
It's delicious.
Of course it is!
Because you're alive!
And they all feel the same way!
Inoue-san...
These feelings don't just run one way.
I've always known that.
Everyone, alive or dead,
shares a bond through the same feelings.
And through my sixth sense,
I can confirm those bonds are real.
But I can't see them
or hear their voices anymore.
I've never once thought about
what I'd be without my sixth sense.
And now that I've lost those precious bonds,
I don't even know who
I'm supposed to be from now on...
I'm so lost...
So scared...
That's why you holed up in your room
and wouldn't even see us?
I didn't want to worry you any further.
We wouldn't have become friends
if it weren't for my sixth sense.
So now that I've lost it, now that I have nothing,
I wasn't sure if our friendships would survive...
Let's go, Amami.
Go where?
There are people I want you to see.
Please, wait... I...
Sorry, Amami.
I'm this close to snapping right now.
R-Right!
Um, where are we going?
You'll see.
Oh, Inoue-san and Amami-san.
Huh? Moriya-sensei?
Hello.
What a relief.
I heard you were out sick yesterday,
but you seem fine now.
Still, don't overdo it.
Are you guys out on a date?
Oh...
Well...
We're going to make an announcement.
Congratulations!
You mean...
I never had the courage to go back
to the place where I'd stayed with her.
But since she came to see me...
I felt it was my turn this time.
I see.
And we have you to thank, Amami-san.
That's right. You reconnected us.
I'm sure she'll be thrilled.
Yeah...
Hibiki-chan?
I thought it was you.
I was worried since I hadn't
seen you at the supermarket lately.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
Out shopping with your friend?
I'm making meat and potatoes tonight.
Every now and then,
I feel like my daughter comes home.
The gal ghost?
So I can't be lazy with my cooking!
It really isn't easy.
Thank you, Hibiki-chan.
Caution
Slasher
Murder
Site
Sir...
Slasher
Murder
Site
Slasher
Murder
Site
Slasher
Murder
Site
Slasher
Murder
Site
You again?
What's that?
Slasher
Murder
Site
Caution
Slasher
Murder
Site
Slasher
Murder
Site
Slasher
Murder
Site
Slasher
Murder
Site
I've got no relation to this kid whatsoever, but...
Caution
Slasher
Murder
Site
Slasher
Murder
Site
Just a whim.
Anyway, young lady!
Y-Yes?!
Your spirits are too low!
Caution
You're still young, so straighten up!
Have some nasty chocolate or something.
Caution
Um, Inoue-san, were these the people you wanted me to see?
Nope.
They were all total coincidences.
But now maybe you see how you—
Narumi! Hibiki!
And there they are.
Is that...
How have you been?
Yuuki-san! It's nice to see you again.
Is this your sister?
Yeah! Look how big she is!
Sorry for the short notice.
It's cool.
I wanted to show Kyouka off to Hibiki, anyway.
Your name is Kyouka-san?
This is the first time we've really gotten to talk.
My name is Amami Hibiki...
"Kyouka"?
Inoue Kyouka
The characters mean "an echoing song."
The first character in her name is the same as yours.
My name...
I never really thanked you properly, so... Thanks!
Because of you, I've been a really good big brother!
Yuuki-san...
Hi-mi-ki!
Did she just talk?!
That's awesome, Kyouka!
See you later!
And I'm sorry I said your eggs were gross!
They were actually really yummy!
Do you see how you're still connected?
Yuuki and everyone else,
they all care very deeply for you.
So are you still going to cry
about your sixth sense?
But I don't have anything else...
Don't be stupid!
You were the one who brought them together!
Maybe it was the sixth sense at first,
but it was you, and you alone, who actually
formed their connections to the ghosts!
You, Amami Hibiki.
Nosy, soft-hearted,
oblivious, and infinitely kind.
And it's because you're you that,
even though you still completely terrify me,
I want to be friends with you forever!
Inoue-san...
You really don't mind... staying connected to me?
Of course not.
You're allowed to be a little selfish, you know.
If I really can...
Then I want to stay friends with you all,
and the ghosts, even if I can't see them!
Caution
Amami-dono.
Slasher
Murder
Site
'Sup, Hibikicchi?
Caution
Slasher
Murder
Site
Slasher
Murder
Site
Amami-chan!
Slasher
Murder
Site
Caution
What's the matter? You look terrible.
Everyone...
All right, let's check out those panties!
For crying out loud...
Well, I can't blame you for being happy.
We, too, wish to stay forever by your side.
Everyone...
I guess I was already connected to them, huh?
Oh, Amami-san!
I'm so glad you're doing better!
Good to see that things are already lively again.
Well, this is how it should be.
Yes, I believe so.
With or without her sixth sense,
Hibiki will be fine now.
Caution
They've all been here with me.
They stayed connected to me.
Caution
Don't cry if you can't see them.
Don't be sad if you can't see them.
Kind feelings, warm feelings,
feelings of love...
They are feelings everyone has
that bind them to someone.
We can't see them, but they're right there.
Should you still worry that they might not be,
just hold out your hand,
and they'll surely...
Is something wrong?
Would you like to tell me about it?
Wow!
Mysterious fluffballs!
Wow! Wow! Wow!
We won't tell the adults!
Have you noticed it? Do you feel it?
See with the mind's eye.
I want to get possessed and be loved.
An after-school sensation.
Common sense means nothing to high-school girls
with a "que sera, sera" attitude.
Out of our way, ghosts!
Abracadablovelove!
Wow! Wow!
You should join us too!
Smile! Smile! Smile!
Let's have a blast!
We only have one chance to be young,
so we should enjoy it to the fullest.
Evil spirits, vengeful spirits, all welcome.
Yeah!
Nothing's impossible in this world.
There are all sorts of strange events and phantoms.
Yeah!
Come what may, we'll never back down.
What does it mean to be ordinary?
Yeah?
If only the gods know the answer,
Yeah!
they can keep it to themselves!
After all...
Ignorance is bliss.
Next Time
A lot has happened, but I'm so glad
I get to spend time with everyone again.
Amami-san, hurry up!
Everyone else is ready!
Let's get going!
The amusement park isn't
gonna run away, you know.
I think you're more likely to run away, Inoue.
Because of that one attraction...
Sh-Shut up!
The final episode of Re-Kan!:
"Summer Memories."
Summer Memories.
I hope today will bring us
another wonderful connection.