Well?
Tell me this ain't the plan for the perfect crime.
Yeah...
Looks we're finally ready
to use our powers and make a huge score!
I'm getting a little excited!
The world's always treated
people like us as if we were trash.
Now we're gonna get some damn payback!
Saitama and the Mediocre Gang
First time meeting and we're already hitting it off!
But hey,
weren't we supposed to have one more?
Maybe he got cold feet.
Well, we'd only talked online.
Huh?
Jeez, were you here the whole time?
We're already done with introductions.
Huh?
Well, whatever...
I'll explain from the top, okay?
First, Blaze, that's me,
will use my fire powers to melt the lock.
Flame User
Blaze
Then I, Shivers, use my Cold Breath
to put the guards on ice.
Ice User
Shivers
Then I, Animal Lover,
will have my animals carry off the loot.
Animal Manipulator
Animal Lover
So, what can you do to help?
Uh...
what're you guys talking about?
Aren't you here because of the post
on the anonymous forum?
The one for people with abilities?
Nope, not me.
J-Just who are you?!
I'm Saitama.
I'm a hero.
We're not about to let a hero
walk away after hearing our plan.
I don't get what this is all about.
He's pretty scrawny, but he's still a hero.
It's our chance to test our powers.
Did you hear what I said?
I'll get him!
Hyper Big Bang Burst!
Hey...
Now deal with me!
Cold Breath: The Final Typhoon!
Time for the coup de grâce!
Flying Bird Critical Attack!
Next?
He's still standing after our killer techniques?!
He's pretty strong.
But can he withstand my master finishing strike?
Miracle Hyper Big Bang Burst!
Whoa!
Cold Breath: The Final!
The Final! The Final! The Final!
Cold! Ow ouch! My hand!
Big Bang Burst! Big Bang Burst! Big Bang Burst!
Big Bang Burst! Big Bang Burst! Big Bang—!
Hot! Hot! Hot!
I-I got this!
Flying Bird: Blow in the Wind!
They'll use their wings to extinguish you!
Can't they flap any harder?!
I can only summon little birds and small critters!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
It's super hot!
Hey fellas, need a hand?
What gives?
Okay,
we get it!
Our powers suck!
Now hold on, Animal Lover...
No, they friggin' suck!
Look at the big names out there.
They make a living out of their powers
by becoming martial artists and so on!
Compared to them, we're worthless.
Screw those guys.
We have powers, same as them.
Maybe mediocre ones...
But they're better than nothing, right?
Despite being mediocre.
Guys...
Remember our vow?
We're going to show everyone by making it big!
Exactly.
Right!
We're like the "Mediocre Gang".
Hold up. Are you guys thinking...
...of becoming heroes?
What?
That's why you tested
your powers against me, right?
Oh! Could you be fans of mine?
No, not at all.
Right, right.
Then why? Was it to show off?
What?
Were you trying to say, "Look at what our
powers can do..." by using them against me?
Hey, don't make such a big deal out of it.
We don't even know who you are. Right, guys?
Yeah.
You're some smalltime hero, right?
Mind if we ask your name?
You little...!
What's happening?!
No idea!
This is an emergency evacuation warning!
A dangerous creature has been detected
under City M Central Park.
Evacuate immediately.
Is it under us?
D-Did she say "dangerous creature"?!
We better clear out of here!
Wh-What the hell is this?!
The ground's caving!
I am the monster Dirt Worm.
Wh-What...?
Your time has come!
Every spot of soil,
you humans pave over with concrete
or tunnel through with sewers and subways
like you own everything.
Now arrogant humanity will be taught
a lesson about who truly rules under the surface...
...by my ability to control the soil itself!
Th-That power is incredible!
We got nothing on that!
I'll show you just how
powerless you bipeds truly are!
What the—?!
B-Better back off for now!
Huh?
Uh...
That crash came from this area.
Master Saitama!
Oh, it's you, Genos.
A dangerous creature was reported nearby...
Yeah, I kinda already—
Ah, I see.
I get the picture.
You do?
See, I was walking along when
suddenly I had to do a number two.
What? Are you okay?!
But it was one of those,
"You think you can't hold it any longer...
Are we safe now?
...but then you feel okay" ones,
you know? What's with that?
Seems like it.
Oh. It comes in waves, I believe.
Look.
Isn't that a Class S Hero?
It's Demon Cyborg Genos!
I will ask Dr. Kuseno to explain
the mechanism in detail.
Check it out.
The ground's all cracked.
He must've killed the monster.
He really does live up to his name.
Who are you people?
Eek!
Oh...
They uh...
challenged me to a fight to test their strength.
Something along those lines.
They did what?
You pissants have beef with Master Saitama?
N-No! We uh... you know...
We want to become heroes... right?
Yeah! That's right!
We wanted a hero we admire
to see our powers. Right, guys?
Y-Yeah!
Right! Right!
Master Saitama, whom we greatly admire!
You guys...
You should've told me!
You were my fans after all!
Master...
You mustn't let these ruffians butter you up.
Soon they will be begging to become your disciples
and move into your apartment.
Uh huh. Coming from you,
that's a convincing argument.
You heard him.
My master is a busy man.
Move along!
G-Guess that's how it is...
Aww, shucks!
Well, we'll be leaving.
G-Goodbye...
One sec.
You guys won't be safe at your skill levels.
Even if you do become heroes,
you'll be up to your necks in no time.
You're gonna have to toughen up.
Besides, you were blessed with special powers.
It'd be a waste not to push yourselves
to your ultimate limits.
U-Ultimate limits?
For example...
Let's say a huge swarm of mosquitoes is coming.
You need to at least be able to cover the town
with an ice dome to keep them out.
And in your case,
if a giant meteor is hurtling down,
you'd better be able to push
it back into space with your fire.
And when alien monsters start
invading the Earth, I want you out there
turning them all into pets.
In your shoes, I wouldn't stop 'til I was that strong.
Even when speaking hypothetically,
he never abandons his ideals...
Incredible, Master!
All right, ready to start?
Huh?
S-Start what?
Isn't it obvious?
Your training.
Sprints!
Sit-ups!
Push-ups!
Listen up!
Think of special powers as "extras"!
If you're not in tip-top shape, they're wasted!
Such wisdom... That is good to know!
You'll never pass the hero exam like that!
Now we're taking... the hero exam?
Who knows? I'm just too scared to stop.
We should never have tried to make it big!
Let's just live under the radar.
You have a long way to go before you
can even think about becoming disciples!
Next up...
...Squats!
Can we...
...just go home?
He almost had me, that one.
The saving grace was that his punch
was too massive to hit me.
But nature is my ally.
The destruction of all humans is demanded of me...
...by the voice of the soil, nay, the Earth it...self?
Our dreams of future feats, our sorrows of the past
That we all have etched deep down inside our souls
Will they help us along or will they hold us back?
We may never know until the end of time
Still, we hope that finally days of serenity will come
When we'll find it in ourselves to forgive each other's sins
Even if we tried to split apart, we're so important to each other
That we never could forget, no matter what
Our bond can teach us that our kindness is another kind of strength
That you can use just by reaching out your hand
It's something dear to us we couldn't bear to live without
So I swear I'll make it back to you
I swear that I’ll come back here to you