Genos and Amnesia
It's the Vehicle Variety Show! Let's go!
What kind of vehicle are we
learning about today, Professor?
It's one you've probably seen at least once:
Emergency vehicles.
"Emergency vehicles"?
That's right.
Does that ring any bells?
No...
Professor, what's an emergency vehicle?
Come on!
I can't get this open!
Let's go and see one!
Is something the matter, Master?
No, but if I use too much strength, it'll burst.
Huh?
"Pro Hero Chips"?
Could you be checking to see
if they made a trading card of you?
Oh crap.
Then I shall buy out the store's stock—
That's not the point.
You're so... How should I put it?
Slow on the uptake?
Or naïve...
DEATH
Huh?
What's wrong, Genos?
Oh right,
I felt my hand bump something just now...
You okay, Genos?
Hey.
Oh, good.
You okay?
Who the hell are you?
Huh?
Who am I...?
Yes, who?
Is this a joke?
You really don't recognize me,
or even know who you are?
Yup...
But I got that my name's Genos
and that I'm a cyborg!
Why do you sound like a kid?
Right?
I'm a cyborg, right?
Is that right, Professor?
How a car
engine works
SSSSS
That's right. They're all powered by engines.
How a car
engine works
SSSSS
That's right. They're all powered by engines.
How a car
engine works
SSSSS
That's right. They're all powered by engines.
How a car
engine works
That's right. They're all powered by engines.
How a car
engine works
That's right. They're all powered by engines.
How a car
engine works
That's right. They're all powered by engines.
How a car
engine works
That's right. They're all powered by engines.
How a car
engine works
That's right. They're all powered by engines.
How a car
engine works
That's right. They're all powered by engines.
Oh...
So, why am I here?
What?
Oh!
Hey, is it okay if I read this?
Y-Yeah... Sure.
So, why am I here again?
Well, because you came and insisted
that I make you my disciple.
You shitting me?!
Huh?
I'm your freaking disciple?!
Hell no!
No way I would ever become
the disciple of a guy whose face
I could draw in 20 seconds!
What the...?!
How about you let your head do the joking, dipshit?
Yo, hurry up and get the door.
Y-Yeah...
Why now, of all times?
What are you doing?
Huh?
Hell if I know...
I just got a feeling something fun
is gonna happen if I do this.
What?
Genos, I wouldn't...
You in there, Saitama? I'm opening the door.
Wh-What the—
What's going on here?
Amnesia?
Yeah.
What's worse, I think he's glitching.
His memories are all mixed up.
It's like he's not quite tuned in. He's a bit unstable.
Hey...
You look pretty cute. You live around here?
Looks bad.
What's the
matter?
You're
beautiful
What?!
Right?
Have we met before?
So he's even forgotten that he's a Class S hero?
Probably.
I see...
You free? Wanna grab a bite?
I just remembered something I have to do.
See you.
What?! Aw man!
Maybe next time, okay?
Ciao!
What was she even here for?
Eyelashes...
Listen.
Call the Blizzard Group and get them here now.
You heard me, so get a move on.
We have a golden opportunity.
Well, Genos?
Remember anything yet?
I'm sorry.
Something inside of me isn't right...
I see...
Yeah, and what would you know?!
You got a problem?!
No, no problem...
Gah! I have no idea what's what anymore!
That's my line.
I feel like I have forgotten
something very important...
I mean, you forgot everything.
Elevated energy levels!
Hey baldy, the hell does
"elevated energy levels" mean?
You're asking the wrong guy...
Something is coming!
Huh?
Hey!
It's moving...
My body is moving by itself!
But if I go along with it...
I might be able to remember something!
Hellstorm!
Come on out, Genos.
Wh-Who are those people?
You may have lost your memory,
but your body remembers how to fight.
That's reassuring.
You sought greater heights
despite already being a Class S hero,
and came knocking at the door
of my Blizzard Group.
Our star rookie...
Gunshot Genos!
No, wait! Please do not kill me!
You seem to be mistaking me for someone else.
That's not who I am.
Sorry!
What? Just a minute...
He ran off way too fast.
There's nothing we can do.
I'm so scared...
Why are they attacking me?
MUNAGEYA MARKET
Will I ever be able to remember who I am?
Huh?
This place seems familiar...
Like I had some sort of important mission here...
MUNAGEYA MARKET
A monster!
I am the Lord of the Mountains.
I was created by the spite
of the creatures driven out by you humans.
Lord of the Mountains
Threat Level
Demon
I speak to you, humans!
To take my vengeance,
I shall uproot you from your homes!
What is that thing...?
A hero!
There's a hero here!
A hero, you say?
That's Demon Cyborg, all right!
The Class S hero, Demon Cyborg!
Thank god!
There's a hero here!
Oh ho... So you seek to challenge me?
N-No...
Thank goodness!
We're gonna be okay!
No... I'm not...
My body's doing it again...
How foolhardy!
C-Come and get me!
As you wish.
That woman earlier...
She called me... a hero.
I need to get back to her...
This is where you wish to be buried?
Great Mountain Wail
Volcanic Shot
S-Someone help me...
You want me to spare you?
You're...
a machine?
You cursed manmade artifice!
Can you even understand? This is revenge!
Revenge...?
You drove us from our tranquil homes.
Now you'll feel the pain of our anger!
I-I'm not ready yet...
I'm not ready to die here!
What?!
Seems you're not a complete weakling.
Weather Change!
Whirlwind
Hailstorm
This feeling...
What's happening?
I'm remembering something!
Weather Change!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
LIGHTNING STRIKE
I can't win like this...
Doctor Kuseno...
Master, I...
Lord of the Mountains!
Hmm?
H-How did you...?!
Thanks to you, I was able to remember everything.
I appreciate it.
As a token of my gratitude,
I will get rid of your anger for you.
Incinerate.
I am so, so sorry!
No, it's all good.
By the way, what is this?
It's game meat!
Oh... I see.
Well, I'm glad you got your memory back.
But I wanted to ask you...
Yes?
Do I really have a face you could draw in 20 seconds?
Can't you at least try to deny it?!
Well, that's the kind of guy you are.
Guess you're back to normal.
Yes, thank you!
I didn't mean...
Well, okay.
You're like this, and that's fine.
Our dreams of future feats, our sorrows of the past
That we all have etched deep down inside our souls
Will they help us along or will they hold us back?
We may never know until the end of time
Still, we hope that finally days of serenity will come
When we'll find it in ourselves to forgive each other's sins
Even if we tried to split apart, we're so important to each other
That we never could forget, no matter what
Our bond can teach us that our kindness is another kind of strength
That you can use just by reaching out your hand
It's something dear to us we couldn't bear to live without
So I swear I'll make it back to you
I swear that I’ll come back here to you