Four Class S heroes
including myself were dispatched
to defeat a monster that had appeared
on a snowy mountain.
I'm freezing to death!
This is nothing if you've got muscles.
What doesn't kill you...
However, we were unable to locate the monster
in the worsening blizzard.
We made our way to a lodge
owned by the Hero Association.
When we got there...
Oh, hey.
You guys get stuck up here too?
Tch!
And there was another man
who basically lived there.
You just better not interfere with my me-time.
It's not like this is your house.
No one there had yet realized
that this lodge would soon be the site
of a most gruesome tragedy.
The Murder of
Zombieman
~                            ~
Snowed in Heroes and
the Mountain Retreat
Just so you know,
we will be taking the biggest room.
Hold up, there are enough rooms
for everyone to get their own.
I'm fine with anything as long as I can work out.
Your neighbors are gonna love you.
Mind if I take the quietest room?
Hey, who put you in charge?!
Calm down a bit, Metal Bat.
It's not his call!
Never thought I'd run into Saitama
while training here.
I'll wait until he's alone and catch him off guard.
How does it take this long just to choose rooms?!
Patience, Sonic.
You've trained for this.
This cold should be... nothing...
Aren't you...
"Spike Around..."
No, "Speedos Down..."
Was it "Faintest Sound Sonic"?
Speed-o'-Sound.
Is this the monster you guys were looking for?
No, he looks nothing like
what the witnesses described.
Let's throw him back outside, then.
Screw you!
If we put him outside, he's done for.
He might be a wanted criminal,
but we can't just condemn him.
Here. Drink this.
Isn't it a bit warm in here?
I'm chilly, okay?
What if Master catches a cold?
Just give it a rest, alright?
Low temperatures are bad for the muscles.
Any logical reason we shouldn't crank the heat?
Spoiled bastards...
At any rate, I managed to infiltrate their base.
And I'm so going to kill you,
Saitama!
That should do it.
So annoying.
Big Brother.
What's the matter?
Nothing! Just talking to myself.
Please ignore me and continue your training.
Seriously, I'm just reading some manga.
Go on back to your room.
Intruder detected!
Beneath us?
Did you hear me?
To a ninja, freeing oneself from ropes
is like untying shoelaces.
Saitama will never see me coming from below!
What are you doing here?!
Observing Master in order to
become stronger, of course.
Exploding Shuriken!
Incineration Cannon!
Aw man...
What's wrong with you two?!
Good grief...
What was that?
Something's up.
Hey!
What was that?
Calm down, I'll get the breaker.
What happened?
How would I know?
Was it from the living room?
Looks like it.
Was it the monster?
Damn! I'm gonna whack it good!
Wait!
Other than us, I'm detecting
no life forms in this lodge.
No one entered from the outside.
I concur.
Wait. So you're saying...
Yes.
The culprit is one of us.
Huh?
You're back to life already?
Yeah, sorry about that.
I wanted to see what was going on.
But it was too dark to see who was there.
The perp could've cut the power
so he wouldn't be seen.
But I can't imagine anyone among us
would want to kill Zombieman.
We're all heroes here.
No, one of us is not.
He is likely the culprit.
Just a minute!
I didn't do it!
Hey. He's gone...
That was a residual image.
I thought we tied you up!
I couldn't even tell if you tied the knots.
Of course, I could escape right now if I wanted to.
But I've got a score to settle
and false accusations to clear up.
Listen up,
it's not because I can't handle
the cold outside, you hear?!
Sure...
But it's inconceivable that
the murderer could be a hero...
Not really.
There are monsters that can
control minds and shape-shift.
Which means...
Yeah.
One of us might be under a monster's control.
Or a monster might have
swapped places with one of us.
We were lucky that I was the first one killed,
but we might end up with more victims.
Let's catch whoever it is before that happens!
Let's start with everyone's alibis.
Master Saitama's alibi is iron-clad.
I was observing him the entire time.
Well said, Genos!
We had just encountered this "ninja,"
and then...
But you couldn't see each other
with the power out, right?
With his speed, he had more than
enough time to kill Zombieman.
Your accusations show that
you've acknowledged my capabilities.
You fool.
One kill is the limit with your speed.
I would have two kills,
and Master Saitama could exceed ten.
Genos, what kind of debate is this?
You're making me look bad.
And you, Blackluster?
I was doing reps while nuking my chicken tendies.
So you were alone the entire time?
Well, yeah.
I was just video chatting.
Ask my younger sister.
She'd be a bit of a biased witness, though...
Then what about you, short stuff?!
I was asleep, of course.
Lack of sleep can stunt one's growth.
In other words, none of us has a solid alibi.
That makes everyone except Zombieman a suspect.
Wait... Aren't we forgetting something?
Did I miss leg day?
Did I set the DVR?
If it's the trash, I put it out.
No, that's not what I mean...
Try to remember!
In times like these, the tiniest detail can be the key.
It's no use. Can't remember.
Then it wasn't important.
Yeah, you'd remember if it was.
Please do not worry, Master.
It must've been something absolutely insignificant.
Anyway,
let's calm down and have a late-night snack.
Oh...!
When the muscles aren't right, the mind isn't right.
These look great.
Unless they're poisoned or something.
Damn it, this is pissing me off!
Let's just torture confessions out of everyone!
The man has a point.
I'm going to go change.
You guys need to calm down a bit.
You know, how's this for a theory?
One person is killed first,
driving us to kill one another out of suspicion.
But that was actually the perp's true objective...
Indeed, a plot by the one who died first!
You don't think Zombieman did it?!
Given all your accusations,
couldn't that make you the real culprit?
Now you're just fanning the flames by saying that.
Enough!
Who's the one under the monster's control?!
Or which of us is the shape-shifted monster?
It's from the Hero Association.
The monster has been identified!
Its name is Bruinado.
It's believed to be a violent monster
with a threat level no lower than Demon.
Punches and kicks are its sole form of attack.
Simple, but powerful.
We're counting on you all.
Huh? Wait a second.
Just punches and kicks?
No shape-shifting or mind control powers?
So none of us are puppets?
Then what's going on?
Are you okay, Master?
You're sneezing again.
I think I've got it!
What?
Are you familiar with dust explosions?
When dry air filled with fine particulates
is exposed to an ignition source,
an explosion can occur.
Having the heater on full blast dried out the air.
Genos and Sonic's battle created
a large amount of particulates.
Saitama's sneeze spread them
throughout the living room.
Then, the power went out
because we overloaded the circuits.
And when Zombieman lit his lighter...
Hey,
what's going on?
We're all... Nothing.
Yeah! Nothing!
I am Bruinado, the mighty monster!
Wandering this cruel wasteland,
I have awoken to the power of the wild!
I am the strongest...
creature... alive...
Okay!
R-Right...
Our dreams of future feats, our sorrows of the past
That we all have etched deep down inside our souls
Will they help us along or will they hold us back?
We may never know until the end of time
Still, we hope that finally days of serenity will come
When we'll find it in ourselves to forgive each other's sins
Even if we tried to split apart, we're so important to each other
That we never could forget, no matter what
Our bond can teach us that our kindness is another kind of strength
That you can use just by reaching out your hand
It's something dear to us we couldn't bear to live without
So I swear I'll make it back to you
I swear that I’ll come back here to you