You know, Silverfang...
What is it, Atomic Samurai?
It's kind of...
What's the word...
Tranquil, isn't it?
Yeah...
Fishing With the Old Boys
Has it already been a week
since we fought those aliens?
Luckily, we haven't had a major incident since.
It's been nice.
Are you healing up okay?
Huh?
In the end, they weren't too challenging,
but you must've taken some damage.
Hmph.
My body was getting soft. I needed the jolt.
In fact,
I could've used an even harder workout.
Cut that out, Silverfang.
You'll scare off all the fish.
Oh...
Sorry 'bout that.
But there's no fighting Father Time.
Nowadays, I'm winded after just
running a few dozen kilometers.
I've laid off the sake a bit myself.
A decade ago, 30 straight nights of
drinking and carousing was a good time.
These days, though...
But as a result, my body's shaping up.
In fact, I feel even sharper.
Hey, you're doing it too, Atomic Samurai.
Scaring off the fish.
Oh...
Sorry 'bout that.
But you know...
It sure is tranquil now.
That it is.
These are...!
Hey, Unlicensed Rider! Found something!
You did?!
These tracks are unmistakable.
The monster escaped into this lake.
Seems it was aquatic.
We better watch ourselves...
Chain Toad!
Some people are fishing out there!
What?!
We need to warn them!
No, if we tell them now, they're apt to panic.
We'd be leading the monster straight to its prey.
We have to defeat it now,
before any innocents get hurt!
But, you know...
Hmm?
A lot of these kids today sure think they're hot stuff.
Oh, indeed...
Hot air is all they're full of.
The battle with the aliens
reminded me just how incredible Class S heroes are.
I have to put it all on the line too!
Shh...
I sense a presence.
Speaking of youngsters, is lairon okay?
Huh?
It must be pretty hard on him...
...to lose an arm.
All the more because he's a swordsman.
Heh.
Don't underestimate my disciple, Silverfang.
Hmm?
Even as we speak, the kid is working his butt off
to become even more dangerous
with one arm than he was with two.
That's the kind of man one has to be
to make it as my disciple.
My apologies.
It was a foolish question.
Forget it.
Such dedication, such honor...
I thought I'd found them in him, too.
You could say it broke my heart.
Nothing you could've done.
These days, even some of the younger heroes
make no sense at all to me.
I'd say the Hero Association's
methods are partly to blame.
Points, rankings, popularity...
They've all lost sight of what it means to be a hero.
There's even a guy who wears headgear
because he isn't popular enough.
Found ya!
I think I scored a hit!
And so often they misjudge an opponent's abilities...
Chain Toad!
But there're others who are trying their utmost...
Even if all they're really doing is being reckless.
Everyone needs to think deeply
about what they're getting into.
You said it.
It's no good!
If it struggles any more,
those fishermen will get hurt!
So what do we do?!
If we injure it, it'll slow down!
That's all I can think of!
Hey, Rider!
Damn it!
Hey, have you noticed the increase
in vicious monsters lately?
Ah, so you felt that too?
Yeah.
And it's not just the quantity, but overall power too.
Is it the times we live in?
Could be...
Crap!
How about this?!
Oh ho...
You've got some skill, but no matter!
Guess that was the best he could do.
Seems that way.
On the battlefield, only a fool
pursues the enemy into his element!
Challenging the mighty War Salamander
in the water is pure folly!
And you two call yourselves heroes?
Now to begin turning this lake into
a base of operations for world conquest.
And for starters...
See those fishermen?
They're trembling in fear so hard,
their legs don't work!
It's time someone hooks and guts them!
Hold it!
Huh?
You stay away from those men.
You've still got bigger problems
right in front of you!
Hmph.
Have you already forgotten our fight just now?
No way a talentless tadpole like you
could ever hope to defeat me!
Or perhaps you're intent on dying in battle?
Impudence!
Oh...
Hmm...
Justice...
Tackle!
Let go of me, you finless runt!
He's got guts, I'll give him that.
But listen here, young one.
Guts alone don't cut it.
Wh-Who are you, bastard?!
Just a guy out fishing.
The hell you are!
Too true.
A hero must also be...
...strong, you see.
Huh?
Well, looks like it'll be some time
before the young heroes are ready.
But we can't afford to wait on that, can we?
Not when you consider how
ferocious the monsters are getting.
Isn't there anyone who can step up?
There is one...
He's a real piece of work.
Oh?
Is this hero stronger than my disciples?
He's far past them.
Even surpasses me, I imagine.
What?!
In fact, you've already met him.
Really? Who is it?
You'll find out eventually.
Right now, we have more important fish to fry.
Though we have to catch them first.
I suppose so.
Sitting for all this time makes my back ache.
Shall I have my friend Queer Blade
give you a massage?
He's pretty good, you know.
Queer...
Think I'll pass.
Our dreams of future feats, our sorrows of the past
That we all have etched deep down inside our souls
Will they help us along or will they hold us back?
We may never know until the end of time
Still, we hope that finally days of serenity will come
When we'll find it in ourselves to forgive each other's sins
Even if we tried to split apart, we're so important to each other
That we never could forget, no matter what
Our bond can teach us that our kindness is another kind of strength
That you can use just by reaching out your hand
It's something dear to us we couldn't bear to live without
So I swear I'll make it back to you
I swear that I’ll come back here to you