Puri-Puri Prisoner and the Jailbreak
A monster appeared today
near a waste disposal facility in City J.
It appears to be heading towards a prison...
SSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS
WWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWW
NEWS FLASH
MONSTER ATTACK
SSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSSS
WWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWWW
NEWS FLASH
MONSTER ATTACK
The prison houses violent inmates.
And now, our next story...
No wonder...
That's right nearby.
Sure is noisy out there today.
Can't see outside from here.
Seems like a storm, though.
Excuse me. Let me through.
Huh?
Come on! Step aside.
Huh?! Why would I—
You'll get used to it.
Should we make a run for it?
Better not, newb.
Oh, that's right, you're new here!
Armed guards will come storming in any second.
Take one step outside
and you'll be full of bullet holes.
That fast? I heard this prison was huge.
A monitoring system tells them
where the breach occurs,
and a response team immediately rushes in.
Exactly.
Only one guy can get out,
and that's the Boss!
Uh-oh...
I get that Boss is a hero, so he's special.
That's all well and good,
but it's been over a minute...
Where's the response team?
The system's down from a power surge?!
Where's the breach?!
D-Block!
But the system went down before we—
We're back online. Getting location.
Here they come!
Hey you!
See ya!
Tsk!
How many inmates escaped?
Ten from D-Block, Module 35!
Get BOLOs on them, stat!
I knew it, they were too late...
If I remember, the guard in charge
of the security monitors is...
Pretty Boy might lose his job because of me!
I need to fix this!
Feels so good to be out!
We even found an empty house ripe for the taking.
Lucky us!
This place'll be our hideout
while we scrounge up some cash.
When the heat dies down,
we'll team up and get back to business!
We're back.
Here.
Check out the goods we got in town.
Guys, where's 3016 and his two mates?
Huh? I don't know.
They went out saying they'd catch up to you.
Damn it! They ran off!
Oh well, there're always guys
who can't work in a group.
Jeez.
I told 'em we shouldn't split up
until the cops lift the perimeter.
Damn them!
Hey...
Something's up. 3452 and 4051
should've been back by now,
but they're still out there.
Tsk! That makes five runaways!
What if the cops got them?!
We got trouble!
3452 was c-caught
by Puri-Puri Prisoner!
No hard feelings.
I'm giving you this punishment out of love.
Hey you!
People will see you!
Huh? Is that...
Little Sonic!
Escapees?
So, these guys got out through
the gaping hole you smashed open?
That's right.
If you see them, let me know.
I have to catch them all and teach them a lesson.
In that case, want to try and capture me, too?
Huh?
Have you forgotten, Puri-Puri Prisoner?
I also escaped...
using the hole you made.
No, I won't capture you, Sonic.
You got out using your own abilities.
Not because of my mistake.
I have to go.
Hey!
But remember, Sonic...
If you ever get lonely, my arms are open!
Like hell I will, mammoth.
This is bad. 2015 hasn't come back either.
Yeah, this is definitely the Boss's work.
No telling what he'll do if he gets hold of us.
He's merciless with criminals.
Yeah.
You guys probably remember
what that old Class A bounty
came back looking like.
Maybe we should just turn ourselves in.
If we're lucky, they'll put us in a different prison.
Let's do that.
2015, that you?!
What're you doing in my lair?
I've been lying low,
awaiting a chance to avenge my people,
and here a bit of prey just falls right into my lap?!
I thought maybe some fool would wander in,
but who'd have thought
so many would show up at once!
This is exactly
what I'd wished for!
Jarhead
Threat Level
Tiger
H-He's one of the Clan of the Seafolk!
It just so happens that I'm absolutely starving.
Don't mind if I do!
Where the hell'd you come from?!
You with them?!
Don't you dare lay a hand
on my sweet honeys!
I know you...!
Those boys look so scared, the poor things.
Maybe I should show them my heroic side.
Keep yourselves hidden, boys!
I knew I'd seen you before!
That get-up...
you're that Class S hero...
Transform!
Puri-Puri Prisoner Angel Style!
Class S heroes are no joke...
I'm no match... damn it.
I would estimate your Threat Level at Tiger.
If you were at Demon-level, it might've been a fight.
He's the monster!
If we get caught again,
we're doomed in more ways than one!
Now then...
It's your turn.
Do you regret what you did?
Yes!
If I see that even one of you doesn't show remorse,
you'll all get 100 French kisses—
punishment by asphyxiation.
Huh?
Not so fast...
You bastard...
How dare you get your kicks by assaulting my body!
Oh, you're still alive?
My pride's been shattered, giant fool.
You should've just stayed down.
You're injured. You don't stand a chance.
I know that much.
I'm aware I have no chance of beating you.
No one needs to tell me anything like that!
It's not about winning or losing!
It's about me taking on this weirdo
right here, right now!
I can't die without standing up for myself!
What are you babbling on about?
I can't understand a word.
I... don't like pervs!
Me neither.
Get him...
I hate pervs!
You can do it, monster...
Beat him!
Good luck!
Huh? They're...
Now!
Angel...
...Rush!
Thanks for rooting for me.
From what I can see,
you've mended your ways.
Yes! We're sorry!
Let's go back right now!
Our dreams of future feats, our sorrows of the past
That we all have etched deep down inside our souls
Will they help us along or will they hold us back?
We may never know until the end of time
Still, we hope that finally days of serenity will come
When we'll find it in ourselves to forgive each other's sins
Even if we tried to split apart, we're so important to each other
That we never could forget, no matter what
Our bond can teach us that our kindness is another kind of strength
That you can use just by reaching out your hand
It's something dear to us we couldn't bear to live without
So I swear I'll make it back to you
I swear that I’ll come back here to you