15 Years Ago
Fifteen years ago...
First World Collision
The purported Entrances, tears in reality that
connected the human realm to another dimension,
suddenly appeared all over the planet.
Every military force on the planet
suffered a horrible defeat,
never truly knowing who they were fighting.
The Entrances vanished two
weeks after they appeared,
and the danger seemed to have passed.
But then...
Six Months Ago
Second World Collision
...they returned.
The world's governments
evacuated to oceanic Megafloats.
However, only a small portion of
the population was able to escape.
The world is still being invaded by enemies
pouring in from the open Entrances.
But we haven't been sitting
here twiddling our thumbs.
We've developed the Heart Hybrid Gears,
which let us face the enemy on equal ground.
This is Ataraxia's Heart Hybrid
Gear ace team, Amaterasu.
They're some of our most important fighters.
Great work today.
As principal and high commander
of Ataraxia, I'm proud of you.
Sis, are you seriously the principal
and high commander?
And now we have the means
to make Gears even stronger.
A way to make the Gears stronger?
I'll introduce him.
This is Hida Kizuna, a 2nd-year student
joining the High School Tactical Division.
It's already been decided that he'll join
Amaterasu upon enrolling at the school.
This is the key to our victory.
Wow!
I thought he was a beta,
but I guess I was wrong.
Wait, I...
What is this?!
Wait a second.
Um, you're...
High School Tactical Division, Class 2-1,
Disciplinary Council member Himekawa Hayuru!
What were you doing in the middle of a battle?!
I can't believe it!
It's indecent!
Disgusting!
Perverted!
This is not a game!
By sharing love and pleasure with Hida Kizuna,
the lost energy of a Heart Hybrid Gear
can be dramatically restored.
This is a Heart Hybrid.
Heart Hybrid...
These are your new orders:
Members of Amaterasu are to restore
their energy and power up
by doing lewd things with Hida Kizuna!
This goes for all who wish to join Amaterasu.
After joining, you'll be required
to Hybrid Heart with Kizuna.
Don't get the wrong idea, everyone!
I definitely didn't think of it as erotic!
Eros!
He's a pervert!
My love for you is like a bucking colt
You act so innocent, but I know you're feeling it
I'm not a wizard anymore
The craziest things you can imagine all start from nothing
It's like we're in a fairy tale
But this is real life
My charm makes you swoon
Our hearts beat in unison
Just let your passion explode
My feelings won't reach you like this
I need to shoot them at you with everything I've got
They're on a direct course to your heart
My spirit is on fire
I'll expose your true nature
Don't worry, I'll be gentle
I'll take you to a secret paradise
And offer you a grand feast
When the two of us become one
An innocent flower blooms
EPISODE 2
How can you wake up later than me?
You're slacking off.
Ch-Chidorigafuchi...
Why?
I've come to seduce you tonight.
It's morning.
They talk about the
"morning walk of shame," right?
Well, maybe, but I don't think that's right.
Okay, let's get started.
Wai—
O-Okay, Hybrid Heart with me right now!
W-Wait a second.
Why are you in such a rush?
Um, Hida?
Good morning.
Himekawa?
Maybe you had your reasons
for doing what you did yesterday.
I'm sorry I got mad at you without even
trying to hear your side of the story.
Hida?
I'm coming in, okay?
So, I know this doesn't really make it any better,
but I wanted to walk you to school...
You animal!
You brought Aine to your room to seduce her?!
That's not true!
How is it not true?!
Everything about it isn't true, Hayuru.
I'm the one who's attacking him.
I'm trying to seduce him to perform a Heart Hybrid.
I-I've had it!
Neros!
I'll teach you both a lesson!
Zeros.
Ladies, please. Not in my room!
Did you hear the explosion this morning?
Apparently it was Himekawa and Chidorigafuchi.
That's right!
It was in that Eros boy's room!
It doesn't make any sense that he's in
the same dorm and classroom as the girls!
We're hoping that intimacy develops
between them through time spent together.
But still, you know...
Girls, it's wrong to judge someone based on
their appearance and first impressions.
Better to decide after you've seen
if he's worthy of special treatment.
How compassionate you are, Julicia!
I feel better just hearing you speak!
Yeah, figures...
Good morning, Kizuna.
M-Morning.
Hey, perv!
Julicia Farandole is an American
military ace and a rich celebrity!
You're not even worthy of speaking to her!
Now, now. Calm down, everyone.
Hey, is what the high commander said true?
If I seek pleasure with you,
will my Hybrid Count really go back up?
I-I don't really know...
Ms. Farandole...
Call me Julicia.
Would you like to try right now?
Julicia, a classroom is a sacred place,
so I won't let you do anything indecent here!
Then it's fine as long as we're not in the classroom?
No, it's not fine anywhere!
Um...
Are you busy?
Who are you?
Sylvia Silkcut, Middle School Year 1!
The commander wants to
talk to you, Captain Kizuna!
This is the Heart Hybrid Gear research lab,
also known as the Nayuta Labs.
The basic technology behind the
Hybrid Gears was developed here.
Yeah, that's right.
That's Dr. Hida Nayuta, right?
The super-important person
who developed the Gears.
Mom...
Shikina Kei
It's Sylvia.
Come in.
Wow...
This way.
I'll introduce you.
This is the lab's director,
Chief Engineer Shikina Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Well, don't let it bug you.
Anyway, Kizuna, I'll give you this to start with.
It's a portable terminal that also
functions as a student handbook.
Yours is special.
Tap the icons of the Amaterasu members.
This is private information!
That's why it's special.
You can see one of the listings
is for Hybrid Count, right?
When their count goes below five percent,
it becomes difficult to maintain their Gears.
Keep that in mind.
Keep that in mind?
Simple.
If you Hybrid Heart, the count will recover.
Gear energy doesn't recover naturally?
Natural recovery takes far too long.
And the energy loss in combat is huge.
So we need you and your Gear, Eros.
Our latest research shows
that Eros has a special function.
Heart Hybrid, a technique that
can rapidly restore Hybrid Counts.
It's no exaggeration to say that the fate
of humanity rests on your shoulders.
Do your job as captain justice.
Wait.
I'm captain?
Starting today, you're the captain of Amaterasu.
But that's so sudden!
I'll help as best I can!
Sylvia is going to keep me updated
on whether things are proceeding smoothly
between you and the members of Amaterasu.
Yes!
I'll do my best!
This is crazy...
Work hard. You've got a mission now.
A mission?
I'll go over the mission details again.
Your job is to gather data on a nearby
island and recover resource samples.
This is your first mission as Amaterasu's captain.
Stay sharp out there.
How can someone so indecent be our captain?!
I'll go on ahead and scope out the area!
Wait a second—
Oh, Hayuru, you're so silly.
Julicia.
Oh? What is it, High Commander?
Be careful.
Your Hybrid Count is at twenty percent.
Avoid combat as much as possible.
Don't worry. This place is safe.
Shouldn't you worry about
your little brother instead?
Doesn't seem like he's flying very steadily...
Okay, I'll go catch up to Hayuru.
They're both so fast.
Of course.
Hayuru is Japan's ace,
and Julicia is America's.
I-I see.
By the way, how good are you?
Japan's #2?
Or some foreign ace?
Don't underestimate me.
I'm the ace of the entire Earth.
Earth?
Oh no, I got it wrong.
I meant the entire universe.
The entire universe, huh?
Data recovery initiated.
It will take two hours or so to finish.
So we get our samples during that time?
Okay, let's go, Kizuna!
Make sure you escort me right.
Come on!
You're such a worrywart, aren't you, Kizuna?
Entrances only appear on land
masses above a certain size.
That means this tiny island is safe.
No, that's not it...
So, what are the specs on your Gear?
Not exactly sure how to answer that.
That's right.
What's your kill score, then?
Zero.
So what, you're really a complete rookie?
Any combat experience?
The battle yesterday was my first.
Though all I did was grab Chidorigafuchi as she fell.
I didn't do anything else, really.
How many enemies have you defeated, Julicia?
About three hundred.
Three—?!
That's America's ace for you.
There's nothing amazing about me.
Julicia?
Come, let's regroup with Hayuru and Aine.
Okay.
Aine, let's go meet Julicia and—
An Entrance?!
No, that doesn't make any sense!
Equip your Gear, Hayuru!
Fire!
This is Kizuna!
Ataraxia, come in!
Shikina! Sis!
Connection Failed
Don't bother.
When an Entrance appears,
normal communications stop working.
But Gear users can talk to one another.
Aine? Hayuru?
No... why?
Julicia!
Connection Failed
Hida!
It's not working.
Hayuru, look!
What's happening?
Blade!
No way!
We're locked in?
Kizuna, go grab the others.
But then you'll be all by yourself.
You'll just slow me down!
Go!
Fine!
Eros!
Now then...
You boys ready?
Damn it!
A girl's risking her life in combat!
And I...
Julicia!
My Hybrid Count is down to six percent.
That's cutting it awfully close.
A Dragorie?
That's a Category-A Magitech weapon.
Fire!
My beam's power is dropping!
I can't move my hands...
Or my legs...
My body feels so heavy...
Wait!
My chest...
Julicia!
Kizuna!
Wh-Why?
Why did you come back?
Julicia...
Run...
Why?
Why are you doing this for me
when we've only just met?
What are you talking about?
A girl's... in danger...
Of course I have to help her.
That's the only reason he did this?
Run, Julicia!
No...
Kizuna...
Don't...
I...
No...
What is this sensation?
What's going on?
Amazing. My whole body
is overflowing with power!
So this is a Heart Hybrid?
Thank you for coming to save me, Kizuna.
Just watch.
This is my...
Showtime!
Hellfire!
This time!
What?
The Entrance is gone!
Aine! Hayuru!
Are you okay?
Julicia?
Best I've ever been!
I did a Heart Hybrid with Kizuna,
and now I'm better than ever!
Hey, Julicia...
So that means you too, Julicia?
How could this be?!
We let our guard down today.
That island increases in size as the tide goes out,
so it became large enough
for an Entrance to appear.
We missed that.
I wouldn't have made Julicia go with
such a low Hybrid Count if I had known.
After her Count got in the red zone,
she seemed to be in a lot of pain.
Are you sure you don't want to tell him, Reiri?
I think we can wait until you're ready.
You're late.
How could you keep me waiting?
Why are you here?
To do a Heart Hybrid, of course.
You don't even understand that?
I refuse to understand!
Kizuna!
Julicia?
Are your wounds okay?
What about you? Are you okay?
Yes!
All thanks to you, Kizuna.
So...
Let's do some more, okay?
I'm first, Julicia!
Oh my, Aine.
You want to do a Heart Hybrid again?
Well, I'm sure you do.
The one before was basically an accident!
Hida, this is Himekawa.
Are you feeling okay?
As a fellow Amaterasu member...
How indecent!
Neros!
I'll punish you!
Not happening.
Come on!
No fighting in my room!
Why, you...
High Commander, I've got my report!
How about an apple, Snow White? Relax, it's safe
You know, that shit-eating grin really pisses me off
I'm gonna punch you
Forgive me for being cold to you
It's just that there was this girl looking at you in the cafe
I'm gonna kill her
She'd probably leave you before the night is over
Let me show you the storm of emotions trapped beneath the surface
Go beyond your dreams, love's waiting for you there
What do you want so badly that you'd cry for it?
All I want is your heart's warmth
There's no escape from the love that's seeping through your veins
Hold me, hold your breath
You're my prince
Just kidding
Illustration
Shinpei Kobayashi
Kyoto, Okinawa, Akihabara!
Megafloat Japan's the perfect place
for a date, isn't it, Kizuna?
A date?
Are Julicia and Hida...?
NEXT TIME
GENTLE DAYS - MEMORIES
How indecent!