Don't worry, everyone!
The Special Assault Team
will be providing support now!
Stay calm and follow whatever orders you're given!
The Tokyo Float...
We're really abandoning Japan, aren't we?
What's wrong?
Are you scared?
What about you?
Aren't you scared?
Not at all.
I'll beat all the bad guys for you!
Really?
Yup!
Don't worry.
I'll protect everyone!
My love for you is like a bucking colt
You act so innocent, but I know you're feeling it
I'm not a wizard anymore
The craziest things you can imagine all start from nothing
It's like we're in a fairy tale
But this is real life
My charm makes you swoon
Our hearts beat in unison
Just let your passion explode
My feelings won't reach you like this
I need to shoot them at you with everything I've got
They're on a direct course to your heart
My spirit is on fire
I'll expose your true nature
Don't worry, I'll be gentle
I'll take you to a secret paradise
And offer you a grand feast
When the two of us become one
An innocent flower blooms
Episode 5
Beauty of the Land of Rubble
Baths
I never thought this day would come!
There's a huge bath in this building,
but I can't use it since it's the girls' dorm.
Then I'll let you have it all to yourself tonight.
Have fun.
Thanks, Sis!
Let's get bathing!
L-Listen, Himekawa!
Wh-What are you doing?
Lecher! Pervert!
Peeping Tom! Eros Overlord!
N-No! It's a misunderstanding!
Hear me out!
No excuses!
Neros!
L-Lewd.
When I gave you sole access to the baths?
Well, of course I didn't tell Himekawa.
Your relationship isn't developing at all,
so I prepared a bit of an event.
I'm rather disappointed with the result, though.
So it was your fault!
I'm disappointed in you, Commander!
I can't believe you'd do something like this!
Then let me ask you something:
how much of your Hybrid Count is left?
How much has recovered since the last battle?
W-Well...
Julicia and Aine have already
successfully performed a Heart Hybrid.
You're the only one who hasn't.
Heart Hybrid?
Why would I do something so indecent?
And with Hida, no less!
A map of the world isn't really
all that useful nowadays.
All the world's megafloats have had their
communications cut off from one another.
We don't know where they are.
Megafloat Japan is...
Hmm...
If we were going to run into anybody,
it would be West USA, maybe.
It's true that I haven't done
a Heart Hybrid with Himekawa yet.
I don't really get it, either.
I'll need to fix that soon.
And...
I won't let any of them die.
Call me a pervert if you want...
I'll...
Kizuna!
Sis?
Come to Industrial Area 18, warehouse 4.
There's something I want to show you.
What's this?
The simulator we'd been
working on is finally complete.
It's capable of recreating any situation.
This is the simulator's scenario function.
It can also change clothes.
Wow! This'll make it easy to have
mock battles with Magitech weapons!
It's perfect for a guy like me to train.
It can also recreate any kind of date spot,
hotel, or anything else one might prefer.
It can also create accessories, toys, and tools.
It has a bed, a shower, a jacuzzi,
and even a karaoke machine.
A bed?
Is this...
Of course.
It's a dating simulator that we developed
to help things with the girls run more smoothly.
We call it the Love Room.
By the way, the Engineering Division
put their full efforts into this project.
Say thanks to our young talents!
Hooray! Hooray!
Even if it's to help the Eros Overlord,
as long as we can be of use to Director Shikina...
I, Kurumizawa Momo, will do whatever it takes!
That's not what advanced technology is for!
Incorrect!
Deepening the bonds of trust between you
and creating mental and physical
pleasure and excitement...
If you want to get the maximum
out of your Hybrid Hearts,
that's indispensable.
How can you keep a straight face while saying that?
So this is what you like, huh?
No, I—!
Anyway, I order you to use this facility
to perform a Heart Hybrid immediately.
I need you to test out how effective it is.
So what did you want me to do?
Try and patch things up with Hayuru for you?
Um...
I wanted your help testing a new simulator.
Wow!
This is amazing!
What kind of situation would excite Julicia?
I can't exactly ask her.
Something wrong, Julicia?
N-Nothing.
What's with this room?
It's low-class. And perverted.
Can you switch it back to the other hotel room?
S-Sure...
Maybe...
Wh-What is this?
S-Sorry.
Looks like the system's malfunctioning.
It's malfunctioning?
Jeez...
Does he like seeing me this way?
When I think of Kizuna looking at me, it turns me on.
Then maybe my system will screw up, too.
I'll do better things to you than Hayuru ever would.
Wh-What?
K-Kizuna?!
What are you doing?
Take these off!
Was this the pleasure and excitement
Sis was talking about?
Then...
K-Kizuna?!
Where are you touching me?
No!
Julicia...
Can I take off your top?
I'm going to take it off.
What is this?
This is...
Julicia...
Kizuna?
Are we done?
Don't worry.
The Heart Hybrid... was a success.
Come on, go out with me.
Huh? I don't know...
What are you doing?
The school is a sacred place.
Crap, it's the disciplinary committee!
What am I doing?
Himekawa!
Listen, Himekawa.
Will you go out with me for a little?
Go out with you?
I can't just ask her to Hybrid
Heart all of a sudden, can I?
Um, I...
Captain!
Sylvia?
What is it?
Look!
The results of my last test!
Wow!
Straight A's!
I got the best grades in the class!
I worked really hard so you would praise me!
I see.
Good girl.
Sorry, but I have somewhere to be.
Himekawa?
What was I expecting?
I'm such a fool.
I don't...
...have the right!
Mysterious radio waves?
Yes.
Last night, at 2:10 Megafloat Japan Standard Time,
we detected a weak radio signal.
Its source was...
Guam.
Guam?
We know nothing about the origin of the signal,
but there is a US military base on Guam,
so it's possible someone sent it from there.
Which means there might be a survivor?
A survivor?
Friend or foe, someone sent
us a message from there.
Our mission this time is to determine
the source of the radio waves.
You will make land at Guam.
Make land?
But there's an Entrance there, right?
It's too dangerous!
Don't worry.
I'll wipe out the enemy with my
Immoral Weapon if I have to.
Oh? I thought you couldn't use
the Pulverizer anymore.
It disappeared after a while, right?
That Immoral Weapon you're so proud of.
Th-Then I can just do a Climax Hybrid again.
No way! It's my turn to try!
Say, Kizuna.
How about we pick up where we left off?
Enough!
What did you think?
Those radio waves seemed to be
sending some kind of data.
We won't know what we'll find until
we get there, but if we're going to look,
we may as well go all the way.
And if the sender is Dr. Nayuta?
Then I'll handle it myself.
So this is Guam.
It's quiet.
Let's split up.
Himekawa and I will check the city of Tumon.
Julicia and Aine,
you two check out Anderson Air Base.
Roger!
Looks like they cleared
the place out before they left.
A shining example for soldiers everywhere.
Yup.
Except for this.
This is terrible.
Damn it.
Himekawa?
It's nothing.
I see.
If there's a survivor, this time I'll...
Thanks, miss.
Are you a survivor?
Don't worry.
It's okay now!
We're with Amaterasu, from Megafloat Japan.
My, my.
It's just like she said...
If I wait here, I might meet them.
You're not the one I've been waiting for,
but that's all right.
You'll have to do for now.
Zeeru!
Is that a Heart Hybrid Gear?
So that's what you call the Magitech armor, huh?
What country are you with?
Where did you get that Gear?
Country?
What other country could I be from?
The proud Empire of Batlantis!
Batlantis?
You don't know it?
That's a shame.
It rules more than half the planet.
Of course, I'm talking about the world
on the other side of that.
An Entrance?
N-No way!
You're not...
My name is Aldea.
From your perspective,
I'm from another dimension.
So, anyway...
I'm going to...
...take your cores out, okay?
What is she?
Is she really from another dimension?
That's boring.
You started running right away?
Let's have some more fun.
I'm not sure what's going on,
but it's clear she's our enemy.
Then...
Sword!
Blades!
What?
I've seen this before!
Is that all you've got?
Entertain me more!
Hida!
Why, you!
This is so boring.
Let's finish it.
What's that?
I wondered what all the fuss was.
Julicia!
You've got guts, having a clandestine
meeting with a strange girl.
Aine...
I want more information, but it's okay.
I'll catch her and make her tell me.
A white Magitech armor...
So we finally meet.
Are you the one who sent that signal?
What are you talking about?
Anyway, you're the one who fired
that huge cannon before, aren't you?
What if I am?
Who is she?
Hey, can I ask you a question?
Are you...
You bitch!
Get out of my way!
Oh dear.
Now I've done it.
Sheesh!
What a pain.
What?
I'm bored, so I'll finish this quick.
I can just take the cores off your bodies,
so relax and die.
What is that?
A-A bomb?
This is...
Himekawa!
Blades!
Himekawa's blades aren't working?
Take this! Take this! Take this!
Take this! Take this!
Himekawa!
Its armor is so thick!
Move, Aine!
Fire!
No way...
What do we do, Kizuna?
At this rate...
We've got no choice but to retreat.
Himekawa?
That Magitech weapon...
I'll destroy her, no matter what!
We're retreating, Himekawa.
That's an order.
Roger.
Oh, do you really think I'll let you escape?
Crap, so my magic does run out fast in Lemuria.
Still...
This should be fun.
What is that thing?
Hey, Kizuna?
What's going on?
The Batlantis Empire?
People from another dimension?
And I've never seen that Magitech weapon before.
How about an apple, Snow White? Relax, it's safe
You know, that shit-eating grin really pisses me off
I'm gonna punch you
Forgive me for being cold to you
It's just that there was this girl looking at you in the cafe
I'm gonna kill her
She'd probably leave you before the night is over
Let me show you the storm of emotions trapped beneath the surface
Go beyond your dreams, love's waiting for you there
What do you want so badly that you'd cry for it?
All I want is your heart's warmth
There's no escape from the love that's seeping through your veins
Hold me, hold your breath
You're my prince
Just kidding
Creator
Kazuya Morimae
Eros You
Next Week!
The day Tokyo burned,
I decided that I would never forgive myself.
Eros You
Next Week!
That was my punishment.
Eros You
Next Week!
But when I met him...
Eros You
Next Week!
Next Time
WORLD-SPLITTER
Eros You
Next Week!
What is this feeling?
Eros You
Next Week!