Immoral weapon?
That's right.
Your Heart Hybrid Gear contains a hidden
weapon called an Immoral Weapon.
Once your Hybrid Count goes above a certain level,
you'll probably be able to use it.
You should grow to be much
stronger than you are now.
Keep it up.
Deploying defensive utilities over
all of Ataraxia and Megafloat Japan.
Attention all students:
This is not a drill or a school event.
Everyone, this way!
This is a real battle!
Show these otherworldly invaders
what you've learned!
We'll give 'em a taste of all the
things we've been working on!
My love for you is like a bucking colt
You act so innocent, but I know you're feeling it
I'm not a wizard anymore
The craziest things you can imagine all start from nothing
It's like we're in a fairy tale
But this is real life
My charm makes you swoon
Our hearts beat in unison
Just let your passion explode
My feelings won't reach you like this
I need to shoot them at you with everything I've got
They're on a direct course to your heart
My spirit is on fire
I'll expose your true nature
Don't worry, I'll be gentle
I'll take you to a secret paradise
And offer you a grand feast
When the two of us become one
An innocent flower blooms
Episode 4
The enemy fleet is approaching
Ataraxia at high speed.
Fifty kilometers until we're in main gun range.
Sis, why can't I sortie?
Look.
Luck and fighting spirit won't do us
any good against these numbers.
Your time will come later.
Amaterasu is within range of the
enemy Magitech weapons.
Listen.
Your target is the enemy flagship,
a 2000-meter-long battleship.
Destroy it before its main cannon gets
a chance to target Megafloat Japan!
Sheesh...
You make it sound so easy!
Here I come!
There!
Don't focus on the Magitech weapons!
Thirty kilometers until we're within
the enemy battleship's range.
Everyone...
I'm... number one!
A Dragorie...
Aine's Hybrid Count is dropping faster than usual.
If Chidorigafuchi's Count drops to zero...
Ten kilometers until we're within
the enemy battleship's range.
Chidorigafuchi.
This is...
...all I have!
Chidorigafuchi, you're overusing your Absolute Zone!
I can defeat Category-A weapons too.
I'm every bit as good as Julicia and Hayuru.
You're overdoing it!
That took your Hybrid Count
all the way down to...
It's below ten percent!
That's plenty!
Wait, Chidorigafuchi!
Hold on, Kizuna!
We're in range of the enemy battleship!
Just wait, Chidorigafuchi!
Eros!
I'm almost there...
But I'm out of energy.
Am I supposed to head that way?
Chidorigafuchi...
Chidorigafuchi!
Wake up!
Hida...
Good, you're awake.
Where am I?
The tuning room in Nayuta Labs.
You took a direct hit from the enemy ship,
but you're doing just fine.
I think you were lucky.
Stay down.
What's the situation?
Their cannons have stopped firing,
but a drop squad of Magitech
weapons is landing now.
I need to get back out there...
Wait a second.
I can't send you out there, Chidorigafuchi.
Why?
I see.
My Hybrid Count is under five percent.
That means I can't even equip
my Heart Hybrid Gear...
Move.
I can't let you go out there
and throw your life away.
I...
The Heart Hybrid Gear is all I have.
I'm not allowed to be worse than anyone at using it!
And you're telling me I can't fight,
or even equip my Gear?
That means I'm worthless.
There's no reason for me to exist!
And there's no reason for me to live!
Chidorigafuchi...
I have nothing.
Absolutely nothing!
I don't know who I am or where I'm from.
I don't remember my name, my home, or my family.
You're not surprised, huh?
That's right.
I was brought to this lab.
And after that, I spent all my time as
a test subject in Dr. Nayuta's research.
I don't remember anything
before being brought here.
And all I remember after that
is being a guinea pig here.
That's all I have.
When I try to take an interest in something,
I start to wonder if the real me,
the old me, would've cared about it.
And once that starts, I can't bring myself to care.
Once the combat tests started and
I came to the high school, it got worse.
You never thought about making friends?
I'm afraid of being around other people.
I mean, I never even talked to anyone at the lab.
I'm incapable of holding a proper conversation.
But there is one thing I can lean on.
The Heart Hybrid Gear.
Whenever I got stronger, Dr. Nayuta praised me.
She was happy.
I was the only one who could use
the Heart Hybrid Gear back then.
But outside of that,
there was nothing else I could do.
I'm better than anyone at using the
Heart Hybrid Gear, and I'm stronger too!
That's who I am!
But I can't defeat the enemy at all!
Hayuru's defeated 200 enemies. Julicia, 300.
And I've only defeated thirty-eight.
Dr. Nayuta once told me...
...that there's an incredibly powerful
"Immoral Weapon" inside me.
When my Hybrid Count goes over
its capacity, it might appear.
My mom said that?
I told myself that everything would work out
if I got my hands on the Immoral Weapon.
But how could I get my Hybrid Count
above full when it just kept going down?
Just when I thought it might be impossible
after all, you appeared, Hida Kizuna.
The man who can break
the limits on the Hybrid Count.
I was overjoyed.
I was filled with hope,
and the whole world seemed different.
You felt like a prince that Dr. Nayuta had sent me.
I told myself I had to make you like me.
That I had to make you love me.
But I didn't know what to do.
I looked at everything I could find in the database.
A magazine boys read said that they
like it when girls make them lunch.
But I couldn't cook, so I didn't know what to do.
I made a lunch even though
I didn't know how to cook.
And then I read a naughty book for boys
to find out what would make you happy.
That's why you came to wake me up that morning?
I-I was actually planning on doing
all sorts of things to wake you up.
B-But I couldn't.
And the other day...
I didn't know what you would do, and I was scared,
but I thought it might get you
to make a move on me.
It didn't work, though.
I didn't get my Immoral Weapon.
In the end, I was useless.
There was no reason for me to even be alive.
Either way, with that huge fleet out there,
Ataraxia's probably done for.
Everyone's going to die, and it's all my fault.
Enough!
What?
Worthless?
Useless?
You're just whining since nobody's
telling you how great you are!
Don't act like you know anything!
So what if you can't beat someone?
So what if some people are just better than you?
Don't throw a tantrum and put yourself down.
Shut up!
I don't want to be lectured by someone
who doesn't understand a thing!
Zeros!
Even if you think you don't have any talents,
and that you're nothing special,
try to figure out what you can do,
and how you can be of help.
That's the kind of outlook you need to have.
If you do, you'll find that everyone
in this world has a purpose!
Why didn't you dodge?
At least deploy your Absolute Zone, you idiot.
You're right.
No way...
Let me see that.
The enemies hit me harder
than I thought they would.
You dummy! You dummy!
You fool! You useless dummy!
You're weak... You don't have any power...
So dodge!
Why did you do that for me?
I can't even fight anymore...
All I can do now is die...
I helped my mom, Hida Nayuta,
with her research here.
But somebody who was better for the research
appeared, and I was told I wasn't needed anymore.
I didn't know anything besides the experiments,
but she threw me away anyway.
When I went on my own to the Tokyo Float,
and started attending school, things got really bad.
Because I could barely even talk to anyone.
But...
A person's value isn't decided by their abilities.
It's decided by how they live.
We can always go back and do things over.
We can always start over.
That's what I learned then.
But...
I don't know how to live.
Neither do I.
So, why don't you think about
how we can live with me?
Chidorigafuchi?
Kizuna, um...
Do a Heart Hybrid with me, please?
I can start over, right?
It's embarrassing, but I don't mind if it's with you.
Aine...
Take responsibility, okay?
Roger.
Don't play with my body...
Does it hurt?
It feels good.
You're so cute.
It worked, Aine.
Kizuna, I want more.
You haven't had enough either, right?
Hey, Kizuna...
My body feels hot.
Hurry up and take responsibility.
Wh-What's gotten into you, Aine?
Allow me to explain.
Shikina!
It's a side effect of the Heart Hybrid.
When the Heart Hybrid is successful,
your partner will be overcome by
strong symptoms that resemble lust.
Their libido goes into overdrive.
That's a huge nuisance!
But if you use that effect properly,
you can proceed to a higher stage.
A higher stage?
Yes, a new kind of Hybrid that will allow
for the acquisition of Immoral Weapons.
The Climax Hybrid.
Hey, Aine, what are you...?
You're talking to another woman when
you should be having fun with me?
Th-That's not true, Aine.
You're all I'm thinking about right now.
Then prove it.
Hurry.
Aine...
Oh, Kizuna...
It feels so good, Kizuna...
Kizuna...
I-I can't breathe...
No! At this rate, I'll suffocate!
N-No!
Don't...
No!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Aine!
Are you two okay?!
Yes.
You saved us!
You're going to pay for all this.
Pulverizer!
What's that?
Zeros's new weapon?
Connect!
The Climax Hybrid succeeded, didn't it?
That is her Immoral Weapon.
Now it's our turn.
Charge!
I can buy you some time to charge that thing.
Zeros Mode!
That's Eros?
It seems as fast and powerful as the Zeros!
Take this!
Blast!
Enemy battleship has disappeared from the radar!
The enemy fleet has withdrawn
beyond firing range.
We've won!
Yay!
Hooray!
Why are you standing out here, looking so glum?
What about you? Did you enjoy the party?
I'm tired after being dragged around everywhere.
I see.
Hey, Kizuna.
I got something else besides my Immoral
Weapon when I did my Climax Hybrid.
What was that?
A fragment of my memories.
What?
A beautiful lake, and snow-covered peaks.
A huge city with tall buildings.
And a huge, complicated mechanical
clock that covered an entire wall.
That's great!
So I want you to do it again—
How about an apple, Snow White? Relax, it's safe
Ah! There you are!
What are you two doing?!
You know, that shit-eating grin really pisses me off
Well, if it isn't the Japanese and American aces,
who couldn't shoot down a single enemy battleship!
I'm gonna punch you
Don't want to hear that from
the first one to get shot down.
Forgive me for being cold to you
That's right.
You were the one who...
Didn't you know?
Know what?
I got in trouble deliberately.
It's just that there was this girl looking at you in the cafe
You don't want to stop them, Captain?
I'm gonna kill her
She'd probably leave you before the night is over
I probably should.
Let me show you the storm of emotions trapped beneath the surface
Why the sudden call?
Go beyond your dreams, love's waiting for you there
Reiri, take a look at this.
What do you want so badly that you'd cry for it?
A human?
All I want is your heart's warmth
And they're wearing something that
appears to be a Heart Hybrid Gear.
There's no escape from the love that's seeping through your veins
What's a human doing with the
Magitech weapons from another world?
Are they from that other world as well?
Hold me, hold your breath
You're my prince
Just kidding
Found you!
Illustration
Choboraunyopomi
Did something happen between Kizuna and Aine?
Sure looks like it.
I'll have to go after him hard, too.
NEXT TIME
BEAUTY OF THE LAND OF RUBBLE
"Love Room," you say?
What's that?