Ouch!
Time to go.
Here I come!
Manaria Friends
Anne and Grea
Was first period potions?
That looks good!
Wasn't it healing magic?
With Ms. Miranda?
Have you filled out the room-sharing form?
I'm still thinking about it.
Princess! Good morning!
Good morning.
Morning.
Good day.
Good morning.
A wonderful morning to you.
Grea!
Morning!
I finally found you!
M-Morning.
Thanks.
Um, Princess Anne...
Come on, you're the Dragon Princess yourself.
Just call me Anne.
Anne!
Anne...
Yes, what is it?
Do you remember the book we borrowed together?
The one I recommended?
Yeah.
I'm still only partway through it,
but I'm learning a lot about Manaria.
Or rather, about you. I'm enjoying it.
That's great!
The library here has so many books
in all sorts of languages.
Don't you just want to read them all?
Y-Yeah.
Oh yeah, I found a book about
the land of the dragons the other day.
What kind of place is it?
Um...
There are lots of big animals, unlike here, I suppose.
That sounds lovely!
So what made you decide to come to this academy?
Um... Well, my mother was once a student here.
And, you know... I'm also a half-dragon.
Oh, so your mom is an alumna!
Anne!
Ann—whoa!
Lou?!
Are you okay?
Thank you so much, Anne.
There's trouble in the library! Come quick!
Huh? Wai—
Sorry, Grea!
I'll just be a minute!
O-Okay.
What happened to him?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
You okay, Hanna?
Princess?
I'm sorry for stepping on it...
Everyone, get back!
The princess is amazing!
We're saved!
Is it fine if I seal it?
Y-Yeah.
Okay.
Ice Bind!
Sorry.
Don't be.
Achoo!
It's not your fault, Princess.
I was the one who asked you
to seal the Lord of the Library.
But Hanna, you—
I wasn't even strong enough to help you.
I'm a failure of a president.
I'm so weak.
I'm a disappointment.
I'm not cut out for this.
Thank you.
Um, I can help out if there's anything else you need.
We should be fine for today.
Thank you for your assistance, Princess.
G—
Grea?!
Anne...
Uh...
Are you all done now?
Y-Yeah.
It got encased in ice when I sealed it.
I mean, the Master of the Library was really mad.
It was going berserk.
And, well...
I was helping everyone clean up after me...
But I then left first...
You did well.
Were you waiting for me this whole time?
Yeah.
I think that was a little bit
more than a minute, though.
What's wrong?
Oh, uh...
Are you hungry, Anne?
Oh, now that you mention it,
I haven't eaten since this morning.
Should we get something to eat?
Yeah!
Do you prefer sweet or spicy food, Grea?
Um... Sweet.
I thought so! I do too!
My name is Owen.
Though I am but seventeen,
I am a proud and noble paladin.
One day, in the course of my position as a guard
at the royal palace, I was given a new duty.
Upon my honor and my very life, I, Owen,
pledge to protect you, Princess.
You don't have to be so formal!
Come on, chin up.
But Princess...
It's fine, come on!
As you wish.
Let's have a good time together, Owen.
The princess had always had
exceptional magical talent.
She also studied the ways
of a good ruler.
In spite of this,
she wanted to reach an even greater height.
She decided of her own volition
to enroll at Manaria Magical Academy.
She actually summoned it!
That's amazing!
It didn't take long for her to draw
the attention of those around her.
Actually, I had a really hard time
forming my first summoning contract.
It was with a fire spirit that ended up
burning some of my hair off!
But behind her gentle smile lay a modicum of...
People always got mad at me
back when I was in the palace.
...shall I say loneliness?
I caught glimpses of something
like that hidden within her.
However...
It's important to eat your vegetables.
My name is Owen.
I offer everything I have to my liege,
the princess, as a proud and noble paladin!
- Episode 2 -
The Anguished Dragon Princess
Manaria Friends, Episode 2:
"The Anguished Dragon Princess."
Illustrator: Onda Naoyuki