Are the costumes all ready?
Where are the props?
We're about to start the rehearsal!
All done!
I'm so glad I finished in time.
It was really worth going the extra mile!
Now then, I must go see to the other girls' costumes.
Break a leg!
Grea...
Manaria Friends
Backstage
Where's the president?
It looks like she has her hands full overseeing the play.
Oh, the one that the princess is going to be in?
Once more from the top,
as if this were the real thing!
Start the music from the beginning, please.
This one is for you, Lou.
I made it so you'll really shine up there!
Thank you.
I'm still so nervous.
Like a scene from a painting...
What is it?
Oh, it just hit me how great you look in that.
You don't think it looks strange?
Not at all.
Wouldn't you have been
better suited for this role, Anne?
Come on, everyone's saying they
want to see you as the princess!
Chin up!
But I feel so weird wearing all these frills.
You'll be fine.
We've practiced plenty!
I think I might have a stomachache.
Whereabouts?!
Anne!
I'll heal you up in no time!
I-I'm fine, really!
Are you sure?
It's not that bad!
Really?
Yes, I'm fine.
Let me know straight away if you start feeling ill.
A-All right.
Thanks.
How do the lights on that side look?
All right!
Yes, we'll have it ready right away.
Okay, let's go with that.
Don't forget, now.
All right, let's start from the opening scene.
Lighting, make sure you coordinate
your cues with the music.
Do you want to go over it one more time?
I already did before I went to bed last night,
and again before I left this morning.
Grea...
I don't know if I can do this.
I know!
In and out...
Take a deep breath.
And let it out.
Anne?
Don't worry.
I'll be with you.
Close your eyes.
Now let's try floating a bit.
Floating?
Use your imagination!
Huh?
Anne?
Don't move.
Relax your arms and legs...
Relax...
Open your eyes.
I implore you, look my way.
You have nothing to fear.
Aren't those her lines?
The voices that fill your frightened heart
come not from the countrypeople you abhor.
They are your lack of faith in yourself given voice.
Despair becomes a disease that torments all.
I cannot help but to hesitate
for fear of taking the first step.
I cannot do this without you!
Anne...
Prince...
You have nothing to fear.
You are like a songbird at dawn.
He who has brought me salvation.
Princess.
Thank you.
We're about to start.
Please take your places.
Grea!
You have nothing to fear, Princess.
Not as long as we stay together.
I shall remain by your side, my Prince.
Whoa.
It's a full house.
Break a leg, Hanna!
Thank you.
Die neue Welt wird umarmt von dem sich ausbreitendem blauen Himmel
The new world is embraced by the expanding blue sky
Und in Ewigkeit das war verschwunden indes
With it comes the end of an eternity
Zum Schutz dessen nehmen die Weiden im Winde
The wind sweeps protectively across countless pastures
Haben sich unter Bergen zum Hof der Schimmel
From mountains' hearth to courtyards bathed in moss
Wow, Hanna.
We have to follow this?
Yeah.
Now I think I might have a stomachache.
Huh?!
:
Hat dir die Hoffnung in der kleinen Welt der Menschen mitnichten erfullt
Are you not filled with hope in this small world of ours?
:
Der Name dieses Hoffnungstrager ist
That which carries this hope is called
Der Name ist Mystalsia
It is called Mystalsia
Der auf ewig funkelnde, der auf ewig funkelnde Mystalsia
The ever luminescent, ever radiant, Mystalsia
It's already morning...
The day of the performance is already here.
What am I going to do?
- Episode 9 -
One Day...
Manaria Friends, Episode 9:
Illustrator