Everyone, evacuate through here!
Younger students first!
Please follow the student council's instructions!
Don't push!
No talking!
Get moving!
We're closing the gate!
The barricade is ready to be deployed!
Where's the barricade?!
Is there anyone still inside?
Close it! Quickly!
We still haven't figured out
how many monsters there are!
How do they keep multiplying?
If they have a magic circle set up, where could it be?
A barricade here would keep them from advancing!
They'll break through in an instant.
We need to replenish our mana.
How are we doing?
We don't even know how many have escaped!
We'll have to count again.
Can't we coordinate with
the other groups somehow?
They sure did a number on us.
It looks like the monsters are appearing
from somewhere within the academy.
We need to stay calm.
Our control tower is down!
They barely even put up a fight!
Areas with the largest number of students were targeted,
so our first line of defense wasn't particularly effective.
Make sure you record all of this.
Okay!
President, the southwest gate won't hold!
They're about to invade the southern tower!
What about the barricade?
What is the defense team doing?!
President...
I know.
I have to get as many students
to safety as I possibly can.
There should still be a way.
President, the southwest gate has fallen!
Invading forces entering the medical tower!
We need help!
Manaria Friends
President!
The Academy Falls
Excuse me...
Do you know where to evacuate to?
Y-Yes!
Then you should hurry.
Okay.
Thank you so much!
Grea...
Don't forget why you're here.
But Grea's still out there!
I'm sorry, Anne.
Why?
Why am I being left out?
We didn't expect the medical tower to fall.
What happened to the students inside?
How do our medical supply reserves look?
I'll go and check.
Take whatever's left to the auditorium.
Understood!
How many students are still on campus?
We don't know exactly, but there are still a fair few.
I see.
The princess would've done a much better job...
President...
I've really been put in my place.
They've taken the auditorium!
I'm gonna go check!
Don't leave your posts!
Gather the medical supplies!
What's the situation?
The defense team has been taken out!
The barricades have also been destroyed!
Monsters will be here any minute!
Quickly!
We haven't finished evacuating everyone!
Where's the rescue team?
We'll be surrounded if we leave now!
Calm down!
But—
President...
Where is the rescue team?
If we're gonna die, then what's the point?!
But—
I need a messenger—
Wait!
Leaving now will just increase
the number of casualties.
Are we just going to leave them behind?
We're abandoning the western tower...
and this place as well.
Everyone, bring only what
you need and head to the gate.
What?!
Prepare a barricade for the grand staircase.
This means half of the academy's already done for.
Understood.
The barricade at the grand staircase
seems to be standing fast.
The main building is also holding up for now.
I wonder how many people we can
bring here and lead to safety.
I'm going to the eastern tower.
Can you send some forces to the library as well?
Everyone's fighting while I'm just sitting here.
Let us be on our way.
Let me come too!
Please respect our wishes.
But—
What's the situation at the main tower?
How can everyone leave me out of this?
Can we make it in time?
Are you okay?
Please give me a moment.
Okay.
There are still this many students left?
Grea!
I'm so glad you're safe!
I'm so sorry. I couldn't hold them off.
There's still more we can do.
Please lend us your strength.
Princess.
Allow me to accompany you.
Bring those over here!
Please form groups by color and stay together!
Keep the queues nice and orderly!
We'll intercept them at the gate!
Draw them in as close as possible!
Keep the monsters inside the academy at all costs!
Are we ready to close the gate?
Yes.
Please hurry!
Please hurry! We're about to close the gate.
What's going on?
Wh-What in the world is that?
What the heck is that thing?!
I've never seen anything like it!
Looks like no one was injured.
What do we do?
What's going on—
Oh no!
Grea!
P-Princess?!
Where?
What is she doing here?
Princess!
Why did you come?!
Anne!
Hey! What do you think you're doing to Grea?!
How uncouth.
I did it!
Should you really be celebrating?
Huh?
What's going on?
What happened?
This must be Anne's handiwork.
Stop the drill! Stop the drill!
Wait, what?
Hey, they're calling it off...
Huh, why?
I heard there was a golem.
No way!
Was that a summon?
I wonder.
Do you think it can be repaired?
The evacuation drill is now over.
No... Definitely not.
All students not performing repairs,
promptly head to the communications
tower before leaving school for the day.
I repeat—
Goodness me, don't you know
how to hold back, Princess?
If she'd just stayed put, the academy wouldn't
have been subjected to this level of destruction.
This is why we asked you to sit this one out!
Hanna.
Yes?
It seems that problems arose due to ambiguity
in the chain of command during the drill.
It's important to make appropriate decisions,
even under pressure or unforeseen circumstances.
The front line of defense should
have been deployed by the gate first,
to ensure the evacuation route—
Do you think it can be repaired?
No... Definitely not.
I suppose we'll have to suspend classes for a while.
...which is why we decided it would be worthwhile
for the students to run a disaster drill on their own.
That sounds like a lot of fun!
Specifically, it will involve evacuating
all students through the gate
and into the communications tower
in response to a monster invasion.
Right.
Yeah!
The teachers will summon dummy monsters.
We'll be pumping them out, so stay on your guard!
I haven't gotten a chance to go
all out for a while! I can't wait!
Don't you worry. I'll take out anything that comes our way.
Um, Princess, about that.
Huh?
We'd like for you to sit this one out, Princess.
Sit it out?
This is meant to be training
for the students, after all.
What does that mean?
You won't be participating, Princess.
Huh?
Many were of the opinion that the other
students would come to rely on you,
which wouldn't make for very good training.
That's totally fine! Let them rely on me!
But Anne, your magic is really powerful.
You might destroy the whole school!
I won't!
The general consensus among the student council
is that the students should handle this themselves.
But I'm a student too!
Come on, I won't get in the way! Please!
Just to be clear, we don't want you
participating or helping out at all on the day.
Grea!
Oh, Grea, we'd like you to be
part of the interception team.
What?
Oh, okay.
I'll do my best.
Lucky you!
I want to be in the drill too!
- Episode 6 -
Floating at Sea
Manaria Friends, Episode 6:
Floating at Sea.
Illustrator: Yoh Yoshinari