Manaria Friends
One Day...
I won't be a moment.
Thanks, Hanna.
Oh, Princess.
Anne?
N-No way...
Why?
What's wrong?
Don't give me that...
I'm sorry?
You never let me into your room,
even though I've asked you so many times!
What are you talking about?
I'm not talking to you, Hanna!
Don't be rude, Anne.
You didn't have to snap at her.
Oh dear, what's going on?
Oh, Hanna.
Are you two still fighting?
It's none of your business.
Grea, I've called the repairman.
Shall we head up and wait together?
Yeah, sure.
H-Huh?
Oh, um... Uh...
Let's go, Hanna.
Sure.
Oh, come on! This is all wrong!
Pitty pat pat, build the snowman just like that!
Pitty pat pat—
Okay everyone, open up your textbooks.
Today we'll be talking about how
healing magic can help clear your mind.
Holy magic is well known for its effects on the body.
Take exorcism and strengthening spells, for example.
Now turn to the next page.
In fact, experiments in holy magic
from ancient times have demonstrated
that it can have tremendous
effects on the mind as well.
So not only can it be used to heal your body,
it can also to help you overcome negative emotions.
In practice, spirits need to be—
Anne...
Er, spirits need to be convinced
to lend their power—
Okay, that's enough for today.
Don't forget to revise.
What should we do after school?
Wanna go to that place again?
What place?
That place we went last time.
Look, Anne, aren't those—
How did things end up like this?
Anne.
Were you playing the piano?
Yeah...
It's so cold that...
my hands went all numb.
Shall we go and have tea?
Yeah!
Once, two opposing, chaotic powers
engulfed the world in the flames of battle.
This land became a battlefield.
The people that fell to pain
and sorrow raised a prayer to God.
It was then that Seraph Manaria
was sent from the heavens
to quell the flames of battle that ravaged the lands.
But we now face a crisis
that threatens that very peace.
I—no, all of us—must face it.
You may not be aware of how dire the situation is,
but even the most trivial of disagreements can form
a vicious cycle of confrontation and hatred.
Two chaotic powers are about
to rise from our very academy.
By "two chaotic powers," do you mean...
...the Princess and Grea?
If these powers collide, an endless battle will ensue.
Not only will it affect the academy,
the entire world will be plunged into chaos!
All will be led down a path of grief and sorrow!
Are you saying this could spark war
between the two kingdoms?
To turn a blind eye to this problem
would be to disgrace our ancestors,
who prayed for and protected the peace of this land.
So those of us who love Manaria and came
here to gather the fruit of her knowledge
must stand together to protect her peace!
Allow me to take this vow!
As student council president, I will stand firm against
these powers' chaos to avoid this terrible fate!
I pray you'll give me your blessing.
President...
Hanna!
She's so dazzling!
I will now head out to battle,
to protect the peace of our academy!
President!
I'll fight with you too!
I'll come with you as well!
Me too!
And me!
Thank you.
Princess, Grea!
Please spare a moment to listen
to what we... have to... say?
This really warms you up!
Yeah, it's very relaxing.
Oh, Hanna?
What's everyone doing here?
By the way, where did you buy these tea leaves?
Have they made up?
There's a store in town I'm really fond of.
We should go together some time!
Yes, that sounds great.
How can you two worry everyone like that?
My determination was all for naught!
- Episode 10 -
Their Promise
Manaria Friends, Episode 10:
Their Promise.
Illustrator: Mizuta Kenji