Anne?
What's up?
Oh, you cut your hair!
Huh? Yeah...
Hey, Grea, let's go into town. We'll go shopping!
Sound good?
But I don't have any clothes that—
Your sizes changed after you molted, right?
Here, try this on!
Okay.
Manaria Friends
The Princess' Day Off
This is a disguise, isn't it?
I'm glad the clothes I brought suit you so well.
We're going undercover today.
I feel like this just makes us stand out more.
It's fine, no one will know!
Oh, it's the princess!
Oh?
Out shopping?
Princess, Princess! Show us some magic!
How are you on this fine day, Princess?
What are you out shopping for, Princess?
Welcome back, Princess!
I'm sorry they're bothering you, Princess.
Would you like some flowers, Princess?
Yeah, okay... Everyone's so full of energy.
Princess, Princess!
Sure, thank you.
I'll take one.
Princess.
Princess!
Yeah, thanks!
I guess it wasn't much of a disguise.
You're definitely a princess, Anne.
What's that supposed to mean?
Anyway, let's have fun shopping today.
Oh hey, a suspicious-looking alleyway.
Have you ever been down here, Grea?
No, I haven't.
This place is kind of dreary.
Yeah, it is.
There's no one around, either.
Maybe there's just nothing here.
I wonder if that's another boutique?
Want to have a look?
Yeah.
Is it really a boutique?
Maybe it's a studio.
It sure looks like one, but...
What kind of clothes are these?
The top looks like a gym uniform.
But isn't the bottom from a swimsuit?
Welcome!
These are combat garments,
a specialty of the Eastern countries—
Oh, Anne?
M-Ms. Mira?!
"Welcome"?
This is your store?
Well, um, yes.
I'm a seamstress, so I figured I'd try
to make some profit off my hobby, I suppose?
Does the academy let you take on side jobs?
F-Fine! Go ahead and take whatever you want!
Really?!
Of course.
Yay! Let's hurry and try all this stuff on, Grea!
But in return, you have to keep
this a secret from the academy.
Hey, wait!
This one is so cute!
Ta-da!
How does this one look?
How about this?
They look great.
You're really starting to enjoy this, huh?
Would you like to try something on too, Grea?
Oh, I'm fine—
Please bring us the cutest outfit you have, Ms. Mira!
Oh, she's running away.
Oh dear, Grea.
Huh? W-Wait!
How do I even put this on?
Those are pajamas!
You could get a matching set
and have a sleepover—
I'm sure you'd have a blast!
A matching set?!
All done, Grea?
Grea?
We'll take this one too!
Sure, it's yours!
It's so cold!
It was definitely worth the wait.
That looks relaxing.
Sure does.
Want to give it a go?
Huh?
Hey, Anne.
Yeah, wh-what's up?
Umm...
Do you not like being on boats?
N-No, I'm totally fine!
Please don't tell anyone.
I've been keeping this a secret my whole life.
I actually...
can't swim.
Huh?
B-But I can use my magic to float and dive,
or walk on water!
I think that's much more remarkable.
I just can't swim by myself.
So, umm...
That's good to know.
Huh?
I guess there are things that even you're bad at.
Well, yeah...
Um, thanks for taking me out today.
Huh?
And for picking an outfit for me.
No problem, I had fun too.
Umm...
I'd love to go out with you again sometime.
Really?!
Are you okay?
I-I'm fine.
Oh yeah.
Ms. Mira gave us a matching set of pajamas.
Can I come and sleep over at your place
...sometime?
No.
What?!
Why won't she let me stay over?
I wonder why...
Why, Grea?!
I've always slept like this.
I've been doing it for so long
that I just can't break the habit.
But sleeping like this is so embarrassing.
I can't let Anne see me like this.
See you, Ms. Mira.
Yeah, good work today.
Take care on your way home.
You're not leaving yet, Ms. Mira?
No, it's almost exam period, after all.
And I have my classes to prepare for.
Oh, that must be rough.
Can we help with anything?
Don't worry about me.
Thanks though, I'll see you two tomorrow.
All right, bye!
Excuse us.
Now, then...
Time to let loose!
I haven't had the time to go to my store lately.
Just a bit should be fine...
This feels great!
I need an outlet for this burning passion!
Just for a bit, just for a bit!
F-Finished.
Now then, who should I have wear these?
It has to be...
Sorry, Ms. Mira, I left something here.
Huh?
Anne, Grea...
Manaria Friends, Episode 4: Exam Period.
- Episode 4 -
Exam Period
Illustrator: Norio Tsukudani