Don't think we'll go easy on you
just because you're younger.
We're playing to win.
We aren't
gonna lose!
Then let's get to it!
Hey, Grea...
Do we really have to do this?
Like, really?
Manaria Friends
Floating at Sea
Wow, what a view!
It really is beautiful.
It's kind of romantic being alone with you up here.
Wh-What are you talking about?
Anyway, we've seen this magnificent view,
so let's head back.
Not so fast.
Let's go. It's just through there.
Come on.
Really?
Just you wait.
Hey, Grea...
Don't you think we should head back after all?
We've already come this far.
It's not that I don't enjoy being alone with you.
I'm really happy, but...
We're almost there.
Stop, I can't walk like this!
Then let's head back already!
Are you sure you want to go back?
Hey, what are you doing down there?
I didn't do anything!
Oh, Anne! This was your idea, you know!
Then let's spend the night together too.
Okay, Anne.
I heard the night sky is really pretty here.
Let's check it out together.
Okay, Anne.
Let's set off some fireworks, too!
And then we'll have a sleepover!
Okay, An—
What?!
I brought our matching pajamas and everything!
No, I can't!
All right, it's settled!
Off we go!
It's so pretty.
It's a nice place, right?
It's really pretty!
How did you find this place?
No one will bother us here.
Shall we get started?
What are you doing?
I'm making a sandcastle.
Wanna help?
Hurry up and take off your jacket.
Why?
Come on, hurry up.
I'm not ready yet...
Don't give me that!
Take it off for me, then.
Why do I have to?!
Not bad.
There's more where that came from!
Now shall we get started?
Get what started?
Aren't we here to practice?
You said you wanted to come here because
you were embarrassed about other people seeing you.
Come on, take off your jacket.
Take it off.
Fine...
What do you think?
Stop using your magic, Anne.
What do I need to swim for, anyway?
I can just walk on the water!
No.
Don't worry, I'll stay with you.
But I can't reach the bottom anymore!
Calm down.
Why don't you try floating on your own?
Float?!
Humans weren't made to float!
You'll be fine. Just give it a try.
Come on, Anne.
Take a deep breath.
Now let it out.
And in.
And out.
Relax your body.
It's fine. Don't be afraid.
Try to relax.
You're doing fine.
That's it. Keep your eyes on the sky.
Relax your arms and legs.
Don't tense up.
Relax.
Open your eyes.
So this is what it feels like to float.
Yeah.
Thanks, Grea.
You're telling me you hold
these fireworks in your hands?
Apparently they're from the East.
Ms. Mira ordered them for us.
Are these really safe?
I'm sure they're fine.
You always say that before
you do something dangerous.
We're shooting off fireworks
even though we can see the stars?
You don't do that where you're from, Grea?
Not really.
I've heard fireworks have also been a part
of auspicious occasions since olden times.
I can't wait!
It'd be way more fun to have a fight with 'em,
rather than just setting them off.
Shall we light them up?
They're so pretty!
Wow!
Whoa!
DO NOT ATTEMPT
What do you want to do now, Grea?
Huh?
We're finished with the fireworks.
They were a lot of fun.
Yeah.
It's sad to think that we're leaving tomorrow.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
But we did everything we wanted to.
All that's left is the sleepover.
Huh?!
I did my best today!
I've come such a long way!
We can finally wear our matching pajamas!
No, wait!
I can't wait to sleep together!
It's not
going to happen,
Anne!
Let's greet a lovely morning together!
I said no!
- Episode 7 -
Hide and Seek
Manaria Friends, Episode 7:
Hide and Seek.
Illustrator: Enarain