After Kakeru's mother passed away,
he lived with his grandmother.
This is our second visit here as a group.
The last time we were here was for Kakeru's funeral.
I've been waiting for you.
Please, take your time talking to Kakeru today.
Sure thing.
Thanks for having us.
My, how adorable.
Yours?
Oh... Yes, mine and—
We married.
You haven't changed a bit.
Suwa-kun and Naho-san, right?
You remember us?
Yes, of course.
Azusa-san. Takako-san.
Hagita-san.
Kakeru always used to talk about you all.
Especially you, Naho-san.
To the Kakeru living ten years ago...
I'm sorry I couldn't save you.
I wanted to talk to you so much more.
I could never find the courage to talk to you,
and that's something I deeply regret.
What was it you wanted to tell me that day?
Beads of all shapes, sizes and colors
Sat on a table, shining
Shining at each other
Sparkling in a rainbow of colors
Even if our days shatter, breaking bit by bit
Those broken pieces still shine on
Sometimes coming closer, sometimes separating
The matching fragments connect
Even the sad things we've gone through
Even all the tear-filled memories
Make up your smile's colorful glow
The setting sun shines against the orange sky
Making our matching shadows sway
I wanted to tell you something but I couldn't
And with time, our light slowly dies
The robot works until 10:30
On today's menu
strawberry
Medium and
large available
1 cone: 320 yen
I guess Kakeru's on a date with
Ueda-senpai right about now.
Wonder what they're doing.
Going on a date, duh.
A date...
I've decided! Let's buy matching pairs!
Huh?
Uh, they're cute, but aren't they kinda short?
Well, they're called shorts for a reason.
Oh, yeah.
Azu, does your dad bake bread even
on the days when the store is closed?
Yup. 'Cause bread's his hobby.
So the baker likes bread.
What kind of hobby is that?
How about your folks, Naho?
Huh?
You weren't listening, were you?
Yeah...
I guess we... look after ricefish?
What, you grow them big, then eat them?
They don't get big.
They're just ricefish.
They won't turn into frogs or anything.
Suwa, how many ricefish would
you need to eat to be full?
A hundred million!
No way, no way.
That ain't enough. Not even close.
So you plan to eat all the ricefish in Japan?
That's a giant's appetite for you!
When are you gonna get over the giant thing?
Okay then, what about loaches?
Loaches?
You're killin' me here!
Golden Week Campaign
Special
Plenty of goods
Like this eco bag
Why aren't you coming?
I told you, cell phones aren't allowed in my family.
Good morning!
Oh, morning.
NO
I wonder what happened to that note.
What are you gonna do about Kawakita's test?
Not gonna bother.
You can't do that!
Man, I'm beat. Got the post-vacation blues.
Morning.
Why didn't you wake me up this morning?
I kinda overslept a little.
Sorry.
No, it's fine.
Did you forget?
No.
You have a girlfriend now.
I didn't think it'd be okay if I called you.
Also, I didn't make you a lunch today.
I see.
Thanks for all the ones you made me.
It must've been tough making them
for two people every day...
I really appreciated them.
Sorry for being pushy about it.
Really?
Man, you're all sweaty!
Kakeru!
What is it?
Seriously, just tell her.
Really? You think I should?
I—
Kakeru!
Good morning!
Oh... Morning.
What is it, Naho?
Never mind.
Let's go, Kakeru.
What were you talking about?
Nothing much.
All right, we'll pick up where we left off next time.
Did you watch yesterday?
Totally.
That was so wrong.
What? No way!
Hagita, let's go grab some bread!
Want to come—
Kakeru!
It's Ueda-senpai.
So they're dating?
Ugh, what a shock!
Sorry, Hagita-kun.
That girl from before was nice.
She's so plain and bumpkin-ish.
Have you gone many places since coming here?
Not at all.
Yeah, there aren't any good places
around these parts. I'm so bored.
It's totally different out here, isn't it?
Like how the kids go about their lives and stuff.
It's all mountains out here.
Just nature and more nature.
But it's cool in the summer, at least.
I guess it's okay if you've got a car, though.
Bet you'll never get caught up
in a traffic jam out here.
Right?
Yeah.
Oh, next time, let's go to the live club.
Huh? Where's that?
By the station.
My friend's a DJ there.
He's really good.
Okay? You'll come, right?
Huh? Er, sure...
May 17th
After Kakeru started going out with Ueda-senpai,
I lost all chances to talk to him.
May 17th
After Kakeru started going out with Ueda-senpai,
I lost all chances to talk to him.
Then show me a picture.
In your dreams, man!
Come on! One picture can't hurt.
I don't have any.
But you just said you did.
I did not!
Oh, come on! Why are you so flustered?
Where's Kakeru?
Senpai took him somegromf.
Again?
Yup. She nabs him every free period.
To be honest, I don't like Ueda-senpai.
Me neither.
I wonder if Kakeru's on her side or ours.
Well, Kakeru's only been here
for a month and a half.
And Senpai's apparently from Tokyo, too.
I'm sure they've got plenty to talk about.
Plus she's hot.
No one asked you, Hagita.
Man, why did Kakeru agree to
go out with her? What an idiot.
We should've stopped him.
We made a mistake.
You were happy for him before.
I know, but still.
Why didn't I just tell him "no" face-to-face?
Even though I know the future,
I'm the one who has to make the choice.
Huh? You finished already, Naho?
Do you feel sick? Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm just full.
I'm going to buy some juice.
Oh, me too. Naho, come with us.
I'm coming, too.
Sure, sure.
Hagita, you too.
Rich and Smooth
Café au Lait
Hey! My fried chicken!
Don't sweat it!
Hell no! Give it back!
MILK
Come over here.
Oh, sure.
I set that picture from the
other day as my wallpaper.
Oh? So you did.
Isn't it great? I'll send it to you.
Sure. Thanks.
Hey, Naho...
Are you hiding something from us?
No. Why?
Huh? What's going on?
What about those shorts?
Huh?
Are you wearing them?
They're so cute, I've got them decorating my room.
So you're not!
Oh, look, this one's totally great.
This one too!
Takamiya Naho
After Kakeru started going out with Ueda-senpai, I lost all chances to talk to him.
During lunch break, he called out to me,
This was the first day.
but I ended up avoiding him when I saw Ueda-senpai.
After this, I avoid him a number of times.
When Kakeru calls out to you, please answer him.
I want you to start talking to him, too.
And don't just wait around.
When Kakeru calls out to you, please answer him.
I want you to start talking to him, too.
And don't just wait around.
When Kakeru calls out to you, please answer him.
I want you to start talking to him, too.
And don't just wait around.
When Kakeru calls out to you, please answer him.
I want you to start talking to him, too.
And don't just wait around.
Me, start talking to him?
I can't.
Her bag's gone.
She ditched again? I'll kill her!
Hey, Takamiya.
Come to the staff room, will you?
You can come after you're done.
Oh, okay.
What's wrong?
I got called out.
Why?
Seriously?
Kakeru's... all by himself?
Naho!
I want to talk to you.
When Kakeru calls out to you, please answer him.
If it's something that would upset Senpai...
If it would just get in Kakeru's way...
I'm fine with not being able to talk with him.
Kakeru, sorry I'm late.
"I should have done that back then."
It sure is easy to say that...
What is it?
...when you're in the future.
I can't do it.
I can't do it!
In hindsight, it all seems so effortless.
But in the present,
you're already doing everything you can.
Sometimes things just don't work out.
I've experienced that.
During lunch, he called out to me,
but I ended up avoiding him when I saw Ueda-senpai.
After this, I avoid him a number of times.
During lunch, he called out to me,
but I ended up avoiding him when I saw Ueda-senpai.
After this, I avoid him a number of times.
It was seriously trouble!
Suwa!
May 21st
I'm beat!
You're on cleaning duty.
Huh? Me?
May 21st
After school, after I say "bye-bye" to Kakeru,
Kakeru and Ueda-senpai get in a fight.
May 21st
After school, after I say "bye-bye" to Kakeru,
Kakeru and Ueda-senpai get in a fight.
Bye-bye.
Later on, I found out that Kakeru had been deeply troubled at the time.
Kakeru...
Wai—
Kakeru!
Whoa, she fell.
What do you think you're doing?!
Huh? What do you mean?
My bag just hit her.
Then apologize!
Are you okay?
Yeah? Well, it was your fault, Kakeru!
You're always talking to her!
I don't want you talking to other girls!
Kakeru, you idiot!
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
Don't run away, Naho.
This wasn't in the letter.
Is the future changing?
But... Those two had a fight
because I called out to him.
I... I thought... I shouldn't talk to him... like I used to.
The truth is, there's something
I want to say to him, but...
I don't see what's wrong with you talking to him.
We're all friends, aren't we?
Besides, he's given me quite the headache.
The guy's not focusing at all during practice.
He's down because he wants to talk to you,
but can't find the right opportunity.
He is?
How can Kakeru talk to you
if you keep running away?
I'll go see him!
I'll talk things out with him!
Good. Now get going.
Thank you, Suwa!
Even though Kakeru called out to me,
I avoided him.
Oh! Sorry!
I was doing to Kakeru the exact same
thing I didn't want to happen to me.
I have to tell him!
Thanks, Suwa.
You, thanking me? That's a first.
Naho's hiding something from us.
I can tell.
Yeah.
Knowing Naho, there's no way
she'll tell us what it is.
But I'm relieved that Kakeru stood up for her.
Senpai really pisses me off.
If Suwa hadn't stopped me,
I'd have smacked her good.
I'm sure the me ten years from now
has been feeling regret
a lot longer than I have.
Kakeru may not be there in the future,
but right here, right now, he is!
Kakeru!
Kakeru, you know what?
Making lunch for you isn't tough at all!
I had a great time doing it!
I was happy!
You called out to me the other day!
I'm sorry I didn't answer you!
What did you want to say?
What was it?!
You're too late, Naho.
I already forgot what I was going to say.
But...
There's something bothering you, right?
How'd you know?
I've been thinking about breaking up with Senpai.
Huh?
Guess deciding based off
looks alone was a bad idea!
Is it because of that fight?
That's not it.
You told me "no," remember?
I felt awful not being able to talk to you.
And besides...
There's somebody I'm more
interested in than Senpai.
Somebody you're interested in?
Yeah.
I figured it out after I started dating Senpai.
Is this someone you're in love with?
That's a secret!
I wonder if my future self
knows the person Kakeru is interested in...
If my love for you could stay as it is
I'm fine with these feelings never reaching you
Not truly tied, yet never fully detached
Deep within my heart, tears are shed
At the end of this thin, delicate branch
Your future is being born
Don't prune back those as-of-yet undiscovered days
I want to protect you so that one day, you'll look back and smile
Deep within my heart, tears are shed
But I cherish them
Because I want to be by your side