Chow time!
Check it out!
They're our uniforms for the cheer-off!
Well? Are we cute?
Of course you're not cute, you moron!
Not at all.
Not really.
At least say we're cute, even if you don't mean it.
Talk about cold.
Let's go.
Didn't anyone ever teach them to compliment girls?
What's wrong with them?
Damn, they're short. Those skirts are short!
Damn, damn, damn!
Beads of all shapes, sizes and colors
Sat on a table, shining
Shining at each other
Sparkling in a rainbow of colors
Even if our days shatter, breaking bit by bit
Those broken pieces still shine on
Sometimes coming closer, sometimes separating
Though they may not match, the fragments connect
Even the sad things we've gone through
Even all the tear-filled memories
Make up your smile's colorful glow
The setting sun shines against the orange sky
Making our unmatching shadows sway
I wanted to tell you something but I couldn't
And with time, our light slowly dies
The afternoon portion of the athletic meet
will begin with the girls' cheering battle.
The red team has a cheerleading routine.
Go, go, win!
Yay!
Kakeru really is acting strange.
There's still the afternoon relay, too.
Is he really okay?
I told my dad to snap some pics.
I'll give you one of Azu, okay?
I don't want it!
Kakeru, I'll give you one of Naho.
Sure.
Let's go, let's go, red team!
Yay!
When Suwa said things were
moving in "the right direction"...
I wonder what he meant by that?
Go! Go!
Go!
Blue team!
Let's turn this around.
Naho—
Hey.
Takamiya, Naruse, come here for a sec.
Sure.
21st
Athletic
Meet
Huh? Where'd Naho and Kakeru go?
Running errands.
What? At a time like this?
I hope we can pull off the relay.
According to Naho's letter,
after Kakeru fell and we lost,
he blamed himself, right?
It'd be weird to say, "Don't worry if you fall,"
before the race even starts, huh?
Even if we said, "Be careful you don't fall,"
it's not like that would change anything.
So what do we do?
I think Kakeru's actually hurt his ankle.
No way!
In the pole-toppling game?
Did Kakeru say that?
No, it's in my letter.
Hagita Saku
The future me noticed it.
But Kakeru said he was fine, so I didn't stop him.
Apparently he wanted to keep it a secret from us,
so he told me not to say anything.
Why didn't you tell us before?!
You were at the first aid station with him!
Well, because...
You okay?
It's heavy for me, too.
Come on.
Sorry.
Let's put it down for a sec.
Yeah.
It's the final round of tug-of-war.
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
This is tough for just two people, huh?
Yeah.
Naho, your mom...
seems nice.
Really?
You really get asked to do errands a lot, don't you?
I can never say no.
Shall we go?
Oh... Yeah.
Ready?
One, two...
I'm fine. Come on.
Dumbass.
If your ankle's hurt, tell us.
Hurt?
How did you...
Sorry we didn't notice it before.
Kakeru, is the athletic meet boring for you?
That's not... Why?
We were talking about how you seem down.
We wondered if something had happened.
Huh? Not really.
We'd all be more than happy to lend an ear.
It's exactly because we're close friends
that you should talk to us!
We don't want to laugh,
not knowing what you're going through.
I'm sorry.
I've been lying to you all.
The truth is...
My mother's gone.
She died.
So the reason you're down is because
your mom couldn't be here today?
I'm not sure if it's okay for me to have fun.
What do you mean?
I always thought that when I'm
with you guys, I want to be laughing.
But...
I feel like I can't do that today.
My mother...
might be watching from somewhere.
If she were still alive,
she would have been here today.
She should never have died.
I'm sure, right now, my mom is very sad.
Should I really
be laughing like I don't have a care in the world?
Well, if your mother is
watching you from somewhere,
isn't it better if you do laugh?
That's right. If you're bummed out,
your mom will worry about you, too.
Worry?
Why?
Look how worried we are about you.
I'd say a mother would be even more worried.
Just look at Suwa.
He's always "Kakeru" this and "Kakeru" that.
And he keeps looking at you and sighing.
Are you a girl?
L-Like hell!
The one with her eyes glued to Kakeru is Naho!
You got that right.
She's been watching Kakeru instead of the games.
She's so worried she doesn't know what to do.
Yeah.
I'm watching.
But I'm sure...
I'm not the only one.
We don't mean to force you
to smile when you're hurting.
But when you're actually having
a good time, it's okay to smile.
You've been looking forward to the relay, right?
Yeah.
Then go get that ankle treated.
I'm fine.
It doesn't hurt that much.
You're not fine at all.
Go get it treated.
We can take care of this.
It's okay.
I'll carry it with you guys.
We're telling you not to overdo it.
If it's heavy, you don't have
to push yourself to carry it.
We're here for you.
It's okay.
If everyone takes hold, it's no longer heavy.
I know it won't be easy
to erase Kakeru's regret and anguish.
But...
I hope we can at least
make it a little lighter for him.
It's sprained?
You won't be running anything with that.
I'll be fine.
The doctor said he should
sit out of the relay, just in case.
Hey! Don't tell them that!
It doesn't even hurt, now that it's taped up.
I can run all I want.
You and your "I'm fine"!
I won't overdo it.
If it worsens, you might have to take
a break from the club for a while.
I'll be fine.
It really doesn't hurt?
Not at all.
I'm sure I won't regret it.
Shall we run, then? Together?
I'm starting to look forward to this!
Right, Hagita?
What's wrong?
It hurts.
It might be a sprain.
You're not hurt.
BLUE
TEAM
RED
It's time for the final event of today's athletic meet.
The final event
is the class relay race.
Senpai!
Hey!
Kakeru!
Do you want to switch?
I mean... Let's switch!
I hope Kakeru
can give a smile from the bottom of his heart.
We've put a lot of effort into training for this day.
So there's nothing to be afraid of.
What matters is that we have fun.
That's all.
Right.
Your turn, Hagita.
Team spirit cheer, if you would.
Why me?
Hey, hey, ho!
Class 6, give 'em hell!
Yeah!
Seriously, why?
Hey, you didn't forget, did you?
That promise.
Promise?
We made it during practice yesterday.
If he passes one person,
I'll give him some of my family's bread.
You two were practicing together again?
Are you two going out?
We are not going out!
Why the hell not?
Say, if you can pass at least two people.
Oh, fine. You got yourself a deal.
It's not "fine"!
That's more like a punishment!
Embarrassed?
Hell no!
Kakeru, why don't you
ask for a reward from Naho, too?
How about a kiss?
If Kakeru crosses the finish line
in first place, you owe him a kiss.
Huh? Uh...
Whoa, hang on!
That's asking too much.
And if Kakeru doesn't take first,
then the kiss is mine.
Why you?
Well, I'm definitely taking first.
Go for the kiss!
You've got no choice now.
All right!
We're over there.
They're kidding...
Right?
RED TEAM
GOOD LUCK!
Azalea Hill Public High School
No matter what happens,
it's not your fault, Kakeru.
No one will blame you.
You're not alone.
Ready!
In the first leg, Class 6 is in the lead.
Wow.
Look at Suwa go! Run!
Takako!
Pass a message on to Kakeru!
"Don't lose!"
You can do it!
Takako!
Don't lose! Don't lose! Don't lose!
Taka-chan!
Pass a message on to Kakeru!
"Don't lose!"
"Promise me!"
Azu!
Don't lose!
Promise me!
Promise me.
Don't lose!
Sorry!
Pass a message on to Kakeru!
"Don't lose!"
"Promise me!"
"We'll always be together!"
Class 6 has slipped to last place!
I figured Hagita would blow it.
Way to go!
You can do it!
Pass a message on to Kakeru!
"Don't lose!"
"Promise me!"
"We'll always be together!"
"Even ten years from now!"
Thank you, everyone.
I couldn't have done this alone.
Go for it, Naho!
Let's change the future!
Kakeru!
I have a message from everyone!
"Don't lose!"
"Promise me!"
"We'll always be together!"
"Even ten years from now!"
"We'll all be...
waiting for you!"
We'll be waiting!
Whoa!
Go, Class 2!
The anchors are running the final lap.
Class 2 is currently in the lead.
Look at him go!
Kakeru!
Class 6 is closing in from behind!
If it's heavy, you don't have
to push yourself to carry it.
We're here for you.
Kakeru!
Go for it!
Class 6 takes first place!
Kakeru!
That was awesome, Kakeru!
You were great, Kakeru!
Thanks!
You were on fire!
Damn, you looked cool, Kakeru!
The winner of the 21st
athletic meet is the red team.
Our team, the red team, won.
The blue team won the competition.
Congratulations!
It's thanks to the others.
It's just like the last time.
Last time?
Your athletic meet in preschool.
No matter how many pictures
your mother took, you never smiled.
She was so worried about you.
I hope Kakeru is okay.
To have his parents divorce when he's that young...
I feel terrible about it.
But in the final race,
you won first place,
and you finally smiled.
When your mother saw that, she was overjoyed.
And I'm sure she feels the same way now.
Yeah.
I hope so.
What's written in the letter
isn't always the only right answer.
Bring a relative of Kakeru's to the athletic meet.
Make sure he has fun and doesn't feel like crying.
Today, I learned that.
Bring a relative of Kakeru's to the athletic meet.
But...
That doesn't mean the letter was wrong.
This...
Oh, that's right.
Can I keep it?
Sure.
Uh, I'm sorry about what
I did at the first aid station.
No, I'm sorry.
No, it wasn't your fault.
It was just...
When I saw Suwa, I sort of felt like it wasn't fair...
I guess I was jealous.
Oh... So you weren't angry with me?
No, I wasn't angry.
Oh, how's your scrape?
Want one?
Does it hurt?
No.
I got my reward.
Thanks.
The future
is changing significantly.
If my love for you could stay as it is
I'm fine with these feelings never reaching you
Not truly tied, yet never fully detached
Deep within my heart, tears are shed
At the end of this thin, delicate branch
Your future is being born
Don't prune back those as-of-yet undiscovered days
I want to protect you so that one day, you'll look back and smile
Deep within my heart, tears are shed
But I cherish them
Because I want to be by your side