I've been looking for you, Akane.
Don't follow me.
Hurry it up, Akane.
I can't make kaiju anymore...
I'm fine with you becoming a kaiju yourself.
Instance Abreaction!
No!
Akane!
Grid...
...Full Power...
...Finish!
Night Light...
Wave Missile!
Thanks.
We couldn't have won without you.
In my dying breath, I will defeat you.
Stay alive until then.
Right.
You're... our Hibiki, right?
Yes, but I'm also the Hyper Agent Gridman now.
Hyper Ag...
Okay, then.
If all of us combine and reunite
Gridman's split consciousness,
the original Yuta will likely awaken.
However...
We can't let Alexis Kerib run amok.
Which means we'll need everyone's power.
Everyone, yeah?
But Utsumi and Rikka aren't here, you know.
That kaiju... Shinjo... is up to you.
And you?
I have something I must do.
All right. Pay your debts.
You're not a kaiju!
You're Shinjo Akane!
A human that makes kaiju is a kaiju themselves.
Well, well...
Um, who were you again?
I'm a friend of Akane's.
A friend, you say?
Wouldn't that be nice?
You're a counterfeit born from Akane's kaiju.
A fabricated human... A replica...
You're a creation that Akane
made for her own benefit.
A creation that thinks they are human.
A creation that believes their god is a friend.
How pitiable that is.
Whether it's pitiful or not is up to us to decide.
As her friend, what do you think? Of this world's—
No...
Of this cramped city's god's downfall.
You're the one who made Akane this way.
She's always been like this.
Nothing has changed. That's what made her a perfect fit.
In that case, we'll change Akane.
At this point?
Try if you wish.
Hibiki!
Long time no see.
Glad to see you're well, Hibiki Yuta.
Sorry, but it's Gridman now!
Let's go, Rikka!
Everyone's waiting!
Shinjo... Akane!
Good luck, Anti.
Utsumi!
Yuta...
No... Now it's Gridman, right?
It's both. Please come with me.
No...
Huh?
I'm not like everyone else...
I'm just a useless normal person.
Calling yourself normal when it's convenient for you?
What happened to the Gridman Alliance?
I wasn't even the one fighting...
And Junk belongs to your family.
Utsumi... Junk needs everyone to be there.
Hey!
Ouch!
Listen here...
What are you to Hibiki anyways?
What am I...
I'm...
Yuta's friend!
And that friend is asking you to come.
No...
No!
Why did it have to be you?
You really are...
a failed creation.
Yeah.
I'm the failed creation you made.
I'm sorry it took so long.
Finally disposed of him.
Well, then... I'll have you prove useful one last time.
Magnificent!
You said you couldn't make kaiju anymore!
And yet, here you had such terrible
emotions inside of you!
Now, then...
There's nothing of value here anymore.
We're all here.
Huh? The heck's this?
You've all got an Accepter now!
Accepters join hearts and make them one.
Let's go! Together!
Yeah!
Good luck.
Access... Flash!
Access...
Flash...
Enter the battle code!
The access code is...
...Gridman.
That access code was...
This is the true Access Flash!
GRIDMAN!
BABY DAN DAN BABY DAN DAN
This is the true form of Gridman!
Shine on!
CRY! Your dreams are clamoring to be heard
That's the big guy from yesterday!
FLY! Spread your wings how you want
Yesterday...
No... Way before then...
Even if your heart is wounded
What a nostalgic look that is, Gridman.
However, I...
Don't be scared
I will defeat you and search for the next Akane.
You're not alone anymore
There won't be a next! It all ends here, Alexis Kerib!
GRIDMAN!
Everyone has a hero within them
Dance onto the stage of the future
Spark... Beam!
Forever a Hyper Agent
GRIDMAN!
BABY DON DON BABY DON DON
Dream on
Neo Superconductive Kick!
GRIDMAN!
BABY DAN DAN BABY DAN DAN
He's immortal?! What the heck?
Gridknight Saber!
What?!
My life is endless and infinite.
Grid... Beam!
But that leaves me with deep emptiness inside.
Which is why the only thing that satisfies my heart
are the emotions of people like Akane.
Is that why you dug your claws into her?!
No, no... She was the one who sought me out.
Akane...
is in there?
There was nothing in this world to begin with.
However, providing kaiju allowed
Akane to build her ideal city.
And destroy it again...
Destroy her ideal city?!
She couldn't control every irregularity,
nor all the lives that were born here.
Which is exactly why she needed kaiju.
I wished to satisfy my heart by allowing it all to repeat.
For such a selfish reason!
But now, Akane has reached the end of her usefulness.
There's nothing for me in this world now.
He's getting away!
Akane!
You, whose life is limited,
cannot hope to defeat me with lives unlimited!
That cannot be called a life!
In that case, I'll deliver your
inevitable end right now, Gridman!
Grid Beam!
Wake up!
Our world is being infiltrated by something unknown
I see...
My power... is not just the power to fight and destroy.
But my true power is...
In these days which feel like they're not real
Grid...
The signal of our SOS is getting faster
Fixer Beam!
Though we know some things have changed
Fixer Beam, you say?!
What is this power?!
The sky above and sights that fill our days remain the same
Fixer Beam is the power to mend this world!
For this world's creator...
What was the pledge that we made on that day?
To rescue the heart of Shinjo Akane!
What did we talk about in the classroom on that day?
At this rate even our promises will fade away
Shinjo.
Shinjo?
Shinjo!
Wake up!
Akane...
Our world is being infiltrated by something unknown
I can't...
I'm...
This is not a drill, nor is it a rehearsal
terrible.
It's okay.
Once the veil concealing a hidden everyday
You're not alone, Akane.
Is torn down vigorously
Nobody's perfect, which is why we rely on others.
The bell sounds on a new fight
If you can learn to rely on someone,
this city will grow and grow.
So for starters
Together let's make a union
I'm here to make things exciting for you
Not just this city...
The world you made will also—
I can't!
A big world's too much for me!
That's why we want you to rely on us...
To believe us...
With these memories that feel made up
That's what our relationship is.
Our... relationship?
It's easy to say "Things were better back then"
You're all my...
My...
Though it may only be in vain
friends?
I hide my scars by turning a blind eye and pretending to understand
This is a world that I created...
Please do not leave personal
belongings on top of lockers
Which is why I can't be here...
"There's no way I'll ever be a hero."
I have to leave by my own free will!
"Someone else is the protagonist."
Don't give up without even realizing
To where... I belong...
The world before us can't be replaced by anything else
I-It can't be!
To think you really mended Akane's heart?!
The same goes for young and old alike
And that's not all!
When you start falling for the rule that every day has to be the same
Humans have the power of potential!
Which I...
Which we believe in!
What kind of power is that?!
That's the time to rise in defiance
This is...
Together let's make a revolution of our own
the power of humanity!
A wish, wish come true
A wish to the night star
Together with you
This is...
the power of a life which is...
A dream UNION!
finite?
Wake up!
Our world is being infiltrated by something unknown
This is not a drill, nor is it a rehearsal!
Once the veil concealing a hidden everyday
Is torn down vigorously
The bell sounds on a new fight
Just like back then
Together let's make a union
I'm here to make things exciting for you
FRAGILE
You're leaving, then?
Here, I... I did lots of things that can't be undone.
I know.
I...
I'm a coward...
I know.
I'm such a wimp...
So unfair... So weak—
I know.
I know all the things that you are.
I'm so... sorry.
I really am...
so sorry.
Open it.
A pass holder...
Telling me to get lost?
Not even close.
So wherever you go, I'll be there with you.
Yeah...
You know, Akane...
Wherever you go, make an impression.
Because you're our god.
Yeah... I will.
So, God...
Would you hear one last request?
Yeah...
I want to be together with you, Akane.
Let's hope that my wish...
never comes true.
Didn't you want to tell Shinjo something?
So much I could die!
But...
I can't get there after all.
It's not that big of a deal.
Though, we won't be in the
same class as a god anymore...
Gods have a world of their own.
Gridman has one too, right? A world like that...
Yeah.
When you get home, tell everyone of my exploits.
Right.
If you come back, dwell in me instead of Yuta.
That way I can avoid another sad farewell.
All right.
The real Yuta will wake after this,
so take care of him for me.
Will Hibiki even remember us when he wakes up?
Don't worry.
You can just become friends with him again.
Even if he doesn't remember,
it's all engraved in his heart.
Just as his feelings for you shone through,
even as I dwelled inside.
F-For me?
As a Hyper Agent, I'm grateful for all your help.
Alexis Kerib is sealed.
Now we must return to the Hyper World.
Our mission is complete.
You all fought so bravely.
Rikka's bold actions saved us time and time again.
Though Utsumi's worthless
predictions always led us astray.
But it was fun.
You're all... not alone.
Shinjo Akane, too.
If not for all of you, our mission may not have succeeded.
Thank you.
I learned again the importance
of having friends I can trust.
And I learned it from you.
We should be thanking you.
Thanks, Gridman.
Well then... Take care.
Goodbye.
What about Anti?!
He's not coming.
Can't pay our debt now.
Tsurumoto, you've got this!
Keep it up!
Seriously?
I wonder why Gridman chose Yuta to dwell in.
I guess because Hibiki was in the seat next to Akane.
That's the only reason?
I'm sure that's not all of it.
I knew it was cold, but now it's actually snowing...
Snow...
Kamesan Park
BDEGH
Who the hell are you?
Me?
I'm the one who saved your life.
You a kaiju?
You too, right?
Yeah...
But I pay my debts.
Just like my family does, then.
Awakening
- Fin -