23! 24! 25! 26!
Narisako, you've got this!
Keep it up!
29! 30! 31...
Oh, you're awake.
Good morning...
You were out cold for half an hour.
Are you feeling all right?
Yeah, can't say I feel sore or anything.
You suddenly collapsed and fell asleep,
so you really startled me.
Want to wash your face?
The washroom is over there.
Who is that girl?
For that matter, who am I?
Hang on, what's going on?
I can't remember anything.
Surely I haven't lost my mem—
Yuta!
Yuta?
Is that my name?
Yuta!
Episode 1: Awakening
The computer?
I am a Hyper Agent, Gridman.
Okay... G-Gridman?
You have to remember your calling.
My calling?
What are you doing?
Oh, that guy was calling to me.
Who?
Gridman.
There's nothing on the screen.
Huh? No, he's right...
Huh?
Only I can see him...
Huh? Am I hallucinating?
Hibiki, you're acting weird.
Gridman told me to remember my calling.
Your calling? As in what you're called?
Probably not...
Huh? What are you talking about?
What is this place?
Home. This is the shop.
Whose?
Mine!
Yeah, but I'm asking whose specifically?
And I'm asking
whose...
who else's?
Yours.
Seriously...
Are you screwing with me?
No, I'm serious.
I really can't...
Can't remember anything.
Are you screwing with me?
I have no memories.
You have amnesia?
Yeah, that's it.
Are you screwing with me?
Hey...
Keep it down.
Mama...
Rikka, why don't you take him to the hospital?
Huh?! Me?
Of course, you. You're classmates, right?
If he has amnesia, he might have hit his head.
You really aren't looking great.
Yeah, I keep seeing and hearing things.
Remember your calling.
Isn't this mist a little thick?
Is it?
Yeah, this is thick, right?
What is it?
Up there! Up there!
That's totally a kaiju! A giant kaiju!
Huh? Where?
Beyond the mist!
There's nothing there.
No, no, I see it! It's right there!
Let's get moving, before the hospital closes.
Hey, if you have no memories,
does that mean you don't remember
anything that happened today?
Yeah.
Oh.
But still, if you're just pretending
to have amnesia, you really suck.
Huh? Did something happen?
How did it go?
I didn't quite understand everything
but they said I should be back to normal soon.
Is that all?
Wait, do you even have your insurance card?
What's that?
You can go home now, right?
Yeah. Thanks for looking after me.
Sure.
Well, see you.
See you.
What?
I don't know where I live.
Huh?! You've forgotten that too?
I don't know where, either.
Wait, let me see your phone.
Oh, sure.
Utsumi would probably know where you live...
Ah... Okay, okay, got it.
Anyhow, I'm taking Hibiki home,
so I need you to tell me his address...
Do you know it?
Got it! Thanks.
idk
You think it'll be okay?
He's such an asshole.
How is Yuta, anyway?
Yes.
5-33-7-402
Tsutsujidai, Nerima, Tokyo
This is pretty far, though.
Is it?
And it's already 7:00!
I'm getting hungry.
Why was I even sleeping at some girl's home?
Not "some girl." Takarada Rikka.
That's my name.
Hibiki, you passed out in front
of our place and wouldn't respond to us.
The hell?
Wh-What's our relationship?
Are we friends?
I hate to burst your bubble,
but this is the most we've ever spoken
since we were put in the same class.
Oh, I see...
That hit the spot.
Whoa, what's his deal?
What's the hold up?
Oh, nothing.
Hibiki
Ah, this is it.
Okay, I'll be off.
A guy called Utsumi said he'll
come pick you up in the morning.
Okay. Thanks for everything.
Bye.
I'm home...
It's pitch black...
After looking around the house,
I discovered that my parents were on a business trip.
They wouldn't be home for three months.
It all seemed so unreal—like living someone else's life.
Gridman... Did I really just...
hallucinate him?
Are you Utsumi?
Looks like you really do have amnesia, huh?
You've even forgotten my face?
Sorry...
Well, whatever. We only really
got to know each other in April.
We'll just pretend we've become friends again.
Thanks. So anyway...
What is it?
What kind of person am I?
Damn, that's a tough question.
Though, even if you ask me...
I'd have to say normal...
Yeah.
You aren't a bad guy.
You wouldn't happen to know
what Gridman is, would you?
No, what's that? Some new trend?
No, I wouldn't say that. You see, yesterday...
Hey, I saw you yesterday!
Huh?
You were with Hibiki, right?
With a boy!
Huh? So what?
Oh, thanks again for yesterday.
Hey! Hey!
I knew it!
Ouch!
You've got a guy!
I do not!
Yuta, your desk is over there.
You've got such slender features.
Really? I wouldn't say that.
Out of order
Hey.
My friends are giving me a real hard time.
Conserve Water
You mean I shouldn't talk to you so much?
Do not block the fire exit
I'm not saying that, but just kinda keep your distance...
Sorry, I don't understand.
Never mind.
Whoops...
Let's eat outside.
Oh, I don't have any lunch.
Ah, you forgot to pack anything?
My brain’s at its limit just dealing with school itself...
You can have this.
Huh?
Hibiki, are you the type
to laugh in the face of adversity?
Um...
Shinjo Akane.
Looks like your amnesia has turned
you into a transfer student, huh?
Yeah, I really can't remember a thing.
This is a special dog.
I have an extra, so you can have it.
Oh, thanks.
Not at all.
Ah, watch out!
Paging Professor Inui.
You have a telephone call on line 1.
Please come to the staff room immediately.
Aww...
I'm so sorry! I'm really sorry!
Are you okay?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Tonkawa, do that outside.
I'll think carefully on my actions. Okay, finished.
But your special dog...
Oh, it's just a little squashed.
Chalk up another one to girls' volleyball.
I can still eat it just fine.
That's the class' ball, though.
That's not what I meant...
Another kaiju? Something bad must have happened, huh?
Something you just can't let go of.
Today was pretty rough, huh?
Yeah. But Shinjo sure was nice.
Nice? There's a difference
between being nice and taking pity.
Let's not split hairs.
No, let's!
Shinjo Akane is one top-tier girl,
with both beauty and brains.
She's like a miracle girl,
someone the whole class adores!
Utsumi, do you adore Shinjo too?
N-No, not me, she's too unapproachable, if you ask me,
and I can't see us ever getting together...
But never mind her!
I'd like to see this Gridman guy too!
Oh, uh...
Hey, where's Tonkawa?
Outside.
She's probably skipping.
She always slacks off whenever Yotsuba isn't around.
I'm home!
Come on...
Don't come in through the front.
I thought you were a customer.
Yeah, well, we do have customers...
Sorry to bother you again.
Ah, the boy from yesterday.
How are you? Still have that amnesia?
Yeah, but I'm all right.
I see.
Rikka! Keep an eye on the shop!
I have to head out for a bit.
Huh?! Well, nobody will come in, anyway.
Hey!
Oh, you heard that?
You're getting nothing but cold tofu for supper.
Huh?!
You guys sure get along well.
How so?
I think we're pretty normal.
Yuta! Which one of these has Gridman?
That computer there.
Wow. Were old computers really this huge?
Look how it's cobbled together.
This really is a pile of junk, huh?
I am a Hyper Agent, Grid—
You told me that yesterday.
Yuta, hurry. There is danger closing in on this world.
What danger?
Who are you talking to?
Huh? You can't see him either, Utsumi?
Nope.
Oh...
Huh? What do you mean?
This isn't good, is it?
Right, but what is that? I don't get it!
Yeah, not good.
The danger is almost upon you.
Oh... Such a nice and emotive form.
Now, to put it in motion...
Instance Abreaction!
What is it?
I don't know, but I have a feeling there's trouble.
Yeah, I've thought you were troubled all day.
I don't mean that!
I hear a kaiju.
Maybe we should take you to the hospital again.
Safety First
As we reported earlier, at this moment...
Great, a fire?
At around 18:00 this evening,
For real?
a kaiju-like moving object...
Looking at the area from above...
Please evacuate away from—
The train has come to an unexpected stop.
We apologize for the inconvenience
to our passengers at this time—
There's something over there.
I'm gonna go see!
Utsumi!
What is that?
It really is a kaiju!
Is that the kaiju you mentioned, Hibiki?
I'm not sure.
We really can't see from here, anyway.
We need to get to the main road.
Huh? No way, it's too dangerous!
Whoa, the heat!
That was the school.
...are currently assessing the damage to Tokyo.
We are receiving reports that
residences are being destroyed...
Can you confirm what you're seeing there?
I'm standing behind a building, so I can't be sure...
Yuta... Yuta!
Gridman is calling me.
Hibiki!
Yuta!
Gridman! You called me, right?
That's right. You and I must awaken.
Awaken? Does that mean...
I'll explain later!
Huh? But I feel like it's pretty important—
Yuta!
Whoa, what's happening?!
Yuta's been swallowed by Junk.
Old computers are terrifying...
Looks like I can finally see something.
I see it, too.
No way! A giant?!
Is that the Gridman that Yuta was talking about?
We still can't see very well from here!
I have to stop... this kaiju...
Yuta's voice is coming from Junk!
Yuta has become Gridman and is fighting...
to defend the city from that kaiju!
Ah, Junk!
Old computers sure are something!
Y-You don't suppose that Junk
and Gridman are linked, do you?
What? Are you saying that Hibiki is in trouble?
Ah, if only this were the Ultra Series!
The kaiju would have some kind of weakness!
Huh? What do you mean?
Damn! My body is so sluggish!
The neck... Its neck is weaker and coming apart!
If he aims for that...
Then we have to tell Hibiki right away!
But how?
The school's on fire! The school!
You're kidding!
He can't hear what we're saying.
Isn't there any way to contact him?
With this computer?
I'll give it a shot.
Utsumi, I'll type what you say
and try to get through to Hibiki.
She's fast...
I hear you.
Wake up!
I hear you!
Our world is being infiltrated by something unknown
Both Rikka and Utsumi's...
words!
In these days which feel like they're not real
The signal of our SOS is getting faster
Though we know some things have changed
The sky above and sights that fill our days remain the same
What was the pledge that we made on that day?
What did we talk about in the classroom on that day?
At this rate even our promises will fade away
Wake up!
Our world is being infiltrated by something unknown
Amazing...
Go, Gridman!
This is not a drill, nor is it a rehearsal
Grid...
Once the veil concealing a hidden everyday
Beam!
Is torn down vigorously
The bell sounds on a new fight
So for starters
Together let's make a union
I'm here to make things exciting for you
He did it! Awesome!
Oh, Yuta! Thank goodness!
I'm...
I'm back.
That was awesome, Yuta!
You fought a kaiju and won!
No, it wasn't just me.
Yuta!
Yuta, you must realize your calling.
Huh? I thought we just did.
That was just the beginning.
Hey! The three of us and Gridman beat that thing!
Y-Yeah.
You know what?
We definitely need a name for ourselves!
Something like "The Gridman Alliance"!
Hey, hold on!
Everything is crumbling
I hate to say this, but I'm done for today...
The scenes we're staring at
Huh?
And with it the blueness of the sky
My head's in a jumble right now.
I don't understand what Gridman is.
In this season that makes you sweat
I'm worried about my friends too.
This sense of emptiness
I'm sorry, but...
Nobody knows the reason for
Should we go?
Even if you can't remember, I'm sure our meeting was
Yeah.
Rikka!
Ah, are you all okay?
Youthful
Meant to be connected to something, somewhere
Thank goodness. Rikka, answer your phone!
Huh?
Connected
Don't "Huh?" me. I was worried!
Today, tomorrow
Well, let's get going.
Yeah.
And forevermore
I'll be with you
And now, some reactions from
the people at the scene in Tokyo.
Fires break out in residential areas!
It doesn't matter what you choose; to stay or not,
Giant Kaiju Spotted
I'll still run
If I were to just get my feet to move
I'll be the light
It would seem that we had some company show up.
Was a moment in time that goes by instantly
Ever this beautiful
Ever this beloved
May it fill the hole inside your heart
What gives? What's happened here?
The school burned down yesterday, right?
What are you doing?
Well, look.
Oh... No way...
The school's back to normal.
Now that's strange, isn't it?
Yeah...