Resound, Towards Tomorrow
Minato...
Do your best!
Summer came to an end,
and the school festival was drawing near.
The world around me seemed so monochrome
I got scared when I saw a new color budding in my heart
Hid it away, far from people's sight
Knew I failed to become like the others, the right dye
Just dream now!
Don't be afraid of what you love
Hold your head high, let yourself shine
Just look around, the world's so vast
You should take every chance
Be yourself!
Selfishness is what makes us whole
Don't look back, waver not, aim for your dreams
Now's when you end negative thoughts
Time to leave them behind
You should just be proud of your own color
It's yours, no one else's
Your feelings will now bloom like flowers
And color the world
No need to get all shy, I'm here with you
Don't avert your gaze
You're so special now, so stay who you are!
Do what you want and let nothing ever stop you
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
From Spring To Autumn...
Suidobashi Animation Academy
Recital
For dreams everything's fair play
From Spring To Autumn...
Recital
Suidobashi Animation Academy
From Spring To Autumn...
Recital
Suidobashi Animation Academy
From Spring To Autumn...
Recital
Suidobashi Animation Academy
From Spring To Autumn...
Recital
Suidobashi Animation Academy
From Spring To Autumn...
Recital
Suidobashi Animation Academy
From Spring To Autumn...
Recital
Suidobashi Animation Academy
From Spring To Autumn...
Recital
Now, don't let others dictate your own life
Charybdis and Scylla
Recital
Listen to your heart instead
Charybdis and Scylla
Recital
I can see that you're really trying your best
So let's sing of our dreams
I will protect this town!
The Lake of Tomorrow
Recital
I'm glad you're back to normal.
Well, there's no point sulking forever.
What are you doing for the festival?
A recital called "The Lake of Tomorrow".
Maybe you'll be doing it next year too.
Hmm...
What's your role?
The Captain.
It's the main role.
That's awesome!
Th-Thanks.
The Captain, huh?
The Captain must be happy too.
Huh?
To be played by you.
Y-You think so?
I also want to...
I want to breathe life into characters.
I really do.
Yeah.
Let's breathe life into characters together!
O-Okay.
But...
We might not be able to meet up as much.
Huh?
I'm thinking about spending more time practicing.
You okay with that?
Being together less, I mean.
I-It's fine!
I need to improve as well.
I'll come and watch you during the festival.
Everyone, take your instruments!
All right, let's do it!
Wait! But what if Mom finds out about it?
Then we just need to not get caught!
That's enough!
Suyama, you definitely put enough feeling into it.
Resound, Towards Tomorrow
Recital
Thank you.
It's just that...
I think you put a bit too much energy into it.
It was too enthusiastic.
Try paying attention to how much emotion
the others put into their roles.
Yes, sir.
I still have a ways to go, I guess.
Once more, from the top!
Yessir!
We'll be practicing here starting today.
Recital
The Lake of Tomorrow
It's a bit smaller than your actual stage,
Recital
The Lake of Tomorrow
but think of it as though it were
the actual performance.
The Lake of Tomorrow
Recital
Yessir!
L-Let's take to the s-skies!
The Lake of Tomorrow
Recital
Follow my lead!
The Lake of Tomorrow
Recital
Oomori.
The Lake of Tomorrow
Recital
Relax.
The Lake of Tomorrow
Recital
I'm sorry.
You okay with that?
Being together less, I mean.
I-It's fine!
It's fine. It's fine.
Everyone, take your instruments!
All right, let's do it!
Wait! But what if Mom finds out about it?
Then we just need to not get caught!
How was it?
Everyone, take your instruments!
Resound, Towards Tomorrow
All right, let's do it!
It's the famous Kanna River.
To the new tenant.
Wait!
So you're living in my old room?
Yeah.
I wasn't expecting to meet the new tenant!
Maybe I should go there again.
Good afternoon.
Minato!
It's been a while.
Say...
Are you the Knight, perchance?
Bring the Captain immediately!
Captain! Captain!
Was Chikako here today?
About that...
No, she wasn't.
She's not feeling well today,
so she's skipping practice.
I... see.
She seemed down lately.
We're a bit worried about her.
Do you know anything, Minato?
No, not really.
Chikako.
Huh?
You can have this, if you like.
Honey Lemon Drink
It'll warm you up.
Minato...
I heard from Ryouta that you skipped practice.
So I thought that you might be here.
Thanks.
To think I'd be comforted here again...
What's wrong with that?
Huh?
You comforted me here as well.
But you're constantly moving forward.
Meanwhile, I'm stuck in place.
I still get stage fright,
even after everything.
Even if I become a voice actor,
I won't be able to act well
if I stay weak like this.
I can picture my future self.
Surrounded by applause, she says
"I'm glad I kept chasing my dreams".
No one ever pays attention to me anymore...
"No one ever pays attention to me anymore..."
I don't think it's a problem
that you get worried about things.
It helps you understand a lot of different characters,
and it'll be fine anyway.
When you stand on the stage,
it's like you're a completely different person.
You seem to become the character you're playing.
I want to be able to do that as well.
Thank you.
I'll make my dreams come true!
I'll become a voice actor!
I can picture my future self.
Surrounded by applause, she says
"I'm glad I kept chasing my dreams".
Speaking of that, who wrote that poem?
It's a secret!
Was it you?
Not telling!
I see. Okay.
And so, the day of the festival came.
NOTICE
Trains are currently experiencing disruptions due to issues with signals.
Are you serious?
Guess I don't have a choice.
Now we will proceed to
the performance of the second year students.
The Lake of Tomorrow
Recital
I'll come to watch you during the festival.
The Lake of Tomorrow
Recital
What a familiar-looking town...
The Lake of Tomorrow
Recital
Are you the Knight, perchance?
The Lake of Tomorrow
Recital
Bring the Captain immediately!
The Lake of Tomorrow
Recital
Captain! Captain!
The Lake of Tomorrow
Recital
Have we, the Warriors of the Lake,
been summoned?
The Knight has arrived!
What? I've grown tired of waiting!
The Lake of Tomorrow
Recital
At last, my life-long dream shall finally be granted!
The Lake of Tomorrow
Recital
Try as you might, nothing will change!
You are far too weak!
Even still, I will continue to challenge you!
Again, again, and again! I will not give up!
I shall become the greatest warrior in the land!
Amazing.
Let's perform now, then.
You're being unreasonable again.
You really never change!
But now he's the best musician in this town!
Must be nice, having that talent.
Resound, Towards Tomorrow
I want to become a good musician as well.
I'm having the most fun I've ever had right now.
Resound, Towards Tomorrow
I'm so glad I got to play this role.
Two Years Later
Great! Now I'm a voice actor too!
Well, I guess it's too early to say that.
How pretty.
I'm Suyama Minato.
It's my first time working on an anime,
but I'll do my best!
Excuse me!
I'm Oomori Chikako.
I'm sorry for calling you here on such short notice.
Thank you for giving me this chance.
I'm a stand-in.
Glad to work with you.
Me too.
Okay, let's try it.
Yessir!
In that instant,
from the bottom of my heart, I felt...
so glad that I kept chasing my dreams.
I won't ever lose
I have dreams to fight for
Try putting your heart into song
Ah, make the most of your life
Do you want to cry?
Don't tell me you're running away?
Nothing will stop me from trying my best
Don't give up!
As I try my best
Aiming to make my dreams come true
You're with me, here to support me and help
Looking at the sky so dull and dark
Tears flowing as it weighs me down
It's always those times when I cry
I remember our song
Resonating deep in my heart
Yay!
I won't ever lose
I have dreams to fight for
Try putting your heart into song
Ah, make the most of your life
Just sing now!
Just hold your head high, and get ready to fight
Don't fret, you have friends on your side
Ah, I won't stop till I get
A happy end
Yes! Yes! Yes!