We can't monitor them?
Not at all. We lost the signals of the
entire 1st Unit about five minutes ago.
They're probably in an area
that causes radio interference.
Team B has reached their core acquisition quota.
Split the unit and dispatch scouts.
Roger!
What's wrong?!
Team B's device is malfunctioning!
Same goes for the devices at
the locations of Teams C, D, and E!
This is...
It's the same phenomenon as with the 1st Unit!
They're preventing us from moving?!
A snake in one's bosom... this is just that.
Director.
With all teams combined,
we'll reach our core acquisition quota.
The operation...
I understand.
I authorize you to destroy all of the devices.
At the same time...
Locate Dr. Ooguruma as soon as possible.
Thank you, Director.
This is the only decision a director can make.
I hope everyone is safe,
along with Captain Amamiya.
Yes sir.
I still have uses for the 1st Unit, after all...
Sakuya!
No way...
It's my fault.
Rindou was killed?
Soma!
We don't know that for sure just yet!
Let's go, guys!
That's right.
We don't know for sure yet.
Attacking senselessly will only get you killed!
Move. You're in my way.
Soma!
There's no way. It can't be!
Don't be so reckless, Sakuya!
Stop! That won't work!
We can't win like this!
This is...
Rindou...
Rindou!
No!
What should we do?
Mister!
That girl...
Are you all okay?
I knew it was you!
What about the others?
Everyone got out. We're fine for now.
What can we do?
We'll help too.
Please save everyone... Please!
If they lose their way, show them the path...
He's right...
If I waver here, then he'll be laughing at me.
You guys, get my comrades to regroup!
Soma!
Pita can't be destroyed by one man. Help me!
Well, you'd better have a plan!
Are you okay?!
You're the girl from back then...
This way.
We meet again!
You're all...
Let's fight together this time.
We're going to fight alongside Utsugi.
No... It can't be true...
Rindou...
Miss Sakuya, do you remember this girl?
You're the one from back then...
Rindou brought them all here.
So that those rejected by Fenrir could survive.
Rindou did?!
Miss Sakuya... Everyone...
What we must do now
is remember Rindou's wishes,
and obey the orders he gave us.
But how do we destroy that thing?
We'll be fine.
We're strong!
Believe in yourself.
Believe in your friends!
Destroy it!
Rindou's wishes...
Miss Sakuya!
The guiding device, right?
Leave 'em to me.
Then Miss Sakuya and I will distract the Vajra.
What about me and Lenka?
We'll take on Pita!
Let's do it!
Every single Vajra is headed in the same direction.
The device must be...
That's right. We heard something
fall into the lake a few nights ago.
We rushed to check if it was an Aragami,
but nothing was there.
That confirms it.
That's where the sound came from!
Um...
Did Rindou...
He had an errand to run.
But you have us here with you.
Rindou, you tried your best to protect them...
But now it's my turn to!
Lenka!
Alisa!
That's...
Lenka!
Alisa!
Soma!
I destroyed it, as you wished.
Lenka!
Miss Sakuya!
Kouta!
Are you okay, Alisa?
Thank you.
What about the Vajra?
We killed those that had gotten in.
The civilians with us are heading to the shelter.
There's one thing left.
Pita!
That was a direct hit, and yet...
Just shut up and keep firing!
a feint?!
That's...
Soma, look at his right wing!
There's a crack in it!
Aim for that spot!
Kouta, let's do it!
Right!
Here we go!
Roger that!
The sparks are being absorbed!
Looks like you guys
really saved my skin there.
Thanks.
You can thank Kouta!
Oh?
Kouta came up with the idea for that round
and helped with its development.
Leave the backup to me, Soma, sir!
Just Soma will do.
I owe you one, Kouta!
Oh no you don't!
It broke!
We did it!
Utsugi!
Lenka...
It's too strong!
Is this even doable?
It's...
Lenka!
Unchecked predation will cause further strain.
Are those bruises...
Oracle cell erosion?
You...
Bastard!
Do you know why we're laughing?
Aren't you short one?
Do you know what they call us?
Lenka!
In order to survive...
In order to protect...
Go!
We devour even gods...
Get Pita!
We are...
Destroy it!
God Eaters!
We won?
Lenka...
Lenka?
We are hope.
Lenka... No way...
Is that Soma? He's really grown.
Welcome to the Far East Branch, Dr. Sakaki.
First of all, let me return this to you.
That foundation that you created...
I used it as a prototype to develop
an even stronger armored wall.
My present status wouldn't
have been attained without it.
How do you like the feel of that seat,
Far East Branch Director?
This is just ornamentation, Dr. Sakaki.
However... I've acquired the power to save mankind.
"Aegis"? A plan for a massive shelter?
However, Aragami will evolve.
If you think this will save mankind...
That is merely a cover. Look at the next file.
This is...
As instructed, I disposed of Amamiya Rindou.
Thank you.
I threw away my entire career.
I hope I can get aboard, as you promised.
The Aegis Project...
Its true purpose is to act as
the launching pad for that rocket?
Carefully selected humans will go into space
to wait out the Devouring Apocalypse
as part of this Ark Project.
Everything will end
and man will return to a barren
land to start a new civilization.
It sounds quite preposterous...
And? When is this Devouring
Apocalypse expected to occur?
"Expected"?
We will make it happen
by our own hand!
But you can only save around a thousand people?
Do you know what is painted there?
Two people being tossed about
in a storm, and a single plank.
The Plank of Carneades?
If both grabbed the plank, they would sink.
Then...
In order to save the human species,
you will save a small handful.
Is that it?
Will you stop me?
Or will you turn and run like you did that time?
I am merely an observer.
I don't intend to interfere
with this crucial decision.
However, I will search for my
own way to save mankind.
Have you found the answer since that day?
If they continue to evolve like this,
Aragami will eventually acquire intellect.
Are you saying that we'll be able
to communicate with Aragami?
Yes, and beyond that, they may even
be able to co-exist with mankind.
You're too sentimental, just like always.
Aragami are monsters, that's all.
Enemies that must be destroyed.
Johannes, in my eyes, you're a pessimist.
Will humans become God?
Or will God become human?
The race begins.
Due to the success of Operation Meteorite,
we were able to amass the cores necessary
to complete the Aegis Project.
On behalf of all mankind, I thank you.
Your brave efforts as God Eaters have saved us all.
However...
As you fought hard, there was one
who schemed to doom this project,
In this lonely dream
and as a result of his actions, we lost a
valuable comrade, which fills me with regret.
This will never happen again.
my tears quietly mix into the gentle rain
The perpetrator,
Ooguruma Daigo, will be found
and brought to justice!
In the spiraling currents tainted by mud
This is Soma.
No contact with the special duty target.
there's a ray of light that pierces through its darkness
Did I just imagine it?
that I want to embrace forevermore
If you'll stay strong until the end
I'll rest my fate in your hands
It's unusual for her to be late.
Your life ties all of us together
Late on the day of the
new captain's installation,
Alisa?
I'm sorry!
like a flower that grows in this polluted wasteland
Were you in the toilet?
Don't ask such questions.
Captain, would you like to say a few words first?
I only give three orders.
Don't die.
If your life is threatened, run.
And hide.
And wait for the day
when you can destroy them!