It all began when some country launched
a genetically engineered bioweapon.
This was swiftly responded to by the launch
of several retaliatory thermonuclear warheads.
The war dragged on for years,
claiming countless lives from all over the globe.
The few remaining survivors have
little interest in things like stars.
Basically, what I'm trying to tell you is...
The society you remember is a thing of the past.
I have attempted to query
the support center's databases,
but I have been unable to connect.
Not surprising.
On a different note, Mr. Customer,
I think perhaps you may require this tool soon.
Nope.
Is that so?
I'm asking nicely now, stop sticking
your nose in every little thing.
Order acknowledged.
By the way, Mr. Customer,
will you be requiring the
assistance of this tool soon?
Sure, help me out and
clamp your own mouth shut.
Chapter 2
Repairing the Projector
I don't even know why I'm doing this.
What I do know is that,
now that the sun has set,
venturing out is dangerous.
Also, this primitive contraption
is a lot hardier than it looks.
Mr. Customer, how long do you estimate it will take
for your repairs on Miss Jena to be complete?
Hell if I know. Ain't got a clue.
Will it be fixed in time for
tomorrow's 11:00 am projection?
I highly doubt it.
If that is the case, may I put out a notice that
tomorrow's projections will be postponed?
Do whatever you want.
Acknowledged. I will register
this as a critical directive.
This light bulb's filament is burned out.
Is there a spare—
Mr. Customer.
I apologize for the inconvenience,
but it is almost midnight.
As per protocol,
I will be switching into sleep mode.
Huh?
Reboot from sleep mode is scheduled for 9:00 am.
Remaining operation time
after reboot will be 75 hours.
Well then, good night.
Hey, wait...
God damn it.
Mr. Customer.
Good morning, Mr. Customer.
Were you the one calling me?
Yes, sir.
I was dreaming.
Oh, how wonderful! Was it pleasant?
Not at all...
As I am a robot, I am incapable of dreaming.
But how shall I put it?
I have very much longed to experience it!
Most dreams are not worth longing after.
Is that so?
Wait a sec.
So you're saying you're only operational
for one week out of the entire year?
Yes.
For the past 30 years,
the quantity of electricity delivered to
this department store has declined sharply.
Per protocol, I have activated energy-saving mode.
Two days ago at 9:00 am, I became operational
for the first time in 8,601 hours.
Just as I happened to be passing through.
Talk about bad timing...
Five days from now, at midnight,
I will return to recharging hibernation mode.
I see.
To think, the emergency power's
still running after all that's happened...
By the way, Mr. Customer, what do you
intend to do with that rainwater?
Drink it.
Unlike you, I'll die if I don't drink water.
If you would like, I could prepare a beverage for you.
A beverage?
Yes.
To tell you the truth,
brewing tea is one of my specialties.
Or perhaps you'd prefer
a freshly ground coffee?
Coffee, huh...
How about alcohol, then?
I'm talking bottled distilled
liquor with unbroken seals.
It's actually very important to me.
Certainly, we have those in stock.
Really?! Where?!
Our department store has several vendors
located on B1 that sell high-grade liquor...
Yeah, yeah, I get the idea.
Of course.
In that case, Mr. Customer, may I inquire
about Miss Jena and her current state of repairs?
No change from last night.
Repairs are still underway.
I see...
In that case, I will go and announce
the cancellation of today's projection.
Hey, do you have spare light bulbs
stored away somewhere?
Recently, two of the latest 905 series
have been assigned to the
help desk at the main entrance.
Being FT models, they both have a much
more adult appearance compared to myself.
Their faceplates are quite detailed,
and they even feature the capability to shed tears.
Tears, huh. Try turning it on.
Understood.
This one's okay...
So what, you can't shed tears?
Correct.
Tear-generation functionality
was first introduced in the
predecessor models, the 9000 series.
I see. Good for them.
Switch on.
Understood.
This one's busted.
Guess I have two usable ones...
By the way, may I remove this cable now?
This is a shameful emergency measure
that I should not be showing to customers...
Wait a bit longer. I wanna try the motors.
Understood.
By the way, Mr. Customer.
What is it now?
How does shedding tears feel?
Can't really say.
When I'm crying,
I'm usually not thinking very clearly.
Is that so?
I do not know how to put this,
but I would very much like to be able to shed tears.
As I am an Economy Edition model,
I lack that functionality.
Let's just say you're not really
missing out on anything.
Is that so?
Yeah, no doubt about it.
All righty.
Move the latitude axis upwards, bit by bit.
Yes, sir.
For your safety, please evacuate from the radius of revolution.
Mr. Customer, might you have an estimated
time of completion for the repairs of Miss Jena?
Who knows?
Do you think it will be in time
for tomorrow's 11:00 am projection?
Dunno. Feel free to pray to God.
Which god should I pray to, then?
What'd you say?
For instance, there are the ancient Greek gods:
Zeus, Athena, Apollo, Hermes,
Artemis, Demeter, Poseidon, Hades...
You sure know a lot.
Just pick your favorite or whatever.
Understood. In that case, I shall pray to Dionysus.
Who the hell is that?
The god of wine and fertility,
also known by his Roman name, Bacchus.
I felt that this god would surely
be most to your liking, Mr. Customer.
Well, you're not too far off...
Pray to your god, not mine.
My god?
The god of robots.
The information you have requested
does not match any entry in my database.
I see.
However, I have found something related.
This is from a meeting we had
about the mythological heavens,
which we featured as a special presentation.
I have the file saved as a hologram.
Is there a heaven for robots?
Hm?
Of course there is! There has to be!
Right, manager?
Ah, yes, that's right.
What is that place like?
Well...
It's free of malfunctions and
batteries never decay! Right?
Huh? Um, yeah, and no software bugs
or any need to replace parts, I heard.
You'll be granted all your other wishes too!
Is that so?
Yes, yes.
I see.
The god you're looking for is the one
in that robot heaven. Keep that in mind.
Understood. Critical data registered.
I am very pleased to have learned about this god.
In fact, I have a wish I would like
to ask the God of Robots to grant.
A wish?
What could you possibly want?
Well, it is about Heaven...
What is it?
Mr. Customer.
I apologize for the inconvenience,
but it is almost midnight.
As per protocol,
I will be switching into sleep mode.
It's gotten that late already?
Reboot from sleep mode is scheduled for 9:00 am.
Remaining operation time
after reboot will be 60 hours.
Well then, good night.
Why don't you come to the planetarium?
The beautiful twinkling of eternity
that will never fade, no matter what.
Projections are temporarily canceled.
All the stars in the sky await...
Hey, I'm done.
Mr. Customer, are you saying that you
have completed your repairs on Miss Jena?
Yeah, that's right.
I've done all I can.
Click!
"The Story of Tanabata and the Milky Way"
~Orihime and Hikiboshi~
When I turn my gaze to the heavens above
"The Story of Tanabata and the Milky Way"
~Orihime and Hikiboshi~
I see a downpour of glimmering lights
Twinkling brilliantly, such wonderful starlight
If I gently close my eyes like so
That glitter will remain in my heart
"The Story of Tanabata and the Milky Way"
~Orihime and Hikiboshi~
And on such rainy days, for example
Screening
When patches of sky peek through the clouds
I collect my wishes for tomorrow
And put my faith in the guiding light
That's always right here
That I always chase
With clear eyes born from innocent times
And so...
Image Archives
Viewing through a telescope
Dazzling
History of the Galaxy
For Families
Waxing and waning of the moon
Observation Diary
Let s go and see!!
A journey around the solar system
A
E
Oh, stars twinkling for eternity!
Oh, prayers of hope!
Carry these feelings of mine to the ends of the galaxy!
Twinkling twinkling twinkling twinkling star
Shining brightly in the sky
We humbly await your return.
What wonderful twinkling starlight