May 5th 11:40
Musashi, Time until Uraga Channel Arrival: 20 Min.
Ships two, three, and four are dead in the water.
Ship one has been reduced to a speed of six knots.
At this rate, the Musashi will enter
the Uraga Channel in 20 minutes!
I repeat: all citizens, please evacuate
to the designated ships immediately.
Principal. We have a call from the Harekaze.
This is Captain Misaki of the Harekaze.
Please give us permission to execute
our plan against the Musashi!
All of my classmates are in agreement.
Please let us carry it out.
I, Munetani Mayuki,
principal of Yokosuka Girls' Marine High School,
authorize you to take action against the Musashi.
However, you may only attack once.
Ground forces are also preparing
to neutralize the Musashi.
There is no need to attack continuously.
If you can buy us five minutes—
no, three minutes, that should be plenty.
Yes, ma'am.
Wait, Principal Munetani!
The Musashi has already disabled
three Blue Mermaid ships.
We can't send out the Harekaze alone!
The Musashi will enter
the Uraga Channel in 20 minutes.
Sis—I mean, Director Munetani.
We may not be able to stop the Musashi.
However, we will be able to buy you
some time by slowing it down.
Besides, Moka-chan—I mean, the captain
of the Musashi is besieged on the bridge.
You can communicate with the Musashi's captain?
We can't get through by radio,
but we can use flashing light signals.
Captain Misaki, I acknowledge your plan
to approach the Musashi and take action against it.
We're counting on you.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's go, Captain.
We're stronger when we're
the hunters instead of the prey!
That's right!
Aye, aye.
Captain, your orders.
30 degrees, steady as she goes!
Full speed ahead!
3,000m from the Musashi.
The Harekaze is approaching!
The Harekaze?
I signaled them not to get close...
Mike-chan...
Tama-chan, aim for the Musashi's main gun turret.
Aye.
Let's stop the Musashi, no matter what.
Aye...
Mei-chan, when we line up alongside
the Musashi, launch all our torpedoes.
The full spread I've always dreamed of... For real?!
We'll probably only get one chance to fire.
I want us to do everything we can to stop them.
Let's aim at their stern.
Understood. I swear I'll hit the mark.
Ricchan, Kayo-chan, let's go!
Aye aye, ma'am!
Roger!
Mike-chan... Don't tell me...
Target is the Musashi's stern. Commence fire!
Our target is the Musashi's stern!
Let's have every torpedo hit!
Prepare to fire!
Fire!
All right!
No good. We're not even making a dent.
All right! 100% accuracy!
The Musashi is slowing down!
Here they come!
All hands, brace for impact!
The Musashi has fired!
Are you all right?
Yes, thank you.
Captain.
The Harekaze...
Our smoke generator in the stern is disabled!
Torpedo launchers are damaged!
Fire in storage room five!
Extinguishing now!
Th-They did so much damage with just one attack.
They really are powerful.
No good. It's broken.
The radio's offline!
The radio too?
Captain. We bought them five minutes.
Rin-chan, get us away from the Musashi.
Leave it to me!
The Musashi fired!
Here they come!
Mike-chan!
Hoists for turret one damaged!
Fire in the mess hall! Going in now to extinguish it!
Is this what it means to face the Musashi?
Its guns are blocking our path of retreat!
There's nowhere to run!
Captain?
What's wrong?
I'm going to stop the bombardment.
That's crazy!
Captain!
If I don't, they'll sink the Harekaze!
Please calm down, Captain.
I'm sorry.
Chief Engineer! Water! Water!
What?
I'm on my way!
Captain, our portside engine room is flooding!
Get all the pumps in here!
Don't let the boilers go out!
Even the engine room...
Captain, should we have all hands
prepare for evacuation?
For real? We're going to run away?
If a hydra loses all its heads,
it can't grow any more!
I'm sorry! If only I were better at maneuvering...
Aye...
Everyone...
All hands! Prepare to evac—
What's this?
Rin-chan, rudder hard to starboard!
Rudder hard to starboard!
Ships in sight beyond our stern!
Is it the Blue Mermaids?
I'll go look!
Identification signals confirmed!
It's the Hiei,
the Maikaze,
the Hamakaze,
the Admiral Spee,
and finally, the Tenjin!
The Tenjin?
They're from our school!
Episode 12
A Troublesome Last Battle!
Instructor Furushou!
I'm glad we made it in time,
but I'm sorry we weren't here sooner.
Noma-san, let them know we can't use our radio!
Coco! Girls!
You came back for us!
The time has come for us to repay our debt!
Captain, what should we do?
With all the others here, we can keep fighting!
I have no objections.
Change of plan! We're going to board the Musashi!
All right!
Aye!
I'll do my best!
Yes!
Let's do this!
Let's do it!
The Spee is requesting our strategy!
We're going to board the Musashi.
Please support the Harekaze!
"Please... give... us... support."
They're requesting support, Captain.
Roger that. Leave it to us.
We're going to support the Harekaze
and their plan to board the Musashi.
The Tenjin and the Spee will attack
the Musashi's starboard side,
and the Hiei, the Maikaze, and the Hamakaze will
attack from the port side to provide covering fire.
All ships, prepare to attack.
Your target is the Musashi!
A wind is blowing.
The wind of hope.
All ships, open fire!
Do not falter!
Remind all of the ships not to strike
anywhere near the Musashi's bridge.
Understood.
And the Harekaze?
We need to get in there somehow.
Captain.
Could this be of any use?
A rocket?
The Akashi's crew thought it might
come in handy, so they installed it.
Tama-chan! Mei-chan!
Aye?
All right, got it!
Aye!
Rin-chan!
Yes, ma'am?!
Please get us in front of the Musashi.
B-Before the bow?!
Shiretoko-san.
Full speed, to the front of the Musashi!
S-Steady as she goes!
They're going to cut in front of the Musashi?
Don't let them hit the Harekaze.
Draw the Musashi's fire over here!
Fire!
Go, Harekaze.
Everything begins here in this world of silent ruin
Tama, there's no time, so let's hurry.
Aye.
Just when the twilight settles in to end it all
A single ray of light; a voice that resides within
Will break themselves free and clear away the darkness
The rocket is ready to go anytime!
Full speed ahead! Rudder hard to starboard!
Get our stern facing the Musashi!
We can see ourselves quickly waste away
Full speed ahead! Rudder hard to starboard!
If you have an insecure step
and a heart broken by a thousand waves
Tama-chan, prepare to fire!
Fire like there's no tama-rrow!
You won't even save yourself
Let our fearless spirits cry on forever
With this shot, we'll seize our chance of victory!
May we leave marks they'll never forget
Let's pray that these faint traces will not fade away
So that our world can see another tomorrow
Let our fearless spirits stay ever strong
As the past collides with our future
Captain! Now!
Aye!
Rin-chan, rudder hard to starboard!
In this time of destiny
To the Musashi's starboard side!
Rudder hard to starboard!
Collect the light around you and make a vow
Th-The wheel won't turn!
What?
Captain, the rudder's been hit! We've lost steering!
to step into the brilliant glory of tomorrow
We have our destinies and futures alike
We have a parachute, right?
Y-Yeah!
Hime-chan, Momo-chan, prepare the parachute!
Clasped tightly in our hands
The parachute's tied on, but now what?
Even though I'm still wandering alone
Throw it to rear starboard!
Within the memories of my unchangeable past
Hurry!
Aye aye!
Whenever I close my eyes I can see
That the path I must walk leads right to you
Let's shout one last time as we sail into the grief-stricken sea
We turned!
We did it! We're facing the enemy!
Toward a world cleansed by our tears
I don't care what happens
to th' tin can! Don't you stop!
Amongst the chaos we'll search far for a glint of hope
I can see the Musashi!
Cut the parachute loose!
A fleeting flash that'll remind us who we are
We're going to crash into it!
Let's shout one last time as we part ways and meet anew
Brace for impact!
As the past collides with our future
In this time of destiny
We did it! The attack was a success!
Rescue team, prepare to board!
We're ready.
Here we go! Storm the ship!
Captain.
Go ahead and join the boarding party.
I-I'll stay here.
I'm the captain, after all.
Get out there, Misaki-san.
I know how you feel.
I can tell you want to go.
It's written all over your face.
Shiro-chan...
Thank you!
Way to go, buddy! You're so cool, Shiro-chan!
I don't know about the "buddy" part...
Moka-chan!
Moka-chan...
Mike-chan!
I'm so glad to finally see you again, Mike-chan.
Moka... chan...
Moka-chan...
Moka-chan.
Moka-chan!
You're way too reckless, Mike-chan.
But...
What'll I do with you?
I'm sorry.
But thank you.
The operation is over.
All ships, return to Yokosuka Harbor!
Looks like you missed your chance
to create history, Mom.
That's all right.
My students did it in my stead.
We're home.
Land, sweet land!
We made it back!
I still can't believe it.
It's not a dream!
Aye.
What's wrong?
No way.
Oh no...
The Harekaze...
Somebody stop it.
Don't y'dare sink!
No!
Harekaze!
nanatsu no ao wa kyou mo sekai wo tsutsundeita
Our world is flooded by a myriad of blue yet again today
kotoba yori mo yasashiku senaka wo osu yo
It nudges me gentler than any words could
sou watashi to kimi no ripple effect
And we share our own ripple effect together
hatenaku mukattekuru nami wa kewashii bakari de
There seems to be no end to these fierce waves
kouro wa doushiyo kimi to erabu mirai
What shall be our course on this journey together?
hohoemi wasuretara watashi ga warau yo
If you've lost the will to smile, I'll laugh for you
namida hajiketa ato wa tsuyosa ga minamo ni hirogaru kara
Wipe away those tears and show the ocean what you're made of
nanatsu no ao wa kyou mo sekai wo tsutsundeita
Our world is flooded by a myriad of blue yet again today
kotoba yori mo yasashiku nami utsu hareta sora to ano kaze to
The clear sky and breeze is gentler than words could ever be
higashi no sora ni hikari ga mietanaraba
If you spot a ray of light to the east of the sky
kaji wo torou namida wo sutete
Wipe away your tears and take the helm
kitto yume wa nigenai hazu dakara
Because our dreams aren't going anywhere
watashi mo
And neither am I
oneday everyday beyond the sea moving fast
Oneday everyday beyond the sea moving fast
mazu wa ikiteikou yo
Let's just try to see how it goes
muki wa kinishinaide sa
Don't worry about where we're headed
kimi ga egao ni naru dake de
As long as you're here laughing
hora mata hitori
I will be too, see?
nanatsu no ao wa kyou mo sekai wo tsutsundeita
Our world is flooded by a myriad of blue yet again today
kotoba yori mo yasashiku nami utsu hareta sora to ano kaze to
The clear sky and breeze is gentler than words could ever be
dareka no soba de yume wo egaku no naraba
If you're going to share your dreams with someone
sono dare ka ga watashi de aritai
I want that someone to be me
tabi ni deyou mitsukete
Let's set off on a cruise
sou watashi to kimi no ripple effect
And we'll find our own ripple effect together