One day, I realized I had nothing.
I'd parted ways with my family,
betrayed my friends and my organization,
and even killed my mentor.
I'd made my friends cry, lost them,
and turned my back on the people who loved me.
And...
I'd even cast myself aside, so it was only natural.
But the pockets I thought were empty
still contained one last thing.
I want to see you again someday.
In order to fulfill a promise
I both do and don't remember,
I will rewrite
the fate of the girl
who has to live alone, forever in solitude.
This song is making Kagari
suffer and trying to cause ruin.
I have to make it stop.
I can hear the song coming from over there.
But if I take on everyone in my way,
I'll run out of steam before I even get there.
Tennouji...
You got some nerve to be taking a
leisurely stroll, you double-crossing scumbag.
Are you one of Gaia's spies?
Nope.
I'm just Tennouji Kotarou, the man.
Don't you want a quick and painless death?
I can't die here, not yet.
Not until I show her
the potential this planet has,
and the fond memories she seeks.
Just tell me one thing before
we send you off to hell.
Just who the hell are you?
I'm...
the Earth-Saving Hunter.
Not so fast!
Hey!
He's headed toward...
Gaia's temple!
After him!
We'll destroy him and
Gaia's core in one fell swoop!
Looks like he was hiding his powers all along.
That son of a...
This place is way too defenseless.
They must have something
really dangerous up ahead.
Well, all yours then.
Shimizu-san!
Now ain't this ironic.
Us losers are the only ones who survived.
Damn it!
Get back.
I don't fuckin' get it.
Thought you stabbed us in the back!
The hell's up with you?
Why have you been hiding your
incredible power this whole time?
Why'd you deceive us?
What the hell is your game?
Like I said, I'm saving the planet.
There's this girl.
Can't steal her heart unless I do.
Wh-What do you mean, save the planet?
I'll put a stop to this song.
Though even then, the most it'll do
is leave us teetering on the brink.
Still, it'll let me pass on the baton of possibility.
To, let's see... Nishikujou's
future students, I guess?
Oh, and while we're on the topic...
This brat's got a bit of cheekiness in her,
but deep down, she's a good, kind-hearted girl.
Sorry I don't have any better pictures of her.
Her contact details are in there, too.
What? Wait, this...
Imamiya, Nishikujou.
I'm leaving the future to you.
Why do you have to say it like that?
That makes it sound like you're...
But a single, solitary hunter?
You must be an excellent individual,
chosen from among many by fate.
Daemons who live long become sentient, huh?
Gaia's guardian deity.
Indeed.
In my eyes, the Gaians are my children.
All life has the right to die as it sees fit.
And should they wish for this ending,
then I shall grant them their wish.
In order to fulfill my children's desire,
I cannot allow you to take
a single step further, hunter.
Rewrite
Don't Rewrite
Oh... So I'm this far gone.
It's not even my blood anymore. It's my very life itself.
And it's time to call it forth.
The point of no return...
I just crossed a line from which I can never come back.
You're going down, Gaia!
Kashima Sakura.
Did my actions have any meaning at all?
All those daemons are nowhere to be seen now.
The song is over, but the world still hasn't ended.
That means Kagari's still holding on.
The conflict between Gaia and
Guardian will soon come to an end.
Will that not make a fond memory?
Tell me, Kagari.
Iko-san?
Kotarou-kun?
Why are you here?
I mean, you were doing all you could...
So why?
Because my kids had no future.
I'm pretty sure Akane grew up, slowly but surely.
Sakura-san was looking out for her.
Where is Akane right now?
I sent her to the City of Stone.
Tell me, what happened to the world?
It's still alive.
It's filthy, sad, and cruel...
It's on the verge of death...
But it's still alive.
So I failed, huh?
Maybe I should bring Akane-chan back here...
Screw that...
Screw that!
Neither Kagari nor I have that much time left...
Akane, I still have work to do.
So you'll have to save yourself now.
I'll give you some bodyguards.
Dima, Lyuba.
You can control them?
Without any training?
Nice, Akane.
Listen.
Go to the safest place you can find
and tell the nicest-looking person there this:
"Help me."
Help...
Yeah, just like that.
But stay away from pedophiles.
Pedo...?
Say it like you did a second ago.
Got it?
That's the way.
Now get going.
I can't believe how calm and
collected she is in this situation.
My time's almost up, huh?
Kagari, I wanna see you...
Why do I want to see her so badly, anyway?
Oh, I see.
I've been chasing after her since forever.
Kagari?
Thank you.
Those were indeed some fond memories
of the greatest kind.
Did I make it in time?
No, unfortunately not.
If only I'd witnessed this
world just a little bit sooner...
I can't help but regret that.
Oh...
No need to be ashamed.
You did very well, for one human.
Hold your head up high, and finish your final task.
Come.
I can't do that
Do it
Kagari...
You should've done this sooner.
You've always shown me the way.
But if nothing changed, we'd never...
So I decided to do this myself...
But...
B-But, you know...
I killed so many people
and betrayed all their trust and love to get this far!
I kept hope alive for the world!
But, even after all that, I have to kill you?!
It's okay.
This is a blessing.
Like hell it is!
This is nothing but a fucking curse!
To make me suffer!
The ability and the will to carve
open a path to the future...
Even if you must consume
your mother planet to do it,
you all must reach out to new frontiers.
That's what will form fond memories.
You did so well without my guidance.
Was this good enough?
There remains hope for the world.
I see.
I only did it because I'm into you, though.
Into me?
It means I'm in love with you.
I didn't realize.
You are pretty thickheaded.
Unrequited feelings must leave
one feeling empty inside.
I'm fine with that.
So stupid.
You're just one human...
That's right.
This love story is perfect for me.
There once lived a young man.
A delicate young man who shared the same worries
and sorrows as many others.
He was a soldier.
A sinful soul who killed people over and over.
But he also saved many, many people,
at the cost of his own heart and life.
And in his wake,
he left a guiding light for the weak,
despairing humans living on this wounded planet.
Holder of the Guiding Light
We will respect his wish
and reveal what some people have been monopolizing,
the guiding light for our survival,
to the entire world.
As Earth heads toward ruin,
humanity only has one resource left to turn to.
It exists within us
as the limited yet infinite power that is life.
The sin of living by devouring
the livesof people and the planet
is one the planet will surely forgive.
Because a child using its mother
as a stepping stone on its journey
is in no way a sad memory.
So please don't forget the nameless young man
who carved open the path for us.
The trailblazer who led the way for us,
the holder of the guiding light.
Did you find a good planet,
my beloved family?
Isn't this the one?
It grew 500 meters tall in three years?
Talk about a pain.
It's magnificent.
Nice color, too.
It looks strong and sturdy!
Were those all double entendres?
No.
Your mind's just in the gutter.
Blame my genes for that.
What is it, Kotori?
It just feels very familiar, for some reason.
But are you sure we can use it without permission?
This is technically municipal property, right?
What they don't know won't hurt them.
If they do, we're in for a
lecture from Touka-sensei!
Shall we get to it, then?
Here goes the countdown.
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
Come on out!
It's almost scary how well that worked.
Can you hear us?
You're our familiar.
Yeah.
You'll dress like a butler
and do our bidding like a slave.
Yeah.
Do you understand what we're saying?
Can't he say anything but "yeah"?
Our stars are only an illusion of the shattered night
hibiwareta yoru ni ikuseisou no sora
He was only just born. That's just how it is.
By the way, this place is quite warm.
On the sky many months and years old
utsuru bokutachi wa maboroshi
We're in an ice age now, though.
It's really cold outside the city.
Well, that thing makes sense now.
I wish to leave behind my past self
moshi kanau no nara kinou to wa chigau
It's like the town is being
sheltered by a layer of life.
Do you realize who and what you are?
And have my true self here instead
hontou no boku wo kono chi ni
Yeah.
I'm a daemon, right?
The proof of our existence vanishes beyond the horizon
bokura ikitekita koto kanata e kieteku
My job is to wear a black tuxedo
and serve you, my contractors.
Just as we inputted!
Your life comes to a standstill like a rusted rail
sabitsuita reeru kimi wa tada tachitsukusu
It was super effective!
But I must respectfully decline.
I'm meant for bigger things,
for I possess a special power, you see.
So long as this blue fire flows through my arm
ima kono ude ni nagareru aoi hi ga aru nara
He suddenly started talking like
I'll be able to take your hand and stop you
furikaeru kimi no te wo hiite
a college student who doesn't want to get a job.
Actually, this is the first time I've seen a familiar
disobey its master.
Vowing to stars born of ashes never to let go
mou nidoto hanasanai to hai no hoshi e chikau yo
This is why I said to avoid a humanoid.
Because it'd turn into my fishmonger.
Your fishmonger?
I will rewrite this poem
kakikaeru kono uta wo
He's sell-fish.
Let's leave that awful joke
on the back burner for now.
He's sell-fish!
I request treatment befitting my talents.
As long as you provide me with life,
I can use it creatively
and do anything and everything.
I have no idea what he's talking about.
So long as this red blood flows through my arm
ima kono ude ni nagareru akai chi ga aru nara
Can you fly, then?
I can grow wings or sails if need be.
I'll be able to take your hand and stop you
furikaeru kimi no te wo hiite
Why don't we put that to the test?
Take us somewhere right away.
Piece of cake.
Vowing to the distant stars never to let go
mou nidoto hanarenai to tooi hoshi e chikau yo
But I have only been provided
five drops of life so far.
That's not enough.
I will rewrite it all
kakikaeru sono subete
How many do you need, then?
At the very least, tens of thousands of contractors.
Your mileage is awful.
How far can we go with that many?
I can even leave the Solar System if you wish.
Why must we go to space, anyway?
Why, indeed?
You people figure out the answer.
That's humanity's job.
Hey driver.
How far can we go with fare for five?
Around there, I suppose.
Oh, it's merely a quick hop.
What lies beyond this heavenly island?
shima no soto ni wa nani ga aru no ka
The boy and the girls used a tree in the forest
shounen to shoujotachi wa mori no ki wo tsukatte
And began to build a watchtower tall enough
umi no mukou ni hirogaru suiheisen wo
To see the vast horizon beyond the sea
miwataseru hodo takai yagura wo tatehajimeta
Successful, they awaken from an endless dream
hatenaki yume wo mezashi karera wa yaritogeta
Episode 24
"A Promise Fulfilled with You"
Have you the courage to brave this unsteady path?
guratsuku ashimoto dokyou wa daijoubu ka
Standing upon the summit of the world right now
sono itadaki ni ima tatsu
Looking over the far, far, ever so vast sea
ano umi wo tooku tooku miwatasu
And beyond it there lies a brand new world
sono mukou ni atarashii sekai ga mieta
Almost like an illusion
gensou no you ni
How could we possibly reach that place?
sono basho ni wa dou sureba ikeru no ka
The boy decided
shounen wa kimeta
To build a boat and cross the sea
fune wo tsukurou to sore de watarou
I finally fulfilled my promise.
I want to
see you again someday.