We wanted nothing more
than to have someone by our side.
We had power.
We ceased to be alone.
But at the end of that humble happiness...
...lay nought but death and despair.
Subsequently, we were reborn.
We soon realized...
that we were fated to pass down our memories,
our emotions, to another "us".
We were to watch over this world till its final days.
There was no doubt that love, beauty,
and virtue existed within this world,
but even more so did hatred, ugliness, and folly.
Each time we were born into this world,
its grip upon us tightened.
And little by little,
that impurity gnawed away at our hearts.
Then,
a great many years later,
our modest desire had twisted into disgust
and despair at mankind's nature.
Does humanity...
Does life...
...truly deserve to be a part of the future?
Wh-What was that?
Shimako...
Thank you.
I'm all right.
According to Sakuya's report,
Kotori's secret base should
be around here somewhere...
I just heard a voice.
Huh?!
K-Konohana-san?!
Wh-What are you doing here?!
You're gravely wounded!
Hold on! I'll get you to a hospital right away!
Over here?
Yeah.
There was some strange feedback in the barrier.
Kotarou!
Kotori!
Huh?
Little by little, the ripples drew apart from one another
sukoshizutsu hamon wa hanarete itta
And before we knew it, they no longer overlapped
itsu shika hitotsu mo kasanaranaku natta
But it's okay as long as you're here with me
sore demo ii kimi to itara
When did I start feeling this way?
konna kimochi itsu kara idaita
This is the love story of a certain boy
tada hitori no shounen no koimonogatari da
To protect you till the end of time
eien ni kimi wo mamotte miseru
I'll etch this upon my heart
kono mune ni kizamikomu
When did it start being just the two of us, again?
itsu kara futarikiri ni natta n da kke
But it's okay
mou ii ka
Just smile
sonna koto waratte yo
On the eve of this world's end
owaru sono hi ni wa
I'd heard about it from Sakuya,
but to think there really was
a place like this in the forest...
Anyway, hurry up and come this way.
R-Right!
What are you doing?
I'm revitalizing Class Rep's life force.
It's kind of like breathing life into daemons.
So you really are a summoner?
Yeah.
A druid, specifically...
It would appear a fierce battle took place here.
One combatant used flames.
As for the other...
I'm sorry.
Could you take a deep breath for me?
Sure thing!
As I suspected, it is indeed poison.
This entire area has been
completely and utterly contaminated.
Don't use me like a canary in a coal mine!
Lucia!
Konohana-san!
The bleeding...
The bleeding won't stop!
Wouldn't her condition improve if you used this?
Just saying.
Kagari, this is no time for playing around—
Wait.
You're right.
I'll use it, Kagari.
She still needs to get some rest,
but she should be okay now.
Really?!
Th-Thank goodness!
How about that?
All thanks to yours truly!
I put the "K" in "Key", 'kay?
Kagari!
Huh?
Oh wow!
Thank you, Kagari.
Thank you so much for saving Lucia.
You're being awfully touchy-feely, Kotarou.
Hey!
Come on!
Not the face!
What are they doing?
I see.
That girl is the Key?
Class Rep.
Lucia...
Konohana-san!
I never thought I'd be able
to see her with my own two eyes.
Rumors need to be taken with a pinch of salt, huh?
Is it okay for you to be talking?
Yeah.
I can't believe how much the pain has subsided.
Is this also the power of the Key?
I'd like to show my gratitude.
Thank you, Kotarou.
And you too, Kanbe-sa—
Thank you, Kotori.
Chihaya.
You're welcome, Lucy!
L-Lucy?!
You went way over the top, Lucia!
By the way, who are you?
You're asking that now?
Um, how to put it...
From your perspective,
I suppose I would be considered the enemy.
The enemy?
Yeah.
I'm with Guardi—
She's a friend!
Huh?
That's right.
She's a fellow member of the
occult club, and a friend of ours!
Yeah, we're friends!
Huh?
Yeah, you're right.
That's really all that mattered.
Lucy?
What's the matter, Lucia?
Are you hungry or something?
I have returned.
It seems she's through the worst of it.
Yeah.
As long as she rests for a few days,
I believe she'll recover her former mobility.
Is that so?
In that case, I shall reinforce the barrier
and extend my scouting range.
Please do.
I will also step up your training.
As a form of personal stress relief.
Hey...
Chihaya...
I hope she was able to meet up
with everyone successfully...
Shuuichiro, who do I look like to you?
Am I still myself?
You are Sakura.
You're still my Sakura.
That was Grandmother's...
Don't tell me this is the saint's...
It's me.
Tsukuno?
What happened?
Grandmother collapsed?!
Yes.
I'll be right there.
Shizuru-chan.
Touka?
I haven't seen Lucia-chan since last night.
Happen to know where she might be?
N-No.
I see.
I-Is that safe?
Don't living creatures melt when they touch that?
Inorganic objects are fine.
What's wrong?
Just my imagination.
Lucy's condition has stabilized,
so we have to bolster our forces while we still can.
Is this how daemons are made?
Yeah.
By giving them a body and forming a contract,
I can bring them to life and use them.
Honestly, though, using an animal's
corpse would be most effective.
A-A corpse?!
Done.
Now just a little of this...
Oh, it actually moved!
All right!
Oh?
Did I mess up somehow?
Yo, Greenhouse Princess.
Your little friends are playing a fun game
of hide and seek in the forest.
What, they leave you out in the cold?
It sounds like you've done your homework.
On the battlefield,
ignorant shits always bite the dust first.
I ain't like those peace-loving
dumbasses in this country.
You're Fogo's master, if I'm not mistaken?
The hell you planning to do
with the Key by bringing the Apex
and that stray superhuman together in the forest?
What are you after?
They're my prey!
If you're gonna fuck around from the sidelines,
I don't give a shit if you're Gaia.
I'll kill you.
That's all.
Keep that in mind!
Poison, huh?
A powerful one at that.
What about it?
What if I said I'd grant you a new power?
What?
This is the legendary...
Yes.
Save for the Apex,
it's undoubtedly Gaia's ultimate weapon:
the Earth Dragon.
If you accept my condition, I'll give this to you.
However, this daemon will consume
your life force faster than any other.
Don't underestimate me!
Not just anyone could use Fogo, either.
So, what's the condition?
That you don't kill the Key.
Even if Guardian attacks, you must protect it.
Damn, what a pain.
Got it?
If anything happens to the Key,
this damned world you detest
oh so much will continue on.
Fine.
But aside from the Key,
everything is my prey,
including your happy little friends.
You okay with that?
Do as you please.
Life is not deserving of a place in the future.
I like you, Princess.
I'll crush everything in my path!
Gil-chan tried to attack Kotarou-san
during his training and got crushed!
Good grief.
The daemons do seem to be acting funny.
It only started recently.
Do you have any idea why?
According to Sakuya-san,
the soil in this area has been
contaminated with poison.
I think the power spot has
been acting up because of it.
Poison?
That most likely means it's my fault.
What do you mean?
Well...
Oh, you don't look well.
Very well. I shall share
my cherished feecof with thee.
Huh? N-No, I...
Gulp it.
Come on, gulp it!
Hey, my body still isn't—
Lucia! Are you all right?
Ow...
What a waste.
Lick, lick!
D-Don't lick my face!
Hey! Stop it!
It tickles!
I know!
H-Hey, let me down!
But Lucia, you haven't recovered
your strength yet, have you?
Isn't she heavy, Chi-chan?
Th-That's rude, Kotori!
It's all right.
I'm strong due to the influence
of the daemon I've contracted with.
The daemon you've contracted with?
Oh, so that's how it is.
This is total bliss!
Oh?
You aren't taking off your gloves?
No.
That's right...
I started to mention this earlier,
but I'm the source of the poison
that polluted this forest.
Huh?
I'm sorry.
That was insensitive of me.
You're saying even flowers are dirty?
It's all water under the bridge now.
Don't worry about it.
No, I won't accept that!
Ch-Chi-chan?
Why do you have to suffer like that?!
I'm sure that deep down, you actually
do want to touch flowers and animals!
Save the world from destruction,
no matter the cost.
That is Guardian's mission.
But...
It feels so strange.
A member of Gaia,
who is trying to destroy humanity,
is worried about my well-being.
That's because I'm your friend!
Mhm!
Right.
It doesn't make sense.
H-Hey, you're totally exposed!
Gaia and Guardian say they're working
toward the same goal of saving the world,
but I can't imagine that's true
based on what I've just heard.
You're right.
That may not have been
enough of an explanation.
Um...
Man, that Sakuya really
doesn't know how to go easy, huh.
Better wash off the sweat right away...
Huh?
K-Kotarou, you...
What are you thinking?!
No debauchery! Let's keep it PG!
I-I'm not doing it on purpose!
I always come here to wash up after training—
K-Kagari?!
Huh...?
Here you are.
Nothing beats a canned feecof right after a bath.
Yeah, I've been wondering about that, too.
Why are Gaia and Guardian fighting
when they have the same goal?
Although our goals are similar,
the essence is quite different.
Hey, you're coughing up blood.
Don't push yourself!
Gaia's goal is to eradicate humanity
and regenerate this world.
Huh?
On the other hand, Guardian's mission is
to preserve the world that mankind has built.
Huh?
It is correct that both wish
to save the world in a broad sense.
And druids...
...exist to protect the Key
until it hands down its judgment.
As for what sort of Salvation
the Key will bring about,
we're honestly not too worried about it.
They're all so extreme.
Yummy.
This question might be a little late as well...
Whoa! What is this?
What are Gaia and Guardian
going to do with the Key, anyway?
Awesome!
It's so pretty!
To be blunt, we'll shelter her.
Shelter?
Yes.
We know scant in regard
to the Salvation she will bring,
and thus we must keep
her secure until then to learn.
That goes for Gaia.
For Gaia?
Then, what will Guardian do?
We'll erase it.
Huh?
As long as there is no guarantee
this Salvation will benefit humanity,
we will erase the Key to maintain the status quo.
That's Guardian's train of thought.
You'll kill Kagari?
How terrible.
Who would have thought there
was such a reason to fight over me?
I am indeed a temptress!
Huh?
It isn't easy being popular, is it?
Lucy?
Oh, I have no intention
of harming Kagari anymore.
I couldn't kill someone who's saved my life,
and who can talk to me, even for humanity's sake.
Thank goodness.
At the very least,
this means we won't end up
fighting you anymore, right?
Mhm!
That's great!
We're all like bees in a pod!
You mean peas...
I don't get it.
If you are able to resolve your
differences with conversation,
why do the majority of humans not do so?
Well...
I studied many things.
Humans have continued to chip away
at the planet's lifespan
through destruction and strife.
Wasting energy like that
is nothing short of pointless.
Foolish humans should
at least give a little more thought
to how they use energy.
Even I can't eat any more...
Accelerating environmental destruction.
Resources on the verge of exhaustion.
And yet a segment of humanity
continues to indulge in their pleasures
without any sense of impending danger.
Just get rid of the humans.
Foolish humans, huh?
Kagari.
Oh, Kotarou?
Is this a booty call?
No, it's not!
I just remembered someone
who said something similar
to what you did.
Say...
Are humans really useless
as far as the Earth is concerned?
Let me see.
It is true that humans are foolish compared to me.
I have learned that well by watching you.
Hey.
But humans do have their decent points.
I also learned that well by watching you.
So, by putting those aspects to good use—
Kagari?
Good... memories...
Good memories?
What's that supposed—
Kagari?!
What are you...
Huh?
Good... memor—
Kagari!
Hey, Kagari!
So it was a booty call.
No!
Last Day of the Harvest Festa
Gaia Japanese Branch
Sorry to keep ya!
Let's move.
Playtime is over, humans.
No,
I won't let you end it yet.
So rough!
Finding so much evidence
while patrolling the Harvest
Festa was seriously rough!
Imamiya-san!
We've lost contact with Charlie,
who was scouting the forest!
Huh?
That's when you send Bravo to check on them—
We cannot get in touch with Bravo, either!
What did you say?!
A short while ago,
Guardian Japanese Branch - Command Room
we lost contact with both the Bravo
and Charlie scouting parties.
We must assume that a considerably
powerful daemon has been sent in.
Doing that at this juncture must mean...
The Key is involved?
It is very likely.
Accordingly, I have decided to send in
combat troops immediately.
We lost contact with the scouting party...
Here.
That's...
Do you hear it?
If so, join them in unison...
The song of destruction...
which will bring salvation to the world!
natsukashisa mo kieta yume
Losing myself in a dream where even nostalgia lost form
Episode 11
Countdown
mayoi kono te ga samishiku kaze wo nadeta
Lonely, I reached out with my hands to feel the wind's gentle caress
kotoba wo shiranai mama naraba
The names of those emotions still eluded me
kono hitomi wo tojiru koto mo
Even closing my eyes for eternity
kantan datta no ni
Should have been simple
hajimete fureta nukumori
But I felt warmth for the first time
chiisaku mebuku kodou ni
A tiny soul began to bud within my heart
tomadoi wo oboeta
And I learned of bewilderment
anata no koe sagashite mugen no michi wo yuku
Walking on the path of eternity, searching for your voice
hoshi no hajimari wo shiru tada sore dake
I'm led to the time when stars are born, nothing more
kuchi ni nokoru nigami mo hiroku mada ki ni naru
This bitterness that lingers inside my mouth tempts my curiosity
itsuka deau anata he saigo ni hohoemi wo
So I'll offer you one last smile before we meet again