We'll protect this princess
from any daemons that attack.
As the occult club, that's our job here.
For how long?
Until she completes her theory.
And when exactly will that be?
When she completes it.
You're asking a lot, Pops.
Who are you calling Pops?
Well, you went and grew up all by yourself.
Whoa, you're right!
Why?
Episode 16
"The Truth Nobody Knows"
What is this theory, anyway?
A way to save Earth.
Via re-evolution, though I don't
suppose you understand what I mean.
Nope, I don't.
That said...
We'll take your word for it.
And who might we be up against?
Kashima Sakura.
Oh, her.
Anyway, I want someone
to stay by Kagari at all times.
Oh, sorry.
I just found it funny that Gaia and Guardian
are going to protect the Key together.
To save the planet, no less.
Yeah. How exciting.
Time to get right to work, huh?
I welcome a challenge.
Have daemons started showing up?
Looks like it.
I should give you these
while I still have the chance.
Sorry.
I couldn't prepare anything
too complicated, like guns.
That won't be a problem.
My body is my first and foremost weapon.
All good.
This will be easy.
You protect Kagari with these guys, Kotori.
Good boys.
You're called Dima and Lyuba, huh?
This one's for you, Prez.
Survey the battlefield with it.
Certainly. I can do that.
As for Chihaya...
This should do.
Why am I the odd one out?
Yoshino?
Sorry. We were no match for them.
No, you were a big help. Thanks.
We'll save Earth.
It's a big job befitting the revival of the occult club.
I'm counting on you all!
For some reason, this battle has me in high spirits.
You don't understand why, Shizuru?
It's because you're fighting for your friends.
I see.
Right, that makes sense.
Of course that'd make me really happy.
Yeah, me too.
Here comes one.
Aim for its legs, Kotori.
Got it.
Dima, Lyuba!
Give it a good hit, Chihaya!
Aye aye!
Area's clear.
You're the last to finish, Kotarou.
Roger that. Good work.
Talk about some dependable friends.
I'm glad you're all okay.
Guess we took the first battle.
That said, they were all way stronger
than regular daemons.
We're up against Kashima Sakura,
so naturally that's a given.
We should expect her to keep sending ones
that are equally strong, if not stronger.
We can do this.
Yeah.
You sure are confident.
Tea is served!
Kagari didn't get any.
Make another cup, please.
Allow me to be blunt.
We haven't been able to see her for a while now.
We can sense a powerful being nearby, though.
Oh...
Even here, Kagari has to be all alone?
This is quite the interesting theory.
It shows the path the world and its life have taken.
It starts off strong,
but peters out in the end.
You can decipher it?
It does somewhat resemble
the process for producing a daemon.
Though this is far more advanced, obviously.
So what exactly is that?
Researching the theory of life, huh?
So even almighty powers have limits.
Yeah.
Aurora isn't omnipotent.
There's nothing it can do if the resources run out.
Value the resources!
But the development of civilization
requires consumption of resources.
And it's too late to stop environmental
destruction once the damage is done.
How utterly foolish humans are.
The final boss?!
Clearly the best option is to destroy civilization
immediately every time it appears.
She really is the final boss!
Okay, then.
Let's run some simulations on a copy.
We can leave the early stages in auto mode.
The Big Splash happens,
and the leftover debris becomes the moon.
It's kinda like a game.
All right, then.
Take a crack at it.
Allow me.
The very fate of the foolish human
race lies in the palm of my hand.
Please don't get any strange ideas!
Why'd you destroy it right off the bat?!
It wasn't my fault.
I'll go next, then.
It got destroyed again!
I never dreamed a demon would show up
and devour the entire world!
Uh, you were the creator.
Can I go next?
Why do you all immediately destroy Earth?!
Oh.
Humanity came into existence
while I was playing around.
For real?!
They've formed a civilization and a country.
The country's splitting up!
We'd better cull some humans.
It's scary how casually she says it.
A huge empire has been created.
It suddenly stopped making progress.
They went on the defensive after it expanded.
But the population is still growing.
What?!
It was destroyed all of a sudden!
Kotarou-kun, look at this!
Is this the Key?
Why'd it end the world?
Probably because Earth's resources
would've been extinguished eventually.
Kotori, can you tell us anything
you remember about Kagari?
Only that according to legend,
she's looking for fond memories.
Fond memories?
For the planet?
Speaking of which,
I wonder how it went during our time.
We died out in the end each time,
but surely there were phases
where things might've worked out.
Indeed, several projects came up
to stave off the impending doom.
There were even plans to expand into space.
But they all failed in the end.
I see.
What were we lacking in order to save the planet?
In the world with Prez,
the one with Shizuru,
the one with Chihaya,
the one with Lucia,
and Kotori's...
Huh?
Wait.
Wait a second.
What is this void that exists in every memory?
That's right.
I always meet Kagari and nearly get killed by her.
Kotori saves me using her Druid powers,
and my time comes to a stop.
I'm actually far older than all of them,
and the time I spent in a coma, over a decade,
was the same in every world.
If that time was what we lacked to save the world,
that'd mean the root cause
was that I got involved too late.
What's up, Kagari?
What's this?
The branch worlds whose deaths were inevitable
now have uncertain futures?
Great job.
You did well.
It's fine, Kagari.
Better uncertain than certain doom.
There's still hope that way.
Oh, yeah.
Can I write a message to commemorate this?
Humans do this all the time.
I want to meet you someday.
- Tennouji Kotarou
It's a bit corny, but oh well.
There we go. It shouldn't affect
the theory all the way over here.
Kagari?
Is this... a new theory?
Why now?
A future was born?
Wow!
All right! You did it, Kagari!
Kagari?
What's wrong?
You completed your theory,
so why do you look so sad?
Hey, the enemy's attacking!
Their numbers are insane!
So you noticed, Kashima Sakura.
Kagari completed her research.
But it looks like it'll take her some time
to put her completed theory into action.
We're hopelessly outnumbered here, but...
Keeping Kagari safe is our highest priority.
Understood?
We'll need to come up with a strategy.
I've enhanced Dima and Lyuba's mobility,
so now we can use them for guerrilla warfare.
I'll just swing some logs around.
I'll set up as many traps as possible.
You girls...
In the new world,
I bet I won't get to spend time
with them as someone their age.
Since this is the end, I'll put on a show
with all the strength I gained living a peaceful life.
Yeah, this is how the occult club should be.
Occult club, give 'em hell!
Yeah!
Yeah...
Listen up, you sorry lot!
Bare your fangs against those that would
dare defile the turf of us wolves!
Go to...
...hell!
If it's for my friends,
I can use this power I hate so much!
Kotarou's counting on me.
I'll give it everything I've got.
Dima, Lyuba... Go!
Get down, Kotori!
Thanks, Chi-chan.
No problem.
Thank you too, Prez!
Don't mention it.
Now, then.
Kashima Sakura...
I don't understand how you must've felt
to send this many daemons across worlds.
A song?
Kagari...
Damn you!
Keep your filthy paws off my girl!
Tennouji.
Yoshino?
What's up?
The enemy sent reinforcements.
All my comrades have fallen.
Really?
Yeah.
Every one of those bastards showed
their rock star spirit until the very end.
Yoshino.
End of the line, huh?
Yeah, I've had plenty...
Great job.
I was... really happy.
We're getting married.
Thanks for everything.
Tennouji Kotarou & Kotori
So, next time...
Kotarou...
For everything you've given us...
Forgive me for giving you
nothing but trouble, Kotarou.
Do what you need to...
And...
Kotarou...
To be honest, just once more, I want—
Keep her safe until the very end.
Sorry.
It's time for me to go, too.
Yoshino...
Tell me.
Was I of any use at all?
I only got to stay a loner because you rejected me.
And I only got to be a trailblazer
because I was a loner.
Tell me in a language I can understand.
I'm saying we'll be rivals
till the end of time, Yoshino.
Now that's what I call mach speed.
I'm gonna go out with a bang,
'cause that's just how I roll.
There's no better last gig for me.
Ain't that right,
Kotarou?
Yeah, exactly.
Give 'em hell,
Haruhiko.
Goodbye, my brother!
See you in the next life!
Yee-haw!
So it's begun.
Aurora is rebuilding this
temporary world into a new one.
You pieces of shit!
Why are you here,
Sakuya?!
Just in the nick of time...
Or so I'd like to say,
but it seems I was a little too late.
I'll unleash my desire to rewrite the life now
It's a wish we all have
Forgive me, Chihaya-san.
I took too long to unite
my various selves and come here.
Even for a path where you can never again step back
This is no time to be spacing out, Slowtarou-kun.
Don't turn around, don't look back
Your beloved sleeping beauty is in grave peril.
You never fail to get on my nerves.
But...
There's no one else I'd rather have
by my side at a time like this.
Indeed.
I believe I'm stronger now
than I was in any other world.
I'll unleash my desire to rewrite the life now
It's a wish we all have
Even for a path where you can never again step back
Don't turn around, don't look back
Rewrite these times to face a brand new day
I once told you that you were my destiny.
I don't remember stuff from that long ago.
However, you surpassed my destiny and repainted
what lay beyond it in your own colors.
I could not have stood here
and created new possibilities.
We have the same abilities
and share the same fate.
So maybe it was because I'm a newer model.
Our foe seems rather determined
not to grant us any reprieve.
Good grief.
I think I depended on you in every world.
I'm counting on you, bro.
Leave it to me,
bro.
Sakuya, don't tell me...
I took too long to unite
my various selves and come here.
You linked every branch-world Sakuya
to this realm?
You shut the door on your fate
in order to stand here?
You dumbass.
I'll remember you.
The me right here will, if no one else.
Guess it's my turn now.
Hit that final switch!
Farewell...
Farewell, Tennouji Kotarou...
Thank you, Tennouji Kotarou...
For caring about me when I'm so selfish.
It's fine.
Love is much more than that.
You said you want to meet me.
But we'll never see each other again.
Wait, Kagari!
Aren't you coming with us?
The moon?
Are we going to start over on the moon?
It's so huge...
Huge?
I see.
So we were on the moon this whole time,
and that's the real Earth?
Earth was teeming with life,
but the moon only gave birth to Kagari.
Kagari...
You used the remnants
of Earth's Aurora on the moon,
where you were all alone,
and made a replica of Earth?
It was an inexcusable act,
born from feelings I shouldn't have accepted.
I'll give back what I took and return to nothingness.
Kagari... Kagari?
With these memories, I can endure the loneliness.
That's all I ever wanted.
Stop it, you idiot.
Bon voyage, humanity.
Kagari!
Earth...
Our home.
Our distant home planet.
A planet that fell into ruin, lost all its life, and died.
We have to start over.
But that Kagari won't be there.
I won't be there as I am now, either.
All I can do is make a wish.
If anyone ever makes it to the heavens,
I hope they find the girl on the moon...
From the very bottom of my heart.
Now, in this new world...
Let's begin the cruel process of selection.