Hey! Over here!
Um, Prez...
What did you just say?
I said, in light of the school's demands,
all occult club activities
will be suspended as of today.
Episode 7
A Place Lost
Wh-What do you mean,
activities will be suspended?!
Does Inoue's disappearance
have something to do with this?
Hit the nail on the head.
It's been five days since Inoue called me,
and then disappeared into the forest.
Inoue-san...
She was a good person.
Shizuru, you knew her?
She gave me sweets.
I see.
We talked about you a lot.
I told her all I knew about your
inclinations, leaving nothing out.
You don't mean "inclinations"
in a dirty way, right?!
Her informant was you?
So, they're saying it'd be inappropriate
to hold club activities right now?
But that's not even the issue.
But, yeah, this is no time to be
having fun without a care in the world.
I'm not happy about it,
but we have to be understanding.
Other clubs will also—
Only the occult club is ceasing activities.
What?
Why are they singling out the occult club?
One, that Inoue girl
made her rivalry with you known far and wide.
And two, you were also
the last person she spoke with.
That about covers the reasons why.
Why are they making Kotarou-kun
out to be the bad guy?
Of course, Inoue's own lapse in judgment
is the cause of this entire mess,
but now that she is missing,
the only ones they can pin
the blame onto are Tennouji
and the dubious group known as the occult club.
Next, they'll go from suspending activities
to disbanding our club completely,
and appease the parents and media that way.
I'm sure that's what the school has in mind.
Disbanding the occult club?
What will you do about it, Prez?
I think the club's disbanding is unavoidable.
If we stubbornly continue,
they might switch targets to individual members.
We haven't done anything wrong!
Why do we have to blindly do as they say?!
Not one person here could possibly
accept something so stupid—
It means playtime is over.
Wait.
Isn't this our rightful place?
We were only getting started,
but we had a good thing going!
Isn't this where we all belong?
We got together, hung out, did stupid stuff...
We're comrades!
We're amigos!
We bonded!
We're friends!
Don't all of you feel the same way?!
We're all completely different people,
but we worked well together.
We had fun being together, right?
Are you really okay with having those fun
times taken from us for no good reason?
I know a time will come where
we all have to go our separate ways.
But that's exactly why
I want to spend my short school life
right here.
I want to enjoy my youth with all of you!
Is that so wrong?!
Talk about a passionate speech.
That was pretty fiery, Kotarou.
I'm sure everyone here feels the same way.
Chihaya...
But we've got a bull's-eye on our back now.
My influence won't do us
any good in this situation.
But, put another way,
this will be dropped as long
as Inoue is found, right?
This hasn't been made public yet,
but the search for her has been called off.
Which means...
They haven't found her body yet,
but they seem to have concluded she's dead.
We just have to find Inoue ourselves, then!
If they haven't found a body,
then she could still be alive!
The adults weren't able to find her.
Do you really think we'll be able to?
I don't know,
but as long as there's even a small chance,
I want to give it a shot!
You're right.
Knowing you, you might be able to pull it off.
If you're going to do it, then so am I.
Yes! I'm fine with it!
Yeah.
I'll help out, too.
Honestly...
What was I thinking,
taking such troublesome people in?
You guys!
All right, is everyone ready?
I made lunches for everyone.
Thanks for that.
I brought a change of clothes and
other things for when we find Inoue.
I've got the medical supplies covered.
You're life savers.
I—
Thanks for bringing snacks.
How did you know?!
Um, and Prez...
Well, it's great that she came at all.
It'd be dumb if a search party
ended up needing its own one,
so we'll look for her until 3 pm, and then pull out.
Okay, then!
Inoue Search Quest begins right now!
This should do for our search route.
If that's what she was after,
then we should be able to retrace
her path to some extent.
Wait for us, Inoue!
Oh, if it isn't Slowtarou-kun.
Sakuya...
To think we'd run into each other like this again...
This truly must be fate,
Pissant Peontarou-kun.
That would sound a lot cooler if you said it
without a convenience store bag in hand.
These are Chihaya-san's snacks for tomorrow.
What does she think this is, a picnic?
As someone with more life experience,
allow me to offer a warning.
If you treasure your current, ordinary life,
then stop sticking your nose
where it doesn't belong.
What's that supposed to mean?
Exactly what it sounds like.
Hey, hold on!
He's just running his mouth like usual.
Kotarou, these look like Inoue-san's tracks.
What did you say?
It looks like an ordinary depression to me.
No, this is definitely a shoe print.
It's fairly old, so it's starting to fade.
That's an agent of a secret organization for you!
Can you follow it, Shizuru?
I'll try.
The trail disappeared.
It's like she wrapped her shoes in leaves
or something and concealed her footprints.
Was she worried about pursuers?
Why would she go to all that trouble?
Oh, when you're doing something secret,
you get wary of pursuers and conspiracies,
and start doing stuff like that.
She must be sick.
Yeah, with a terrible disease exclusive to youth.
You understand how it works,
so don't act like you don't have it, too.
Anyway, excuse me for a moment.
Oh, I need to use the bathroom, too.
I'll join you.
Me, too.
Why do girls always go to the bathroom in groups?
What intel about this forest
did Inoue get her hands on?
Is this place really the scene of
the sort of conspiracy she'd be into?
And if so, then what could it be?
Those girls sure are taking their sweet time.
Wait, it's been thirty minutes?!
Damn!
I totally zoned out!
I can't get through on the phone, either!
What the heck's going on?
Damn! The sun is going to set soon!
Where did you guys go—
What's with that guy?
I'm not sure what his deal is, but he seems dangerous!
Where is everyone?!
The dog from before?
No, it looks similar, but it's different!
Not good.
Not good, not good!
These things...
are looking to kill!
It's fast!
Damn, the enhancement
from the other day isn't enough!
In that case...
I'll kick it up a notch and rewrite myself again!
Rewrite complete!
Crap, my body still isn't used to the enhancement!
No way!
Fucking mongrel!
If I circulate power through my whole body...
Damn you!
What the hell just happened?
What the hell is this?!
It vanished?
I defeated it with this thing?
Seriously, what the hell is this?
Did I hit the accelerator too hard or something?
I'd be dead.
If not for those strange blades,
I would've been dog food.
Wait.
Inoue... Wait, Kotori and the
others are in this forest, too!
Shizuru!
Is that Lucia's voice?!
What are those?
Lucia! Shizuru!
This is bad!
What's going on?
Am I dreaming?
Lucia! Shizuru!
Kotarou!
What in the world is going on?
Why are you swinging those things around?
Shizuru!
What a terrible wound...
I'll heal you right now.
Stay still, Kotarou.
What are those monsters?
Our, that is, Guardian's enemies.
Daemons controlled by Gaia.
Even if those are from Gaia,
what are they doing here?
I don't know.
They could have set up their base in this forest,
or... they could be searching for the Key.
The Key...
Right now, Kazamatsuri City
is in a volatile situation
due to an individual who holds the key
to Earth's survival or its destruction.
Kotarou, you should be okay now.
Taking another look at it, that really is amazing!
Thanks!
Go look for Kotori and the others, quickly.
That's right! Where are the others?
Sorry.
We got separated from them
after we sensed the daemons.
What?
So they could be under attack
by those daemons or whatever, too?
Damn it!
We'll handle things here.
Take care of Kotori and the others for us, Kotarou.
Uh, but...
We've undergone combat training
in order to fight daemons.
These numbers won't pose a problem.
Don't overdo it, you two!
Go, Kotarou!
Thanks!
Where are you, Kotori?!
Chihaya!
Prez!
Take that!
Oh?
Is that you, Kotarou?
I'm sorry.
I thought you were a bear or something.
Didn't I shout your name out loud?!
Hey!
Kotarou-kun, how did you get that injury?
What happened?
Huh?!
Did I do that?
Uh, no.
I'm fine now.
Anyway, hurry, you three!
We've gotta get out of this forest!
We're running away?
But we haven't found the other two yet.
I know!
They're fine, so hurry!
Jeez. Why are you in such a rush?
It's seriously dangerous here!
Anyway, for now, just trust me—
What... is that?
Huh?
K-Kotarou...
Kotarou-kun, your arm.
Run away, all of you!
Lucia and Shizuru are ahead!
Meet up with them and get out of the forest!
Hey, Tennouji?!
It's stabbing through your arm...
Forget me. Get out of here!
A-Akane-san.
I know.
Right away.
Just wait.
We'll get help and come back for you right away!
Damn it!
Let go!
Let me go!
Damn it!
This thing again?
Die, you piece of shit!
Damn it!
Shit. I think I'm dead.
It's you...
S-Stay away!
Don't!
Let me go! She's... She's...
You can't!
Go away!
Kotori.
You can see her?
Let's just go home with everyone else. Okay?
I'm sure we'll find Inoue-san.
Once we do, let's hold occult club activities again.
Yeah, sounds good.
Are Shizu-chan and Class Rep this way?
You're okay, right?
Please be safe, you two...
They defeated them all?
Kotarou?
I'm glad you're safe.
You too, Kotori.
Y-Yeah.
We managed somehow.
Thank goodness.
You managed to meet up?
Stay where you are, Kotarou.
Lucia?
Why is everyone so tense?
Would you answer a few
questions for me, President?
Oh, and what would those be?
When we met up,
there were still daemons around.
And then...
You were both completely defenseless,
so why didn't those daemons go after you at all?
W-Well...
Maybe they were just picky?
One more question.
Why weren't either of you
surprised when you saw them?
It may have looked that way
because we were frozen in fear.
That's a lie.
Your heartbeat, facial muscles, breathing...
All of them were perfectly normal.
It's true that I was surprised.
After all, I never could have imagined this.
Who would have thought you were hunters...
Guardian's superhumans?
Huh?
Prez, what did you just say?
Kotarou.
Those two are our enemies.
Enemies?
By enemies, you can't mean...
G-Gaia?
Kotarou, don't tell me you're with them?
Kotarou isn't like that.
He isn't?
Well, not that it matters.
It won't change anything either way.
I suppose not.
Huh? W-Wait a second.
Why does it feel like you're about to fight?
I believe I told you...
Playtime is over.
Stand back, Kotarou.
What's going on?
What is all this?
Chi.
What is it?
Were you two the ones who attacked us?
What if I said we were?
You bitch!
Lucia, stop!
A high-frequency blade?
Just a little numbing, I must say.
Sakuya?
You're one of them too, Ohtori Sakuya?
Indeed.
I am a member of Gaia, and I serve Chihaya-san.
Also, I will say this for the honor
of Chihaya-san and Lady Akane.
Neither of them had anything
to do with this incident.
This just happened to coincide with an
unfortunate accident within the organization.
You expect us to believe that?
That is at your and Shizuru-san's discretion.
That's how it was?
Shizuru...
You're saying too much, Sakuya.
Let's go.
We have no further business here.
Understood.
Please do excuse us.
I thought I finally made some friends...
W-Wait!
Huh?
W... Wait...
Hang in there, Kotarou.
His body gave out?
That's not surprising.
I see.
It's all going to end...
Good morning.
Your homeroom teacher,
Nishikujou-sensei, had an emergency...
Kotori
Today
Canceled
Call me
I'm waiting
No answer
Heeeey
Where are you
Kotori
No answer
Heeeey
Where are you
No answer
I'm begging you, call me
Canceled
Hey, Tennouji.
Sorry, wasn't paying attention.
What is it?
How should I put this...
Are you in some sort of trouble?
Oh, no.
Everything's fine.
No entry for students
If you treasure your current, ordinary life,
then stop sticking your nose
where it doesn't belong.
Why did I forget?
Just how little it takes to shatter
an uneventful-yet-precious ordinary life to pieces...
dekakegiwa no amazora kaerigake no kitakaze
Rainy skies when I leave, north wind blowing when I come home
itsudemo kimama ni subete aiseru tsuyosa ga hoshii
Give me the courage to cover every inch of this whimsical world with my love
kyou mo isogigachi na hitonami wo miokuru you ni
Fresh tree leaves sway, as if bidding farewell
osanai konoha ga yureteiru
To waves of rushing people
mata hajimaru yo
So it begins, once again
saa bokura mo sorosoro ikou
Come on, it's about time we went too
ikue ni mo kasanaru sekai de toki no nagare ni mi wo makasete
In this stratified world, we entrust ourselves to time's steady flow
kono saki mo itsudemo futari no ayumi wo tsudzukete ikou
Let's walk towards our future, step by step, always just the two of us
eien nante nozomi wa shinai tatoe chippoke demo kamawanai
I don't need an eternity, I'm happy with something small
tashika ni, ima koko ni bokura ga iru koto
But at this very moment, there's no doubt that we are here
sore ga shiawase
And what is happiness but this?