This is a story of love.
Once upon a time, there was
a princess who fell in love.
The one she fell for was the castle's cook,
despite the fact she was royalty, and he a commoner.
Now, this may be beside the point,
but why is it said that people "fall" in love?
Because they plunge into it suddenly,
like falling through a trapdoor?
Oh well, this topic doesn't concern me.
The love they nurtured in secret grew and grew,
and soon, she found she was with child.
Yes—with the realisation of their love.
As illusions start to gain colour and shapes
irodorarete ikeba gensou ga
While they slowly start to become real
katachi aru mono ni naru you ni
I will give them form
egaite yukeru
And grant their wishes
kanaete yukerunda
As the gently blowing wind
yasashiku fuita kaze ga
Stirs the pages of an aged book
furui page mekuru you ni
I may turn back now and then
furikaeru kedo
But rest assured, it will be all right
uun ii no yo
Tales of meeting and parting once more
shiranai koto darake no
All so full of new, yet-unexplored things
deai wakare no hanashi
I gently brushed the words set down in blurry ink
nijimu ink wo sotto nazotta
Where are you going to?
doko iku no
Somewhere just a little far away
sukoshi tooku made
Let the things I left behind turn into dreams
oitekita mono wa yume ni
Choosing what I like best, and in the process
suki dakara erabu erabinagara
Slowly growing into myself
watashi ni natte yuku
"Oh, do let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
"And make it a promise, too!"
yakusoku dakara
You said to me, grinning from ear to ear
anata wa sou hohoenda
"Yes, let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
Linking fingers, we sealed our vow
koyubi no majinai
And as I heard a voice calling to me
dareka no koe ga shite
I opened my eyes
me ga sameta
The Queen With No Subjects
It's utterly in ruins.
Did they wage a war here?
I hadn't heard news of one.
Not a single soul in sight.
Well, now I'm in a pickle.
Even if I headed for another town now, it would be
the middle of the night by the time I reached it.
And that's if I don't freeze solid first.
This is just about the only building
here that's still in one piece.
I don't think anybody's home.
I don't like having to do this, but oh well.
Can't make an omelette without breaking a few eggs.
Pardon the intrusion.
Who might you be?
Ah, that's so much better!
You must have been freezing outside.
You're right there.
But I was honestly surprised to
find anyone living here.
Probably as surprised as I am to have a visitor.
Where did you come here from?
A place very far away from here.
I'm a traveller.
Might I ask your name?
I'm Elaina.
I am Mirarose.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Can you tell me what happened to this city, Mirarose?
I can't, for I don't know.
What does that mean?
I don't know what happened here,
or even how I came to be here.
I opened my eyes and found myself here,
in the middle of a country in ruins.
Are you saying you have amnesia?
That may be so.
Yet you remembered your own name?
"To the one reading this:
You are Mirarose, queen of this land."
Queen?
Well, since you were in a grand room like this
inside a palace, that would make sense.
Oh, yes.
"What you're doing here,
why the country was destroyed,"
"and why you have no memories,
I will reveal by and by."
"Read on if you wish to stay alive."
This is an awfully haughty letter.
The sun has set.
That it has.
"By the way, I presume it's night-time there.
Go to the window and look outside."
Outside?
What in the world is that?
Keep reading.
"The monster you see there is the fiend that
destroyed the country and caused your amnesia."
"It is called the Javalier."
That thing is the Javalier?
This is what the letter says next.
"It wakes with the setting sun and rampages all night,
continuing its destruction until dawn."
"The goal of the Javalier is to slaughter
every last person in the kingdom."
"It will never rest until it finds
the last living soul in the country."
"That is—it's searching for you."
The Javalier is after me.
Then wouldn't it be a good idea
to evacuate to another country?
I'm safe inside the castle.
The Javalier cannot enter.
Why?
I do not know.
And there's more.
"You are now the queen of a country without
subjects, and the Javalier is hunting you down."
"If you try to leave, the Javalier
will pursue you." So it says.
"Finally, I have one request of you.
I want you to kill the Javalier."
"For a witch possessing magic of your calibre,
it should be a simple task to take it down."
"Please, for our sake, for that of your own life,
and for that of all the people who died in agony."
That's all it says.
Oh...
Wait. Mirarose, you're a witch?
Wait. Elaina, you're a witch?
Uh, doesn't one look at me
make that perfectly obvious?
You should definitely have noticed my brooch.
I was only joking.
But still, that letter raises
more questions than it answers.
Why did the Javalier appear here,
and why are you the only one who's
still alive, bereft of your memories?
It doesn't mention any of that.
You're right about that.
But I am the queen of this country,
and the Javalier is ravaging it.
Thus the duty of defeating it falls to me.
Wouldn't you agree?
How many days has it been since
you first saw that monster?
Today marks the seventh.
Have you tried fighting it yet?
No, not yet.
But tomorrow evening I will engage it.
Do you think you stand a chance?
I do, of course.
My, my. You certainly don't lack self-confidence.
It's been a week since I awakened, and I've
finally remembered how to use my magic.
I believe I may have been quite powerful
before losing my memories.
And my magic powers are reaching their peak.
Good luck.
I'll be cheering you on, from a safe distance.
Oh, my. You don't intend to offer any help?
Is there something in it for me if I do?
That thick-headedly honest side
of yours is charming in its own way.
I guess I'll take that as a compliment.
That evening, Mirarose allowed me the use of a room
in what was probably once the servants' quarters.
Now then.
Ooh! It's so fluffy and warm!
I can't thank her enough!
What a wonderful smell...
Good morning...
Good morning! Good timing,
I just took them out of the oven.
What's all this?
It's my baking for the day.
So you can bake.
It would appear so.
Handy in the kitchen for a queen.
I couldn't tell you why, but my body
seems to remember how to do it.
Mysterious, isn't it?
Now come and let's eat while it's hot.
Whoa!
I can't wait to try this!
It's so good!
Glad to hear it.
Would you mind if I go over the plan
for tonight while we eat?
For the fight against the Javalier, right?
I'd like you to help me prepare.
You gave me a bed for the night
and made me breakfast.
Helping out is the least I can do in return.
In that case, how about beating it for me?
Well, I don't know about that...
I figured as much.
For starters, if what the letter said
about you being safe in the castle is true,
don't you have the option of
not fighting the Javalier?
Although I can see how you'd have your doubts
about the credibility of such a fishy letter.
The hatred the writer of that letter bore
towards the Javalier is real.
What makes you say that?
I can feel it.
How bitterly the author hated
the Javalier and wanted it dead.
I can feel the depth of that grudge.
And for whatever reason, I feel the same way.
How is it looking? Think you can finish by nightfall?
B-By the way, at what point
can I consider this "finished"?
Let's see...
Making it twice as deep as it is
right now should do the trick.
That's liable to kill me first.
Mirarose's plan was to lure the Javalier toward the pit,
and then, once it fell in and was
incapacitated, bombard it with magic.
It made sense to me. Even if all it did was prevent it
from fighting back, this was a good strategy.
The only downside was the back-breaking
work necessary to prepare it.
Hah! Th-This is nothing to the Ashen Witch!
You've done well. It won't be long now.
I'll see you later.
Once it's over, I'll treat you to a good supper.
No need.
Preparing a lot of food after strenuous work like
this would be hard on you. I'll handle the cooking.
Just don't get yourself killed.
Don't worry. I don't intend to die.
Off you go.
See you later.
It's time.
It's quite strange, isn't it? I only met her yesterday,
but now I can't stop myself from hoping
she returns safe and sound.
That's why I'm going to fight with her.
With no intentions of dying, either.
Come on! Over here!
Come, Javalier!
There it is.
She did it!
She certainly is quite powerful.
Looks like there's not much
for me to contribute.
Mirarose!
Ah, yes. That's right.
Incredible...
Well?
Do you understand now how deep my despair is?
Goodbye,
Father.
I remember now.
My memories have returned!
Each and every last one!
The princess went to her father, the king,
and told him that she was carrying the cook's child.
This was the king's decree:
"He is to be executed."
He would not permit her to love
someone below her station.
After being subjected to inhuman torture,
the cook was burned alive
right before the princess's eyes.
And our child...
I made a vow then.
That I would kill every last one of them.
I began by making this castle a safe haven
by creating a boundary which only
magic users could pass through.
So that was the reason the Javalier couldn't come in.
Then I wrote the letter for myself to find
and cast a curse over my father
that would turn him into a monster.
The price I paid for the casting
was the loss of my memories.
So it was the Javalier—your father—
who destroyed the city and killed all its people?
Yes.
He tore his own country apart,
retaining his human mind the whole time.
The king's will could do nothing to prevent
the beast's rampage, and all his subjects were—
Even my father couldn't fail to understand
how it feels to lose what you love the most.
The depths of despair.
The bread's all ready. Come, it's time for breakfast.
Let us eat.
How do you like it? Is it good?
Really? I'm so glad!
But it's still no match for the bread you bake, darling!
Would you like some more?
Oh, you silly! You've got jam all over your cheeks.
There ends the story of love,
concluded all according to her plan.
The queen of the country with no subjects,
who had made herself so by her own hand.
As I wander down evening lanes lit by the light of the silvery moon
tsukiakari terasu komichi wo toorinuke
The sweet honeyed poison that hides behind kindness
yasashisa no ura ni kakureta amai doku ni
May it not lead me astray
madowasarenai you
Let me protect those I hold dear
mamoritai mono
Pray, give me that strength
mamoru tsuyosa
Believing that what I seek will one day be within my hands
itsuka kanarazu te ni ireru to shinjite
I'll set off to a brand-new tomorrow
atarashii asu e yuku yo
Crossing over joys and despairs alike
yorokobi mo zetsubou mo koete
Hurrying, ever onward
isogu sono saki e
Simply because I wish to know how I can spin this tale
tada shiritai kara
Of meetings, learning, and choosing my own path
deai manabi erabu michi de tsuzuru
Knitting it all into my very own story
watashi dake no monogatari
And turning to a brand-new page
daremo mita koto no nai
One nobody has ever seen before
sono ichi page wo