"Magic Users Fear For Their Lives:"
"Twenty Years After Defeat,
the Infamous Antique Company Returns"?
The same Antique Company
that's in The Adventures of Nike?
Were they released from prison?
Or is this the work of copycats?
By the way, have you heard what happened?
It's terrible.
They say that awful Antique Company gang
is back and up to no good again.
I thought they'd disappeared years ago!
It's making me fear for my husband.
Do you think the attacks on
magic users will start up again?
I'm so frightened.
This is no time for me to have a fan moment.
I'd really like to avoid a hassle, too.
Perfect! Nobody would possibly
mistake me for a magic user now!
I'm just your average, ordinary peerless beauty!
Now for some sightseeing!
The Two Apprentices
Did you see that?
I'll head to the United Magic Association branch
straight away and get this job over with.
Nothing to it but to hand the chest over
and reap my reward. Couldn't be simpler!
Look! That lady's a witch!
What could she be doing here?
She couldn't have picked a worse time.
Is it my imagination, or are they all staring at me?
Well, no wonder! I mean, look at me! I'm adorable!
Abide a bit there, me lassie.
Hold on! I'm talking to ye!
The lovely little witch lass up there.
Oh? Well, you obviously must be talking about me!
Yes, right ye are.
This town's a dangerous place
as of late, little witch lassie.
Some terrible harm may be lying in wait for ye,
going out in broad daylight dressed that way!
Terrible harm?
Has this town really gotten so dangerous?
Aye, that it has! Ye'd quake from yer toes
to yer pointy hat to hear how bad it's got!
Even my hat, huh?
That sure does sound dangerous!
A youngster like ye may not know,
but there was a time when many a
magic user was waylaid by brigands here.
Each and every one of them
went about shivering in fear!
Be quick about it!
Huh?
Oh, nothing, nothing!
Anyhow, in order to keep yourself safe in
these parts, may I suggest you arm yourself with
one of the implements of personal protection we're
offering here at the Antiqu—I mean, the Curio Company?
I thought so!
I don't want any, so you can
stop with the sales pitch now!
Hold it!
I'm sorry. I didn't get the chest from her.
Tch!
Still as useless a lunk as ever, are ye?
No matter.
Slight change of plan, that's all.
After all, we need only get that chest open.
Shouldn't the branch office
be somewhere around here?
Not good! Is this curtains for me?
Keep your voice down.
This town is a very dangerous place.
Mina? Wow, long time no see!
Uh, so what brings my little sister here?
The Association sent me here
on an undercover mission.
It looks like a local gang of ruffians
is plotting something nefarious.
I haven't managed to infiltrate them yet.
What sort of something nefarious?
How about you? What are you doing here?
I'm here for work, same as you.
Association business!
For the Association? Well, that's just great.
I came to deliver this.
What is it?
Beats me.
The office hasn't said a word to me about this.
For the time being, come with me
to the room where I'm staying.
Oh, I really should deliver this first, plus I'd hate to
impose on you, so I'll get my own room in the inn.
No need to worry about me!
Oh?
Every time you heave a sigh,
away from you does fortune fly!
I know that tearoom!
That has to be where Fura confronted
the Antique Company boss!
Wow!
I wonder which of these tables
is the one where Fura sat?
Wow!
She'll do right nicely.
Are you sure?
She seems like a right twit.
Just the sort who'll open up that chest
with nary a second thought.
Are you listening?
Don't try and do anything, Sister.
Sister?
Where am I?
Wasn't I standing in front of the tearoom just now?
They're planning to rob every jeweller, weaponsmith,
and any other store in town they can.
Is this... a dream?
Guess not.
Sister, are you listening to me?
Excuse me, but who are you?
See, I'm...
This isn't the time to joke around.
I wasn't joking...
and what happened to my voice?
What?
Sister?
Sister, what are you doi—
What is this? Poisonous gas?
Oh?
I was so stunned at this sudden meeting
with my destiny that I forgot to breathe!
Miss Elaina!
Hey, are you all right?
Sis...ter?
Are you feeling sick?
Is it your stomach?
Or a fever?
Do you feel nauseous?
Don't touch me!
Ouch!
U-Um...
Sister...
You're so adorable...
I love you!
Oh, my dear sister, I've loved you for so long!
Do you think that's strange?
But for ages and ages,
you've been the only thing I think about!
Even though you're the older one,
you follow me around like a little puppy.
You're so pathetic, and totally reliant on your
little sister, and that's what makes you so adorable!
You're so cute I can't stand it!
You're so cute, so so cute, so so so cute,
so so so so so cute that it's more than I can bear!
Ahh! You're all I need, my dear, dear sister!
Yet I always treat you so coldly! I'm so sorry!
Sorry that I never made my true feelings known
until now, though I love you so deeply!
I love you so, so, so, so, so, so,
so very much that I could just eat you up!
I really love you so, so, so, so, so, so much!
So please, dear sister,
can't you and I—
No!
Ooh...
Do I even want to know what's going on here?
What are you doing?
Hey, hold on a second!
Wait for me!
Stay away!
Get a hold of yourself!
So long have I loved you!
But I'm in love with your brother!
I love you!
I appreciate the sentiment, but no thanks!
Ah, how I love you!
What happened to you? You're freaking me out!
Wait up!
This is a mite unusual.
And it's probably... no, definitely
happening because I opened that chest.
Ahh! I love you!
Isn't that voice...
No!
Don't be afraid of my love!
I'm so cute! Every single part
of me is simply the cutest!
Th-That's definitely...
I wub yoo!
No mistaking it—that would be me.
...Saya?
Huh?
...Me?
What? What are you talking about?
I have no idea what's going on here!
I demand an explanation for this, Saya!
I don't know any more than you do!
All I know is that when I came to, I found myself
in the adorable form of you, Miss Elaina!
I have no idea what made all
the townspeople go crazy, either!
Oh, that doesn't really concern me.
I know what caused it.
What?!
Anyway, as to why we've switched bodies...
Wait, back up. You know what caused
this to happen to the townspeople?
Let's put that aside for now.
I should have had a chest with me.
What happened to it?
Apparently it was some super dangerous
artefact I wasn't supposed to open, ever.
Wait for me!
Here I am!
You scamp! Wait up!
Don't tell me... you opened it?
Well...
Just a teeny little bit.
Oh, for heaven's sake! What were you thinking?!
Clearly something terrible
was going to happen if you did!
Why didn't my sister stop you?
Your sister?
Haven't you seen her?
A girl with long black hair and
a strangely erotic air to her?
Ahh... yeah, she was there.
You've got dead fish eyes.
Pretty strong family resemblance you two have.
Oh? Do you really think so?
You're pulling my leg!
Please stop. I don't want to see that
drippy expression on my own face.
What? What expression?
Ooh! I just love you!
Would you get away from that window?
No way! I'll never be away from you again, Miss Elaina!
Our first priority should be
putting the town back to normal.
Actually, I guess I should say my first priority.
I'm the reason things ended up like this.
Well, since I'm you right now,
I should do the same thing, right?
I appreciate the thought, but I'd rather
just have you get away from that window.
But what do you suppose was inside that chest?
Rather than magic, it's closer to a curse.
Something like a love potion, I suppose.
Wait up, you big silly!
Do you think they switched us
and then had you open the chest?
Hee hee hee!
Who would rely on such a sloppy plan?
You have a point. That's way too sloppy to be realistic.
Everything went according to the boss's plan!
The United Magic Association totally bought that
fake request, and those dumb witches waltzed right in
and delivered that chest they
confiscated from us right into our hands!
We may not have managed to steal the chest,
but once we switched the witch with that
airheaded girl, she went and opened it for us!
Now the whole town's been turned on its head!
Hurry up and steal all you can!
The effects of that smoke won't last long!
The Antique Company's back in business!
Let's plunder this town for all it's worth!
Come to think of it, your sister did say something
about a gang of ruffians plotting to attack the town.
Could those ruffians be...
The Antique Company has returned, huh?
What's the Antique Company?
In The Adventures of Nike, they—
Never read it!
Well then, forget it!
So, although it was quite sloppy indeed,
that clears up all the mysteries!
I love you!
Uh, sorry. I suppose we got a bit carried away.
No, no, don't worry about it one bit.
You'll tell us where we can find the
Antique Company's leader, won't you?
And after those helpful gentlemen
so kindly told us their leader's whereabouts,
we set off to find her.
But my plan was perfect!
No, it was unbelievably sloppy.
But you sure fell for it, Miss Elaina.
Anyway,
I can't believe I just captured the very same
Antique Company boss as in The Adventures of Nike!
Tch!
Oh, that's right.
We'd like you to put us back to normal.
I have no problem staying like this!
We'd like you to put us back to normal immediately.
Immediately is impossible...
Ye'll go back to normal by tomorrow, probably!
Are you sure about that?
Uh-huh.
However!
However?!
Don't go thinking this means that ye won!
We've got lots of allies on our side!
For every one of us ye caught,
nine more are running free!
While we were having this little chat,
they've already pilfered everything
they could carry and scarpered!
We win! This just ain't yer lucky day!
N-Now what do we do?
Find them, obviously.
Let's split up and—
That isn't gonna be necessary.
Teacher!
M-Master?
Master? Are you talking about Ms. Sheila?
It's been a while, miss snaggletoothed crime boss.
What?
Ye're those apprentice witches from back then, are ye?
Back then?
Dear me. It seems even your snaggleteeth
have fallen out with age. I beg your pardon.
Huh? Huh?
Dear me. It seems even your snaggleteeth
have fallen out with age. I beg your pardon.
Huh? Huh?
Dear me. It seems even your snaggleteeth
have fallen out with age. I beg your pardon.
Huh? Huh?
Dear me. It seems even your snaggleteeth
have fallen out with age. I beg your pardon.
Huh? Huh?
Dear me. It seems even your snaggleteeth
have fallen out with age. I beg your pardon.
Don't worry about the rest of
those Antique Company losers.
We've got their little crime spree well in hand.
Tough luck for you. You lose again.
Again?
Now then, I wonder if you'd mind telling us
how to return the townspeople to normal?
All right...
How come she's unconscious?
Now the townspeople should go back to normal.
Truly a simple task.
So? Why's she unconscious?
About that chest.
Was it an artefact brought here from
a distant land far across the horizon?
It certainly was.
That's my Miss Elaina! You figured it out right away!
It's because of an artefact from that land
that we switched bodies, too, isn't that right?
The smoke inside curses you so that when you see
someone you like, you can't contain your feelings,
and if you see someone
you truly love, you really lose it.
I see!
Who cares about that?
Heh...
Ahem! Miss Elaina.
What is it?
I heard the whole story from my sister.
About how after I left, you taught her about magic,
and then while travelling in
another country, you met again.
She told me all about it,
with the biggest grin on her face!
As I wander down evening lanes lit by the light of the silvery moon
tsukiakari terasu komichi wo toorinuke
Um... so why did you leave Saya behind
in the Country of Magic Users?
The sweet honeyed poison that hides behind kindness
yasashisa no ura ni kakureta amai doku ni
She was really down after that.
Oh, about that,
I wanted her to get in the training
she needed to become a witch right away,
May it not lead me astray
madowasarenai you
so I made her go back to her homeland.
Let me protect those I hold dear
mamoritai mono
It was your idea?
Pray, give me that strength
mamoru tsuyosa
Mina was my apprentice too. Didn't you know?
Believing that what I seek will one day be within my hands
itsuka kanarazu te ni ireru to shinjite
First I've heard of it!
You know how dependent
Saya gets on other people, right?
If she stuck with her sister every waking moment,
it wouldn't do either of them any good.
I'll set off to a brand-new tomorrow
atarashii asu e yuku yo
Crossing over joys and despairs alike
yorokobi mo zetsubou mo koete
I see.
And here I thought Mina went back home by herself
because she'd gotten fed up with Saya.
Hurrying, ever onward
isogu sono saki e
You should have heard how Mina
chewed me out once she got back!
Simply because I wish to know how I can spin this tale
tada shiritai kara
"Why would you tear me and
my sister apart like that?"
Of meetings, learning, and choosing my own path
deai manabi erabu michi de tsuzuru
"I'll never forgive you!"
"I'll curse you for the rest of your life", and so on.
Knitting it all into my very own story
watashi dake no monogatari
Really? Mina said all that?
And turning to a brand-new page
daremo mita koto no nai
How unexpected?
Wait... considering how she acted
yesterday, it's very expected.
One nobody has ever seen before
sono ichi page wo
Huh?
Makes it hard to say who's stuck on who, doesn't it?
P-Please don't say another word!
No! I don't wanna! Don't make me go home!
I wanna stay with Miss Elaina!
Quit your tantrum.
We've got work to do at home! It's time to go!
Fine! Then I'll quit!
How're you gonna earn a living, then?
I won't need to when I'm Miss Elaina's wife!
Oh, that's definitely not happening.
Hear that?
Honestly, Saya, give it up.
That is a seriously hostile look she's giving me!
See you, Fran.
Goodbye. Until next year, then.
Don't wanna!
Don't wannaaaa! Miss Elainaaaaaa!
Well, aren't you popular?
Yes, it seems that way.
Tell me, Elaina.
What is it?
Have you figured it out yet?
Figured what out?
Figured out who my teacher was.
Your teacher? Who was she?
Still haven't learned how to
be frank when it counts, I see.
Can't say I have any qualms about that.
Not like changing a little would hurt now, would it?
I'd like to keep on journeying for a while longer.
There are still quite a few countries I want to travel to.
Going along at my own pace,
doing whatever I want to do.
Once I figure a few more things out...
it feels like my journey will draw to a close.
Even once you learn exactly who
it is that's influenced you so deeply,
I doubt you'll really change all that much.
Do you think so?
Yes, I do.
Did you know?
My teacher seemed like she was always
planning out her every move carefully,
but in actuality, she had a pretty careless personality.
Really?
It's the same sort of carelessness I see in you.
Really?!
So I don't think there's any need to
let a little thing like that trouble you.
But do make sure you go home for a visit, would you?
I will eventually.
Don't forget now.
We're always thinking of you.
And we'll always love you, too.
I love you just as much, Miss Fran,
and everyone else, too.
Take care!
The Adventures of Nike spans five volumes in all.
I'd like my own journey to continue on
much longer than five volumes could capture.
And so,
I set out from the country where Miss Fran
and Miss Sheila first opened up to one another,
and took the first step of
another league of my own journey.
As ever, I remain merely the Ashen Witch,
a traveller, plain and simple.