The Country of Truth-Tellers?
But I don't see it anywhere on my map.
Its name only changed six months ago.
And just like the new name says,
it's now a country where no one can tell a lie.
I see...
The moment a person enters its borders,
they lose the ability to lie.
Not even witches are exempt.
And why is this?
It's because of the mysterious power
within the sword the king wields.
The sword?
The power within that sword
cast a barrier over the entire country that
makes it impossible for anyone within it to lie.
Conversely, I have a hard time believing that's true.
You're already becoming more honest,
eh, honoured witch?
To tell you the truth, I think so too.
So, what do you wish to do? Will you enter?
Let me see.
I'm of two minds, so I keep switching back and forth,
but it seems it would
make for an interesting story,
so I may as well come in and see it myself.
You're an honest one, huh?
Then welcome to the Country of Truth-Tellers.
Welcome to the shithole we call home!
As illusions start to gain colour and shapes
irodorarete ikeba gensou ga
While they slowly start to become real
katachi aru mono ni naru you ni
I will give them form
egaite yukeru
And grant their wishes
kanaete yukerunda
As the gently blowing wind
yasashiku fuita kaze ga
Stirs the pages of an aged book
furui page mekuru you ni
I may turn back now and then
furikaeru kedo
But rest assured, it will be all right
uun ii no yo
Tales of meeting and parting once more
shiranai koto darake no
All so full of new, yet-unexplored things
deai wakare no hanashi
I gently brushed the words set down in blurry ink
nijimu ink wo sotto nazotta
Where are you going to?
doko iku no
Somewhere just a little far away
sukoshi tooku made
Let the things I left behind turn into dreams
oitekita mono wa yume ni
Choosing what I like best, and in the process
suki dakara erabu erabinagara
Slowly growing into myself
watashi ni natte yuku
"Oh, do let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
"And make it a promise, too!"
yakusoku dakara
You said to me, grinning from ear to ear
anata wa sou hohoenda
"Yes, let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
Linking fingers, we sealed our vow
koyubi no majinai
And as I heard a voice calling to me
dareka no koe ga shite
I opened my eyes
me ga sameta
The Country of Truth-Tellers
The Country of Truth-Tellers, hmm?
It looks like a totally ordinary town to me.
First things first, I'll perform a little test
and see whether I can lie.
I'll try and say "I'm not at all beautiful".
Ahem!
I'm not at all...
Not at a...
Not at aaaa—
Aah, I'm incredibly beautiful!
Wow! My lips just started moving and
inadvertently spoke the truth!
It looks like the part about not being able to lie is true!
But I must say, it's a little odd how quiet this town is.
Why doesn't anybody here speak?
That looks tasty.
Are these freshly baked?
I'll take one, then.
Ugh, what is this? It's hard, and all dried out to boot.
I bet it's left over from yesterday.
And to think she nodded when I asked if it was fresh.
"Country of Truth-Tellers" my foot.
Judging from the name,
I expected a country of people
who were honest and pure,
but that certainly doesn't seem to be the case.
The impression it's giving me is awfully cold.
No, maybe "stark"—like a barren wasteland.
What was going on in the king's head
when he made the country like this?
"You're the witch who was dispatched by
the United Magic Association, right?"
No, not me.
The United Magic Association,
in a nutshell, is a mysterious organisation that loves to
stick its nose into anything having to do with magic.
Affiliates of the Association have
moon-shaped brooches, you know.
What just happened?
Would words written on paper
be subject to the same effect?
Is it equally impossible to write
something that's untrue?
"A brand new dessert, now on sale here!"
"It's really the same old one we've
always had, just rearranged a little bit."
"The debut work of a new voice in mystery fiction!"
"'The real mystery is how this boring tripe got published!',
says a best-selling author's review."
My, my.
Let's see. I'll try and write
"I have an incredibly twisted personality".
I have an exemplary personality.
I see. So it's not possible to write anything false, either.
Are you kiddin' me, you jerk? You're one rotten guy!
Big talk coming from a craven coward like you!
You schemin' scoundrel! Why don't you
take a long walk off a short pier?
You contrary son of a bitch! You first!
Excuse the heck outta you!
Oh, dear. I finally get to hear someone speak,
and it's because of a street fight.
You're crazy if you think you have a chance
with a woman that far outta your league!
Says you! She was totally into me!
Excuse me. Isn't anyone going to stop them?
Laugh at me, will ya?!
Get your hands off me!
No way. Watching them helps us blow off steam.
Honestly, I'd rather they really get the claws out!
So that's how it is, huh?
Why is it that nobody in this country ever talks?
Well, because all you can say if you
open your mouth is the honest truth,
and you know where that lands you?
Into fights like this.
Miss Witch, are you stupid or something?
See, this is just one of the many things
we have our stupid king to thank for.
Whoops!
Okay! Stop that right now!
Don't start a fight in broad daylight
in the middle of town, for pity's sake!
Why didn't any of you stop the—
Ehh?
Miss Elaina!
Oopsie! So sorry!
I can't believe you're here, Miss Elaina!
This must be destiny! It has to be!
We have no choice but to get married now!
Uh, I don't know about marriage,
but anyway, it's been a while, Saya.
I'm glad to see you in such high spirits.
Thanks to this hat,
and this precious treasure,
my spirits couldn't be higher!
Uh, isn't that my...
I managed to become a full-fledged witch, too!
That's right, you did. Congratulations.
What did you end up with as your witch title?
The Sooty Witch!
Huh? "Sooty"?
That sounds a lot like the "Ashen" part of my title...
Well, of course!
I asked my teacher to give me a title
as close to "ashen" as possible!
Oh, did you now?
Did you join the United Magic Association?
It sounded like the easiest way
to earn money while travelling.
I'm in this country on business, too.
Business, you say?
That's right! I made a big purchase not too long ago,
so I have to work harder to make a living.
That reminds me. I just met someone who was
looking for a witch from the Association.
What? Who was it?
The request form I got didn't have
a name or address on it.
Not you again, you dunce of a witch!
Get lost already!
Eep! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Let me guess. It's that weirdo over there, right?
It certainly is.
Would you mind letting go of my hand now?
Yes, I would! In fact,
I think I'll leave it right where it is!
You're trying to find the witch
dispatched by the Association, right?
Then I'd like you to meet my good friend, Saya.
Oh, don't be so distant!
We're much closer than friends!
Ah, hello.
"I'm so sorry. I was panicking and forgot to
write down my name or address."
Eyhemia, right? Don't you want to talk?
Or is it that you can't talk?
"For certain reasons, I have lost my voice."
Are you going to write down all of those reasons?
We're going to be here forever, aren't we?
Saya...
Eyhemia told us all about her story.
Or should I say, she wrote all about them.
According to her,
she had been employed as the palace witch until
six months ago, when the king made this request of her.
Eyhemia, the Quicksand Witch.
Use your powers and remove all
who speak lies from these lands.
What?
All my vassals are liars.
I wish to have only those who would
tell the honest truth by my side.
How can I do that?
But if I can be of use to the king, we might even...
Oh, how silly of me!
That's it. I'll put up a barrier
that will stop anyone from lying.
So Eyhemia took some old sword that
happened to be lying around the castle
to use it as a vessel for the magical power
that could create the barrier.
All right.
Ianesana-ha, ianesana-ha.
Ominano motera-do!
But to do this required a very great deal of power.
Ianesana-ha, ianesana-ha.
Eyhemia poured all the magical power
she possessed into it,
Ominano motera-do!
but that still wasn't enough.
So she offered her own voice in exchange,
sacrificing it to create the barrier sword.
Why does everyone leap to offer their voice or
their memories and things like that in exchange?
Huh?
Never mind. Just talking to myself.
Oh? A barrier sword, you say?
"When you hold this sword in your dominant hand,
a barrier that prevents the telling of
any lie will envelop the land."
Is that right?
A country of honest people?
That sounds pretty good!
But wow, is this sword lame or what?
You've got no taste.
I know it's for the barrier and all, but having to
hold this thing is honestly pretty lame.
And that was how the Country of
Truth-Tellers came to be.
Oh, and after she did all that,
Eyhemia was branded useless after losing
her magic and expelled from the palace.
I had no value to him outside of my magical ability...
You were hired as a witch, you know.
What worth would you have to him with no magic?
I still hoped he'd allow me to
stay by his side, though!
You threw all your magic power into it,
and your voice too, for him?
That's pretty heavy stuff!
Do you think maybe that was
a little too much for the king?
I guess you want us to make the country
go back to the way it was, huh?
How do we do that?
All you need to do is destroy the king's sword.
That will restore my magic, as well as my voice, too.
I see. Then should we wait for the king to
leave the palace and get him then?
He'll be holding a speech a month from now.
Miss Elaina!
That means we can share a room
and all our meals for the next month!
Baths, too! And anything else
we might do in the bathroom!
We can even share a bed—
We'll figure out another way!
Getting inside the palace might be the best way.
Hmm... but wouldn't it be awfully hard
to do that if we can't lie our way through it?
It didn't look like we'd have
any luck flying in from above.
It's practically crawling with guards, too.
This is the Country of Truth-Tellers.
Trying to lie our way in is bound to be difficult.
But...
But what?
We'll use that and figure something out.
We will?
Seeing is believing, after all.
What business do you have here?
None are allowed inside the palace
without prior permission from the king.
What are you doing here?
You were thrown out!
Come now.
Saya, hurry and explain the
situation to him, if you would.
Very well.
Ahem.
Mister Guard, can you read what's written here?
"The witch Eyhemia's..."
"...expulsion..."
"...is hereby rescinded."
"The Ashen Witch, Elaina..."
"...and the Sooty Witch, Saya..."
"...will accompany her into the palace..."
"...on the orders of..."
"...the king"?!
Is that really true?
This is the Country of Truth-Tellers, isn't it?
It couldn't possibly be false, could it?
Well, that's true...
May we come in?
Your plan worked like a charm!
No surprise there, Miss Elaina!
Oh, do go on.
It was simple.
I wrote down the sentences
we wanted to say as fragments.
I was able to do so because each
separate fragment, by itself, wasn't a lie.
Then all we had to do was have them read in order,
and we could say anything we wanted.
This must be why they say
the pen is mightier than the sword!
Who says that, exactly?
Which way is the throne room, Miss Eyhemia?
There?
Might you be the king?
Yes. What of it?
Please release that sword.
If you don't—!
Intruders!
What's this? A trio of witches?
Hey, that's Eyhemia! Long time no see!
Man, I don't wanna do this. I'm sleepy!
Hey, that witch may be flat, but she's real cute!
The tomboyish one's more my type!
Sorry to disappoint, but there's already
someone I've given my heart to...
Please don't look at me like that.
Saya, I'll take care of the king.
You do something about the guards.
Leave it to the Sooty Witch, Saya!
I am a noncombatant.
Hand over the sword!
You must be joking!
This is our strongest weapon,
and through it, I guide the country!
As long as it is within my grasp,
I will continue to lead us down the right path!
I'll never release it!
Sorry.
That was mean!
The sword can fire the magical energy stored inside it, so watch out, okay?
It'll really hurt if it hits you!
You could have mentioned that sooner!
Take this!
Did taking away everyone's ability to lie
really benefit your country?
Of course it did!
I'm not sure that's true!
Wh-What did you say?
People with ill intentions can still
do bad things, even if they're unable to lie.
Turning all the citizens of this country into honest people
won't automatically make all of those people good.
Furthermore, you should realise
that not every lie is bad.
White lies help smooth over social interaction
and preserve harmonious
relationships between people.
Take that away, and the citizens will
constantly be at each other's throats.
What are you saying?
If truth is that sword, then there's one
more very important "S" to consider!
Oh?!
No, not you. I meant "scabbard".
You know, for a sword.
You didn't have to lead me on like that!
Excuse me?
If truth is that sword, then lies are its scabbard!
They form a protective cover around it so those
who wield it don't thoughtlessly injure others!
How dare you speak to me that way?
Miss Elaina, there are too many of them!
My brain's close to its boiling point!
Do your best!
All right. Saya's just about had enough,
so let's wrap things up here.
Wrap things up, you say?
It's taking everything you have merely to counter me!
Sorry, but no.
I'm already done preparing to
take that sword from you.
My lame-ass sword!
You did it, Miss Elaina!
Are you saying... that I was wrong?
No, Your Majesty.
Eyhemia!
There was nothing wrong with
your desire for everyone to be honest.
But why don't we try taking a
little more lenient of an approach,
and not worry so much if white lies are told
every now and then for the good of the kingdom?
Fresh-baked bread here!
Catch of the day, right here!
You're a pretty alright guy, you know?
And you're one gutsy dude!
The king acknowledged the error of his ways
and apologised to his countrymen
for making it so that they could not lie.
I don't know whether the country
will return to how it was before,
but Eyhemia was reinstated at the palace,
so I think things will probably turn out all right.
Thank you, honoured witches!
Safe travels!
Um, you know,
it's an Association rule that I need to
do something to thank you for helping me.
I don't need any thanks.
Besides, if you try to follow every rule in the book,
you'll turn into a real stick in the mud.
Still! Please let me thank you!
This isn't much, but...
Ta-dah!
A necklace?
You see,
I spent every last coin I had on this so I could
give it to you when we were reunited!
Thanks to that, I'm broke, which is why
I took the job in that country...
But thanks to that, I saw you again!
This has to be destiny!
Please cherish it like you would me!
Wow, that's kinda heavy.
But thank you anyway.
I'll put it on for you!
Hey, hold on.
Oh, don't be shy!
It looks so nice on you!
Now we match!
I've got to head back to the branch office now.
What about you?
I'm off to another brand-new town.
Where I'm from, this is something people promise on.
Please link your pinky finger with mine.
Let's meet again, somewhere.
I still want to introduce you to my little sister,
and show you what a great witch
I can become between now and then!
It's a promise!
Okay.
I'll be waiting while I continue my travels.
I promise!
As I wander down evening lanes lit by the light of the silvery moon
tsukiakari terasu komichi wo toorinuke
The sweet honeyed poison that hides behind kindness
yasashisa no ura ni kakureta amai doku ni
May it not lead me astray
madowasarenai you
Let me protect those I hold dear
mamoritai mono
Pray, give me that strength
mamoru tsuyosa
Believing that what I seek will one day be within my hands
itsuka kanarazu te ni ireru to shinjite
I'll set off to a brand-new tomorrow
atarashii asu e yuku yo
Crossing over joys and despairs alike
yorokobi mo zetsubou mo koete
Hurrying, ever onward
isogu sono saki e
Simply because I wish to know how I can spin this tale
tada shiritai kara
Of meetings, learning, and choosing my own path
deai manabi erabu michi de tsuzuru
Knitting it all into my very own story
watashi dake no monogatari
And turning to a brand-new page
daremo mita koto no nai
One nobody has ever seen before
sono ichi page wo