The Everyday Tale
of Every Ashen Witch
Let me tell you a story about me.
I am a witch, and a traveller.
My travels have been a series of meetings and partings,
and of decisions to make.
I've made many decisions that can't be reversed,
and doing so has led me to where I am now.
"The Country That Will Grant Your Wishes"?
I wish I were rich!
This is...
Hm?
What's going on here?
This isn't what I wished for...
Isn't that Mirarose's castle?
Stop right there.
Are you a good me, or a bad me?
What on earth is a "bad me"?
Why are there two of me?
And how much did those glasses set you back?
Um, who might you be?
I'm Elaina, the Ashen Witch.
But I'm Elaina,
the Ashen Witch.
I suppose you are.
I'm pretty sure I didn't
wish to meet a second me.
Well, neither did we.
"We"?!
Just how many me's
are there altogether?!
Altogether?
I couldn't tell you.
But we've got fifteen here.
Excuse me, fifteen?!
Settle down, everyme.
Allow me to introduce ourself.
This is the sixteenth me.
Uh, hello.
Wow! Yet another me cosplayer!
I can't have you doing that
without my seal of approval, though!
Just might have to charge you a usage fee!
Ten billion gold coins sounds about fair!
This one's always hyperactive, but mad as
a bag of ferrets, so rather than the Ashen Witch,
we call her the Asinine Witch.
The Asinine Witch...
Whoo! Nicetameetcha!
Over here we have the thickheaded me.
Why hello there, sixteenth me!
Whoopsies! There's nobody there!
Please to meet you!
Whoa!
Ouchie!
Is she just dumb, or a klutz to boot?
This is the me who really likes girls.
Oh my gosh, now there are sixteen of me!
All these me's around me!
Is this what heaven is like?
Does she like all girls, or just herself?
Over here is the me who's bizarrely obsessed
with the size of her breasts.
What? Aren't you supposed to be me?
How come your chest is so
pathetically flat compared to mine?
What's wrong? Haven't been drinking enough milk?
W-Wait for me! Come back, my tits!
Yeah, she's a tit, all right.
The bad-attitude me.
Come back, my tits!
You lookin' at me, punk?
I only see a bunch of other me's here,
so you must be lookin' at me!
Next to her, there's the devious me.
I'll pick the pockets of every last me here,
and then I'll be swimming in riches!
She doesn't seem all that different
from the usual me...
Here's the cringe-inducing me.
Urrgh!
The black dragon of the endless abyss or
whatever sealed within this eye of mine
is threatening to break free!
Everyme, get back!
Here's the me who's a young maiden in love.
Ah, Miss Saya... Miss Saya... Miss Saya!
Why Saya?
Hiding under the table is the me
bearing a heavy darkness in her heart.
I wanna die...
What in the world happened to her?
And there's the me bearing
a heavy darkness in her heart, #2.
Please... Don't make me go outside...
How did that one ever make it as a traveller?
And there's the me bearing
a heavy darkness in her heart, #3.
I can't take it anymore. All these me's should just die...
That's way too grim!
Over there is the me who
pretends to be from a foreign land.
Harasho!
That's weird, for sho'.
The slime me, Miss Gelaina.
Bloop.
Does that one even count as a person?
The me who's a ghoul.
Uh... unh... ungh...
For what purpose?
Finally, there's me, the smart me.
A self-appointed title, huh?
It just so happens to be accurate.
I think we'd better give you a nickname, too.
What do you think we should call me, everyme?
What defining personality traits
does the sixteenth me have?
She don't got none!
She's cosplaying me!
And owes me ten billion gold coins!
Friggin' copycat!
No personality or tits!
No eyepatch or bandages!
Penniless!
Ooh, sixteenth me, ooh!
Wherefore art thou, Saya?
I wanna die...
Me too...
I'm going toward the light...
Harasho!
Bloop!
Gruuungh!
I see. Thanks for my valuable contributions.
I'll take all my opinions into consideration.
...You will?
I believe that settles it.
We'll refer to you as "the protagonist me".
What do you think?
I'd ask you how you got there,
but I have a feeling I don't really want to know.
I took your negative character trait of having
no defining character traits and put a positive spin on it.
I don't really feel happy being told
I have no defining traits, you know...
Why, I think it's a wonderful thing.
If your trait is nothing,
you're capable of becoming anything!
A perfect fit for a protagonist, no?
So what are all you me's doing holed up in this castle?
There is an evil me among us.
A violent me, one who attacks any other me
she comes across with no provocation.
Oh?
As she is so violent, we refer to her as "the violent me".
That's descriptive.
So you're all hiding here in the castle
so you'll be safe from the violent me.
But it's me you're up against, right?
If you take her on, you should at least
be able to fight her to a standstill.
Use your head, protagonist me.
She's also me, so fighting against her
would mean hurting myself.
If that me were to die,
do you know what might happen?
No, can't say I do.
Neither do we!
Nobody knows! That's why
we all came here to talk about it!
Booyah!
What do you think we should do?
Hey, don't ask me.
What are you saying?
You're the protagonist me.
It's your job to take command at times like these.
By the way, it's my job to advise
the protagonist, as chief strategist.
I see. You picked me to be the protagonist
so you could use me, huh?
That's very like me.
If that's how it is...
I command every me to go out and
search the town except for me, myself.
I'll wait here for the rest of me to return!
What's this dum-dum saying? Boo! Hiss!
Resign as the protagonist!
Ooh, I'm so gallant! Ooh!
You got lice for brains?
You flattie!
What's it pay?
My right hand! It can't be stopped!
Ooh, Saya! Ooh!
I wanna go to heaven...
I wanna go back home to mommy...
Satan, take me now!
Harasho!
Urghhhhh!
Blub!
What's your problem? You're the ones
who decided I should be the protagonist!
I can't believe how self-centred I am.
Okay, if any of you me's are so smart—
The ghoul me is dead!
Check out that gore!
I'm a goner for sure!
And the slime me has been squished into slime!
Arooooongh!
Burble!
Oh, I'm alive. Darn...
I'm just glad I'm all right.
So this is where you've been hiding.
That's perfect.
Could that me be...
Indeed she is—the violent me.
I'm going to kill every last one of me.
You, the me over there on the throne.
You're the leader of all these other me's, I take it?
I don't know if I'd call myself a leader,
but they do call me the protagonist me.
Oh yes, I see.
The protagonist me. Got it.
How about you die?
I don't know what makes you
dislike me enough to attack me,
but do you really think you
stand a chance against sixteen of me?
Oh, the slime me and the ghoul me
got squished, so we're down to fourteen.
Do you really think you
stand a chance against fourteen of me?
I'm not from some happy-go-lucky
world like the rest of you.
What do you mean?
Sneaky sneaky sneak sneak!
Have you not looked in a mirror lately,
or are you unaware that you are me?
Whoosh!
Eek!
Not my enormous tits!
I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm scared!
I wanna go home!
Please don't come any closer!
Into darkness!
Take me home!
I-It's a trap! We'll probably be executed now!
Let me return to the earth...
It's so nice and cool here that I feel better.
She's gone?
O-Oh no!
Please, spare my gold!
Y-You punk-ass bitch...
Well? Aren't you going to fight back?
I was observing you.
And what have you learned?
I think I stand a decent chance of beating you.
Well, aren't you full of yourself?
True, though I could say the same of you.
Why is your hair still short?
You should know very well why my hair was cut.
Of course. My hair was cut in the same country, too.
I didn't even have the strength to
return my hair to the way it was.
I wasn't able to save a single person from that country.
You've never been through that, have you?
You've never witnessed the instant
when love changes into hate,
never seen someone who you thought
cared for you look at you like they want you dead!
No, I haven't.
So?
Did the Cutter cut your hair off?
Your journey seems to have taken you
somewhere altogether different than I.
Different?
Yes, very different indeed.
Perhaps completely different.
I knew it. I'm nothing like the rest of you.
Are you now?
Do you mean to tell me you lost the
strength to return your hair to normal
and fell into despair simply because
you saw love turn into hate?
I'll say it again, but I never wished
for anything like this.
It wasn't despair!
It was seething fury!
Oh? At what?
Isn't it obvious? At my own self!
At the other me's, for travelling on
without a care in the world, unlike me,
with so many horrible things happening around me
every day that I couldn't do anything about!
Way to take your anger out
on someone else. That's very like me.
You!
You should just disappear!
Who are you saying that to?
Me? Or yourself?
This is The Country That Will Grant Your Wishes.
I couldn't forgive myself for travelling carelessly on,
never feeling a moment of pain or heartbreak,
and that's why I came here!
Because I wanted every other me to feel this pain too!
But that's your wish, not ours!
Then why are all the rest of me gathered here?!
Don't you understand?
Or are you just pretending you don't?
We hurled spell after spell at each other,
but in magical strength,
we were frustratingly evenly matched.
In the end, even after exhausting all of our power,
we still hadn't settled things.
Why did I come here?
Well, first, let me tell you what
it was I wished for, deep in my heart.
I came here to meet my other selves.
I'm sure I desperately wanted to see all
the other possible paths I could have taken.
Possible paths...
A journey is a series of meetings and partings.
And also a series of decisions.
There were certainly different
decisions I could have made.
Other possibilities.
That's why I came to this country, and why we met.
But...
that still wouldn't explain why I came here.
Yes, it would.
I'm sure you longed to meet
your other selves, just like me.
You were led here because you longed to meet a me
who never went through that tragedy
in the Clock City of Rostolf.
You wished you'd never experienced
something so sad, and that led you here.
It wasn't so we would be hurt.
It was so our pain could be healed.
That's a self-centred way to see it.
Self-centred, you say?
Well, what else, when my selves
are the only ones here?
Won't you let me tell you
about the things I saw in that country,
ten years in the past?
That's the reason I'm here.
Okay.
And that's how we reconciled,
After that, we talked together until night fell.
We returned to the palace,
brought out the diaries we'd kept,
and took turns reading about each other's journeys.
I just had a great idea.
What kind of idea?
We've all been keeping our diaries
so we could tell Mom about our travels,
but what do you think of publishing them?
Publishing?
Yes. As a book like The Adventures of Nike—
no, a book even greater than that.
The story of our adventures!
That's a great idea.
Nice going, protagonist me.
Yeah! Me three!
What a fab idea!
|
A tome of my
dark history... not bad!
Harasho!
Bloop!
Unghgrh!
|
Meow!
Now, what to call it?
The Adventures of Elaina!
That's straightforward.
Let's-a Go! Elaina!
Elaina: For Whom the Lily Blooms!
Enormous Boobs: They're Within Your Reach!
Glaring At Punk-Ass Bitches For Dummies.
How I Stole My Trillions!
Elaina and the Traveller's Diary.
My Lovey-Dovey Days With Miss Saya!
Elaina: The Hell Arc...
Elaina: Knockin' On Heaven's Door!
Don't Make Me Go Outside Ever Again.
Harasho!
Glub: Burble!
Euonnghhhh!
Pardon me, everyme, but we should take this seriously!
After several more hours of this spirited discussion,
at long last, we settled on a title for the book.
Saya!
Ahh, you're so cute...
Harasho...
Saya...
What are you going to do next?
I think I'll go get my hair back.
It's still attached to that doll.
You're kidding.
No, seriously.
Well, the Cutter's already in custody,
so it's just a matter of finding out
where the doll is now.
As illusions start to gain colour and shapes
irodorarete ikeba gensou ga
Thank you, Elaina.
Don't mention it, Elaina.
While they slowly start to become real
katachi aru mono ni naru you ni
Goodnight.
I will give them form
egaite yukeru
Goodnight.
And grant their wishes
kanaete yukerunda
As the gently blowing wind
yasashiku fuita kaze ga
Stirs the pages of an aged book
furui page mekuru you ni
I may turn back now and then
furikaeru kedo
But rest assured, it will be all right
uun ii no yo
Tales of meeting and parting once more
shiranai koto darake no
Huh?
All so full of new, yet-unexplored things
deai wakare no hanashi
Was it a dream?
Wandering Witch
I gently brushed the words set down in blurry ink
nijimu ink wo sotto nazotta
Where are you going to?
doko iku no
Somewhere just a little far away
sukoshi tooku made
Let the things I left behind turn into dreams
oitekita mono wa yume ni
Well, I should get going!
Choosing what I like best, and in the process
suki dakara erabu erabinagara
Now then, who might this lovely young witch be
Slowly growing into myself
watashi ni natte yuku
who would turn the head of anyone
who might see her speeding along
"Oh, do let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
"And make it a promise, too!"
yakusoku dakara
through the clear blue of the sky,
and make them sigh in rapture?
You said to me, grinning from ear to ear
anata wa sou hohoenda
"Yes, let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
That would be the very same girl who travels on,
spinning the story of her own Journey of Elaina—
Linking fingers, we sealed our vow
koyubi no majinai
And as I heard a voice calling to me
dareka no koe ga shite
I opened my eyes
me ga sameta
Why yes, that would be me!
Wandering Witch
S-Sorry! I was totally wrapped up in my writing...
Don't worry about it. Half the fault is mine.
But you ought to keep an eye on where you're going.
Don't limit your own field of view that way.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
Oh...
Well, we could both be a bit more careful.
R-Right!
Wandering Witch
Make Sure You Read This First Thing in the Morning
I didn't know at the time,
but she and I would soon begin travelling together.
Her name was Amnesia.