A witch flew through the sky upon her broom,
her ashen hair fluttering in the wind.
Who might this young witch be,
lovely and perfectly formed as a doll,
possessing such beauty that the summer sun
would burn even brighter upon seeing her?
Why yes, that would be me!
These clothes make for awfully hot
travelling this time of year.
As illusions start to gain colour and shapes
irodorarete ikeba gensou ga
While they slowly start to become real
katachi aru mono ni naru you ni
I will give them form
egaite yukeru
And grant their wishes
kanaete yukerunda
As the gently blowing wind
yasashiku fuita kaze ga
Stirs the pages of an aged book
furui page mekuru you ni
I may turn back now and then
furikaeru kedo
But rest assured, it will be all right
uun ii no yo
Tales of meeting and parting once more
shiranai koto darake no
All so full of new, yet-unexplored things
deai wakare no hanashi
I gently brushed the words set down in blurry ink
nijimu ink wo sotto nazotta
Where are you going to?
doko iku no
Somewhere just a little far away
sukoshi tooku made
Let the things I left behind turn into dreams
oitekita mono wa yume ni
Choosing what I like best, and in the process
suki dakara erabu erabinagara
Slowly growing into myself
watashi ni natte yuku
"Oh, do let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
"And make it a promise, too!"
yakusoku dakara
You said to me, grinning from ear to ear
anata wa sou hohoenda
"Yes, let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
Linking fingers, we sealed our vow
koyubi no majinai
And as I heard a voice calling to me
dareka no koe ga shite
I opened my eyes
me ga sameta
The Cutter
Well, this is creepy.
You know why I called you here.
Tell me what you know about those incidents.
If you've got any information, let's hear it.
Oh, my poor little Bébé! Your shoe's about to fall off!
Incidents? Oh, you must mean—
The people of this country sure love their dolls.
This is all because of that.
I just knew that was behind it!
The Association is taking the investigation
of this matter very seriously.
I'd also like to ask for your cooperation
to return public order to this town.
She's from the United Magic Association?
I put a brand-new outfit on my doll today!
What do you think?
Ooh, it's lovely!
What a cute dress! Where did you buy it?
I guess something's been happening here.
It was pricey, but I decided it was worth the splurge!
Lucky you. My doll's still wearing last year's fashions!
What about you?
Have you seen this Cutter around?
Hmm? Cutter, huh?
No, I haven't seen a thing.
But I do know that the lives of four women
were taken by the Cutter's knife!
There was another victim just this morning.
A woman with green hair this time.
A fifth victim?
And that's just the fifth this year.
Counting other similar incidents in the past,
there have been over a hundred attacks.
The lives of over a hundred women?
My, that sounds scary.
What about you?
Yes! I saw the Cutter!
Tell me everything!
It happened seven years ago,
on a night when the moon was full.
I saw a man transform into a werewolf, and—
Uh, no.
That's not it! The culprit is a woman
who turns into a werecat!
It's not a man or woman, it's some strange lifeform!
My cousin's friend's boyfriend's
girlfriend told me all about it!
Excuse me, who?
What are you talking about?
The one doing this is a doll!
It comes to life at night and attacks any woman
unlucky enough to cross its path! Oh, I can't take it!
I'm going home and locking all the doors and windows!
Well, this seems like trouble all right.
Hey, you. Hold it right there.
Yes?
How may I help you?
You from around here?
No, I'm a traveller.
I'm the Midnight Witch, Sheila.
As you can see, I'm with the United Magic Association.
I am the Ashen Witch, Elaina.
Do you know anything about the incidents
that have been going on around here?
Are you talking about the Cutter?
Yes, I've heard of that.
Mind telling me why a traveller
like you would know that?
I overheard you talking to the townspeople
about it just now, Ms. Sheila.
Unfortunately, I don't know anything beyond that.
Dang, that's unfortunate.
These people sure don't have a clue.
It's nothing but a load of nonsense with them.
Come straight to me if you uncover any clues.
You can find me at the meeting hall over there.
I doubt that will happen, but all right.
Goodbye, then.
I know they may be this place's claim to fame, but I
can't get used to being surrounded by all these dolls.
"Free dolls for everyone!"?
This is incredible.
Welcome to my shop!
Did that doll just—
Every doll here was handmade by me!
I can see your mouth moving, you know.
See one you like? If so, please do take it with you!
Is it true you don't charge anything?
Yes!
Really?
When this is such a shabby—I mean, modest shop?
Really!
What I really want isn't money!
It's just to see happy smiles on everyone's faces!
That's why I make lots and lots of dolls
and give them to all the people in town!
My. That's very impressive.
Please take whichever doll you like, Miss Magician!
Uh, "magician" isn't quite...
Don't be shy, now! Pick out any one your heart desires!
Why, how about this one?
That's my most popular model these days!
Well, then...
A doll would only add to the things
I have to carry, so I think I'll pass.
Thanks for the thought, and do excuse me.
What a pity.
She really didn't want to accept any money
for her dolls. What a charitable soul.
Here you are. You'll be in Room 5, on the third floor.
Thank you!
There's even one in here, hm?
That should do it!
Now then.
"Everywhere you turn in this country,
there are dolls upon dolls."
"It's not as pleasant a sight as it might sound..."
Ugh, hot...
Ah, that feels so nice!
Hm? I don't remember opening the window...
Ah, never mind.
All right. First comes breakfast,
and after that, I'll head off to...
my next... destination?
Who might this be?
Have you seen this Cutter around?
The lives of four women
were taken by the Cutter's knife!
"A woman's hair... is her life..."
Well, you're right. This is the Cutter's
handiwork, no doubt about that.
I'd say that's rather obvious!
I guess even a witch of your stature
can fall prey to the Cutter.
Right then. Let me have a look
at the scene of the crime.
What do you want me to do?
You can continue to lie there like a bump on a log.
Hmm. I don't see anything.
Nothing suspicious under the bed, either.
By far the most suspicious thing in this room is you!
Hey now, don't call me suspicious.
I'm trying to investigate here.
All that's left now is...
to look in there.
Is that the doll's hair?
What doll?
There was a doll sitting beside
the bed, but I put it in here.
Just as I thought.
What is?
These incidents are starting to form a pattern.
All of the victims have been attacked in their sleep.
The dolls inside their rooms went missing.
And remnants of doll hair were left behind each time.
Why?
My theory is that the victims' hair
is being turned into hair for dolls.
For dolls?
The culprit's probably controlling the dolls with magic.
So what are you going to do now?
What do you mean?
Wanna come with me and investigate?
I certainly do!
I intend to catch this cowardly culprit,
see their head chopped off for their crimes,
and give them time to repent in hell!
Don't get ahead of yourself.
What is it?
Um...
I couldn't help but notice how flat you are, that's all.
Let's be on our way.
What's your name again?
Weren't you listening when I told you?
It's Elaina! The Ashen Witch.
Oh.
Oooh.
Oh?
Nothing. Let's go.
Have a pleasant day!
What is it?
Doesn't that doll's hair
look awfully high-quality to you?
I guess so.
It looks fine enough to pass for human hair.
Tell me where you got the doll
and I won't have to hurt you.
I knew it! This is definitely human hair!
Spit it out!
I won her in the black-market auction!
Did you say black-market auction?
Yes!
They always have special dolls like my Little Miss A!
"Little Miss A"? Ick.
Where's the auction held? Fess up!
The place the black-market auction
is held is right up ahead.
These masks barely hide our faces.
Anyone can tell who we are, you know.
Creating the proper atmosphere is key.
Don't you feel like you're doing something
really naughty if you're wearing a mask?
Attending a black-market auction certainly
counts as naughty, don't you think?
Killjoy.
It feels like we're at the opera.
That's because this building
was an opera house at one point.
I'm going to win that doll today no matter what,
so my Little Lord Masa can have a girlfriend!
Gonna win for sure! Gonna win for sure!
I saved up every penny I have for today,
and I'm not going home until I win!
Ah, my adorable little angel!
This crowd sure is fired up.
How can anyone go this crazy over a few dolls?
Can't say I get it either.
The thrill of buying illicit merchandise that
can't be obtained through normal means, maybe.
And now, the moment
you've all been waiting for.
We've got another packed lineup
of fabulous items on offer today!
For the right price, any of them can be yours!
You want them, don't you?
Let's get things started.
Our first lot of the evening!
When you said "illicit merchandise", did you mean...
I see, I see.
Fifty!
One hundred!
One hundred! Do I hear anyone else?
One-fifty!
Three hundred!
Sold for three hundred!
Yeah!
Is the whole auction going to be dolls like that?
On to our next lot!
Ladies and gentlemen, feast your eyes!
No, I don't think so.
Now for our next lot!
I certainly do think so.
And our third lot!
Maybe we should go home.
Ladies and gentlemen, you've waited very patiently.
Now for tonight's featured lot.
Oh, is this it?
That doll with the grey hair!
It looks almost exactly like
the one that was in my room!
No, it is the same doll—and that's my hair!
Feast your eyes, everyone!
See the lifelike hair on each one of these dolls?
Real human hair was used!
All from the victims, no doubt.
Down, girl.
Take a good look at these beauties!
You can see how every detail,
from the clothes to the hair,
How dare they? Whoever did this will pay with their life!
Settle down.
is a cut above the other dolls!
The bidders don't know where the raw
materials come from. They're not at fault.
And that's not all!
They're the handiwork of none other than the one
who's got the whole country in an uproar, the Cutter!
What do you say? Amazing, aren't they?!
Goddammit. Okay, forget everything I just said.
Then let's start the bidding!
Wh-What happened?
Look at her hair! It's the same colour as the doll's!
Could it be?!
Every one of you is an enemy of womankind!
The only fitting punishment
for your wrongdoing is death!
You're here, aren't you, Cutter?
Kindly show yourself.
Oh, you won't? I see.
I'll continue.
Please stop!
I can't bear to watch!
That's quite enough.
I'll ask you not to be so mean to my poor little dolls.
So it was you.
Yep! It was me all along!
Know what I thought when you came into my shop?
"What lovely hair she has!"
I see what you said about
not wanting money was a lie.
You prefer to make it through
these auctions, is that it?
No, no. I truly don't want money!
I donate everything I make from
the auctions to the less fortunate, too!
Then why would you do this?
Think of the sorrow the women
whose hair you cut off felt!
"I want to see happy smiles
on everyone's faces?" Hah!
You see...
See what?!
It's true I wanted to see happy, smiling faces!
My special edition dolls make
all the bidders here so happy,
and the money I earn makes
the people I donate it to happy too!
Nothing's better than a happy face!
Except for a sorrowful face! That's just as great!
Or an enraged one!
Or a laughing face! They're all wonderful!
All the emotions that humans
can feel are so delightful to see!
Ooh, I can hardly stand it!
That angry face of yours really does it for me, too!
Uh, okay. That's enough of that.
Surrender quietly.
Guess what, Miss Magician? I'm a witch!
I'm afraid you're just no match for me!
Why, I'm a witch as well.
Huh?
Unfortunately for you. You're finished.
Well then.
Thanks, Elaina. That was some nice teamwork.
You're ever so welcome.
What is this? What are you doing?
You're angry, right?
Get even angrier!
And let me see it!
Noooo! I wanna see your face!
And thus, we solved the case
and the culprit was delivered to
the United Magic Association
in the custody of the Midnight Witch, Sheila.
They really ought to execute her.
Right. I'm going to go turn you in
and collect the bounty.
Will getting the bounty make you happy?! It will, right?
Show me that joy on your face!
Teacher! Is that you?
Well, look who we have here.
I just arrived!
I was running low on funds,
so I hoped they'd have a job for me.
What's up with her?
She's looking at me with
a disturbing twinkle in her eye.
So cute! Your angry face has to be even cuter!
Oh, this? Well, you see...
Believe it or not, that's the Cutter who's been
going around cutting off women's hair.
She's such a fiend she even managed to
claim the hair of a wandering witch!
Huh. The hair of a wandering witch?
She wore a hat just like yours,
and a necklace that matched yours, too.
And she had lovely grey hair!
A grey-haired...
wandering witch...
I don't know who you are, but I can see
that you're nice and angry!
Mind filling in a few details for me?
Ooh,
that angry face is great!
Truly amazing!
As I wander down evening lanes lit by the light of the silvery moon
tsukiakari terasu komichi wo toorinuke
The sweet honeyed poison that hides behind kindness
yasashisa no ura ni kakureta amai doku ni
May it not lead me astray
madowasarenai you
Let me protect those I hold dear
mamoritai mono
Pray, give me that strength
mamoru tsuyosa
Believing that what I seek will one day be within my hands
itsuka kanarazu te ni ireru to shinjite
I'll set off to a brand-new tomorrow
atarashii asu e yuku yo
Crossing over joys and despairs alike
yorokobi mo zetsubou mo koete
Hurrying, ever onward
isogu sono saki e
Simply because I wish to know how I can spin this tale
tada shiritai kara
Of meetings, learning, and choosing my own path
deai manabi erabu michi de tsuzuru
Knitting it all into my very own story
watashi dake no monogatari
And turning to a brand-new page
daremo mita koto no nai
One nobody has ever seen before
sono ichi page wo