Magic users exist in great numbers in our world.
You can broadly lump them together
under the title of "magic users",
but they can be further divided into the categories
of magicians, who can only use simple magic,
novice witches,
and at the top, full-fledged witches, renowned by all.
Now then, who might this beauty be,
wearing a witch's brooch as proof of her mastery,
ashen hair flowing in the wind,
overflowing with beauty so dazzling
and talent so brilliant
that the sun itself would
shield its eyes if she drew near?
Why yes, that would be me!
As illusions start to gain colour and shapes
irodorarete ikeba gensou ga
While they slowly start to become real
katachi aru mono ni naru you ni
I will give them form
egaite yukeru
And grant their wishes
kanaete yukerunda
As the gently blowing wind
yasashiku fuita kaze ga
Stirs the pages of an aged book
furui page mekuru you ni
I may turn back now and then
furikaeru kedo
But rest assured, it will be all right
uun ii no yo
Tales of meeting and parting once more
shiranai koto darake no
All so full of new, yet-unexplored things
deai wakare no hanashi
I gently brushed the words set down in blurry ink
nijimu ink wo sotto nazotta
Where are you going to?
doko iku no
Somewhere just a little far away
sukoshi tooku made
Let the things I left behind turn into dreams
oitekita mono wa yume ni
Choosing what I like best, and in the process
suki dakara erabu erabinagara
Slowly growing into myself
watashi ni natte yuku
"Oh, do let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
"And make it a promise, too!"
yakusoku dakara
You said to me, grinning from ear to ear
anata wa sou hohoenda
"Yes, let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
Linking fingers, we sealed our vow
koyubi no majinai
And as I heard a voice calling to me
dareka no koe ga shite
I opened my eyes
me ga sameta
The Country of Magic Users
Welcome to the Country of Magic Users!
Please proceed, honoured witch.
You're not gonna ask me for my documentation?
There's no need. Only magic users are
able to come here in the first place.
That brooch you're wearing
certifies your status as a witch,
Miss Ashen Witch.
I see! Well, don't mind if I do!
As its name suggests, only those with magical abilities
are permitted to enter the Country of Magic Users.
This is why, as rumour would have it, witches at the top of
the magical hierarchy are especially revered here.
They're the envy of all, and are
treated like royalty everywhere.
I've really been looking forward
to visiting this country!
So flying is the preferred way of getting around here?
What a charming town.
First things first, I should go find myself an inn—
Ouch! Ouch!
Who might this girl be?
Uh, are you all right?
O-Oh no, what do I do?
There's no way I can mend this many tiles!
How about you make amends
by apologising to me first?
I'm sorry! I'm really, really sorry!
Are you all right?
I'm perfectly fine, but how about you?
Huh?
Oh, I'm all fine and dandy!
In fact, I'm in tip-top shape, as you can see!
Here.
Eh?!
But...
I'll mend the roof, so you should go rest for a moment.
No, no! I'll help you!
Don't worry about it!
But—!
Okay.
Ooh, ouch!
Time-reversing magic!
That should do the trick.
Wow!
Now it's your turn.
Huh?
Whoa! It's healing already!
Incredible!
To a witch, this is nothing.
Goodbye then.
E-Excuse me!
Be sure to watch where you're going
when you're in flight!
P-P-Please wait!
Won't you let me make it up to you, honoured witch?
I'll be going now. Take care, nameless magician.
Now, where was I? Oh yes, an inn.
That place looks splendid.
"Please choose our establishment for your stay, o honoured
witch! Your presence is all the payment we need!"
Oh, whatever would I do if they said that?
Please leave. We have no lodgings to offer you.
What?
We beg your pardon, young miss,
but please try another inn more appropriate for you.
What on earth?
What in the earth and heavens is going on here?
Far from treating me like royalty,
inn after inn turned me out like a beggar.
This is the only inn in
the whole town I haven't tried yet.
Fortunately, I doubt a shabby place
like this will be too fussy.
At least, I really hope so...
Good afternoon to... you?
Oh! It's you again! I-I-I'm so very sorry!
Are you here for retribution? Oh, you must be!
Please, spare my life! I beg you!
Um...
Y-You're gonna tear me limb from limb
starting at the shoulder, is that it?
No!
I only came looking for a room for the night.
Huh?
Oh, is that all?
You sure saved me
the trouble of finding you!
What?
Please write down your name in our register!
I really am sorry about before, Miss Elaina.
I wanted to apologise to you properly, but...
How do you know my name?
It's right there.
Ah, right, right.
Well, my name is Saya!
Is there anything at all I can do to thank you?
Let me see...
Well, it would be very nice if you'd
give me a discount off the witch rate.
Certainly! Consider it done!
Then allow me to take your luggage up for you!
Your room will be—
What?
It's gone...
It's gone.
How could my brooch have gone missing?
That's why the other inns turned me out
instead of fussing over me.
Miss Elaina!
I don't see it over here either!
We've searched every nook and cranny,
and there's still no sign of it?
Oh, Miss Fran...
How could I have lost the brooch you gave me?
What are you doing in my room?
I've been waiting here to ask you
for a very important favour, Miss Elaina.
I'm fairly sure that door was locked.
I don't just sit at reception for show, you know!
That doesn't give you the right
to sneak into your guests' rooms!
How mean!
So? What's this favour?
Oh! I almost forgot!
Please, honoured witch!
Teach me the secrets of how to pass
the novice witch exam!
First, would you tell me what
you're doing crouching on the floor?
This is a tradition where I'm from!
It's called dogeza!
"Dogeza"?
You come from a place with
some unusual traditions, I see.
But I can tell how sincere you are.
Go on and tell me about your circumstances.
Okay!
I have a younger sister.
That's her. Adorable, right?
Sure.
We come from a country
in the east, very far from here.
She and I travelled here to become novice witches.
Far from here?
We both worked here to save up money
while we took the exam... again and again.
But neither of you rose above the level of magician?
Is your sister out right now?
The last time she took the exam, she passed.
Then she went back home by herself.
Having your cute little sister
surpass you was bothering you,
so you thought you'd ask
the witch you ran into for help.
Does that about sum it up?
Well, when you put it like that...
When is the next exam being held?
One week from today.
A week?
Well, I suppose I wouldn't mind
helping you out while I look for my brooch.
Thank you so much!
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
I'll be forever in your debt! Thank you!
And that's how I became Saya's teacher.
Teacher...
It has a nice ring to it!
For a magician to be promoted to a novice witch,
they must first pass a written exam.
If I may say so myself, that part isn't so bad
as long as you know the material.
Where it gets difficult is the practical exam.
Candidates have to endure
a long flight on their brooms
while attacking each other
with non-fatal offensive spells.
Only the last witch standing will pass
and be granted the title of novice witch.
I sure am glad I never have to take that exam again!
I'll be frank with you, Saya.
As you are right now, your odds of
passing the exam are close to zero.
You don't have to be that blunt about it!
However, as close to it as they may be,
the odds are still above zero.
That means I have a chance, right?
First things first, I'll teach you how to handle
a broom as well as I do, if not better.
Really? That sounds awfully tough!
Don't go getting cold feet now!
Do you want to fail the exam right out of
the gate because you fell off your broom?
Now we'll move on to manoeuvring.
Shift your weight correctly and
let me see a nice, sharp turn.
Yes!
Next is sudden braking and acceleration.
Force the broom to come to a stop
using your entire body,
and then move like you're
kicking the air and go right back up.
Yes!
Next, let me see you perform
an aerial dismount.
Let go of your broom in mid-air,
then call it back to you using magic.
I'll catch you if things get dicey,
so don't worry and just go for it.
Yes!
Saya learned how to control her broom
as well as I could in no time at all.
Look what you can do when you try.
I wonder if this is how a mother feels
when she's teaching her child to fly.
Still...
If she's learning the ropes this fast,
just what was she up to before now?
You practised hard again today.
Now let's eat up.
Mmm! It's delicious!
I'm glad you like it!
Who snuck this in here?
You don't care for mushrooms?
I hate them! I mean, they grow out of trees!
So this is no different than eating a tree!
No way am I eating any trees! No thanks!
You'll never become a witch
so long as you're so picky.
Huh?
A novice witch has to be able to endure a lot,
including food she doesn't like.
Are you serious?
Very much so.
So I want you to eat these, too.
As part of your training.
Wha—wait, no—
That's so many...
Using wind magic,
shake down the fruit from that tree.
Give it a try.
Yes!
You need to have good control of offensive magic.
I'll let you in on a somewhat underhanded—
I mean, rather clever trick I used
when I was taking the exam.
I used wind magic to change
the direction of the air currents
and make things harder for the other candidates.
It works better than you'd think.
Wow! That's so like you, Miss Elaina!
Not sure if I appreciate that remark,
but that aside, give it another shot.
Okay!
Like this. Let your body remember it.
M-My body?
That's the way. Hold it gently.
Please do be gentle...
Okay, let's do it.
Okaaaugh!
Wind magic!
What's this?
And so I spent several more days like that.
In between training Saya,
I spent the time searching for my brooch.
I can't find it anywhere.
Oh, I saw your witch's brooch all right.
And where might that have been?
Please tell me, lovely village lady!
I've been getting so forgetful these days, you see...
My, my, what have I here?
I remember now!
This is what I saw—
Come in.
Um, Miss Elaina.
What is it?
W-Would you mind if I sleep with you?
The bed's not very big.
Sorry about that. It's a cheap inn.
I didn't mean it as a complaint.
No, I don't suppose I mind.
Hooray!
You've improved a lot.
Enough to hardly need my help anymore.
Huh?
That's not true!
There's still so much I want you to teach me.
I'm a traveller. I'll be leaving this
country behind before long.
But while you're here,
we'll spend that time together.
Please keep teaching me all kinds of things.
This conversation is pointless, Saya.
Huh?
So would you mind returning my brooch now?
You were far too quick to improve.
I almost thought it was because
I'm such a good teacher, but that's not the case.
You were already perfectly capable at flying.
You told me you came from
a country far away from here.
How would you have gotten here
if you were no good on a broom?
After what the old lady told me,
everything suddenly made sense.
Saya, you...
Okay.
This isn't the way to get someone to stay with you.
I was so lonely.
I'm not your sister.
I know that!
But...
I wanted someone to be with.
Being alone makes me feel so awful and frightened,
so I—
Hey.
Ouch!
What was that for?!
That's no excuse.
Everyone is alone when they're giving everything
they have to accomplish something.
You have to be alone for that.
Trying to pal around won't get you anywhere.
I know fighting battles by yourself
is hard, and it's frightening.
Believe me, I understand that well.
So here.
What's this?
It's for you.
You'll be fine with this little part of me
by your side. Even if you're alone.
But this is your hat, Miss Elaina!
Don't worry about that.
That's my spare.
We'll match now.
From now on, you'll be on your own.
But you won't be lonely.
I'll be watching over you, just like your sister.
I won't charge you for your room, Miss Elaina!
I'll take it out of my pay!
For weeks, if I have to!
I spent my last night in this country with Saya.
I comforted her while she blubbered like a child,
taught her my secrets for acing the practical exam,
listened to her stories about her sister,
and told her about my own journey.
Saya looked to me somehow
ephemeral lying there, and so fragile.
Almost as though I were looking at my long-ago self.
Six months passed.
I travelled on to somewhere new,
far from the Country of Magic Users.
The latest candidate to pass
the novice witch's exam, hm?
An account of her days of toil and
her future full of hope was written there,
as were mentions of her younger sister,
and of a certain traveller she had met
who gave her the strength to carry on
by herself, as well as a witch's hat.
Of how she'd become a novice at last.
And, finally:
"After I become a full-fledged witch, I'm going to go
see a traveller who's very important to me!"
I'll enjoy waiting for that day
as I continue my travels, Saya.
As I wander down evening lanes lit by the light of the silvery moon
tsukiakari terasu komichi wo toorinuke
The sweet honeyed poison that hides behind kindness
yasashisa no ura ni kakureta amai doku ni
May it not lead me astray
madowasarenai you
Let me protect those I hold dear
mamoritai mono
Pray, give me that strength
mamoru tsuyosa
Believing that what I seek will one day be within my hands
itsuka kanarazu te ni ireru to shinjite
I'll set off to a brand-new tomorrow
atarashii asu e yuku yo
Crossing over joys and despairs alike
yorokobi mo zetsubou mo koete
Hurrying, ever onward
isogu sono saki e
Simply because I wish to know how I can spin this tale
tada shiritai kara
Of meetings, learning, and choosing my own path
deai manabi erabu michi de tsuzuru
Knitting it all into my very own story
watashi dake no monogatari
And turning to a brand-new page
daremo mita koto no nai
One nobody has ever seen before
sono ichi page wo