"Because the people of the eastern side of the country
and the people of the western side of the country
did not get along,
they decided to build a wall right down the middle,
so that they would never have to
associate with each other again."
It's a pretty dull sight, isn't it, Ms. Witch?
What might you mean by that?
The people on this side of the wall and the ones
on the other side really can't stand each other.
But even so, this wall we put up
makes for an awfully dull view.
I see.
We don't want to lose face to
that rabble on the other side.
It would be nice if we could boast that, dull as it is,
our side of the wall is better than theirs.
Do you have any suggestions, Ms. Witch?
I might have an idea or two.
Tell me, Mister Minister,
have you got a knife on you?
Yes, I do, but...
What are you planning to do with it?
Why, this.
"This side of the country is truly splendid."
This side of the country is truly splendid.
Signed, A Wandering Witch
"Signed, A Wandering Witch."
What is this supposed to be?
This wall stands for the separation of
the two halves of the country.
At the same time, it's also a symbol
of how wonderful your half is.
Well...
You should invite travellers who pass through
to inscribe messages on the wall.
The more messages accumulate, the clearer
it will become how great your side is.
I can't say I care much for that method.
Oh, that reminds me,
the wall on their side already had
inscriptions from lots of travellers.
"I then went to the other side of the wall,
Oh, come to think of it, the wall on their side
already had inscriptions from lots of travellers!
What?!
and told them the very same story."
This side of the country is truly splendid.
Signed, A Wandering Witch
"So, on that very day,
the custom of having travellers to that
country inscribe the wall was established."
As illusions start to gain colour and shapes
irodorarete ikeba gensou ga
While they slowly start to become real
katachi aru mono ni naru you ni
I will give them form
egaite yukeru
And grant their wishes
kanaete yukerunda
As the gently blowing wind
yasashiku fuita kaze ga
Stirs the pages of an aged book
furui page mekuru you ni
I may turn back now and then
furikaeru kedo
But rest assured, it will be all right
uun ii no yo
Tales of meeting and parting once more
shiranai koto darake no
All so full of new, yet-unexplored things
deai wakare no hanashi
I gently brushed the words set down in blurry ink
nijimu ink wo sotto nazotta
Where are you going to?
doko iku no
Somewhere just a little far away
sukoshi tooku made
Let the things I left behind turn into dreams
oitekita mono wa yume ni
Choosing what I like best, and in the process
suki dakara erabu erabinagara
Slowly growing into myself
watashi ni natte yuku
"Oh, do let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
"And make it a promise, too!"
yakusoku dakara
You said to me, grinning from ear to ear
anata wa sou hohoenda
"Yes, let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
Linking fingers, we sealed our vow
koyubi no majinai
And as I heard a voice calling to me
dareka no koe ga shite
I opened my eyes
me ga sameta
The Wall That Travellers Inscribe
Why did she say that travellers
should do inscriptions in the wall?
Let me see.
Perhaps it was something like a popularity contest.
Why?
Each side wanted to be able to claim that
they were better than the other side.
"See how many more messages
praising us there are?", like that.
Oh...
So which side was better?
Which wall had the most inscriptions?
You'll have to go see for yourself.
Okay!
When I'm a witch and I go on my own journey, I will!
Wow! This is incredible!
"This country is the best!"
"Greatest place I've ever visited!"
"Next time we're here, we're getting married!"
"Travel buddies forever!
Our friendship's stronger than this wall!"
This country is just as splendid
as our muscles.
Pardon me.
You must be from the United Magic Association.
The Sooty Witch, Saya, at your service.
I'd heard stories about this, but they
don't do the real thing justice!
A record of the vast number of people
who've visited, right before your eyes!
As we said in the request, Ms. Witch, we'd like you
to please do something about this wall.
Do something about it?
It hasn't been drawing in crowds like it once did
back when we started letting
travellers inscribe the wall
on advice of a wandering witch many decades ago.
We need to come up with something new.
Something new, huh...
I think this wall is pretty awesome
just the way it is, but...
A wall that travellers inscribe. Hmm...
Hmm? Travellers?
Hey, mister! Let me borrow a knife!
Uh, certainly.
...I love you, Miss Elaina. I love you, Miss Elaina.
I love you, Miss Elaina. I love you, Miss Elaina.
Miss Elaina, Miss Elaina, Miss Elaina,
Miss Elaina Miss Elaina Miss Elaina Miss Elaina...
What do you think you're doing?
Miss Elaina, Miss Elaina, Miss Elaina, Miss Elaina—
Our wall is not the place for your obscene graffiti!
What do you think you're doing, stopping me?!
This is really important stuff!
What are you talking about?
This wall is here for travellers to write
about how splendid our country is!
Oh yeah, that. How about changing that rule?
What?
From this day forth, let the people of
this country leave their own inscriptions!
Like their passionate feelings for
the one they cherish the most,
or their hopes for the future,
or how much I love Miss Elaina!
Why should we do that?
Because
you're the ones who built this wall, after all!
That means it exists for you, right?
It's not just for the travellers!
Make it into a wall you can enjoy looking at every day!
Now I get it.
Thanks for this.
I'll be going, then.
All right.
I've got a request from the
other side of the wall to answer!
What might be the reason for the anticipation
that was making my heart swell that day?
See you!
Why, because that was the day I was at last going to
visit a place from my beloved Adventures of Nike,
the country of the wall inscribed with words.
It's gone!
Step right up! We've got wall for cheap!
Makes a lovely souvenir!
This is no ordinary rubble!
It's rubble from the famous wall!
No, it's definitely ordinary rubble.
Hello, wandering witch!
It's been decades!
You know who I am?
Hm?
Her face looks a lot younger than it did before.
You're right!
And now that I look closer,
her bosom's not like it was then, either.
You're right!
Drat. I guess she's just a stranger after all.
What a pity.
Excuse me. You seem to be ministers from this country.
Or perhaps I'm mistaken,
and you're just two withered old men?
You're right, we are ministers.
But you're right about us being withered old men, too.
Very well, then.
Would you tell me why the wall was torn down?
And this is what they told me next.
On the advice of a witch who visited a short time ago,
I love you! Forever and ever!
the people of the country were allowed to
inscribe whatever they wanted into the wall.
I hate that big jerk!
The king has
donkey ears!
That was all well and good at first,
Lo, I am the Angel of the Wall,
arisen from the blackest darkness!
but as time went by...
"Forever" my left foot! We already broke up!
Oh my god! I can't believe I
wrote this stuff while I was drunk!
How dare anyone write this? Who was it?
"Embarrassments incurred while travelling are
easily scratched out", or so the saying goes,
Ugh! This is so embarrassing now!
but the inscriptions left by the people who lived there,
where their words confronted them every day,
were not so easily erased.
In no time at all, they brought the shame
to those who had left them.
This continued until the wall came crumbling down.
And once it did,
the people of both sides came to find that their
resentment towards one another was no more.
Each side wanted to believe that
they were better than the other...
...but we repudiated that with the
embarrassing inscriptions that we ourselves left.
I suppose this country never needed
a wall in the first place.
We're all exactly alike when all is said and done.
We'll go back to being an ordinary country
and live together in harmony from now on.
Oh.
Goodbye then, Ms. Witch.
Wait!
Please tell me. Before the wall came down,
which side had more words of praise inscribed on it?
Isn't it obvious?
Both sides were perfectly equal.
Equal?
Originally, we were a single country.
Each side worked its hardest to outshine the other side.
How did no one ever realize
that the people on the opposite side of
the wall were doing the exact same things?
Since our side believed we were superior,
we never concerned ourselves with
what the other side was doing.
The same went for us.
This side of the country is truly splendid.
Signed, A Wandering Witch
I suppose this was for the best.
A country doesn't exist for the sake of travellers.
It's for the people who live in it.
Although it's a shame I didn't get to see the wall.
Did Nike inscribe this here because she knew
that the wall wouldn't last, perhaps?
No, that's silly.
Hi there, cute little witch.
How about a fragment of the wall as a souvenir?
Hmm. All right, to remember this
country by... I'll take this one.
Thank you!
Come again any time!
Ela...
"Ela"?
Mhm! Another good crop this year.
We'll get some fantastic wine out of these grapes.
I can't wait!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Yeah.
Look, Grandpa! My new clothes
for the grape-tossing festival!
Now don't you look dashing!
Hey Grandpa, where did the
grape-tossing festival come from?
Oh, you want to hear that story, eh?
Let me see.
Well, a long, long time ago, our village
was divided into two separate villages,
the Village of Over Here and
the Village of Over There,
and their people fought like cats and dogs.
One year, during the season of the grape harvest,
a witch came to visit.
The Grape-Stomping Girls
Welcome to Over Here!
"Over Here"?
That's right!
Our village is Over Here, and that way,
past the fork in the road, is the village of Over There.
I've heard that Here and There are both
famous for the wine they produce.
You heard right!
Our wine is renowned throughout the land.
Tell me, honoured witch, do you fancy wine?
I've never tried it before. That's why I came here.
Oh?
For my first drink of alcohol, I wanted to taste the best!
Heh, I see!
Then it's a good thing you came Here!
The wine Here is so delicious that the wine
from There can't hope to compare!
You'll swear it was bottled by the gods themselves!
That certainly sounds impressive.
Is that wine from Here you're holding?
Uh!
Ah, actually, no.
This wine came from Over There.
It's all because of the shameful plot
the people from Over There came up with!
"I'm the Grape-Stomping Maiden
from Over There, Rosemarie,
and I squish-squashed the grapes
for this wine with all my love!"
With this lovely label featuring
the ravishing Rosemarie,
sales Over There keep climbing higher and higher!
Oh.
And that's not all! Rosemarie has been
certified as the wine's place of origin!
Um, its place of origin?
That's right!
The origin? Not the maker?
Referring to her as the "origin" gets a certain
segment of the buying public more fired up!
Fired... up?
In other words, making the product relevant
to certain interests drives sales like crazy!
Wow. And that makes it sell.
All they have to say is that this cutie's
feet squish-squashed those grapes!
"Squish-squashed?"
Well, then why doesn't Over Here get in the game
and find a cute girl to squish-squash its grapes?
Brilliant!
It's just as you say!
If we get a charming maiden to
squish-squash our grapes,
victory will be ours!
So you will help us out, won't you?
Won't you?
Good news, everyone!
Our honoured witch guest just agreed to
become our grape-stomping maiden!
Wow! This adorable witch is going
to squish-squash our grapes?
Hooray! Please step on me, too!
Excuse me, but what am I—
We start at once!
H-Hey, wait!
Why am I wearing this getup?
The body of a grape-stomping maiden
should be clad in the traditional garb!
It's way more exciting that way!
"Exciting" how?
Heave-ho!
Dearie me, what's happening here?
Greetings to you, Mister Mayor,
and to your boring, obsolete village too!
I-It's you! The beauty of the
Village of Over There, Rosemarie!
Rosemarie...
Oh, my! What's that bottle you're cuddling up to?
Eep!
Do my eyes deceive me, or is that a
bottle of our wine with my picture on it?
I never knew you were a fan of mine!
F-Fan? Perish the... thought...
I'd be happy to autograph the label if you'd like.
Autograph!
And who's this scrawny weed of a girl
dressed up like a grape-stomping maiden?
I happen to be a wandering witch.
A witch, huh?
I see, I see.
You couldn't beat me,
so you're trying to get this underdeveloped witch
to squish-squash the grapes for you?
Who might you be calling underdeveloped?
Her face could use a little work, too!
Come again?
I mean, look at her, she's basically a kid!
Excuse me?!
Oh, I see! You actually are a kid!
If you think you can beat me by having her
stomp your grapes, you'd better think again!
Do excuse me now!
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Mister Mayor?
I'll do it.
I will be the grape-stomping maiden!
Squishy-squashy! Squishy-squashy! Squishy-squashy!
Die! Die! Die die die die die!
I'm dead tired!
Good work, honoured witch.
I must have squished and squashed for hours.
How much wine did that yield?
Let me see.
Half a barrel's worth, perhaps.
That's barely any!
After all that squishing and squashing?
This grape-stomping maiden job
is harder than I thought.
How are sales of the wine from Over There?
Oh, it's just selling like crazy!
They've moved hundreds of bottles—
no, perhaps even thousands!
Rosemarie would have to work from dawn to dusk
to squish-squash enough grapes
for all that wine, wouldn't she?
Don't you find that strange?
I believe you're right.
Heave-ho! Heave-ho! Heave-ho!
Make with the squishy-squashy!
You want my wine to sell, don't you?
Come on, stomp!
What's the meaning of this?
Do you mean to tell me Rosemarie
never squish-squashed those grapes?!
Yes, that's exactly what I'm telling you.
Okay then.
You were concealing the true origin
of this wine all along.
This is grounds for legal action, you know!
Ho...
Uh-oh, looks like the jig is up.
And we were really raking it in, too!
I can't believe we got away with it until now.
Rosemarie's wine really was stomped
by a bunch of burly men!
So we lied about the origin! So what?
It all tastes the same!
I see.
Now that I'm drinking it for the first time,
I agree that it's quite delicious.
The feeling that comes with it is what's important!
Even if it tastes the same,
knowing that Rosemarie is the one who
squish-squashed the grapes makes all the difference!
That's...
That's what makes it relevant to my interests!
Shut up! Rosemarie doesn't
have to listen to your bitching!
Silence!
How dare you!
What do you think you're doing to our mayor?
Oh, so that's how it's going to be?
What then? What happened next?
Everyone succumbed to the hail of grapes raining down,
and was knocked unconscious.
When they came to the next morning,
the witch was nowhere to be found.
And that was how the
grape-tossing festival came to be.
The grape fight was great for blowing off steam,
and it soon became tradition to hold one
every time the grapes were harvested.
In time, the two villages ceased fighting
and became one again.
Wow! We should say thank you to that witch!
You're right.
What about Rosemarie?
Well, you see...
What, what?
I'll tell you some other time.
Go wash your hands for lunch.
Okay!
She aged just like a fine wine. No matter how old
she gets, she can still get me fired up.
Good work over there! Shall we go in for lunch?
Okay!
As I wander down evening lanes lit by the light of the silvery moon
tsukiakari terasu komichi wo toorinuke
The sweet honeyed poison that hides behind kindness
yasashisa no ura ni kakureta amai doku ni
May it not lead me astray
madowasarenai you
Let me protect those I hold dear
mamoritai mono
Pray, give me that strength
mamoru tsuyosa
Believing that what I seek will one day be within my hands
itsuka kanarazu te ni ireru to shinjite
I'll set off to a brand-new tomorrow
atarashii asu e yuku yo
Crossing over joys and despairs alike
yorokobi mo zetsubou mo koete
Hurrying, ever onward
isogu sono saki e
Simply because I wish to know how I can spin this tale
tada shiritai kara
Of meetings, learning, and choosing my own path
deai manabi erabu michi de tsuzuru
Knitting it all into my very own story
watashi dake no monogatari
And turning to a brand-new page
daremo mita koto no nai
One nobody has ever seen before
sono ichi page wo