It may have been a better idea to fly
over the forest rather than through it.
Though it's a little too late now.
I'll just have to push on through.
"The most beautiful flowers have thorns."
Beauty itself can hide sharp fangs that spring out
at those who unwittingly approach.
Pardon the sudden change in subject,
but who might this lovely maiden be,
blooming with such youthful possibility
that she outshines the flowers beneath her?
Why yes, that would be me!
As illusions start to gain colour and shapes
irodorarete ikeba gensou ga
While they slowly start to become real
katachi aru mono ni naru you ni
I will give them form
egaite yukeru
And grant their wishes
kanaete yukerunda
As the gently blowing wind
yasashiku fuita kaze ga
Stirs the pages of an aged book
furui page mekuru you ni
I may turn back now and then
furikaeru kedo
But rest assured, it will be all right
uun ii no yo
Tales of meeting and parting once more
shiranai koto darake no
All so full of new, yet-unexplored things
deai wakare no hanashi
I gently brushed the words set down in blurry ink
nijimu ink wo sotto nazotta
Where are you going to?
doko iku no
Somewhere just a little far away
sukoshi tooku made
Let the things I left behind turn into dreams
oitekita mono wa yume ni
Choosing what I like best, and in the process
suki dakara erabu erabinagara
Slowly growing into myself
watashi ni natte yuku
"Oh, do let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
"And make it a promise, too!"
yakusoku dakara
You said to me, grinning from ear to ear
anata wa sou hohoenda
"Yes, let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
Linking fingers, we sealed our vow
koyubi no majinai
And as I heard a voice calling to me
dareka no koe ga shite
I opened my eyes
me ga sameta
A Girl as Lovely As a Flower
What a splendid field of wildflowers.
Oh?
Excuse me!
Oh my, hello.
Are you the one who cares for these flowers?
These flowers have no caretaker.
I'm here simply because I love them.
To play among the blossoms and bathe in the sunlight.
Does that mean all these flowers grew here naturally?
That's incredible.
Miss Traveller, could you be a witch?
Might I ask you a favour?
Sure, if it's within my power.
Would you take this bouquet with you
to the next country you visit?
All right, but who should I give it to?
It doesn't matter who, as long as
they think the flowers are beautiful.
So you're asking me to help drum up
publicity for this field of flowers, is that it?
No.
I'll be glad to take them.
Thank you, Miss Traveller.
Leave it to me. I'll make sure
to pass them on to someone.
Have a pleasant journey.
Stop right there, girl!
"Girl"?
Hmph!
Hey! Didn't you hear me? Stop!
Whatever business may you have with me?
Are you a traveller?
Can't you tell I am?
What's that bouquet for?
Nothing in particular.
Hand it over!
Hey!
You...
Where did you get these?
What does it matter where I got them?
It's none of your business.
Now please give them back.
Hey! What's going on here?
You stand down. I'll take it from here.
Sir, this mantle! And these flowers! They might be—
Stand down like I told you!
Have you gone deaf?
Go take a rest.
Return that bouquet!
Here.
Thanks.
Sorry about that, missy. His younger sister
disappeared not too long ago.
He's been in that mood ever since.
Don't take it to heart.
Not to worry, I won't.
That was a lie, by the way.
Either way, I'm sorry, but I'll
have to dispose of those flowers.
Bringing them into this kingdom is strictly forbidden.
Why is that?
Those flowers contain a poison.
A poison?
But I sensed nothing like that.
A witch like you may not be affected,
but they hold a power that can twist the hearts
of humans who are unable to use magic.
Are they really that dangerous?
They are.
The affected people are drawn to where
those flowers bloom, like insects lured by nectar,
and when they arrive there, they get consumed.
That's why you dispose of them?
Is something wrong?
Oh, no.
Sorry about this.
You can go in.
It was all me!
You're dreaming!
A field of flowers...
There was a story in my beloved
Adventures of Nike about a very strange plant.
Ordinary plants receive the light of
the sun and exude magical energy.
But a mutation occurred in one plant
that made it absorb magical energy instead,
causing it to become sentient,
and then turn violent.
I wonder...
The next day, before I set out for my
next destination, I went back to the flower field
to confirm something for myself.
Hello.
Oh, hello again.
Is this thing your sister?
I finally found her.
It's all thanks to you for bringing
the bouquet and her mantle.
When I saw that, I knew she was here.
I finally... finally found you.
You've grown so lovely...
You were keeping this beautiful place
all to yourself, weren't you?
Hey, why don't we invite everyone
in the country to come here?
I'm sure they'll love it.
I want to show off to everyone how lovely
you've become, too. Like a flower.
Doesn't that sound nice?
Oh, really? Thank you.
You're just so lovely...
Bottled Happiness
Hey!
Whoa! She stopped!
Hello there.
Hello!
Wow, a real witch! Incredible!
What brings you here?
I'm travelling, for I am a traveller.
What about you?
I'm searching for happiness!
Happiness?
What's that you have there?
This is the bottle I collect happiness inside of!
Happiness inside a bottle?
I can transform the moment a person or
animal feels happiness into magical power,
and gather it inside this bottle!
So you can use magic, too.
You're transforming emotions into magic?
Yeah, I guess so.
May I open that bottle?
No can do!
If I let you open it, all my hard work
will have been for nothing.
This is like treasure I've gathered for the girl I like.
Oh no, you're angry.
No. I'm rather impressed, actually.
You reminded me of a book I once read.
A book?
Yes.
There once was a man with a sickly wife.
Because she was bedridden,
he travelled all over the world,
and reproduced the breathtaking
sights he saw with magic.
He would take them home to show her.
That's how the story went.
Wow.
And what happened after that?
I'm sure his wife was overjoyed!
Hmm... now how did it go?
She got better and lived a good, long life, no doubt!
Perhaps you're right.
So who's this girl you like?
Her name is Nino. She's my family's servant.
She looks so down all the time,
so I want to cheer her up.
That's why I've been bottling all this happiness.
I see.
The feelings of plants?
That's right!
I tried to see if I could get happiness
out of them, but it went kinda so-so!
Good thing you weren't turned into a meal instead.
What?
Oh, nothing.
There it is!
Quite the peaceful village.
Isn't it?
Is that the mayor's house?
It's mine, too!
I see.
You're not showing much of a reaction, Miss Witch.
Would you have preferred for me to be surprised?
Wow, it's incredible! You must be incredibly rich!
Um, forget I said anything.
When are you planning to present the bottle?
I was thinking of giving it to her after lunch!
Hey, now that's a good idea!
How about having lunch with us?
Nino is a great cook!
I appreciate the invitation,
but I had breakfast not too long ago.
Then I'll tell her to keep your portion small!
Oh, and are there any foods you don't like?
I don't care for mushrooms.
Got it. I'll have her leave them out.
Really, I'll be fine with a small portion.
Leave everything to me.
You're in for a delicious meal! Thanks to Nino!
Sit back and relax.
Thank you.
G-Good day to you.
Good day.
Would you perhaps happen to be
from an eastern country?
What? Um, I...
You remind me a little of a girl
I know who is, that's all.
That's right!
My father found her in a country to the east!
He found her?
And that's how you came to be here?
Yes. The mayor treats me very kindly.
And where might this mayor be right now?
He is at work in his study—
Hey, Nino, what's for lunch today?
Th-The mayor requested broiled fish today.
Would you make enough for our witch guest, too?
She agreed, Miss Witch!
Thank you, but a small portion will be plenty.
V-Very well.
Hey, Nino!
After we eat, I've got a present for you!
F-For me?
That's right! Look forward to it!
No! I don't need anything!
And the mayor will be angry!
It's okay! I'll deal with Father!
No, but...
Fine. It's an order, then!
Accept my present, Nino.
How's that?
If it's an order, then...
Good!
Can I help with anything?
You just sit tight and wait, Miss Witch.
We'll take care of everything!
Well now.
It's rare for us to have visitors.
Might you be the mayor?
The very same.
My name is Elaina. I am a traveller.
Pleased to meet you.
You're quite well-mannered. Likewise.
Enjoy your stay here.
Here we are!
Here is your lunch.
My small portion...?
Is something the matter?
No, no. Thank you for the food.
Let's eat!
Thank you. The meal was delicious.
Oh, yes. Don't mention it.
I'll clear the plates now.
Allow me to help.
No need, Miss Witch!
Is it true you met Nino in a country to the east?
Yes, that's where I bought her.
Bought her?
As a slave.
My wife up and left a few years ago.
None of the housework was getting done.
It was a damned nuisance.
Then, while I was travelling to the east
on business, I spotted her.
She cost a bundle, but she knows
how to keep the household in order,
and most of all, she has the makings of a real beauty
when she matures, so I didn't hesitate to buy her.
My eyes didn't deceive me.
She makes a fine servant.
Does Emil know about all this?
I told him, but he doesn't seem
to get that she's a slave.
Hey, Nino! Where should I put the big platter—
What the hell do you think you're doing?
You're useless!
How much longer will it be before
you can do your job properly?
Clean that up at once!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Clean it up!
Stop it, Father! This was my fault! Nino isn't—
Shut your mouth!
I said clean it up!
Yes, sir!
That won't be necessary.
Oh?
Be careful not to drop it again, all right?
M-My, I'm sorry about this!
Even after witnessing such a disgraceful display,
you still went out of your way to fix it for us!
You thank her, too!
Oh, I'm so sorry!
A "thank you" is all I need.
Thank you... very much.
You're welcome!
Magic like that is easy. I could have done it.
Oh, dear. My apologies.
I suppose you didn't need my help.
No, that's not true. Thanks.
You're welcome.
But I can do spells like that too, you know...
Come to think of it, Nino must be very upset right now.
This would be an ideal time to give her
your present, wouldn't you agree?
You're a genius, Miss Witch!
Oh please, do go on.
Remember how I said I had a present for you?
Y-Yes.
Here it is!
It's a bottle filled with happiness.
With happiness?
The happiness of all sorts of different people
from across the land is bottled up inside.
All sorts of people's... happiness?
You'll only get one chance to see it, so look closely.
Now go on and open it!
Ready? Go!
See all the little pieces of happiness?
The outside world is filled with happiness like this.
So don't be sad.
I'll make you happy.
Happy? Me?
Come visit us again!
Nino and I will make you even tastier food next time.
Right?
I will. Farewell.
See you again!
What a beautiful sunset.
It was at that moment that I remembered
the ending to the story I read long ago.
To the bedridden wife, the lovely scenery
her husband kept showing her
only served to drive her to despair.
In the end, she...
"The things we think we do for the sake
of others aren't always what's best for them."
An awfully heavy-handed moral, if you ask me.
Kindness and beauty can sometimes be quite cruel.
What happened to Nino after that, I don't know.
And frankly, I don't want to know either.
As I wander down evening lanes lit by the light of the silvery moon
tsukiakari terasu komichi wo toorinuke
The sweet honeyed poison that hides behind kindness
yasashisa no ura ni kakureta amai doku ni
May it not lead me astray
madowasarenai you
Let me protect those I hold dear
mamoritai mono
Pray, give me that strength
mamoru tsuyosa
Believing that what I seek will one day be within my hands
itsuka kanarazu te ni ireru to shinjite
I'll set off to a brand-new tomorrow
atarashii asu e yuku yo
Crossing over joys and despairs alike
yorokobi mo zetsubou mo koete
Hurrying, ever onward
isogu sono saki e
Simply because I wish to know how I can spin this tale
tada shiritai kara
Of meetings, learning, and choosing my own path
deai manabi erabu michi de tsuzuru
Knitting it all into my very own story
watashi dake no monogatari
And turning to a brand-new page
daremo mita koto no nai
One nobody has ever seen before
sono ichi page wo