Hm?
The Adventures of Fran?
Is this anything like The Adventures of Nike?
Looks like she doesn't just have the
same name as Miss Fran, either.
She looks an awful lot like her, too.
As I leafed through the book,
I reminisced about the experiences
I had in a certain country half a year ago.
It was a grand country,
located very far away from here.
The name of this country was Royal Celestelia.
As illusions start to gain colour and shapes
irodorarete ikeba gensou ga
While they slowly start to become real
katachi aru mono ni naru you ni
I will give them form
egaite yukeru
And grant their wishes
kanaete yukerunda
As the gently blowing wind
yasashiku fuita kaze ga
Stirs the pages of an aged book
furui page mekuru you ni
I may turn back now and then
furikaeru kedo
But rest assured, it will be all right
uun ii no yo
Tales of meeting and parting once more
shiranai koto darake no
All so full of new, yet-unexplored things
deai wakare no hanashi
I gently brushed the words set down in blurry ink
nijimu ink wo sotto nazotta
Where are you going to?
doko iku no
Somewhere just a little far away
sukoshi tooku made
Let the things I left behind turn into dreams
oitekita mono wa yume ni
Choosing what I like best, and in the process
suki dakara erabu erabinagara
Slowly growing into myself
watashi ni natte yuku
"Oh, do let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
"And make it a promise, too!"
yakusoku dakara
You said to me, grinning from ear to ear
anata wa sou hohoenda
"Yes, let us meet again!"
mata aimashou
Linking fingers, we sealed our vow
koyubi no majinai
And as I heard a voice calling to me
dareka no koe ga shite
I opened my eyes
me ga sameta
Royal Celestelia
It's so cute!
Wow!
Well, now.
Look at all the magic users using
their powers to entertain everyone.
How lovely.
Let's hear a round of applause!
Thank you very much! Take a look at my muscles!
The Royal Academy of Magic?
I didn't know they had something like this here.
It wouldn't be right of me to
just barge in here, would it?
I really shouldn't, should I?
But still...
In I go!
Hey!
This campus is strictly off-limits to the public!
Oh! Excuse me, honoured witch!
Please forgive my rudeness.
Think nothing of it.
Do excuse me, then.
The campus is still off-limits.
Even to a witch?
I'm afraid so.
What would it have hurt to let me in?
I suppose I'd better find a room for the night.
Excuse me!
A paper route, hm?
This country's magic users are certainly—
Uh, may I help you?
Good day. Might you be the Ashen Witch, Miss?
Um, w-we're students from
the Royal Academy of Magic!
From the school I tried to visit just now?
What do you want with me?
U-Um, would you please come along
quietly and not ask us why?
Why?
B-But I said not to ask—
Certainly not.
Why not?
Because something feels off
about this, so I refuse.
Oh, won't you please?
Just go along with it and come with us.
Absolutely not.
Goodbye.
Okay then, guys, we'll make it a team effort.
Good idea. Let's all work together to capture her.
Capture me?
No fair taking all the credit for yourself, y'hear?
Look who's talking!
I haven't the faintest idea what's going on here, but...
Hey, wait up!
Miss Ashen Witch?!
P-Please don't run away!
You, head toward the river.
The rest of you, circle around the royal state house.
Ooh! There she is!
Surrender quietly!
As I thought. They have knowledge
of the terrain on their side.
They don't give up easily, I see.
They've got spirit, if nothing else.
All right, if that's how they want
to do this, then let's play.
I've got you now, Miss Ashen Witch!
I'd recommend opening your eyes.
I-I've got you now, Miss Ashen Witch!
I'm worn out.
I-I'm done for!
Got the picture now? Even if you gang up on me,
it's not going to do you any good.
Do yourselves a favour and give up.
Goodbye.
Good work, boys and girls.
P-Professor!
You were no match for her at all, were you?
N-No...
Age means nothing.
This is what separates you in ability
from a full-fledged witch.
It's been a long time, Elaina.
Miss Fran...
It was the first time in years
I'd seen Miss Fran, my teacher.
That concludes today's extracurricular lesson.
Your reports are due tomorrow.
Y-Yes...
Thank... you...
Goodness me, they're nearly dead on their feet.
Don't you think you were a bit too hard on them?
How is this my fault?
I suppose I'm to blame as well.
You're a professor at this school, Miss Fran?
That I am.
The king invited me to the position.
Come, Elaina. Let's continue our chat
somewhere more comfortable.
For their extracurricular class today,
I instructed my students to bring you back here,
even if they had to use a little force.
How did you know I'd come to this town?
You tried to enter the academy, didn't you?
I caught a young witch with hair the colour
of ash trying to sneak onto the campus.
She could be a foreign spy!
A spy? Really? What did that guard take me for?
I knew at once that it must be you.
I simply couldn't wait to see you again,
so I had my class go out to find you.
Searching a country this large all by
myself would have been a chore,
and it's good practice for my students.
After all, what better practice could there be
than matching wits with a brilliant witch?
Oh, I don't know about that!
I suppose I am brilliant, but...
It was quite the rare opportunity.
I'm sure the students were delighted.
And that goes for me, too.
Your travels have taken you
far and wide, haven't they?
Yes.
You knew I've been travelling?
Why, of course. Your mother told me.
You saw my mother?
She worries about you all the time.
Next time you're near home,
you really should stop by and visit.
I'm planning on it.
That's good to hear.
Why was it that you wanted to be a traveller?
Because of your mother, I suppose?
Why because of my mother?
Oh? Am I wrong?
It's mostly because of a book called
The Adventures of Nike that I've loved since I was little.
Ah, is that it?
I'm fond of that book as well.
I particularly like the last chapter,
when Fura, the novice witch, arrives.
That's my favourite chapter, too!
Said chapter tells the story of how Nike
makes a novice named Fura her apprentice
and helps her grow into a splendid witch.
At the end, Nike reveals that she's moving to
the countryside to live the life of an ordinary woman,
and Fura becomes a traveller herself.
That's where The Adventures of Nike ends.
This really brings back memories.
Oh?
Ah, no. Of the book, I meant.
Promise not to tell this to anyone else,
but I love this book so much that I started
writing a novel of my own during my travels.
Ah. Is that right?
You sound thoroughly uninterested.
Not at all! I'm very interested!
So, what happened?
Once my manuscript had reached
one hundred pages and I read it over again,
I found it was so embarrassing
that I could hardly bear to finish.
I see.
So I consigned it to the bottom of my
travelling bag and forgot all about it,
but then, while I was visiting
another country, I sold the bag.
Wow...
That bag once belonged to
a legendary traveller, you see.
What legendary traveller?
Who knows? I bought it for cheap at a pawn shop.
So you sold the bag with your novel still inside?
Oh my, how did you know?
It wouldn't take a brilliant witch to figure that out.
Just remembering it makes me want to squirm!
If someone found that manuscript and
read it, I don't know what I'd do!
Oh, Miss Fran.
Well, it makes for a funny story now.
What's the point to this story?
Why, isn't it obvious?
All sorts of things await you
as you continue your journey.
So make sure you come back and
let me hear all your stories some day.
That's what I wanted to tell you.
Got it.
Don't forget to keep up with your diary.
My mother told you about that?
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm sure your mother is, too.
Well then, I suppose I'd better not procrastinate!
Now class,
I'm sure you remember meeting her yesterday,
but let me introduce her again.
This is Elaina, the Ashen Witch.
Uh, hello there.
She'll be holding a special lesson for us today.
Do any of you have questions for her?
Me!
Go ahead.
Got a boyfriend?
No. I'm a traveller, after all.
Let's keep the questions to those
concerning magic, shall we?
Anybody else?
Um,
wh-what kind of magic are you best at?
No one kind in particular.
From offensive to transformative and every sort
of magic in between, I can manage any kind of spell.
I-I see!
Out of all the countries you've visited,
which one is your favourite?
It's this one.
Yes?
Was that flattery just now?
No. I really mean it.
Where are you from?
The peaceful country of Robetta.
Is being a traveller fun?
Yes, it's loads of fun!
Me, me!
What colour are your knick—
I joined Miss Fran in offering
instruction to the students.
The flow of your magic is uneven.
Fill your heart with calm. That will help steady it.
Yes!
Hey! This isn't recess.
No making the water into a sword.
Professor Elaina!
I can't get my water to form a nice sphere.
What should I do?
You're pouring too much magical energy into it.
Try and relax.
Okay.
Relax...
Maybe not by that much.
U-Um, would you mind helping me with something?
Not at all.
I'm not very good at controlling the water.
I can barely lift it out of the bucket.
What should I do?
Let me see you try it.
Um, all right.
Oh, dear.
I don't know what to do!
Looks like you haven't gotten the hang of it yet.
Start out by focusing on just lifting up the water.
Y-Yes!
Once you've managed that, return it to the bucket,
and then lift it up again.
Like this.
N-Now I see!
Keep practising and you'll get used to it in no time.
Y-Yes! Thank you!
No problem.
Look at me, Professor Elaina!
Check it out! Aren't I cool?
Augh, that's chilly!
Teaching others isn't something I often get to do,
and I really enjoyed myself.
This is my favourite place in the city.
I wanted to make sure I showed it
to you before you leave.
The view from here is so lovely.
It really is.
You leave tomorrow morning, don't you?
Yes.
That's too bad.
The students are so fond of you.
They'll be sad to see you go.
Having such a young witch around
was a novelty to them, that's all.
I'll miss you, too.
What will your students do after
they graduate from the academy?
They'll go out and get jobs.
Jobs?
That's right.
Delivering parcels, or carrying passengers
on their brooms. All sorts of jobs like that.
Are the street performers using magic also graduates?
Do they make money that way?
Probably only a pittance, but I expect they do.
But they aren't showing off
their magic to make money.
Why do they do it, then?
Because it's what they love.
You're travelling because that's what you love, isn't it?
The same holds true for them.
They do it because they love making
other people happy with their magic.
Because they love it...
I'd thought repeatedly to myself
that this was a lovely country.
The beauty of the city streets,
the smiles of the people who live there.
I felt a tug at my heart every time I saw these things.
Could it be
that Royal Celestelia itself is like
a distillation of my entire journey?
By the way, what else do you love?
Why do you ask?
Well, travelling, of course.
Besides that.
Books, I suppose.
And besides that?
What's this about?
I was curious, that's all.
Are you planning to give me
some sort of farewell gift?
Ah, you caught me red-handed.
You don't have to do that!
Now now, don't say that.
How do you feel about flowers?
I feel you're trying to push that onto me.
How about them, though?
Oh! Or butterflies!
For the last time, you're the one who likes those.
Don't you like butterflies?
They're average.
So you like them about the average amount!
So? How about flowers?
This conversation just went full circle.
How about it?
Well, I like them, I suppose.
All right. We'll say you like flowers.
Meet me in front of the city gates tomorrow.
She isn't here...
I thought Miss Fran was planning to give me flowers.
While I'd have been happy to receive them,
a bouquet would wilt before long.
If I saw the same kind of flowers
in another country later,
they would only remind me of Celestelia and
Miss Fran, and make me feel sad.
I decided to head out without waiting for her,
and avoid feeling sorrow later.
Farewell, Miss Fran.
A flower?
Elaina,
you became a traveller because that's what
you wished for. I can't stand in your way.
The most I can do is see you off.
Miss Fran...
Does this make you happy?
Yes! Very happy!
The students and I wish you happiness on
your journey, from the bottom of our hearts.
Please remember that.
I will! I'll remember each one of you, too!
F-Farewell!
Come hang out with us again!
You're always welcome!
We'll be waiting!
Let's meet again soon.
Until then, farewell.
Yes!
Above the rolling fields, a witch
on her broomstick flies by.
A sense of joyful anticipation filling her heart.
What sort of country might her
journey take her to next?
What sort of people might she meet there?
Imagining it makes her glow with excitement.
Now then, who might this traveller be?
Why yes, that would be me!
As I wander down evening lanes lit by the light of the silvery moon
tsukiakari terasu komichi wo toorinuke
The sweet honeyed poison that hides behind kindness
yasashisa no ura ni kakureta amai doku ni
May it not lead me astray
madowasarenai you
Let me protect those I hold dear
mamoritai mono
Pray, give me that strength
mamoru tsuyosa
Believing that what I seek will one day be within my hands
itsuka kanarazu te ni ireru to shinjite
I'll set off to a brand-new tomorrow
atarashii asu e yuku yo
Crossing over joys and despairs alike
yorokobi mo zetsubou mo koete
Hurrying, ever onward
isogu sono saki e
Simply because I wish to know how I can spin this tale
tada shiritai kara
Of meetings, learning, and choosing my own path
deai manabi erabu michi de tsuzuru
Knitting it all into my very own story
watashi dake no monogatari
And turning to a brand-new page
daremo mita koto no nai
One nobody has ever seen before
sono ichi page wo
This might be a bit too much for her to live up to...
One thing's for sure.
I'll certainly have an interesting story
to tell Miss Fran the next time I see her.