Yumeno Bath
Building No. 13 - I Want to Go to the Bathhouse!
The bathhouse!
There's coffee milk!
Not so fast!
You can have one after the bath.
Pretty please?
Please?
Those puppy-dog eyes only work on Haruki.
Let's hurry so we can get out quickly!
Yeah!
Hey!
If you two won't take your time
in the bath, you won't get a reward.
Okay! We understand!
I'm still not comfortable
with undressing in public.
Okay! Just the bottom left.
Stop caring so much about getting naked!
H-Hey!
Now there's really only the bottom left!
Stop that! Don't touch me!
shampoo
Cease this ruckus, please.
Shampoo
It's nice to have a bath you can
stretch your legs in once in a while.
Let's wash each other!
Other!
Nee-chan, your boobs are so big!
S-Stop it! Don't fondle them!
Take that!
It's hard to get excited
about your own sisters.
We're out!
Out!
Our reward for getting
in the bath like good kids!
Coffee milk!
We'd like two coffee milks, please.
Here you go.
COFFEE MILK
Um, would you happen
to have them in bottles?
We switched to cartons recently.
Sorry, my dears.
Well, you got your reward, so cheer up!
We'll make sure that the next
place we go to has them in bottles.
Right now?!
Now?!
Another time.
By the way, why are you drinking milk as well?
Got a problem with it?
Oh, I get it.
You compared your boobs
with Sis's, and now you're trying to—
Dash
Stupid Haru-perv!
I-Isn't this where you're supposed to hit me?!
He made her cry!
Yayoi!
sorosoro kaeru toki
It's time to go home
chikai wa hatasareta
My vow has been fulfilled
mirai wa mamorareta
The future has been saved
boku wa Princess Durandal
I am Princess Durandal
mahou no kuni e to
I'll cross space and time
jikuu wo koete kaeru
to return to my magical land