Megafloat Japan and Megafloat West USA
are presently 300 kilometers east
of Amami Oshima, heading northeast.
We have liberated Guam and Okinawa
and are moving in on the Japanese mainland.
It's finally time for the mainland battle!
We will take back Japan, our home!
Our target is the capital, Tokyo.
My love for you is like a bucking colt
You act so innocent, but I know you're feeling it
I'm not a wizard anymore
The craziest things you can imagine all start from nothing
It's like we're in a fairy tale
But this is real life
My charm makes you swoon
Our hearts beat in unison
Just let your passion explode
My feelings won't reach you like this
I need to shoot them at you with everything I've got
They're on a direct course to your heart
My spirit is on fire
I'll expose your true nature
Don't worry, I'll be gentle
I'll take you to a secret paradise
And offer you a grand feast
When the two of us become one
An innocent flower blooms
Episode 9
Academy Festival -First Concert-
On Wednesdays and Fridays,
the beef bowls at the cafeteria have less sauce.
And on Thursdays, the portions get smaller.
If you overlap the part-timers'
shifts on top of it like this,
you'll see that when Suzuki is working, you get
extra sauce, but when Yamamoto is working...
No one cares.
There's other stuff to talk about, right?
Like... you know.
Oh, I figured this would be more interesting.
Hell no!
Sheesh...
Fine.
These are life-sized data figures,
made from my experience and analysis
performing Heart Hybrids during actual combat.
The models use log data from the love room.
They're more than 97% accurate.
This is an erogenous zone map, created using my
activities during the Heart Hybrids and their responses.
Erogenous zones?
I don't know what that means!
Dunno what that means,
but it sounds freakin' awesome!
However, they don't always
react in an identical manner.
The way it feels to them differs depending
on the strength used and friction coefficients.
Hida Kizuna is a terrifying man!
How much experience does he have?!
The girl's psychological state,
as well as the situation you set,
also change things drastically.
Different individuals react differently,
so there's no real general theory.
Each case requires its own individual decisions.
I'm totally lost!
But there's something more important.
What?!
To understand the feelings of the girl.
What they wish...
What they're seeking...
You need to sense that and
make use of appropriate methods.
He's no amateur!
He's a pro!
Pro-zuna!
For example...
This is data from Himekawa, during our attack
on the Super-Category Class Tri-Head.
What the hell are you doing?!
It's your last chance to relax before the big battle.
Holiday
Go enjoy yourselves.
You're enjoying yourself a little too much, idiots.
I've finished presenting my science project
for the first day of the festival...
Maybe I'll go check out what everyone's up to.
Well? Did you find her?
Nope, no luck.
We can't do our rehearsal like this.
Jeez, where'd she go?
Is something wrong?
Kizuna!
Yurishia, don't grab onto him
every time you see him!
Oh, did you get hurt?
Anyway, is there a problem?
Didn't Hayuru just go talk to you?
K-Kizuna was doing an indecent presentation!
I didn't have time to tell him!
It's time for our rehearsal,
but there's no sign of Aine.
Aine's missing?
We had everyone go look for her,
but nobody's seen her.
Did you try using the PA system?
Sure did. Made an Ataraxia-wide announcement.
But no luck.
She's either asleep or hiding out somewhere.
All right.
I'll go look.
You two start rehearsing without her.
Still, how am I supposed to find her in this crowd?
Hey, it's Kizuna.
The hell are you doing, asshole?
Gertrude!
You're okay now?
Sure am.
No way in hell I'm spending the festival in bed.
Well, don't push yourself too hard.
Oh, right.
Have you seen Aine?
I've been to every food stall out here, but...
I haven't seen her.
Maybe the slut's in the school building?
I see.
Thanks.
Sorry. Have you seen
Chidorigafuchi Aine from Class 2-A?
It's Eros!
Wow, it is him!
Run, everyone!
Hey!
Wait!
I don't—
Curse you!
Huh? What's wrong, Captain?
Sylvia?
That's right!
This is my class!
But where did everyone go?
Uh, thing is...
Sylvia.
I need a favor.
Just in case we can't find Aine,
I brought you a substitute.
You mean me?
Kizuna, that's not fair to her!
Sylvia, let's practice a little.
Yurishia?
I can't! It's too sudden!
I'll keep looking for Aine, then.
Good luck!
Captain!
Come on in!
You can test-fire the Engineering
Division's latest railgun with no wait!
Kurumizawa.
Eros Overlord!
Kizuna!
My name is Hida Kizuna!
What's your problem? That was a compliment.
It was not!
That aside, have you seen Aine?
Chidorigafuchi?
No, can't say I have.
I see.
Hey, while you're here...
How about you try out our new railgun?
But I'm in a hurry...
Just come with me!
It's not going to just blow up, is it?
It's not. Don't underestimate me,
the Engineering Division's top student!
Yeah, got it.
I've got stuff to do, so I'll only fire one shot.
There's nothing difficult you need to do.
Good luck!
Put the target in the middle of the sights,
then flip the switch.
Got it.
Shikina, what are you doing here?
Uh... Never mind.
Have you seen Aine?
No, sorry.
Welcome back, Master.
Huh? You're the Masters...
Oh, it's you, Kizuna!
Did you come to see me in my maid outfit?
In this café, you get to be the master of the Masters.
Order a lot, okay, Master?
This way.
What will you order, Master?
Let's see...
Wait, I'm not here for tea...
I'm looking for Aine.
These are our specialties.
Moe Menu
Lap Pillow
Ear Picking
Instant Photo
Polaroid
Slap
Abuse
Hug
Patting
We also have a secret menu...
Care to take a look?
Crap.
This maid café is dangerous!
You're leaving already?
I remembered something I have to do.
Here's your receipt, then.
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Bill
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Bill
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Bill
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Bill
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
Seating Fee
Gratuity
Information Fee
Total
That's expensive!
It includes the fee for the information we gave you.
Thank you.
You didn't give me any information...
It's almost time for the concert.
Where in the world is she?
If you want to kill me, then just do it already!
General Grabel of the 6th Expeditionary Force.
You've gone from hero to traitor.
She decided on her own to make contact
with the Lemurian barbarians,
discovered Zeros and yet said nothing,
and tried to keep it for herself, the traitor.
Zeros is in Lemuria?
Put together a fleet immediately!
Get Zeros, even if it means
killing every single Lemurian!
We've conquered more than enough of Lemuria!
What's the point of more murder?
There are civilians there, not just soldiers!
What of it?
Compared to what we seek,
their lives are meaningless.
I was originally a soldier of a country
that was conquered by Batlantis.
S-Stop it!
I can't allow you to invade...
or oppress them for no reason...
I won't kill you.
I'll let you taste heaven without dying.
Wh-What is this?
Why?
I should only feel hate and pain, so why do I feel so...
How about this?
What's wrong?
Surrendering already?
Endure.
Aldea will come for you.
And then...
You think your friend will come for you?
Zelshione!
Please, show me more love!
I'll do anything!
I'm your pet, after all!
Mind control?
Don't worry.
I'll make you my pet as well
soon enough, Bronze Beast.
First, you're going to tell me where Zeros is.
We're going to Lemuria.
Our target is their mobile fortress.
Please wait a moment, Zelshione.
You're...
Performing on the special stage on the ground
AMATERASU
Now, it's time for a special
academy festival performance!
They're usually a combat group, but just for today...
...they're school idols!
Still no sign of Aine...
Let's go, Sylvia!
I-I'll do my best!
Give a big hand to the idols of Ataraxia, Amaterasu!
It's started, huh?
Seriously, where'd she go?
Hey, everybody!
Something was bothering her.
What's going on with her?
H-Hello!
Excuse me! I'm standing in for Aine!
Sylvia...
I'm Sylvia Silkcut!
Is she going to be okay?
Aine?
Kizuna...
Okay, everybody, here we go!
What's wrong?
Why are you sitting here by yourself?
I told you before, right?
That each time I do a Heart Hybrid,
some of my memories return?
Yeah.
But maybe they're not memories.
What do you mean?
I searched the database for the things I saw,
but they don't exist anywhere on Earth.
It's like another world...
Don't think too hard!
Take back hope!
Another... world...?
Aine?
I don't want to remember anything else,
so I'm not going to do any more Heart Hybrids.
But your Hybrid Count's getting real low.
If you don't do it, your count'll
drop to zero in the next fight—
No!
I'm scared!
I don't want to remember any more strange things!
I feel like if I do, I won't be the same person.
Aine.
Don't worry.
No matter what happens, you are who you are.
Kizuna...
No matter what's in your past, I...
No, we won't change.
You'll always be one of us.
To me, you're just Chidorigafuchi Aine.
I'll shoot you through!
A burning hot gaze...
Get closer to me and make it so you're only mine.
My heart's beating so fast.
Aine...
Don't hide them.
But I'm embarrassed...
Does it feel good?
D-Don't ask me.
You know it feels good...
No!
Love Gun High Power!
Aine!
Aine?
Midsummer love shooting through your heart!
Captain, I did it!
What?
Kizuna!
Amaterasu needs to emergency scramble.
An enemy fleet has appeared.
The enemy fleet has come
from the Kanto region of Japan.
If we want to take back Tokyo,
we have to fight them at some point.
Let's go!
Look!
Someone's there!
Why is she there?
Mom...
It's been a long time, Kizuna.
How about an apple, Snow White? Relax, it's safe
You know, that shit-eating grin really pisses me off
I'm gonna punch you
Forgive me for being cold to you
It's just that there was this girl looking at you in the cafe
I'm gonna kill her
She'd probably leave you before the night is over
Let me show you the storm of emotions trapped beneath the surface
Go beyond your dreams, love's waiting for you there
What do you want so badly that you'd cry for it?
All I want is your heart's warmth
There's no escape from the love that's seeping through your veins
Hold me, hold your breath
You're my prince
Just kidding
Illustration
Yumi Nakata
That woman was always in front of me.
And so were her cold eyes that always
looked down on, mocked, and derided others.
Hida Nayuta, I will never forgive you.
NEXT TIME
EVE OF THE DECISIVE BATTLE -INSTALL-
No matter what the cost,
even if I have to burn my soul.