What the hell...
...is going on here?
Welcome, Kizuna.
Mom...
My love for you is like a bucking colt
You act so innocent, but I know you're feeling it
I'm not a wizard anymore
The craziest things you can imagine all start from nothing
It's like we're in a fairy tale
But this is real life
My charm makes you swoon
Our hearts beat in unison
Just let your passion explode
My feelings won't reach you like this
I need to shoot them at you with everything I've got
They're on a direct course to your heart
My spirit is on fire
I'll expose your true nature
Don't worry, I'll be gentle
I'll take you to a secret paradise
And offer you a grand feast
When the two of us become one
An innocent flower blooms
Episode 11
Operation Take Back Tokyo -Apocalypse-
What's going on?!
Tokyo was destroyed!
How's it back to normal?!
It's not back to normal at all.
What...?
What you just saw was an illusion created by magic.
A reflection of what once was.
Why would you do that?!
This city is a Plant of sorts.
I've excluded only you from the effects
of the magic field covering this area.
The rest of them are all caught
in an illusion of peaceful days.
That allows me to efficiently and
continually harvest their life energy.
The field absorbs the life energy,
turns it into magical energy,
and then sends it to Batlantis.
It's a small area for now,
but will cover all of Tokyo soon enough.
Then all of Japan.
Until eventually the whole world becomes a Plant.
What...
What the hell do you think their lives are?
You're always like this.
You only see everything as a subject
for your experiments!
Me, Sis, everyone in Amaterasu...
I'm taking you back with me!
I'll force you to tell me a way to safely
remove the Heart Hybrid Cores!
It's impossible.
Those things are out of place artifacts
even in the other world.
I merely used the cores to create a system
that would allow a normal person
to produce life energy as a
replacement for magical energy.
You didn't make them?
I did not.
Th-Then how can they be removed?
I just told you it was impossible.
Shut up!
Everyone... They're all...
They're all going to die!
Every last one of them!
All humans die, right?
Damn you!
That's enough.
I'll be your opponent now.
Get ready!
I can't fight here.
I won't let the people of Tokyo get caught up in this.
You don't think I'll let you get away, do you?!
Everything's going according to plan, isn't it?
Let us go as well.
Yes, Dr. Nayuta.
No—
Come...
Amaterasu!
Come get some.
I'll send you all to heaven.
Looks like you'll entertain me.
Everyone...
Let's do this!
Right!
This is the Entrance sealing team.
We're in the Yamanote Line area.
Roger.
Proceed with the mission.
Magitech signals to the northeast!
What?
They found us?
Everyone, stay alert!
Work teams, get to it!
We'll defend this place to the death!
That big one's tough.
Those two were powerless against it...
I'll leave them to Kizuna and buy some time!
Okay, here we go, fatass!
She disappeared?
Too slow!
Don't get cocky!
Aine!
Are you okay, Aine?
Hang in there!
Just wait! I'll—
I told you I wouldn't let you get away.
The girl I'll take back.
But the rest of you are apparently useless,
so I'll take you out instead.
If I only had...
...more power...
What?!
I'm sorry I'm late, Captain!
Sylvia!
Is that your...
Yes!
This is my Heart Hybrid Gear,
Taros!
Taros?
Leave this to me!
Hurry up!
Fine.
But don't take any risks!
That's an order!
Roger!
Sorry, Sylvia.
How dare you...
How dare you do that to me?!
I'll protect everyone!
I won't let you lay another finger on them!
Intercept!
Hit her!
I won't...
...lose to someone like this!
Someone like this...
I won't lose!
Neither will I!
Impact!
Get lost!
Wow...
What power...
That is... Taros...
I lost?
Me?
That's impossible. Me?
A member of the Royal Guards?
To someone like her?
No, that can't be!
I'd rather die than lose to a Lemurian.
That's right.
I'll die!
What are you—
Shut up!
This is your fault!
For doing this to me... To me!
So it's all over!
For you!
For your friends!
Everything!
Everything! Everything!
I'll blow it all away!
No!
Inferno!
I won't let you!
No!
The energy ball that appeared has a calorific
value of 7.2 exa-high-megajoules!
And it's still rising!
Forget Tokyo, it'll destroy the entire
Kanto region at this rate!
I'm blocking it with my shield, but it's still hot!
Are you okay, Sylvia?!
Captain!
I'm coming!
No, don't!
Your shields probably can't handle it!
But the people of Tokyo...
I'll use my Immoral Weapon.
What?
Wait, Sylvia!
Connection Failed
Leave it to me!
Sylvia!
Shield generator, full drive!
Immoral Weapon:
Titania!
Full Power
Ignition Impact!
Sylvia!
Are you okay?
Captain...
Did I protect everyone?
Yeah.
You did great, Sylvia!
Enough power to create a black hole...
That was quite the splendid sight.
Let us meet again, Kizuna.
They just keep coming.
But our Counts...
They're heading this way!
We won't get a chance to resupply?
I thought this might happen,
so I prepared something ahead of time.
Something's coming!
What?
What is that?
A mid-range ballistic-type supply room.
AKA The Bullet Love Room.
Start with the ones whose Counts are the lowest.
The others are to provide
as much support as possible.
Roger.
Okay, we'll start with Himekawa.
R-Right!
The others are to provide support!
Roger.
Aine, Sylvia, let's clear out the small fry!
No problem!
No, don't!
What's going on here?
No need to worry.
They're simply having a delightful dream.
Who's there?
You!
She disappeared?
Now, Lemurian, what is your dream?
What's wrong with me?
Not there... No!
What am I doing?
At a time like this...
I can't concentrate?!
Because I don't have any strength?
Fighting was all I had!
But now I'm like this.
I want power so that I can keep being me!
I'll finish it now!
Take this!
No!
You're finally out.
Yurishia!
Your Heart Hybrids always take so long, Hayuru.
Well, you were having a good time, I suppose.
Th-That's crass slander!
I would never do something
so indecent for such a reason!
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
Anyway, now that you've recharged, get to work.
Of course!
Neros!
See you.
Aine!
Aine?
A-Aine? What do you think you're doing?
It's supposed to be my turn next! No fair!
Talk about an annoying crowd.
Wha—
Aine?
Kizuna, do me right now.
Huh? But your Hybrid Count is still high.
I want to use the forbidden weapon
to change the course of this battle.
But that's...
Don't worry, Kizuna.
I'm me.
No matter what happens, that won't change.
So just do me...
Let's Climax Hybrid.
How about an apple, Snow White? Relax, it's safe
You know, that shit-eating grin really pisses me off
I'm gonna punch you
Forgive me for being cold to you
It's just that there was this girl looking at you in the cafe
I'm gonna kill her
She'd probably leave you before the night is over
Let me show you the storm of emotions trapped beneath the surface
Go beyond your dreams, love's waiting for you there
What do you want so badly that you'd cry for it?
All I want is your heart's warmth
There's no escape from the love that's seeping through your veins
Hold me, hold your breath
You're my prince
Just kidding
All right.
I'll take you someplace special.
Illustration
Hiroyuki Yoshikawa
Aine, ever since we met that day, I think I knew.
That I was here to protect you!
Me, too. I was able to really
feel it because I met you.
NEXT TIME
I'm not scared of anything anymore, Kizuna.