It's been a long time, Kizuna.
Mom...
What's going on?
Why is Dr. Nayuta here?
Let's leave this to Kizuna.
Dr. Nayuta...
Seven years and twenty-one days, huh?
You've grown a lot while I wasn't around.
What happened, Mom?
What are you doing here, on a Batlantis battleship?
Part of my field work.
I needed to travel to the
Batlantis Empire for my research.
Research?
You are not needed anymore.
There's so much I want to ask you.
But first, come back to Ataraxia.
We can talk then.
I can't.
My research isn't finished yet.
What the hell do you mean, "research"?!
That voice... Reiri, am I right?
Why are you in bed with the enemy?
What are you plotting?
Reiri, you can't understand
the meaning of my actions?
Hell no!
You really are stupid.
Oh, but there's no need to worry.
They say the stupider your child,
the more lovable they are.
And most people are stupid.
Kizuna!
Bring her back!
Mom!
A hologram?
Sorry, but that's all for today.
I just came to deliver a message to you.
If you want to see me, come to Tokyo.
I'm sure you'll find something
very interesting there.
To Tokyo?
And...
Bye, Kizuna.
I'll see you in Tokyo.
Wait!
I want you to do something
about everybody's cores!
How do you remove them?
How can I save them all?
Tell me!
Mom!
Um, we're done here.
Please leave.
Well, I'm not done!
Give me back my mom!
Kicking us out all of a sudden? How rude!
Kizuna!
Are you okay?
What was that?
Huh?
How's that feel?
I am the great Ragrus,
and this is my Magitech armor, Demon!
It's so huge!
Is that really a Heart Hybrid Gear?
Now come get some!
Take that! And that!
W-Wait!
Mom!
My love for you is like a bucking colt
You act so innocent, but I know you're feeling it
I'm not a wizard anymore
The craziest things you can imagine all start from nothing
It's like we're in a fairy tale
But this is real life
My charm makes you swoon
Our hearts beat in unison
Just let your passion explode
My feelings won't reach you like this
I need to shoot them at you with everything I've got
They're on a direct course to your heart
My spirit is on fire
I'll expose your true nature
Don't worry, I'll be gentle
I'll take you to a secret paradise
And offer you a grand feast
When the two of us become one
An innocent flower blooms
Why?
Episode 10
Eve of the Decisive Battle -Install-
Why do the proud royal guards
have to flee from the enemy?
Did you show mercy 'cause
they're fellow Lemurians?
That was our chance to catch Zeros!
I'm afraid our only goal there was to meet them.
Capturing Zeros wasn't part of the plan.
L-Lady Zelshione was aware of this...
Please wait a moment.
She told us to do everything Dr. Nayuta said.
But Dr. Nayuta...
Now that they know we'll be waiting for them,
will they really come to Tokyo?
They'll come, Varde.
After all, I set things up so they would.
What?
The plan to retake Tokyo was all a setup by Mom?
What are you saying, Sis?
Yeah.
Now I'm sure of it.
Kizuna, we found out about
your Eros unit's unique ability,
restoring Hybrid Counts through Heart Hybrids,
from data an anonymous source provided.
Someone sent it to us...
You don't mean...
The impetus for the operation to retake Tokyo
was the data we acquired that
allowed us to seal Entrances.
That data was also submitted
by an unknown party from Guam.
And you're saying that was Dr. Nayuta?
Only a genius scientist like Hida Nayuta would
be capable of putting together such perfect data.
So what do we do now, Sis?
We have to go.
No matter what's waiting for us.
Even if it's a trap set by a witch.
That's what I like to hear.
Aine?
Don't make weird noises.
I'll just obey orders if I have to, is all.
Wait, Aine!
Oh, dear. It's like she's back to the old Aine.
Wait, Kizuna.
There's something else I need to tell you.
What?
A new Amaterasu candidate?
We need talented people to take back Tokyo.
But that means installing
a Heart Hybrid Gear core, right?
In other words...
I'm aware.
I'm no better than that woman.
Still, we can't afford to lose this fight
if we want this war to end someday.
Sis...
This is the list of candidates.
Th-This is...
Okay, see you tomorrow, Sylvia!
Bye-bye, Sylvia!
Bye!
Okay, what should I cook today?
Sylvia!
Captain?
You want me to be a Heart Hybrid Gear pilot?
Y-Yeah...
You've got the grades and aptitude for it.
Then I can be a part of Amaterasu too, can't I?
No, you should think about it
more carefully before you decide.
This is an important decision for you.
Nobody will complain if you turn down this chance.
Captain?
I won't force you.
If you don't want to, you don't have to.
You don't have to fight.
Why are you saying that?
I'm saying you don't have to force yourself to fight.
You don't think I'm good enough, Captain?
It was always my dream...
But you don't want me in Amaterasu, do you?
N-No, Sylvia!
I just...
Forget it!
Sylvia!
Why?
Am I that useless, Captain?
But everybody's fighting...
I want to go back to London.
Sylvia...
Let me go!
Wait.
I don't want you to die.
Captain...
Not just you.
I don't want anyone to die.
I couldn't give that order.
Guess that makes me a failure as a captain, huh?
I've always wanted to be a part of Amaterasu.
So I could find my parents
who went missing in London.
But now I have another goal!
I'm begging you!
Let me fight with you.
Let me fight for you!
Let me join Amaterasu!
Sylvia...
This room is so cute!
It's supposed to be a lab...
Listen, Sylvia.
Y-Yes?
I'm about to install this core in you.
The way this core works, uh...
I have to be the one to do it.
I don't mind if it's you, Captain...
No, I want you to do it!
Oh, then... um...
Well?
Do I look weird?
You're pretty.
I'm glad.
Good work, Sylvia.
Captain...
I love you.
I guess she still needs tuning before she can sortie.
I won't let anyone die.
I'll save them all.
And to do that...
Mom!
I'll bring you back!
The mission starts tomorrow.
Hurry!
Everyone, the Engineering Division
comes bearing gifts!
Wow! Amazing!
Anti-Magitech particle rifles and the new railguns!
Anti-materiel rifles!
My lil' Luger too!
Lil' Luger?
That's its name!
Isn't it cute?
Well, this is enough to make sure
we succeed tomorrow, right?
We can't let Amaterasu outshine us!
Let's show them what the Masters can do!
Yes, ma'am!
By the way, where are all
the members of Amaterasu?
Figured you'd be here.
I like looking at the sea.
And being alone when I do it.
It's fine. You don't have to say anything.
It would make me happy if you just left, though.
U-Um...
Are you worried about me?
If you are, I'm fine now.
But because of, uh, how things went last time,
you haven't done your Heart Hybrid yet.
I just said I'm fine.
Are you so stupid that you can't
understand something that simple?
Aine...
Sheesh...
That wasn't like me.
Bawling all over an Eros Overlord like you
just because I had a weird dream.
It's the biggest mistake of my life!
And the worst moment of my life to boot.
What?
I was just worried about you...
I'm me.
No one but Chidorigafuchi Aine.
Right?
I'm looking forward to tomorrow.
As the best pilot in the universe, I can't wait.
Aine...
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Self-Study!!
On Account of Operation
Take Back Tokyo
Tokyo, huh?
"Ah, how I've missed my beloved hometown"...
probably isn't what you're thinking, right?
That's right.
When I heard we were going back to Tokyo,
to be honest, I was scared...
Scared that my past might crush me again.
But now I can look forward to the future.
And it's all thanks to Kizuna.
That's right.
Same here.
I was able to change because of Kizuna.
I finally realized that it's okay
to rely more on others.
Though it's a little upsetting that a single boy
like him was enough to change me.
It's not just that something's changed.
It feels like something new has begun.
Something new has begun, huh?
Is something beginning for her too?
This is where it all began, right?
Hey, what's wrong?
Why are you crying?
I don't know...
You don't know why you're crying?
I don't know anything about myself...
H-Hey...
Then I'll think with you.
If you don't know,
then I'll think with you and figure it out.
So...
That's right.
No matter how stubborn
and strong-willed she may act,
she's a crybaby,
and just like any other girl at heart.
Back then...
What would've happened
if I hadn't grabbed her hand?
Well? Get any sleep last night?
Yup. Don't worry.
I slept great.
Hi, Kizuna!
Kizuna.
Aine, I'll make sure you're...
Let's go!
Magitech weapons, codename Vikings,
have landed on Ataraxia!
They got here first?
They're over here too!
Fire! Fire!
Leave this to us!
Just make sure you get to Tokyo!
Scarlet!
Got it!
Let's go!
Eros!
Kuros!
Neros!
Zeros!
Amaterasu has taken off!
Wow! Quite the welcome party!
This much was expected!
Everyone split up and head
for the designated points!
Roger!
I can see it!
Fly low and quiet...
Where should I land?
There!
Okay.
Point A setup complete.
About damn time!
Here we go!
It's finally here!
The goddamn data from Point A is here!
Good.
We're getting data from points B, C, and D too.
Analyzing data.
Entrance coordinates confirmed.
Launch the second team!
Set the sealing system up immediately
and close the Entrances!
Roger!
I'm counting on you, everyone!
Now I just have to cause some serious damage!
If you want a decoy operation,
I'll give you a huge one!
What?
What's going on here?
How about an apple, Snow White? Relax, it's safe
You know, that shit-eating grin really pisses me off
I'm gonna punch you
Forgive me for being cold to you
It's just that there was this girl looking at you in the cafe
I'm gonna kill her
She'd probably leave you before the night is over
Let me show you the storm of emotions trapped beneath the surface
Go beyond your dreams, love's waiting for you there
What do you want so badly that you'd cry for it?
All I want is your heart's warmth
There's no escape from the love that's seeping through your veins
Hold me, hold your breath
You're my prince
Just kidding
Illustration
Ken Takahashi
We've finally returned to the homeland
that's been stolen from us.
And now there's only one thing left for us to do:
take it all back!
Come on, Hayuru.
Don't worry about the complicated stuff.
NEXT TIME
Operation Take Back Tokyo -Apocalypse-
Let's just break some things!