Time Remaining
Mock Exam
60 mins
Section 2     Answer the following (A-C)           (44 points)
.         Choose the most appropriate phrase to fill in the blanks in the following sentences.
Mock Exam
60 mins
Stop, Papika! Get back here!
But this was another bust.
I'll go by myself!
Looking for a candidate on foot is highly inefficient.
Don't care!
Dr. Salt?
STOP
Thanks for the welcome party!
Later!
Brr! It's cold!
Whoa, look at the bright lights!
Yahoo!
into the sky
move through the white
anata wa sugu ni anata wo
You're always hard on yourself
tada no mono dato sagesumu
Claiming that you're just a tool
watashi wa sonna anata wo
And that's why
dakishimeru tsumori sa
I've got you in my arms
guuzen sekai ga katachi wo kaetato shitemo
Even if the world suddenly became unrecognizable
anata ga ireba nannidemo nareru ki ga shita
I'm confident I can be anything if I'm with you
masshiro na
Let's search
yume wo atsume ni ikou
Till we find some snow white dreams
bouken ga
Our adventures
iro wo tsumuide iku yo
Will color in all of those lines
majiwaru
Blending
fumihazusu
Slipping
kawaridasu
Changing into
mirai ga kirameiteru yo
A future, shimmering
noriokurenaide
Don't you dare miss it
tooku demo zutto soba ni iru
We're always together no matter how far apart
tsunagu kokoro zutto hanasanai
I won't let go of this heart that draws me to you
Who are you?
Welcome back.
Good morning, Cocona.
Good morning.
What's the matter?
Did you have a bad dream?
Nah.
Were you up late reading again?
Which one should I pick?
Hmm?
Nothing.
I'm off.
Cocona!
We can still make the train!
Smoke?
Stupid.
You still can't decide?
I don't know which is right for me.
Please excuse me.
Oh, Cocona.
You got called to the office?
Our choices for the mock exams
are due by the end of today.
Oh, right. They are...
Just kill me now...
Write down where you want to go.
It could be a step towards your dream job
or a school that suits your hobbies.
Some just pick the school closest to home.
Any reason is fine.
You still can't decide?
What's the big deal? You could get in anywhere.
I don't want to go "anywhere".
There's my list.
I'll keep these in mind.
Thank you, Cocona-san.
Sorry about that. I know you're not on duty.
It's okay. You have a patient.
Where are you going?
Somewhere I can concentrate.
Excuse me.
Goodbye.
Go home if you're feeling sick.
Yeah, I know...
Wanna check out that shop by the station?
A storage space?
Uh, that's a boys' school.
Take this seriously, Yayaka.
What should I do?
Found you!
You're... from this morning...
Hey, hey, hey. What are you doing?
I should be asking you that.
What are you doing here?
I was sleeping.
You took so long to show up, Cocona.
Wha—
I waited forever for you.
Sniff...
Sniff, sniff, sniff.
Wh-What's with you? Who are you?!
Papika.
Papika?
Hey, come with me!
Where?
Er...
P-Puey? Pew?
What was it, again?
Pure Illusion.
TT-392 has secured Papika.
Is she a possible candidate?
Put them to the test.
Palpation time!
Try sending them through!
TOUCH
S-Stop it!
Hey!
Stop!
No!
Please, don't!
You're alive!
Let go of me!
Where are we?
This isn't inside the pipe...
Lookie there.
A way out?
Let's find out!
Cocona!
So cool!
It's all white!
This is totally super cool!
No way.
How?
Where is everyone?
Where did the school go?
This is Pure Illusion.
Welcome to Pure Illusion.
Pure Illusion?
Cocona!
Amazing! We made it!
We made it!
Wanna see what's over there?
Coming?
Wait!
Hup!
SEARCH
Grandma
No Signal
Is this a dream?
I think I've read about lucid dreams somewhere...
Come play, Cocona!
Why, you...
You're silly!
It's sweet...
What's sweet?
The snow.
You'll get an upset stomach.
It is sweet!
Really sweet.
Yeah.
You little...
Come on, Cocona.
Freeze!
Cocona, what are those?
Ghosts?
Hoarfrost?
Frost... what?
The wind blows ice onto the trees.
Wow...
I've never seen them before.
Let's go say hi!
Hey! I was using those to mark the path!
They're yummy!
Snow?
Let's go ahead and make camp, Cocona.
Huh? We're sleeping here?
Hurry! Come on!
Before it gets dark!
Cocona! Cocona!
Look, look!
Cocona?
What is this place, really?
Everyone's just hiding from us, right?
It's okay. I promise.
What is?
Aren't you scared?
Nah. I've got you.
And Bu-chan's here, too.
Let's go on a treasure hunt tomorrow, Cocona.
Treasure hunt?
It's somewhere out here in Pure Illusion.
Something that can grant wishes.
Also, it smells nice.
Smells nice? Like, food?
It smells like you.
Back off!
What was that?
Can you go find out?
Bu-chan!
Um, uh...
What do we do?
No clue.
Are those the hoarfrosts?
醒
AWAKEN
He's alive again!
My glasses are gone.
Glasses?
Did I drop them somewhere?
Your glasses!
It took them.
Oh, no...
Got it.
Hold on tight.
Glasses, glasses...
Found them!
This is challenging.
Hey! Do you want to get killed?!
I'm just trying to get your glasses back.
But it'll be hard to find them if they fall in there.
What are they doing?
Bu-chan!
Wait here.
No!
Wait!
Hup.
O-Ow...
No biggie... I'm fine...
That's enough!
Forget the glasses!
I don't need them! Just get back here!
Stop it! You'll die!
Just come back, hurry!
Just...
a little more...
Come on... Why did you do that?
I told you I didn't need them.
Papika...
Papika.
Papika!
You idiot.
Cocona?
Papika.
Look, I found them.
They're cracked a bit.
Wow, Cocona!
Is it really you, Cocona?
How?
How? How?!
S-Stop it! What's gotten into you?
You look awesome!
How'd you get like that?
What the heck?!
Lucky you.
No! Why?
Why? Why?!
What is this?
It's warm.
Cocona.
Let's go adventuring again, okay?
No thanks.
kossori socchi wo nozoitara
One day I thought I would sneak a peek at you,
socchi mo kocchi wo nozoiteta
But there you were, looking back at me
hitomi no oku ochiteyuku
I went and fell deep inside your eyes
koko wa doko nano kana
Lost, I thought, "Now, where could I have gone?"
sotto te wo tsunaidara
When I hold your hands, enclosed in mine,
tottemo yawarakakatta
Oh so soft, like a lamb freshly sheared
onnaji you ni kanjiteiru to
And I knew, I just knew, without a reason why
nazeka wakarun da
That you felt the same way as me
anata ga miteiru mono wo
I saw it there as you tried to wipe them off,
utsushiteiru dripping tears
Someone just like me, dripping tears
tokei wo sakasama ni tadotte ita
Always chasing the clock the wrong way, here we are
dripping
Dripping
flip flap flip flap
Flip! Flap! Flip! Flap!
tooi koe wo
When I open it
flip flap flip flap
Flip! Flap! Flip! Flap!
tojikometa
This little locked-up box
kagi no kakatta
It's filled up to the brim
hako wo hiraitara
With distant voices
hora hirogaru yo
Look, they spread, they fill us up, so
flip flap flip flap
Flip! Flap! Flip! Flap!
hoshi no hikari mo
Even the stars around us
flip flap flip flap
Flip! Flap! Flip! Flap!
tobihaneteiru
They go and dance around
nikkou fushigi na matataki ga
The twinkling, mysterious sunlight on high
michiibiiteru sekai
Like a guide to ends of this world
anata to futari de
And now with you, together we...
flip flap
Flip! Flap!
What? Why not?!
Let's go!
No, thank you!
What was that earlier?
You mean Pure Illusion?
Was it a dream?
Or, like, another dimension or a parallel world?
Parallel?
Cocona, what's that in your hand?
This?
A fragment was brought back?
Sniff, sniff.
You think this is the...
Ow...
Papika!
Cocona!
Cocona! Cocona!
Next time on Flip Flappers: "Pure—
Cocona! Let's go adventuring together!
Hey! Don't interrupt me!
Pure Converter
Next Episode
Next time, "Pure—
Cocona, Cocona!
Next time!