Good morning, Cocona.
Good morning.
What's the matter?
Did you have a bad dream?
Nah.
I'm off.
Hey.
They said it was my "final warning" for being late.
What's wrong? Muscle pain?
Maybe I slept on it wrong?
You again?!
What the heck?
Yoohoo, Cocona!
Papika?!
in
to
the
sky
move
through
the
white
You're always hard on yourself
Claiming that you're just a tool
And that's why
I've got you in my arms
Even if the world suddenly became unrecognizable
I'm confident I can be anything if I'm with you
mas
shi
ro
na
Let's search
Till we find some snow white dreams
bou
ke
n
ga
Our adventures
Will color in all of those lines
ma
ji
wa
ru
Blending
Slipping
Changing into
A future, shimmering
Don't you dare miss it
We're always together no matter how far apart
I won't let go of this heart that draws me to you
So who're you?
Papika.
Who're you?
Like I'm gonna tell you.
No fair!
You know her?
Nope.
Hey! Cocona!
What's the deal?
I've got school now.
I need to hurry.
Get on, then.
Here we are.
Look, you...
Are those injuries...
Are you okay?
They didn't do anything weird to you?
Stop it! I'm fine!
Thank goodness.
The fragment's safe, too.
Is that it?
The wishing thing?
Yep.
Apparently, we still need more.
Let's go look for them again sometime!
If you want to go, count me out.
I can't do it by myself!
The tunnel only opens up if our feelings are in tune.
I'm not strong enough to go alone.
But I finally found a partner!
I don't care.
But wasn't adventuring with me fun?
Let go of me!
You okay?
Let me make this clear.
Non-students aren't allowed on school grounds.
You'll be removed if they find you.
What was that all about?
Long story.
Cocona?
Uexküll came with me!
Oh, whatever.
It is not whatever!
What do I do?
Good day!
Papika?!
Cocona!
Cocona, Cocona, Cocona!
Seriously, what's your problem?
What was my line here?
I'm a transfer student!
"...it passes the big ship and finally
disappears again into the depths,
sputtering on the water
as though the burning tongs
had been suddenly"—Quiet.
You're awesome!
Cocona!
Want some tamagoyaki?
Hey, why don't you join the basketball team?
Cocona!
Thanks.
Uexküll.
Uexküll?
Found you!
Sniff, sniff, sniff, sniff.
Are you gonna eat here?
What do you think you're doing?
What's with this "transfer student" stuff?
If I'm a transfer student, I can be near you.
Salt said so.
Who?
An important person in FlipFlap.
Did he order you to come here?
No.
I found you myself.
So, anyway, let's go adventuring after school—
I've got cram school after.
Wait.
I'm going to the bathroom. Don't follow me.
Me, too.
Wait up!
Leave me alone!
Cocona.
Cocona!
Is she gone?
Seems so.
Thanks.
Wait.
Yayaka?
It's nothing.
You gotta be direct with people like her,
or they won't get it.
Yeah.
You softie.
Nurse's Office
What do you think?
It's... scary.
But...
But?
Nothing.
Come visit the art club sometime.
I love this painting, too.
Cocona! I've been waiting!
Ow...
Uexküll!
Cocona!
Don't hold him by the ears.
He's terrified of you!
Sheesh.
Before the teachers see him, I have to—
Uexküll! Uexküll!
Hey! Hey!
He's not coming out.
That does it.
This stuff always happens when I'm around you!
Why are you like this?!
You're wild, pushy, and have no sense of danger!
What if you got killed?!
You can't take that back!
Take... back?
Even then...
I thought you'd die.
Go away, and don't come back.
I don't want to go on your stupid adventures.
Cocona...
I heard a cry.
Uxe...kill? What was it, again?
Uexküll.
Uexküll!
Papika?
Is that you, Papika?
Cocona!
Sniff, sniff, sniff...
Papika?
Is that you, Papika?
That...
That tickles!
Papika.
Your ears...
You've got them, too.
No!
I've got all this fur all over!
What do I do?!
Bite, bite, bite, bite...
Is that really safe to bite?
I donno, bud my jaw feews weawy westwess for some weason.
You wanna nibbly-nib, doo?
N-No way.
I'd never do anything so unseemly.
Uexküll?
He ended up here, too?
Where are you going?
To look for Uexküll.
What? But what about the fragments?
Weren't you listening to what I said earlier?
You stay right where you are.
Or else you'll cause another disaster.
Cocona, wait!
Uexküll!
Oh, c'mon...
That looks hard...
Not again.
What's going on?
No. Absolutely not.
You can't nibbly-nib.
Cocona?
What's wrong, Cocona?
You okay?
No! Don't look!
Cocona... Cocona!
No!
Hup...
How much longer, Bu-chan?
Wow.
It's really hard.
Got it!
What's happening?
Cocona!
Cocona! Cocona!
Papika!
Cocona!
Are you...
Uexküll?
Cocona!
Blood
But Cocona's...
Papika!
Cocona's...
Cocona!
This stuff always happens when I'm around you!
Even then...
I thought you'd die.
Cocona!
Papika?
Cocona! Thank goodness!
Papika...
What happened to you?
I feel kinda buzzy now.
What is this about "buzzy"?
Who's that?
This is...
Run for it!
Where?
Is that the way out?
I'm going.
Papika?
Come with me.
I swear I won't let you go.
You'd better not, Papika.
Got it!
It didn't work!
No, it stopped for a second!
I'll do the countdown!
Okay!
Three...
Two...
One...
Go!
Ow...
Uexküll.
I'm glad you're okay.
Cocona...
Now I get why you said you
didn't want to go adventuring.
I thought you were going to die, too.
Sorry.
But it was fun.
That last bit was awesome.
Will you go back again?
Yeah, I want to.
You don't learn, huh?
Well, I don't mind going
with you every now and then.
Okay...
Huh?
Only every now and then. And only if I feel like it.
痛
Pain
Cocona! Cocona!
痛
Pain
Jeez, only every now and then, okay? You got it?
痛
Pain
Cocona!
Where are we going?
To FlipFlap.
I need to introduce you to everyone.
I'm back!
Welcome back.
That must be your partner.
Nice to meet you. I'm Sayuri.
Nice to meet you.
Let's see...
Wh-What is it?
So you're Cocona.
Dr. Salt.
That's Salt.
Keep a fragment on you.
Take them to the Thomasson.
Got it.
Let's go.
Wait!
We call the world you went to Pure Illusion.
Retrieving the fragments scattered there
is your job for the foreseeable future.
Both them are ready to go!
Roger.
Let's get started, then.
Job?
Uh, working is against school rules—
No problem. There's no pay involved.
Papika?
Cocona.
It's okay.
Papika.
Dr. Salt, impedance is approaching zero.
Begin.
Um...
Salt-san.
What are these fragments?
Why are you collecting them?
To liberate Pure Illusion.
Here we go, Cocona.
What is this?
One day I thought I would sneak a peek at you,
kossori socchi wo nozoitara
But there you were, looking back at me
socchi mo kocchi wo nozoiteta
I went and fell deep inside your eyes
hitomi no oku ochiteyuku
Lost, I thought, "Now, where could I have gone?"
koko wa doko nano kana
When I hold your hands, enclosed in mine,
sotto te wo tsunaidara
Oh so soft, like a lamb freshly sheared
tottemo yawarakakatta
And I knew, I just knew, without a reason why
onnaji you ni kanjiteiru to
That you felt the same way as me
nazeka wakarun da
I saw it there as you tried to wipe them off,
anata ga miteiru mono wo
Someone just like me, dripping tears
utsushiteiru dripping tears
Always chasing the clock the wrong way, here we are
tokei wo sakasama ni tadotte ita
Dripping
dripping
Flip! Flap! Flip! Flap!
flip flap flip flap
When I open it
tooi koe wo
Flip! Flap! Flip! Flap!
flip flap flip flap
This little locked-up box
tojikometa
It's filled up to the brim
kagi no kakatta
With distant voices
hako wo hiraitara
Look, they spread, they fill us up, so
hora hirogaru yo
Flip! Flap! Flip! Flap!
flip flap flip flap
Even the stars around us
hoshi no hikari mo
Flip! Flap! Flip! Flap!
flip flap flip flap
They go and dance around
tobihaneteiru
The twinkling, mysterious sunlight on high
nikkou fushigi na matataki ga
Like a guide to ends of this world
michiibiiteru sekai
And now with you, together we...
anata to futari de
Flip! Flap!
flip flap
Next time on Flip Flappers:
"Pure—
Hey, Hidaka-san!
What?
Wasn't last month's electricity bill way too high?
Uh, well...
Pure XLR
Next Episode
Do you have to make upgrades that often?!
Retreat!
He ran away?!