Everyone thinks and everyone lives
Good morning to you, cock-a-doodle-doo!
Luluco
You just have to accept that everything is simply weird
All of your dreams can come true
Alpha-Omega
Nova
Both the big-brained and the bird-brained
Are saying "nice to meet you," cock-a-doodle-doo!
Midori
Suddenly you pretend to be a lantern
And throw important information at me
I'm going now, so get ready, future!
SPACE PATROL LULUCO
I'm Luluco.
This is my dad.
He may look kind of messed up right now,
but he was a good father.
I wish I could've helped him return to normal.
My mom...
I never would've guessed
she'd become a space pirate.
But I'm glad that she seemed to be doing well.
I wonder where she went after I last saw her...
Midori and the chief looked scary,
but they were both nice people.
The secretary was a silent one.
I wonder what she really thought of us...
Oh, this is a picture we took
before we all set off into space.
I hope they're all doing okay.
They—
Man, my life sure didn't amount to much.
I was only thirteen...
But to be honest,
I'm more hurt by Nova's betrayal
than my own death.
Where am I?
Is this Hell?
Did I do something that bad?
Who goes there?
Ch-Chief?
Oh, it's just the Space Patrol.
What are you doing here, Chief?
You've got the wrong guy.
I've never been the boss of anyone.
Sorry. It's just that you look a lot like my chief.
I look like Chief Over Justice?
What a funny joke!
You know the chief?
I know him very well.
I used to be in the Space Patrol too, you know.
I guess that makes you my predecessor...
Want some? It's delicious.
No, thanks.
I just died, so I don't have much of an appetite.
That so?
I was in love with someone.
But he betrayed me, and I died.
I probably died with a horrified look on my face.
If only I'd doubted him a little...
If only I hadn't loved him so much,
this wouldn't have happened.
But now that I'm dead, it's all over.
Everything is finished.
No, it's not.
So long as evil exists,
justice will never be finished.
I died a bunch of times too,
but I came back to life every single time.
So justice will never die?
Normally, no.
Is that normal?
Others don't get to dictate
what's normal and what isn't.
It's something we decide for ourselves.
That's why it's the most important thing to us.
If you wanna leave, take that exit.
Ogikubo East
Hell Exit
Hell ain't big enough for two agents of justice.
But how do I face him once I go back?
What should I say to the guy who betrayed me?
You were betrayed, huh?
What kinda lies did he tell you?
No, I wasn't betrayed.
He never once lied to me.
I'd just assumed he wasn't an enemy
because we were both in the Space Patrol.
Nova had always been himself!
Police never operate on
a different moral compass.
They just use the ones
they have as regular people.
Not yet. It's not over yet!
My first love isn't over just yet!
I have to tell him clearly how I feel,
and ask him how he truly feels about me.
So what if he's a minion of the Blackholeians?
My feelings for him won't go away
just because they were stolen from me!
My first love will sprout
as many times as it takes!
See? You do get it.
If something's truly precious to you,
it'll never disappear.
Especially if it's something intangible.
I'm gonna go confess to him...
And then I'll place him under arrest.
I'm part of the Space Patrol.
I can't stay dead here.
Atta girl. Go get 'em.
A middle schooler in love
for the first time is invincible.
What matters is expressing your love
to the object of your affection.
Everything after that is just a bonus.
Thank you, mister!
Don't be callin' me that.
I'm only 21, you know!
I hope you can arrest him.
Yeah!
I'm gonna arrest him for sure!
After all, he shoplifted
my most prized possession!
Justice... Justice... Justice...
Luluco...
Space Patrol Luluco...
L-L...
Luluco came back to life!
Yay!
It's a miracle of justice!
Justice is a miracle!
Sorry, guys.
Looks like I won't be dying just yet.
After all, this is still to be continued!
I'm searching the entire galaxy for you
Going from one planet to the next
I'm broadcasting my feelings of love to you, beep, beep
So please receive them!
They float gently
In this endless universe
I've locked on to that heart of yours
So you will never be able to run away
I want you to hold my hand
To make my head spin like a merry-go-round
To make my heart skip a beat
The world will be dyed in the colors of my love