Both the big-brained and the bird-brained
Are singing out loud because they want you, cock-a-doodle-doo!
Luluco
They need to do it before their life runs out
All of your dreams can come true!
Alpha-Omega
Nova
Common sense is a good morning call
To keeping the status quo, cock-a-doodle-doo!
Midori
So plan out your life and sew out the mysteries
Every Friday is my birthday!
The planet is still blue today?!
SPACE PATROL LULUCO
I'm Luluco.
It turns out that Alpha-Omega Nova,
the transfer student who showed up in a meteorite,
was part of the Space Patrol, just like I am!
In order to find Save the World,
the alien circulating a quasi-legal Black Hole app,
Shoplifting
we have to start investigating
our school as members of the Space Patrol!
v v                Today's lucky sign: Sagittarius!                v v                Good morning!             This is Space Middle School.                v v                This week's slogan: Hard Work, Victory, and Smiles!                v v
All right. Let's look for the culprit together.
Let's start with the east wing.
v v                Today's lucky sign: Sagittarius!                v v                Good morning!             This is Space Middle School.                v v                This week's slogan: Hard Work, Victory, and Smiles!                v v
How about you investigate
the east wing while I check the west?
v v                Today's lucky sign: Sagittarius!                v v                Good morning!             This is Space Middle School.                v v                This week's slogan: Hard Work, Victory, and Smiles!                v v
v v                Today's lucky sign: Sagittarius!                v v                Good morning!             This is Space Middle School.                v v                This week's slogan: Hard Work, Victory, and Smiles!                v v                Today's lucky sign: Sagittarius!                v v                Good morning!             This is Space Middle School.
v v                Today's lucky sign: Sagittarius!                v v                Good morning!             This is Space Middle School.                v v                This week's slogan: Hard Work, Victory, and Smiles!                v v                Today's lucky sign: Sagittarius!                v v                Good morning!             This is Space Middle School.                                Today's lucky sign: Sagittarius!                v v                Good morning!             This is Space Middle School.
v v                Today's lucky sign: Sagittarius!                v v                Good morning!             This is Space Middle School.                v v                This week's slogan: Hard Work, Victory, and Smiles!                v v
v v                Today's lucky sign: Sagittarius!                v v                Good morning!             This is Space Middle School.                v v                This week's slogan: Hard Work, Victory, and Smiles!                v v                Today's lucky sign: Sagittarius!                v v                Good morning!             This is Space Middle School.
But you just transferred in and probably don't know
much about the school. You should stick with me.
We can't search efficiently if we don't split up.
I guess you're right...
"Save the World"...
The name kinda sounds evil, but I don't
remember anyone called that at our school.
Hey, Midori!
Oh, it's you, Luluco.
I'm looking out for someone selling
a quasi-legal Black Hole app here at school.
Ya want it too?
Well, it is convenient.
It can get ya money or anything else ya want.
Anything?
Yep, anything.
Even a boy, a boyfriend, or an ex-boyfriend!
A boyfriend?!
W-Well, I don't exactly want the app...
Well, ya don't have to buy it.
Why don'cha check it out though?
And if ya like it, ya can think about buying it then.
I-I guess I could check it out...
Yeah, I'll just check it out.
I mean, I have to check it out anyway!
Yeah! Just check it out!
Gimme a sec. I'll go get it for ya.
Get a grip, Luluco!
I'm really close to getting a lead on the culprit!
Gotta focus on the investigation!
Hello, Nova? I've got trouble here!
Looks like it.
You were here?!
Madame Save the World!
This is awful!
Huh?
That fool who got caught
last week spilled the beans!
The po-po are gonna find out who's been
distributin' the quasi-legal Black Hole app!
We're gonna get raided by the Space Patrol!
The Space Patrol?
Gangsters ain't worth jack
if people look down on 'em.
We gotta get the jump on 'em!
Hold yer horses.
They aren't gonna be able to raid us just yet.
Let's take our time and think this over.
This is the Space Patrol!
We've got all the evidence we need! Surrender—
What?! Luluco?!
You were Space Patrol?!
You were Save the World?!
That's right.
I'm Midori "Save the World".
So, ya gonna buy this?
Shoplifting
You'll sell it to me?
How 'bout it?
Shoplifting
I-I don't want it!
You little shit!
M-Midori, you're under arrest
for violating the Ogikubo Space Law!
If you're Space Patrol,
I'm not gonna go easy on ya.
Looks like ya won't learn
yer lesson until ya get hurt.
Can I shoot her now?
Not yet, Nova!
She's a classmate, so let's try
to resolve this without gunfire!
That sounds like a pain.
Oh, you're the transfer student
that came in the meteorite!
Shoplifting.
Shoplifting
Whoops, I got captured.
Darn.
Nova!
All the hotties in this world belong to me.
Get her!
You got it, ma'am!
I'mma whoop her ass!
I can't just open fire out of nowhere.
I've gotta find a way to resolve this without firing!
You're dead, girl!
Somehow...
Without firing, somehow!
On second thought, I'm firing!
Fight for Justice!
You'll pay for this!
Give Nova back!
He doesn't belong to ya!
I don't mind either way.
If you don't mind either way...
...then come back to me!
I can't let you have him!
We're gonna kill you, Space Patrol!
Fight for... Fight for... Fight for... Fight for...
I feel like I can shoot a whole lot today!
Justice!
I'll get my revenge!
Damn, they all got taken out.
Don't waste time resisting, Midori.
Just surrender quietly.
As if! Business is finally booming at school.
I'm not gonna get caught now!
Eat this!
Fight for Justice!
Stop it, Nova!
I'm not the one shooting.
Shoplifting
I can't believe Nova fell into enemy hands!
If I shoot now, I might hit him, too.
What should I do?
Don't worry about me, Luluco.
But...
If you can't resolve this without firing,
then you have to fire.
Shoplifting
You have to fire.
I have to fire...
No way! I can't do it!
Where are ya even aimin'?
You're never gonna stop me—
I did it! I arrested her!
I'm sorry.
I fired, even though I might've hit you.
No need to apologize.
You did what you had to do.
"What I had to do"?
Work with the Space Patrol,
turn Dad back to normal, and then...
And then what?
You shoot enemies with your gun.
It's perfectly normal.
It does require some resolve, though.
Bastards...
So much has happened today,
I'm not sure what I want
to do now or in the future.
It's not that complicated.
Just stay the way you are.
That's what suits you best.
So, I should stay normal?
No, you should stay wonderful.
I'm searching the entire galaxy for you
Shall we head back to the station?
Just a bit longer...
Going from one planet to the next
Okay.
Let's head back.
I'm broadcasting my feelings of love to you, beep, beep
So please receive them!
They float gently
In this endless universe
I've locked on to that heart of yours
So you will never be able to run away
I want you to hold my hand
To make my head spin like a merry-go-round
To make my heart skip a beat
The world will be dyed in the colors of my love
Space Patrol
Brilliant work, you two!
Especially you, Luluco.
By stamping out the evil
in your middle school so quickly,
you showed that you truly are
your righteous father's daughter.
Thank you...
So like, Nova, do ya always
come here after school?
That's right.
I'm with the Space Patrol, too.
For real?
Then maybe I should be
in the Space Patrol, too.
Hey, old man.
Uh, I feel really bad about what I did,
so I'll learn my lesson.
'Kay, lesson learned.
So let me join the Space Patrol and, like,
do that arrestin' stuff with Nova, 'kay?
Do me a solid, won't ya?
Anyone who breaks the law
even once is a criminal!
And criminals must be executed!
I told ya, that was my bad and I'm sorry.
I apologized, so give it a rest! Or I'll kill ya!
Very well.
I welcome you aboard the Space Patrol.
No one has ever volunteered
to join the Space Patrol before.
I shall place my hopes in your unprecedented,
as yet undefined justice.
Hooray!
And thus, the peaceful days
returned to my school once more.
Though I get the feeling that my life has
become the complete opposite of normal!
To be continued, though!