We've come a really long way by believing in ourselves
Even the most impossible dreams can come true
Luluco
Humanity and their lives depend only on them!
We learned that only waiting doesn't lead to anything
Alpha-Omega
Nova
Now it's time to see the greatest outcomes with our own eyes
Midori
There's nothing better than experiencing it ourselves
So let's go! Keep trying our best!
You are the future!
SPACE PATROL LULUCO
I'm Luluco.
I got stuck traveling the
universe looking for Ogikubo.
I'm happy that Nova's here with me, though.
We got an Ogikubo signal from that planet?
Indeed. Ogilog says 3.7 stars!
Magic Planet
3.7? Dayum!
Two of us will investigate the planet this time.
All right!
It will be Nova and... M—
Me! Pick me!
Make sure you get souvenirs, Luluco.
Shit!
I wanna go on a date with Nova, too!
As for Midori...
My flames seem to have grown smaller,
so chop up some firewood of justice for me.
Whaddya mean, firewood?!
Want me to chop up yer sunglasses?!
We'll be on our way, then.
I wish yer flame would go out!
Please leave my sunglasses alone.
Go out!
This place is amazing!
It reminds me of Europe.
Not that I've ever been there...
Don't you think so, Nova?
Really?
Gulp!
What do I do?
I-If I don't strike up a conversation,
he'll think I'm boring as shit!
I need some kind of topic that people
normally talk about on dates!
A-Apparently a Westernunian got
arrested for space fraud yesterday!
He posed as an African prince and robbed
a senior citizen of 100 trillion ZWD!
He's been sentenced to 30,000
light years in prison for his crime!
...Interesting.
Why did I pick such a weird topic?!
I'm such an idiot!
Curse those stupid affiliate blogs!
It's an unidentified flying object.
A witch? Is that a witch?!
Ogilog says in fine print that
this place hosts an academy for witches.
Witches? Really?
Not good. An academy for
witches will be full of girls.
Nova's so handsome, who knows what those
boy-starved witches will do if they find him?
Let's go back, Nova.
It's Ogikubo. It's Ogikubo. It's Ogikubo.
Ogikubo's not here after all.
I hear something ringing.
Never mind that! Let's just leave!
Oh, come on!
Wow, the Ogikubo reading's off the charts.
Ogikubo
(OGKB)
That Way
Ogikubo
(OGKB)
That Way
Ogikubo
(OGKB)
That Way
Ogikubo
(OGKB)
That Way
Ogikubo
(OGKB)
That Way
Ogikubo
(OGKB)
That Way
Ogikubo
(OGKB)
That Way
Over there, huh?
It's up really high.
Let's have the witches fly
us there on their brooms.
No! That's a very bad idea!
Awaken: Judgment Gun Morphing!
I'll go check it out.
Make sure the witches don't find you!
Ow!
So that's Ogikubo?
Okay, I'm almost there.
Ow! Ow!
What are you doing?!
Right back at you.
I won't let you steal the Sorcerer's Stone.
You gun goblin, you!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Stop it! That kinda hurts!
Go to hell! Damn you!
Take...
This! And this! And this!
H-Hey! What are you doing?!
What the hell?! Don't put stuff in there!
Luluco, there was a staircase over there.
Knock it off!
Awaken: Judgment Gun Morphing!
Huh, did something just...
Is that a spell that turns you into a gun?
Who are you?
I'm Sucy. Sucy Manbavaran.
I'm a student at this magic academy.
Oh, it's a stone imbued with power?
It seems the Sorcerer's Stone
has power similar to Ogikubo's.
Guess it wasn't our Ogikubo after all.
That's too bad. We should
move on to the next place.
There won't be a next place.
Those poisonous mushrooms you just
consumed cause death in six minutes.
Three have already passed,
so your remaining life span is three minutes.
You can't just abruptly tell me
I don't have much time left!
Fix it with your magic!
Not everything can be solved with magic.
Life ain't that easy.
No way...
Am I going to die?
In another two and a half minutes, yes.
I'm gonna die?!
I'm totally gonna die!
And in this really abnormal place, at that!
In a place like this...
Two minutes left.
In such a beautiful place...
I'm gonna die.
But I'm going to die a normal death.
I want at least my end to be normal.
My death won't affect the universe in any way.
Ah, my life was so short...
One and a half minutes left.
Short...
Yes, too short!
I still have so much left to do!
Do you want to live or die?
Make up your mind.
I'll live to the fullest until I die!
One minute left.
So...
Nova, uh...
Er...
K-K-K...
Kiss me!
As a teenage girl, my only
regret is that I haven't had
my first kiss!
Wait, since it's the first and
last time, is it my last kiss?
First kiss?
Which is it?
I don't mind either way.
Really?
Can I kiss you?
I don't mind either way...
Ten seconds left.
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
Five!
Fourthreetwo.
One.
Zero.
Thank you, Nova.
Now I can die happy.
The day I met you is flashing before my eyes.
Oh, yeah. Your life flashes
before your eyes when you die.
Uh, I'm totally not dead.
So you're not.
Crud, I got it wrong.
It says the poison takes effect in 60 years.
Hey!
B-But thanks to this,
Nova and I have gotten a whole lot closer!
More than friends, but not yet lovers...
Actually, we might be lovers!
Wipe, wipe, wipe...
So you have 60 years left to live, huh?
Not that I mind either way.
To be continued!
I'm searching the entire galaxy for you
Going from one planet to the next
I'm broadcasting my feelings of love to you, beep, beep
So please receive them!
They float gently
In this endless universe
I've locked on to that heart of yours
So you will never be able to run away
I want you to hold my hand
To make my head spin like a merry-go-round
To make my heart skip a beat
The world will be dyed in the colors of my love