Those Awaiting a Star
Part 2
Welcome to the library of the forest.
Huh?
Um...
I'm the magician of the forest.
No, uh...
Let's see, that's not quite right.
I'm just trying to make you feel comfortable.
Those guys won't come inside.
You can see them?
Sure.
Why?
Can you explain why you can see them?
Besides, none of those horrible
creatures can get in here.
Or rather, I don't let them in.
Everyone's busy with their books.
No one's going to hurt you.
You do understand, I hope?
Have a seat. Make yourself at home.
Let's see if I have a good one for you.
It's been a very long time since anyone's come here.
I'm so glad.
I hope I have a book you might like.
Or, should I say, a book that likes you?
Hey, what's wrong?
I'm sorry for barging in.
You don't need to worry about that.
Hey.
Give me a second, just a second!
Where is it...
It should be here somewhere.
This'll do.
What's your name?
My name is Riichi.
Miura Riichi.
Well?
Hatori Chise.
That's a beautiful name.
Here.
Your library card.
It's yours.
You're going to need it to come back.
Make sure you don't lose it.
Listen carefully.
You're going to run straight through there.
Now, run.
Hatori Chise
That was so much fun.
I'm beat.
Why don't you put your phone down
at least when someone's talking to you?
Hold on.
Come on.
I said wait.
You always say that.
You never listen to me.
Huh?
Do you know what I go through every day?
I know, I know.
No, you don't!
I'm tired, too, you know.
You mean the girl, right?
I'm the one taking care of her!
But you're the one who took her in just to be nice.
Well, so did you.
That's because you...
Don't touch that.
Don't bother.
Daiki, hurry up and get ready.
Why are you even here?
Get lost.
It's your fault that Mom's...
What's wrong, dearie?
Are you hurt?
Oh, my.
Here.
Book Report
Hatori!
May I read some books?
Of course you can.
You have your library card, right?
Listen,
as long as you have this card,
you're a member here.
You can come whenever you want,
and you can borrow the books.
Only one at a time, however.
And you must never leave the front door open.
Mind those rules, and you can
come here every day, if you like.
Every day?
Yup.
Every day.
Hatori Chise
As often as you like, for as long as you like.
Welcome, Hatori, to the library of the forest.
Here you are.
Bees
I'll eat you!
No, really, we can't deal with her anymore.
That's right.
My wife left with the kids.
We've taken care of her enough, haven't we?
It's your turn to take her now.
You're a real bookworm now, huh?
Yeah.
I can forget all my problems while I'm reading.
Oh, I know.
Hatori, if you'd like, why don't you stay—
Oh, no.
What should I do?
Grimm's Fairy Tales
I still can't decide which one
to do my book report on.
Even after you've read so many?
Well, they're all wonderful.
Yeah?
What's that book like?
That one...
That's...
It's always there.
That one, well...
What was that book like,
I wonder...
Which one should I do?
Hey,
I love reading the last page
of a book more than anything.
How could this be?
Miura?
You have to leave for today.
Now.
Hurry!
But...
Quickly.
My book report.
Yeah.
So...
Won't your mom be worried
if you don't come home soon?
No one worries about me.
That's not true.
Auntie left home.
It's all my fault, though...
The weird things bother me,
and because of that I make Auntie angry.
Just this once.
Just for today.
Let's find a book for your report.
I just really didn't want to go home that day.
That is certainly unusual.
It is unlike you to be so insistent.
I was only a child.
Are you okay?
Thanks, Ruth.
I'm fine, really.
As long as this isn't hard on you.
And then? And then?
It became a truly unforgettable night.
There's a book I want you to have.
The Lonely Little Star
"The Lonely Little Star."
A picture book?
I have a feeling you really need this book.
Now, will you clean up these books for me?
It's so pretty.
"The lonely little star, the tiny child of a star,
twinkled in the empty, dark sky all by itself."
Hatori Chise
I'll send her home before sunrise.
All right?
Goodbye.
You'll never come back again.
Miura?
Flowers
What the?
Don't tell me...
How?
Miur—
How did you get in?!
Why?!
I'm sorry.
You, the door!
No!
Not this book!
Hurry, come here!
Miura...
You...
Hurry!
Hurry, run!
Miura...
Hurry!
Good morning.
Morning.
I'll lend you this.
M-Mayumi...
Promise you'll give it back.
Mayumi...
Are you all right?
Can you move?
Don't worry.
They're gone now.
I'm sorry.
If I had closed the door...
Hatori Chise, I want to ask you
to do something for me.
Deliver it for me.
I can't do it.
Miura.
Miura!
See the bunny bees
And puffs of steam
From singing kettles in the trees
Bread and butterflies
With forks and knives
Who like to make a meal of time
Life is clockwork quick, lightning slow
Faster on your toes, so
Eat your sugared dream
And taste the day before it runs away
A promise left unfulfilled.
The girl runs onward,
holding with her a young man's regret.
Not even knowing what she'll find...
Mayumi.
Those Awaiting a Star
Part 3
VOLUME 8 SPECIAL EDITION
ON SALE FROM SEPTEMBER 9TH 2017
Those Awaiting a Star
Part 3
VOLUME 8 SPECIAL EDITION
ON SALE FROM SEPTEMBER 9TH 2017
Those Awaiting a Star
Part 3
VOLUME 8 SPECIAL EDITION
ON SALE FROM SEPTEMBER 9TH 2017
Those Awaiting a Star
Part 3
VOLUME 8 SPECIAL EDITION
ON SALE FROM SEPTEMBER 9TH 2017
Those Awaiting a Star
Part 3
VOLUME 8 SPECIAL EDITION
ON SALE FROM SEPTEMBER 9TH 2017
Those Awaiting a Star
Part 3
VOLUME 8 SPECIAL EDITION
ON SALE FROM SEPTEMBER 9TH 2017
Those Awaiting a Star
Part 3
VOLUME 8 SPECIAL EDITION
ON SALE FROM SEPTEMBER 9TH 2017
Those Awaiting a Star
Part 3
VOLUME 8 SPECIAL EDITION
ON SALE FROM SEPTEMBER 9TH 2017
Those Awaiting a Star
Part 3
VOLUME 8 SPECIAL EDITION
ON SALE FROM SEPTEMBER 9TH 2017
Those Awaiting a Star
Part 3
VOLUME 8 SPECIAL EDITION
ON SALE FROM SEPTEMBER 9TH 2017
Those Awaiting a Star
Part 3
VOLUME 8 SPECIAL EDITION
ON SALE FROM SEPTEMBER 9TH 2017