What the—
Hey now, I want in on the fun too!
A warm light shines upon the ground
With it, that seed can sprout from the earth
There's a magic that can overcome
cold rain, heavy winds, and anything else
So why does it push our backs?
You know we've all had days where we almost gave up
But then a strange power surges from within us,
and we forge ahead like a boy chasing the sun
At the end of the long winter,
spring's warm breath embraces us with the good news
I've been searching for you,
having waited the entire time for this day
Never be afraid of the trust held in your heart
It'll surely come to ease the loneliness one day
So even if you do return to the stars,
let's plant more seeds
Under One Roof
Another one?
Don't ignore me!
That's just plain rude!
Who turns their back on an enemy
without first verifying the threat they pose?
Talk about careless!
Just what the hell is going on?
Let's run while we can.
O-Okay.
Not so fast!
Sogo, hurry!
R-Right.
What, you're more interested
in those kids than me?
Captain Gus Stewart.
It appears that the hexapod loader
sent in ahead of you has been eliminated,
and that the target, "Lima," is on the move.
What is the meaning of this?
Lima's on the move?
Could it be...
Come in, Captain.
Too slow!
All right... Now we're talking!
Where do you think you're going?
Running away, eh?
I know this is a mass-produced unit,
but it's still latest military issue, dude.
The bedrock couldn't take it, huh?
Just a bit more...
Just a little bit more!
What in the world?
Kaon! Sogo!
You're all right?
Roman! Otto!
Save the touching reunion for later!
Oh, right.
We found an exit!
Quick, get on.
All right.
Here we go.
I'm home, Do Mon.
W-Welcome back.
I'm so sorry! The bread...
Lunchtime's long over, isn't it?
You kids must be hungry, I'm sure.
Even including library records,
there are no matches for the target.
A girl who emits Lima's reading...
Captain, a message from
Lieutenant Colonel Jude Pryce.
He wants you to report to HQ immediately.
A girl came out of a Giftdium crystal?
Reality truly is stranger than fiction, huh?
What should we do?
Turn her in to the officials?
No. That can wait until after she awakens.
Besides, if the military's involved,
we should think twice before revealing anything.
You're all looking awfully gloomy today.
Take your sweet time thinking it over
while digging into some sweet dessert!
Don't mind if I d—
She woke up?
Want some?
Want some?!
You can have my Tarte Tatin, if you like.
Tarte Tatin!
Is she parroting Kaon?
No need to hold back, just enjoy it!
Enjoy!
You're right.
Is it tasty?
Tasty!
Can't we find out who she is, Roman?
Oh, come on. Hold it in.
Not when we don't even know her identity, no.
Hold still!
Maybe once she can explain her circumstances to us,
we'll be able to investigate her thoroughly.
I suppose.
Until then, could you take care of her, Do Mon?
I don't mind.
What? Doesn't that mean
she'll be staying with Sogo?
I don't know about this...
You'll be staying too, Kaon.
Hey, where did that come from?
What's your problem, Sogo?
Are you saying you won't listen to Roman?
Until we resolve this issue,
I shall put the wedding on hold.
Try to avoid Mother and Father
until I've persuaded them.
You have a point there.
This could get quite messy, after all.
Is that all right with you, Do Mon?
Sure.
There we go.
And besides, I don't think it's safe to put an innocent
girl alone in a cage with a starving mongrel.
I'm neither a mongrel nor starving!
Don't be forgetting this old dog.
What's wrong?
I felt something by my feet.
Huh?
Later, Sogo.
See you.
Well, we'll be borrowing your shower for a bit.
Huh? Oh, sure.
Is this one of your pickle weights, Do Mon?
Don't lump them in with that thing.
What a strange stone.
Do you find the current state
of the military stifling?
I've heard all about your
heroic acts in the Great War.
That was back when
I was young and foolish.
Does it suit your tastes,
Captain Gus Stewart?
This project has been developed
in secret by Fongerufu.
The Eighth-Gen CQC
Assault Bipedal Armor.
Interesting...
I couldn't ask for a better plaything.
You will use it, yes?
I hold your abilities in high regard.
I've no doubt you'll be able to use this machine,
"Efreet", to its full potential.
Very well.
But on one condition:
I get to choose my men.
Wow, your hair's so silky!
And your eyelashes are so long!
Your skin's smooth, too!
First, we shave off the oxide coating.
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ow!
Ow...
As long as I'm free,
I've got this in the bag.
Th-The stone spoke?!
Now I can keep Felia safe.
Felia?
The girl you all kidnapped.
I'll never hand her over to the likes of you.
Transformation time!
Why can't I transform?
Hey!
Sit still...
No!
It'll be over in a flash.
Why is that crest on your hand?
Settle down.
If you kick up a fuss, the others will notice.
Wait, get back here!
No!
Hey...
Jeez!
If you don't dry your hair properly, you'll catch a cold.
Wh-What's the big deal?
M-Maybe she's not used to dryers?
You a pedo?
What, no!
Pedo!
A-Anyway, I'm not "Pedo."
My name's Sogo.
Sogo?
Yeah.
Sogo!
What was that thing just now?
Get your filthy hands off of her.
Are we clear?
We have tight security,
but please stay alert nonetheless.
You have a visitor.
Listen up.
Try anything funny and
we won't hesitate to shoot you.
You listening to me?!
He disappeared?
Hold your fire!
We'll end up hitting one another!
I can't see a thing!
There you are!
Pathetic.
I can't...
move?
Guess there's no reason to test
if you're fit for reinstatement,
Pack.
Gus!
Any serious wounds?
I got the bullets out.
And by tensing my muscles,
I can stop the bleeding.
You know all about my special skill, right?
Tonight's blue is most vivid.
It is time for our motherland, Planet Gift,
to take its first step toward true peace and prosperity.
The tide has started to turn.
It is as you say,
Master Zoneboyle.
Kaon.
That's right.
I'm Kaon.
Felia.
That's right. You're Felia.
Felia!
Chair.
Table.
Oh, radio!
Sogo!
She sure is chipper.
All things bring great joy to Felia.
When did you get here?
Because she's experiencing
them all for the first time.
The touch of human laughter,
the warmth of the season in the air,
and the ticklish scent of twilight.
Curry's ready, kids!
Could you carry it to the table for me?
Felia, be a good girl and take this to Sogo.
Okay.
Wh-What?
Stop! Don't use your powers so carelessly!
Th-That's hot!
Wh-What the hell?
Moura!
These sounds filling up my heart
wouldn't form into words
I just kept staring at you
But even then I felt a connection
and I wanted to always stay by your side
so I reached out with my hands
Even just touching you
fills me with so much joy
Where do these feelings come from?
I don't understand them
Tell me, my one and only
There are so many fun things to do
It just makes me want to dance
I'm so excited I think I'll just let myself go
So hold me, hold me
With all you've got
Taking flight from the earth,
Felia soars beneath the azure sky.
Within the free-flowing breeze lurks a dangerous trap.
Next time, on Comet Lucifer: Garden Indigo.
Garden Indigo
Grab a ticket and join us on this adventure!