We've been riding for a while now.
How much longer until we get there?
Moura says it's just beyond
the mountain pass ahead.
Can you not go any faster?
I'm already pushing the engine to the max,
and it's not doing too well.
Impossible!
For it is a cutting-edge engine,
the pinnacle of the Valov family's technology.
Blame this hunk of scrap
metal you call the "R7"!
And why are you tagging along, anyway?!
Were I not here, your situation
would weigh heavily upon me.
Did you just call me overweight?
That's right!
Y-You what?!
Moura?
Moura!
Not this again!
We must be getting close
to the Altar of Abyss.
A warm light shines upon the ground
With it, that seed can sprout from the earth
There's a magic that can overcome
cold rain, heavy winds, and anything else
So why does it push our backs?
You know we've all had days where we almost gave up
But then a strange power surges from within us,
and we forge ahead like a boy chasing the sun
At the end of the long winter,
spring's warm breath embraces us with the good news
I've been searching for you,
having waited the entire time for this day
Never be afraid of the trust held in your heart
It'll surely come to ease the loneliness one day
So even if you do return to the stars,
let's plant more seeds
Place of Warmth
My back's killing me...
My throat is parched.
Otto!
Here.
Nice.
It is I, Roman.
Oh, Vee...
Thank goodness! I finally got through!
Where are you right now?
This pay phone is gobbling coins
like there's no tomorrow.
Uh, well...
Eh? Put Sogo on?
Hello?
Hey, where'd my water go?!
It disconnected?
It was you?!
Thanks, I really needed that.
How dare you?!
That was delicious.
Give me back my water!
Say, Kaon...
In your dreams!
So cool and refreshing.
Ah, blessed are we to find a spring here!
Something up, Felia?
No, it's nothing.
He's wounded, so he'll be forced
to hide and wait for extraction.
Don't let him escape.
Over here! I see bloodstains!
You didn't run?
Come to think of it...
With you by my side,
I might still get to see
a lot of good things...
"Good"?
Sure you don't mean
"good for nothing"?
As long you're there with me,
I don't care either way.
Incoming message from Honeybee!
Decrypting.
Can we trust this Honeybee?
Yeah.
If you say so.
Adjust our route northwest.
Roger that!
Jeez, and right at sunset to boot...
Time to call it a day, I suppose.
Rejoice, for my exceptional culinary skills
are at your service, ladies and gentlemen.
Yay!
My, what a delectable aroma.
Très bien!
It looks so good!
Hurry up and make some for us, too.
This mushroom's poisonous!
I am Lieutenant Colonel Jude Pryce,
of the Eighth Division Special Corps.
I would like the Council's opinion
on a certain matter.
Very well.
Thank you for granting me
permission to speak.
The matter I would like to discuss
concerns Secretary Gulf Zoneboyle.
I was under the impression that the
Eighth Division and the Administrative Bureau
were to be a united front
against code name Lima.
Zoneboyle's recent actions, however,
clearly demonstrate a lack of restraint.
What do you, the conscience
of the Bureau, make of this?
Can it be fixed?
Yeah. I'm almost done.
I'll have her back on the road in no time.
That's good to hear.
Trouble sleeping?
Yeah.
You know, I was pretty worried.
We've been through a bunch of harrowing experiences,
and nothing made any sense at all.
Things might even go downhill
from here on out, too.
But I've realized something.
I'm not alone.
No matter what happens,
we're all in this together.
We'll keep you safe, Felia.
Okay!
My mushroom!
Otto, don't you dare
take my mushroom!
Well, uh...
Don't worry...
I'm sure things will work out.
Thanks, Sogo.
I'll believe in you all.
Okay, repairs complete...
We have another long day ahead,
so we'd better get some rest.
Okay.
I'm glad you're all better now, Air Rider.
Felia!
What's the matter?
I saw a glowing butterfly...
Visual on target.
Found you at last.
This way, Felia!
Not on my watch!
You're getting in my way?
I missed you, you son of a bitch!
Roman!
Wake up, Roman!
Damn, those are some killer dance moves!
Quit struggling.
Just sit tight, and I'll put you
out of your misery in no time.
Y-You bastard...
You okay?
Yeah.
You'll pay for that.
Pack, you go after Lima.
Huh?
This guy's my prey!
Aren't you gonna let me kill him?
Get going.
Whoa, there...
Party's not over, kid.
Wanna leave?
You'll have to do it over my dead body.
I know you well.
Too well, even!
I'm gonna enjoy this party all night long!
Ready or not, here I come...
Come out, come out, wherever you are...
Sogo...
It's all right.
I'll protect you, no matter what.
Lima...
Found you.
Felia...
This way!
Come on, run for your little lives!
Or else you'll get shot, you know?
You'll get shot, you know?
That's as far as you go!
Sogo, Felia, get out of here!
Felia!
Okay.
Why, you little...
Bring it.
Now that's more like it!
Let me feel your fists!
Roman Dynamic Special Dynamite!
He dodged it?
You think this is a joke?
No way.
I knew you'd come.
I've been waiting for you, mademoiselle.
Who is it you hate?
Me? Or your own pathetic self?
Hey, you know it isn't
safe over there, right?
So come on.
Leap into my arms,
my mischievous little kitten.
What?
What's their deal?
Al, can you get a reading?
My dear mademoiselle!
Damn it... Useless moron.
What now?
Apparently, the Council desires a meeting
with you at the Berberine resort.
I suspect it is due to Lieutenant Colonel
Jude Pryce's complaints.
I have naught but the utmost respect for
the vast wisdom and knowledge of the elders.
However, that very wisdom might sometimes
stand in the way of our ambitions.
It's so peaceful.
Yeah, it's a far cry from the usual liveliness.
I haven't enjoyed such calm in a long time.
Delicious!
I'm quite fond of times like these.
If I may ask, why do you run a café?
A long time ago, one of my friends
praised the coffee I made.
As a soldier, I had always thought
my hands were filthy and
good for nothing but hurting people.
That isn't—
But that friend...
She said to me,
"Your hands have the magical ability
to make delicious coffee."
What is she up to now?
I have a friend high up in internal affairs.
He told me that she'd disappeared
from this world, to cover up a top-secret case.
I'm so sorry! That was insensitive of me!
It's fine.
But you know, I swore to protect Sogo,
the legacy she left behind.
So let's drop the act, Agent Honeybee.
Could you tell me where
Sogo and the others are?
Where am I?
Guys!
Kaon! Kaon!
Thank goodness.
What in the world happened?
I'm still alive...
Ow...
Where's Felia?
Moura isn't here, either.
Felia!
Moura!
I can't believe a place like this exists...
Yeah...
Look over there.
Merely moments from now
Felia?
H-Hey!
I shall come into bloom
I'll be able to meet you
These petals of mine aflutter
Too many things
Felia...
Sogo.
I've been unable
To tell you
What are you...
And so I plant my roots
What is this place?
I don't know.
I don't know, but its warmth is all around.
And take a breath as I wait for the spring
It's welcoming me.
When I'll bloom into a fluff
That's the feeling I get.
Without an envy in this world
So we'll cover the land
Together with the one
Moura...
You did well.
Who is forever watching over us
The first thing I tell myself
When I wake up in the morning
Is that I love this world
I really, really do
When the light calls for me
I want to reach it even if it's on my bare feet
Don't stop me
I'll go further and further
One step at a time
To look for it
Let's go on an adventure
Past this door that our hearts dream of
Another fun day starts, so let's go
I want to chase those clouds I saw
I wonder where it went?
I want to catch it soon
Let's go as all this fun bursts out
I'll run after it no matter how far it is
I think I'll be able to do it if it's with you
Because with you by my side,
I won't be scared of anything
You care for them.
You love them.
So you know.
And yet...
Next time, on Comet Lucifer: Path.
Path
Grab a ticket and join us on this adventure!