Perfect.
Sogo.
Eat your breakfast quickly and lend me a hand.
'Kay.
Time to dig in...
...dig in!
Huh?
Thanks for the food.
M-My breakfast...
How dare you?
It was pretty tasty.
Why are you acting all high and mighty?!
Why, you little...
Because I am all high and mighty.
I've been living on planet Gift
far longer than you humans.
Get back here...
Quit moving around!
Hence, it's only natural that
your species should serve me!
Shut up already!
Is it good?
Good!
Just get down here, you stupid rock!
Who are you calling stupid?
Talking about yourself?
Hot! It's so hot!
Hot! Hot, hot, hot! Hot!
And spicy!
What is this?
Hot!
But delicious...
A-All of you...
But hot!
Get out!
A warm light shines upon the ground
With it, that seed can sprout from the earth
There's a magic that can overcome
cold rain, heavy winds, and anything else
So why does it push our backs?
You know we've all had days where we almost gave up
But then a strange power surges from within us,
and we forge ahead like a boy chasing the sun
At the end of the long winter,
spring's warm breath embraces us with the good news
I've been searching for you,
having waited the entire time for this day
Never be afraid of the trust held in your heart
It'll surely come to ease the loneliness one day
So when the time comes for you to return to your planet,
let's plant more seeds
Why'd I get thrown out, too?
Garden Indigo
In the end, I didn't get any breakfast...
Thanks to a certain someone.
Garden Indigo
Getting mad over something as trivial
as breakfast just shows your pettiness.
Excuse me?
That's really rich, coming from
the one who leveled my house!
You can't blame me for that.
It was your fault for activating the crest.
Besides, if it weren't for me, you would've
been in a tight spot back in that cave.
In fact, you should be thanking me!
Moura...
Get it now?
Wh-Why, you little...
Now, now.
Do Mon let the roof thing slide,
so settle down.
Kaon! Kaon!
Meow!
This is called a "cat pigeon."
Meowgeon!
Meowgeon! Meowgeon!
Aw...
Oh, I know!
Why don't we all take a trip downtown?
You can see cat pigeons there.
Whoa, there.
Meow!
Did she take it from a store?
Meow! Meow! Meow!
She's taken a real liking to it, huh?
I'm far cuter than the likes of that!
Well...
What are you implying?!
I'd like you all to know
that Felia is a unique being who
controls the breath of planet Gift.
Her presence sustains nature and life itself,
ensuring the continued prosperity of this planet.
And I am the one tasked with protecting her.
Look over there!
Check out that incredible valley!
We should visit sometime.
Listen to me!
I'm dropping juicy tidbits here!
Breakfast at last!
My, how unusual for you two to come together.
On a date, perhaps?
O-Of course not!
We're just out on a walk.
A walk!
Why are you getting flustered, Kaon?
And who might that cutie pie over there be?
Ah, she's a neighbor, kinda...
Her name's Felia!
Th-Th-The stone spoke?
E-Er... This is a stone doll Sogo made.
O-Oh.
Shame it's defective, though.
Say what?!
It's the truth, ain't it?
Your brain's the defective thing here!
Cut it out, you two!
I guess things at Do Mon's
place are as lively as ever.
Sogo and the gang sure are carefree.
Right, Roman?
Otto!
Kaon's parents must be worried sick.
It appears that I must take one for the team!
Uh, take on all you want,
just don't take any more off, okay?
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Ta-da!
Meowgeon!
Didn't we just eat?
Quiet, you.
Love and sweets don't count!
Obviously.
Shut up, you.
Stop it, Felia!
W-We're so sorry!
Please be mindful of your surroundings.
It's okay.
Let's go.
What was that?
I usually keep Felia's powers in check.
What do you mean?
But they probably burst out
because she was startled.
What the hell? Do your damn job!
It's your fault for spacing out!
That was scary, right?
I have an idea, Felia.
Why don't we head to Gold Tower?
There'll be lots of cat pigeons there.
Gold Tower?
Meowgeons!
Do put all your fears to rest...
since you put on such
a marvelous show for me.
As thanks, I shall arrange a most
extravagant party for you.
Come to me, and show me more
of your wonderful powers...
I'm going crazy just thinking about it!
Now...
Are you ready,
my dear, mischievous mademoiselle?
What's happening?
Felia...
Meowgeon!
Watch out!
Felia...
It's all right.
Everything's okay.
What the hell is going on?
Felia, I'm right here with you.
We shouldn't hang around.
Let's move to the upper levels!
The party has already begun, mademoiselle.
And I have many more
fun things in store for you.
Breaking news.
The Administrative Bureau has declared
a special emergency across Garden Indigo.
The city's control system is currently experiencing
severe technical difficulties, causing city-wide chaos.
Jeez, what the hell?
While officials investigate the cause, residents are
advised to stay indoors until the situation is resolved.
And we've even lost Lima's readings.
Man, what do we do?
I've seen this MO once before, years ago.
A guy threw the city into chaos, buying tons
of stock after the resulting market crash.
Who was it?
If I recall, his name was...
The whole city's in disarray.
Is your city always this unsafe?
Of course not!
You don't have to get mad about it.
This is no time for messing around.
What's your problem?
We need to get to a safer location.
Don't worry. I'm here for you.
Here for?
Yes, I'm here for you.
There you are, mademoiselle.
Wh-What now?
Hurry and run away!
Okay!
Damn it!
My, what an exquisite expression!
Did my present fill you with that much joy?
Then allow me to put on
a more entertaining show for you.
Out of my way!
Find somewhere and hide!
O-Okay!
Huh? Where is she?
Where did she go?
Where are you, my mademoiselle?
I can't see through all the smoke.
Where are you, mademoiselle?!
Stay out of my way, you damned brat!
Don't stick your nose
where it doesn't belong!
Hold it right there!
Hurry and get in!
No one will chase us here.
Even a sharp curve won't shake him?
Crap, what now?
Run for your life, little maggot!
Oh, my lovely little mademoiselle.
What in the world is going on?
We meet again, mademoiselle.
I hope you enjoyed the festivities I arranged.
You have long been trapped in my cage.
No!
Those sorrowful eyes... Your every
little action... They grip my heart like a vice.
And they just won't let go...
F-Felia...
Can't you do something about this?
Unless the crest...
Unless Sogo's nearby, I can't transform.
Your eyes, trembling in fear,
are the most exquisite spice.
I want to keep watching you,
get to know you better,
and eat you up!
I...
Sogo!
Felia!
Not that little maggot again.
Well, if I must.
Slightly ahead of schedule,
but let's start the finale.
Now, show me the
greatest dance I'll ever see,
mademoiselle.
What now?
Sogo!
Catch!
Moura!
At long last, you've shown me your power.
More... Show me more!
Today was a disaster...
M-Meowgeon.
That one's real.
Real?
Hey, look at that!
Alfried, if I'm not mistaken?
Alfried Macallan,
I want your skills for my team.
These sounds filling up my heart
wouldn't form into words
I just kept staring at you
But even then I felt a connection
and I wanted to always stay by your side
so I reached out with my hands
Even just touching you
fills me with so much joy
Where do these feelings come from?
I don't understand them
Tell me, my one and only
There are so many fun things to do
It just makes me want to dance
I'm so excited I think I'll just let myself go
So hold me, hold me
With all you've got
Garden Indigo is hit by a disaster
that strikes once every forty years.
Next time, on Comet Lucifer: Storm.
Storm
Grab a ticket and join us on this adventure!