The Boy and the Planet
Sogo?
Felia...
We made it out alive?
Sorry for being late.
Don't be.
I mean, you came to save me.
There's nothing to be afraid of anymore...
It's all over.
You can relax, Felia.
There's nothing to worry about.
Where's Kaon?
What about Roman and Otto?
No matter what happens,
I'll be with you forever.
Sogo?
Oh... So everyone's gone.
Yeah, they're all gone.
But I'm right here.
I'll always be by your side.
Are you worried?
I want to protect you.
Yeah...
I can't do anything by myself.
If we're attacked,
I might not be able to protect you.
That's not...
Oh, I know.
Shall we go?
To a world where we can
live in peace, just the two of us?
A world where I can live in peace?
Yeah, no one will attack you there.
And no one will get hurt.
An ideal world, where everyone is happy.
Everyone is happy?
Yeah.
Does it really exist?
It does.
If you want to go, I'll come with you.
What?
The walls just keep rising!
Let's go, Felia.
Okay.
But...
To go to that world, we need a ticket.
A ticket?
Yes, your powers.
Say, how can your powers be activated?
Is there a trigger of some sort?
I don't know...
Even though they're your own powers?
You really are funny, Felia...
Then how about you use them,
right here and now?
Maybe that'll reveal something
about the key to activating them.
U-Um...
It's simple.
Just use them like you always have.
What's wrong?
Are you going to defy me, Felia?
In order to purge the fools
and bring about my utopia,
I need both the Lucifer fragment
and the key to activating it.
Hurry up!
You're not...
Who are you?
Felia! Felia!
Felia!
Sogo?
It's you, Sogo...
Yeah.
You're safe now.
It's all over.
Thank goodness.
That crest.
I see. So you are the one.
Who's there?
Sogo!
What the hell is going on?
Sogo?
At last, I have the key of destiny
that will fulfill my longstanding desire.
Was he consumed?
Give Sogo back!
Aren't I the one you need?
I no longer have any use
for the empty shell of an angel.
Sogo!
Stop, air current.
Don't get in my way!
Why won't it stop?
Please! I need to get to Sogo!
The two seeds will soon
bear fruit as one fortune.
The key of destiny lies in my hands.
Let me go, Moura!
What do you hope to achieve by going?
Right now, you can't even stop these winds.
Even so, I have to go!
Felia!
Because Sogo was always there for me...
No matter how many dangers
he had to face, he always came for me.
He saved me a bunch of times!
So now it's my turn to save him,
no matter what.
Good grief.
I sure got assigned one troublesome angel.
Sorry, Moura.
Hear me, O noble and sturdy stone servant.
The spirit born of starlight
hereby commands thee
to accept this body into thine own.
Pursuing them at top speed.
Hang on tight!
Got it.
Huh?
What's going on?
Sector B5!
The Planet of Earth
is approaching from above.
What?
It's blocking out the sky!
Explain.
I don't know.
And we're in danger of being
swept away by the winds!
Hear that?
We'll evacuate the southern area.
Gotcha.
All remaining units, head east.
I've opened the gates to the Bureau's shelters.
Pack, escort any stragglers.
Yeah, can do.
Grab hold of something! Anything!
A truly magnificent view.
Oh, how I've longed for this day to come.
Sogo!
Give Sogo back!
That will not happen. He is necessary.
So that I might unite the lofty planet
I serve with the bounty of life on Gift,
and usher light to a new paradise.
The planet you serve?
So you really were an angel's guardian!
Don't! Sogo's in there!
Why must you take Sogo away?
If you're a guardian,
you should already have a master!
My master perished...
She was killed by the people of my home world,
the one you call the Planet of Earth.
Your home world? The Planet of Earth?
But why?
What do you mean, "killed"?
They bit the hand
of the angel that fed them.
Under the blessings of my great master,
that planet once boasted riches
unseen anywhere else in the galaxy.
The land was lush with greenery,
and the oceans caressed the shores with its tides.
How proud I was that my master created such beauty,
and serving her filled me with happiness like nothing else.
Are you really talking about that planet?
And then, the first heartbeat sounded,
and people introduced birth into the world.
They grew rapidly,
spreading to all corners of the world,
until eventually, they consumed
the planet and my master's powers.
And along with my master, the planet died.
Felia...
Left alone on a planet that had run dry,
I fell into despair.
You were all alone?
That was how I saw...
a pure, unsullied planet.
I envied it from the bottom of my heart.
It drove me mad, until I hit upon a realization.
That I could start over on that infant planet.
Infant planet?
Gift?
I would find the angel who had descended
upon Gift, and take her as my new master.
And so, I came to Gift,
bearing the smallest
flame of hope in my heart.
You tried to steal
my place as Felia's guardian?
Then why won't you
take me instead of Sogo?
Yes, I waited for the day
when I would meet you.
For eons...
Three whole civilizations rose and fell.
I had lost my master, grown weak,
and no longer had the luxury of choice.
In the end, I even served that pathetic Zoneboyle.
And that was when I finally found the angel.
Felia...
But would you believe it?
She did not bear the key.
The key?
The key to unlock the powers hidden within.
But that did not disappoint me.
If anything, I considered it a golden opportunity!
Finally, I understood!
All my suffering up till now
must have been a trial!
A trial to forge me into an almighty angel!
A guardian becoming an angel?
I was born from the same seeds.
Surely it cannot be out of the question!
No, this will be the birth of a new power!
You're nuts!
Cry all you want, filth that must be destroyed!
I do not need that Planet of Earth,
nor do I need Gift.
The time has come for me
to birth a planet myself,
and ascend the throne as its angel!
You could just take me instead!
Your foolishness never ceases to amaze me.
You are but a vessel.
Your contents, your power...
Everything rests in my hands now.
All that remains is the key to its activation.
The crest of destiny!
Sogo?
You shall not deny me!
But why do you have to crash
the Planet of Earth into Gift?
To fulfill my long-cherished dream,
and give birth to a utopian planet!
You're awful.
How so? You are the one who
drew that planet toward Gift, angel!
Pardon me...
I suppose I should call you "former angel."
Stop, Planet of Earth...
Please stop.
I beg of you!
You are a shell that has
been stripped of its powers.
What do you hope to achieve?!
Some angel I am...
I'm destroying everyone's home.
I'm destroying Sogo's precious home.
I'm more like a demon.
I never should have come here.
But if you hadn't come here
from the far reaches of the universe,
Gift would have never fostered life.
Believe me Felia, you're no demon.
I have to save Gift...
I have to save Sogo.
I'm really happy to have served you.
It is time for the Planet of Earth to kiss Gift.
Sogo!
Again? Why do you persist so?!
Because...
There's something I have yet to tell him!
Sogo...
Come back, Sogo.
Did you know?
Apparently, the stone born on this planet will have
three dreams while it lies dormant within the earth.
The first, a dream that shines
more brightly than any crystal.
The second, a dream where
it becomes a dazzling jewel.
And the last...
...is a dream where
a handsome prince finds it.
Don't go, Felia.
We'll still be together.
I'll be watching over you forever.
I love you, Sogo.
Don't leave
This warmth
Which lies within me
Don't leave
My memories
Sogo!
Light up the path to tomorrow
Guys!
Even if my wish to be with you
Will lead to nothing but loneliness
I love you too, Felia.
I'll still embrace you
Because I want to become one with you
Even if the day comes
For these hands that once connected us to separate
I'll continue to embrace you
Our lives will remain connected
Even if we're separated
We'll meet again some day
Professor?
Professor!
Man, he's out looking for crystals again.