One appeared from within
a resplendent cascade of light.
And the other emerged
from a murky deluge of darkness.
Both sought to claim
the heavens for themselves.
And they, sometimes on hills,
sometimes in valleys,
would battle on for millions of years.
When it lost to a current of angry tears,
the first bird cried in sorrow.
When tears drowned
its brilliantly blazing rage,
the second bird cried in sorrow.
And in the year that cries rang out
across the skies a third time,
the world was divided into those who
took a stand and those who backed down.
Now, then...
On which side will we fall?
In the days to come,
let us see for ourselves.
Tonight, the heavens exert their radiance
with greater splendor than ever.
Ow...
A warm light shines upon the ground
With it, that seed can sprout from the earth
There's a magic that can overcome
cold rain, heavy winds, and anything else
So why does it push our backs?
You know we've all had days where we almost gave up
But then a strange power surges from within us,
and we forge ahead like a boy chasing the sun
At the end of the long winter,
spring's warm breath embraces us with the good news
I've been searching for you,
having waited the entire time for this day
Never be afraid of the trust held in your heart
It'll surely come to ease the loneliness one day
So when the time comes for you to return to your planet,
let's plant more seeds
The Boy and the Vast Land
Whoa there!
Oh, Sogo...
Mornin'!
Well, aren't you in a good mood?
You got that right!
Good morning, Officer...
Good rider or not,
stay under that speed limit, got it?
'Kay.
You aren't watering them too much, are you?
Nope.
Hey!
Wait!
You okay?
Yeah, sorry!
Thank goodness...
Later.
Up you go...
Do Mon, I'm home!
Oh, welcome back.
Exploring the ruins of the mine
first thing in the morning again, Sogo?
Sure was! I'll be upstairs!
I knew going down the eastern
Giftdium vein was a good idea!
Any chance of discoloration over time?
Nope! Readings are through the roof!
I've finally found evidence that proves
what Mom was talking about!
A hallucination?
Hey, Sogo!
Did you pick up the bread
we ordered for lunch?
Sorry! I'll get it right now!
Abnormal activity in the Lima
was detected early this morning.
At point B-6207.
That's the deepest part of Garden Indigo.
Which squad do we have deployed there?
That would be Captain Stewart's unit.
Gus, huh?
Do you understand, Captain?
Don't do anything stupid.
I'm perfectly aware, Lieutenant Colonel.
You heard the man.
Listen up.
Gear up according to plan,
then move out according to plan,
and execute the operation according to plan.
Roger!
Oh, and when diving, put safety first.
Otter One, all clear.
Diving.
Two, dive.
Three, dive.
Right, here's your order.
And the cream roll is on the house.
Thanks!
Later, Vee.
Sogo! Sogo! Sogo!
Tell Do Mon I said hi.
I might not make it by lunchtime.
Better floor it.
Come on, faster.
O-Ow...
Would it kill you to not ride
like a madman for once?
What are you doing here?
Sogo!
Drive!
Excuse me?
Come on...
Hold it right there, Kaon!
What—
Just drive already!
H-Hey!
Jeez. What's with you?
Hey, Kaon!
Roman?
You were supposed to try on
your wedding dress, not run away!
This is an outrage, Kaon!
Wedding?
Our parents betrothed us without asking!
Betrothed?
Old-fashioned, I know, right?
It's totally unfair!
Old-fashioned, unfair, or otherwise,
so long as it remains a Valov
family tradition, it is the right path!
And what about how I feel?
Feelings carry no weight.
The continued prosperity of
both our families takes priority.
What an idiot.
Don't you think so, Sogo?
Sogo, did you put her up to this?
Of course not!
Don't mind me. Speed up.
Huh?
Don't question it, just go!
This is Otter One. All units in position,
everything on schedule.
Well, looks like it's time
for you boys to earn your pay.
Cease this at once, Kaon!
As it is, I won't be able
to face Father or Mother!
Good. Maybe now you can stop
being such a pampered child.
As heir to the Valov family, I order you...
La la la la! I can't hear you!
So be it...
I give you permission
to use some degree of force!
Roger that!
Stop it, Otto!
Pay him no heed. Continue.
K-Kaon!
Kaon!
Sogo...
Kaon?
Sogo... Sogo...
Wait. Don't move.
I'll turn on a light.
Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I can't hear the bustle of the town.
Looks like we fell pretty far...
Is that the sound of water?
What is it?
S-Something touched my leg...
S-Sorry.
O-Oh, uh...
Me too.
Oh, a newt.
Hey!
You there, Kaon?
Otto, can you locate her?
There's too much magnetic
interference to get a read...
We must escort her back at once,
to prepare for the wedding!
Never mind her, I don't even know
where we are right now!
What?!
Are we going to be stuck here forever?
Once I get this fixed,
we'll be out of here in a flash.
With your Quicker Board?
Yeah.
There's flowing water here,
so there must be an exit somewhere.
Are we going to turn into mummies here?
All units have evac'd to a safe location.
Standing by for orders.
Commencing countdown.
Three.
Two.
One.
Fire!
What?!
An underground lake?
It's glowing!
What on earth is going on?
Sixty seconds have passed.
Emission levels within projected estimates.
The water level's receding?
I'll check it out.
Sogo, wait up.
S-Sogo...
Giftdium?
Wait, this color...
Yeah.
So it was here all along.
What?
What's going on?
D-Damn it!
Whoa.
A girl?
S-Sogo...
She just came out of
that crystal, didn't she?
Y-Yeah.
What should we do?
A rescue squad?
Doesn't look like it...
What are two kids doing here?
What's the hold-up?
Can you secure the Lima?
Yes sir, but uh...
Lima readings stable.
Right! Proceed with the plan!
Yes, sir!
Why is it coming this way?
Dunno, but we'd better run!
What's going on? Give me a sitrep.
I don't know!
There's an unregistered Bipedal Armor!
What? A Bipedal Armor?
Well, things certainly took
a turn for the interesting...
Fire up my unit!
S-Sogo...
Y-Yeah...
These sounds filling up my heart
wouldn't form into words
I just kept staring at you
But even then I felt a connection
and I wanted to always stay by your side
so I reached out with my hands
Even just touching you
fills me with so much joy
Where do these feelings come from?
I don't understand them
Tell me, my one and only
There are so many fun things to do
It just makes me want to dance
I'm so excited I think I'll just let myself go
So hold me, hold me
With all you've got