"It's my life."
This is the story of a man.
A man who just wanted to
live peacefully after his retirement,
Astra Ludger Doomsday,
and how one day, a little witch
named Noah stumbled upon his house.
Along the way will be various incidents,
encounters, partings, as well as reunions.
But first, here's a chapter of one peaceful day,
before all the exciting stuff.
Oh, Master Astra!
I want to have a garage sale!
There he goes again!
I read in this month's issue—
It's fine. I already know where you
get your information, Master Astra.
What is a garage sale, though?
Allow me to explain!
You always sound really excited whenever
you talk about housework, I've noticed.
A garage sale is apparently an ancient tradition
where you put unneeded items
out in your front yard for sale,
and engage in friendly conversation with visitors.
It's a super exciting event!
Huh...
That's why we'll be having a garage sale right now!
Not wasting a single second!
But no one will come by if you do it right now.
Hm, I've already considered that.
Special delivery!
That's why I had the postal service
distribute flyers to the surrounding areas.
Special delivery!
Not wasting a single second!
So I expect visitors sooner or later.
Noah, GorGor, help me put
the merchandise on display.
Jeez, you're so pushy, Master Astra.
Garage Sale — Selling unneeded items!
Hm, exquisitely displayed, if I do say so myself.
But will people actually come?
I've considered that, which is why I also
placed a stuffed toy showing the way.
Garage sale!
300 meters this way.
I think some people would
turn back after seeing that.
Garage sale!
300 meters this way.
Hey! Have you already started the garage sale?
Oh, a customer already?
I rushed over as soon as I heard I could
legally obtain your used everyday items.
We have to deal with this creep first?!
I hope my life savings will be enough.
Exactly what are you expecting to buy?!
We have nothing to sell to you, so please leave.
Huh?!
No fighting here.
Also, I appreciate you coming by,
but do you ever actually work?
I'm sure Rose can take care of things in my stead—
Oh, I figured I'd find you here, Captain Kyuss.
Please do your job!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Well, it's not like there was any other place
the captain would've escaped to.
I apologize for the commotion, Master Astra.
Rose, he's technically your superior,
so please don't be so harsh on him.
You have a point.
You're having a garage sale?
I saw your flyers being handed out in the capital.
Right! Is there something
you were interested in buying?
Let's see...
Could you sell me your uniform?
Could you answer instead of smiling like an idiot?
Rose, no matter how huge of a fan you are of him,
I can't just let you buy a uniform
that's imbued with eau de Astra!
Why, you ask? Because I'll pay any price!
Could I ask you to be quiet for a second
and go sit over there, Captain?
I'll have to file a report and inform
the commander of this matter.
No, wait...
Or, if you prefer, you can hang this around
your neck and reflect upon your actions.
You get scolded an awful lot for a grown-up!
Avert your eyes!
Hey, Malcolm, you see that?
I do see it, Angus.
No idea what this garage sale thing is,
but they've got a bunch of things just sitting there!
Let's snatch 'em while they're busy bickering,
sell 'em off, and then we'll be loaded...
M-Malcolm!
Hey, Astra.
I saw your flyer.
Oh, Elise!
I'm surprised my flyers went out that far.
Did you hear something strange just now?
I don't really get what this whole
garage sale thing is all about,
but since you went through the trouble to invite me,
you must be selling something special.
I didn't really invite you in particular.
I'm a bad captain.
Thanks for coming.
I'd like that.
How does 150 gold sound?
Is that all I'm worth to you?!
I must say, all of this looks like junk.
Will it really sell?
D-Did you really call my belongings "junk"?!
These are some of my most cherished belongings!
It breaks my heart to let go of them!
Elise, Elise!
I'm also selling the picture I drew!
What do you think? Isn't it good?
Do you think it'll sell?
Yeah. It'll definitely sell.
Such blind sisterly love...
Like anyone would buy
something drawn by a child—
Elise!
You're always so cool, Elise!
I wouldn't go as far as to call it junk,
but I admit there's nothing that grabs my interest.
I... I see.
All these things are very valuable to me, though.
What's that? You need some super valuable
and useful tools by your good friend Riff?
I did not say that. I did not invite you.
And I do not want you here.
Ow, that hurts!
Good afternoon, Astra.
I saw your flyer.
Buntline!
I'm glad you're here, but couldn't you
have stopped her from tagging along?
Do you really think that's in my power?
I'm sorry. That was a foolish question.
Bam!
I don't know what this whole
garage sale thing is about,
but I've brought a bunch of stuff anyway!
This day can't get any worse.
You've got it all wrong!
I'm the one who's selling,
and other people are supposed to buy!
I'm trying to clean my place up,
so the last thing I want is more things!
I see!
So you're saying that you want
Riff-grade magic bombs,
perfect for wiping any two-meter-wide area clean!
Are you even listening?!
Well, Riff, look here.
I'm sure we'll be able to find something nice here.
I'm kind of interested in that old tableware.
Ah, actually...
If I polish up some of these rusty items,
I could sell them at the shop.
Wait.
Now that I look closer,
isn't this a magic-boosting ring?
It might not be of use to
Master Astra, but I could use one.
I'm actually... interested in buying Noah's drawing,
and this old book about the continent.
Yay! Thank you very much, Elise!
I'll buy anything for any price!
A-Amazing!
Just one thing Buntline said
made this into a proper garage sale!
He's truly a saint! Thank you, Buntline!
I'll take this.
Sure!
I want this!
Thank you.
I'll be taking this!
Thanks.
Could you ring it up?
What else have you bought?
Isn't this great, Master Astra?
Well...
Look at this. I think it's a very good item.
Mister 'Tra!
Good afternoon!
I see your flyer!
Welcome, Johnny!
Are you here to buy something as well?
No. I do live concert.
Why?
Do you even know what
a garage sale is supposed to be?
I heard this is event where
Mister 'Tra sell unneeded items.
So you do understand! Then why?!
Lots of people gather,
more fun to do concert. That is why.
Don't steal my customers!
I'm sorry, but I have nothing left
for sale, so I'd like to call it a day.
How about then, I buy Mister 'Tra's time?
?!
I-I don't know about...
Exactly! That's unfair, Johnny!
In that case, I'll spend all my money to buy Astra!
Now you're being unreasonable.
Oh, that's so smart! In that case, I want little Noah!
What?!
Wait, I'm not letting you have her.
Before you do that, please let me
buy Master Astra's clothes off him.
You idiot! He's not Astra without his uniform!
Please calm down, everyone.
Now is time! I shall perform!
You know, this didn't really
turn out exactly how I imagined it.
W-Well, we've managed to sell everything,
and you've had your friendly conversations.
I guess. But only the faces
we saw today were familiar ones.
I was hoping to see some unfamiliar ones.
This isn't really the type of place
for someone to just pass through.
Well, I guess it's lively, at least. That's not too bad.
Help! Save me!
No, stop! Don't kill him!
The dragon brothers from earlier...
It hurts!
Hunter
We're here to praise your name
Blazing sun and bitter death
You're the guardian 'cross the gate
Wake up it is a new dawning
Wake up the witches wait
For you, remember the mirror
When she looked in
You were born in the void
In the middle of none
There was nobody else
There was nothing at all
Well sons and daughters
Joy's in the air
The horned one dies
Renewal everywhere
Turn the wheel again
A new beginning
Another end
Dried out the land needs blood
Inside the ring, we're waitin'
Give up yourself, enter life
It's set up for you
Come turn the wheel
There is nothing to fear
Come turn the page
Oh, come turn the page
We do not believe in lies
Do not believe in lies
There's someone crying
There's someone coming
Hear a voice from the underworld
Now everything should move
When a new day begins
God of wind and God of rain
Turn the wheel, you better be aware
The mermaids
They will sing for you
The nymphs will bless the child
Reunite them, sacrifice him
We will be with you until the end
Come move our hearts
We know, there is light beyond the dark
Dried out, we cry for blood
Conquer your fear and join us
Come guide us now
The time is right
It's set up for you
Come turn the wheel
There is nothing to fear
Come turn the page
Oh, come turn the page
A new beginning
Another end
The myth of life
You hold in your hand
We cry out
The land needs blood
The change of season
Praise to the newborn king
It's set up for you
Come turn the wheel
There is nothing to fear
Come turn the page
Oh, come turn the page