Come on, hurry up!
Don't fall!
Hey, watch where you're going!
Yo, mind if I join you?
You joined this map yesterday too, right?
For an avatar this casual,
your information density is crazy high.
You must have access to a ton of memory.
Do I look that way to you?
Are you an upper-class citizen?
You could've rendered a location on a private server
instead of coming to an open map like this one.
You see, my buddies and I run a private map
on our shared memory pool.
It's a lot quieter and higher-res than this dump.
Sorry, but I prefer to spend
my vacations quietly and alone.
Playing hard to get, huh?
You order up a sweet avatar like that,
and all you do is show it off?
Surely you're just wasting it
if all you're doing is enjoying this cheap content?
It's a work thing.
"A work thing"?
What's going on?
What happened?
...What the...
Attention, human beings residing in Deva.
If I may have a moment of your time.
I am Frontier Setter.
I am intervening in your virtual world
to show you the way to a new possibility.
Come on, this again?
This hacking crap's supposed
to be coming from the surface.
After many years of preparation,
No way! That's so scary!
Why isn't System Security doing its damn job?!
I have readied an expedition to explore the
habitable zone of the Milky Way's Orion Arm.
...Ugh, this is why I hate open maps...
Your chance to set out into the
infinite reaches of space,
in search of new worlds
seen by no human eye,
Agent code ZQ875456, Angela Balzac.
and to encounter new,
intelligent life is almost here.
On my authority as a System Security officer,
I request local system root privileges.
Request granted.
Sysadmin rights transferred to
Angela Balzac. Awaiting commands.
The human race has already washed its hands
of the Earth's devastated environment
...You're—
and made the cyberspace world of Deva
the hub of this new way of life.
Display list of all users now online.
However, I would like to propose to
all of you the possibilities of pioneering.
Run trace comparison against Deva citizen IDs.
Of 1,842 users currently logged in to local service,
I have inherited and completed
the legacy of your forebears,
7 IDs are duplicates. Illegal access warning.
Disregard warning.
Ignore them for now! Sort further by connection speed!
imbued with their dreams, hopes,
and aspirations for a boundless future.
Observe.
This is the Genesis Ark,
the embodiment of their lost wisdom.
...This deep space exploration vessel...
was originally designed for a crew of about 100,
That bastard... He's using our emergency line!
but you, who dwell in Deva
as information life forms,
Did you think I wouldn't find you?
Trace access route!
would make it possible to operate it
far more safely and effectively.
You citizens of Deva,
who have forsaken physical form,
are the descendants of humanity
who are best adapted
to face the challenge of the
new world of the stars.
I cannot begin to imagine what trials
we will face along the way.
Scattering decoys won't help you now!
However, I believe they
will be a small price to pay
for the rewards that we will surely reap.
The day of departure is almost upon us.
This is him?!
I hope that as many as possible
of you share my sentiments
and decide to join me in challenging
the vast expanse of the Milky Way.
Pulling the same stunt, huh?!
I am Frontier Setter.
I have you now!
I eagerly await your response.
Damn it!
Third Officer Angela Balzac,
you are being summoned by Central System Security.
Please report immediately.
Third Officer Angela Balzac,
you are being summoned by Central System Security.
Please report immediately.
Well, that's me.
The job I mentioned is
Deva System Security officer.
Care to give me your address
if you still want to hook up sometime?
Uh... Well... Maybe some other time!
The skill you demonstrated
was most impressive.
I allowed the culprit to escape,
though. My apologies.
This makes 184 incidents of cracking
perpetrated by this so-called "Frontier Setter".
All have been carried out over the datalinks
that connect Deva to the surface.
We believe that the perpetrator
is one of the surface dwellers
who are still denied entry into Deva.
We must conclude that the perpetrator's capabilities
exceed those of our defense system.
Someone that skilled exists outside of Deva?
We must acknowledge it
as an unforeseen circumstance.
There is little hope of improving the situation
solely by means of bolstering our security.
As such, we will shift the focus of our mission
to track down Frontier Setter in the real world.
...The real world...
Third Officer Angela Balzac,
we would like you to take part in this operation.
Thank you for this unexpected honor!
Third Officer Angela Balzac.
We will use your gene cache, stored at the time
of your birth, to fabricate an optimized material body.
...ETA to completion of adult body, 35 hours...
That's way too long.
Warning. Equivalent age
of physical body, 16 years.
Maturation period incomplete.
It's enough.
Understood.
No need to break it in.
VR will be good enough.
...This thing is pretty heavy...
So, what equipment am I being provided with?
One Arhan powered exoskeleton
with all option packages.
Also, one support agent
requisitioned to act as a local observer.
Zarik Kajiwara AKA "Dingo".
18 ground missions completed
for System Security Intelligence.
Overall performance evaluation, S-rank.
However, has a poor conduct record.
Just so long as he's useful to me.
What's with this dusty atmosphere?
Do they expect me to breathe this stuff?!
...Kind of a letdown...
I was expecting the real world
to be more amazing somehow.
Control, this is Angela Balzac.
I've reached the surface. Status, all green.
Where's my local guide?
There's no sign of him.
Current location confirmed
as rendezvous point sent to him.
Shall I track the subject
using monitoring satellites?
Please do.
Agent Dingo positively ID'd.
That's him?
Wait, what's that behind him?
A mutated species belonging to
Arthropoda Myriapoda. AKA "sandworm".
Vicious carnivore.
Threat level: B+.
What's he up to?
...Unbelievable...
Trouble right off the bat, huh?
System standing by.
Deva tactical operations online and set up.
Okay, we're good to go!
This might be just what the
doctor ordered to get me warmed up!
Are you some kind of idiot?! Come on!
I don't want to waste ammo
...on these lesser organisms...
Hey! Get off me!
...Their heads? Oh, I get it...
Computational targeting, behavior prediction,
ballistics correction all online!
Automatic smart fire engaged!
Ready!
I'm not gonna waste a single round!
Well, color me impressed.
That was some fine shooting.
I'm much obliged that you took them all out.
So what's the big idea, my observer making
trouble for me as soon as he shows up?!
Oh, don't be like that.
I'm gonna be helping you with your job.
I scratch your back, you scratch mine.
What are those for, anyway?
If you're running from something,
you ditch any unnecessary baggage!
Are you some kind of idiot?!
No, I wasn't running.
I was dragging those jerry cans.
Huh?
Sandworms are highly sensitive
to metallic sounds, you see.
If you drive along while making metallic sounds,
they get angry and swarm after you.
It's a piece of cake.
Wow, what a catch!
Step right up, everyone!
As promised, this is a special sale!
All the fresh meat you can carry,
300 nanokarats per person!
Load up with as much as you can carry home!
Here you go!
This is great!
Thanks!
This is awesome!
Always a pleasure!
...Now look here, you...
Seriously, thanks a bunch.
You helped me out,
and I didn't even ask you to.
It's always nice to have a generous client.
I think you and me are
gonna get along just fine!
What a haul, what a haul!
...About your payment...
Yeah, underground mineral resource data
from satellite scans, same as always.
Make it another good set, okay?
To be honest, I prefer to do business in cash.
...But you Deva folk don't have much use for—
This is your payment upon completion.
If I find your work satisfactory, I'll hand it over.
Hey, now. Shouldn't you establish
a trusting relationship with a down payment?
How am I supposed to trust someone
who sabotages me right off the bat?
Sabotage is such an ugly word.
I simply sensed that you would waste
all those passing-by sandworms for me.
Listen!
What was wasted was my precious time!
7 minutes, 20 seconds, shot to hell!
Every second counts in this situation,
so of course I'd call that sabotage!
Why are you in such a rush?
The op doesn't start until tomorrow, right?
The other agents haven't even landed yet.
Exactly!
This is my perfect chance
to get the drop on everybody else!
I even cut this body's incubation
period short to get ahead!
Oh, so that's what's up with that girly look.
...I just assumed you were into—
Listen close.
If anybody else finds Frontier Setter
before me, you get nothing!
So keep that in mind and do your job right!
Squabbling over who
...gets credit at a time like this...
You have familiarized yourself
with the mission parameters, right?
Deva's been getting hacked relentlessly lately,
and the culprit is somewhere on Earth, right?
...That's the weirdest thing I've ever heard...
Look around.
We surface-dwellers live off
animals that we kill and eat.
And yet, you denizens of cyberspace want me to help you
find someone who can beat you guys in cyberwarfare?
Are you sure it's not some alien or something?
Whatever he is, it's a fact that
the access originated from the surface.
My mission is to locate him.
Your mission is to assist me.
You got that?
...Of course, I get all that...
By the way, that thing was amazing!
How does your robot
handle all that crazy shooting?
The System Security main server provides
computational processing support via satellite link.
Targeting correction is its specialty.
Its future forecasting even lets me
hit targets moving at the speed of sound.
That's amazing.
Meaning that the suit itself is always online,
acting as a sort of Deva terminal.
Impressive. That's a huge help.
Goodness, for someone who lives in the
Stone Age, you certainly catch on quickly.
It uses a satellite linkup, you said?
Where's the antenna?
It runs down its back. Don't touch it.
Hey! Wait!
What are you doing?!
What have you done, you idiot?!
If you want to see the
real idiot here, look in a mirror.
You're up against a hacker way beyond
your powers in cyberwarfare, right?
So why the hell are you walking around
in an online terminal, huh?
Do you constantly shout out "Here I am!"
when you play hide-and-seek, too?
That doesn't mean you had to wreck it!
Never, ever log in to Deva.
Assume you've given away your position to the enemy
the instant you use any satellite-based comms system.
How do you expect me to
carry out my mission, then?!
If all of the agents who are
on their way are as careless as you,
they'll log in wherever they are and let
the enemy know exactly what they're up to.
That's good. Bait is always handy
when you're hunting.
So you and I will hide our tracks
and sneak up on our prey from behind.
Using nothing but our
eyes, nose, ears, and legs.
If we do that, we might be able to get the drop
on this Frontier Setter wizard of yours.
So you're confident?
I guess.
Wits, patience, and strength
are the tools of my trade.
Heaven only knows if they really work.
Oh, right.
Is this tough fella any use offline?
It's a useless pile of scrap metal now!
Scrap metal, huh?
Well, scrap metal has its own effective uses.
This is another fine piece you brought me!
Always a pleasure!
...My Arhan...
...My special class-A backup...
What am I gonna do now?
Don't get cold feet.
I'll use the money I got
for our expenses, so relax!
That's not the point!
So, where are you taking us, anyway?
A map?
Our first stop is the town of Jed
to look for our first lead.
It's about 1,000 km south of here.
Why would we go someplace that far away?!
You think we can find him by
looking under rocks on the plains?
To gather the intel we need,
a city's our best bet.
But why a city that's so far away?!
Aren't there any other
populous areas nearby?
Weren't you listening?
We're using your buddies as bait.
You know the locations of their
drop points and their search zones, right?
Yes.
So, if that information
was shared on your network,
you'd better believe Frontier Setter
knows them just as well.
In which case, he wouldn't
leave any tracks in this area.
He seems to be really cautious
about stuff like that.
So we'll use the process of elimination, giving priority
to checking the cities where System Security has no pull.
Be chill, be patient, and be ready.
In hunting, the first to lose
their patience loses everything.
That goes for both hunter and prey.
What?
Let's make camp here tonight.
Hang on!
Didn't I tell you that we
don't have a second to waste?!
Waste?
How is not sleeping gonna help us?
Sleep if you want to! I'll drive!
Don't you have to sleep?
I haven't engaged in any activity
so taxing that I'd need to rest.
This truck is a manual.
Can you drive stick?
Don't patronize me.
A machine this primitive is no challenge.
Just point me in the right direction.
Want one? It's sandworm meat.
No thanks.
Is that good?
It has no taste.
Come on, you went through
the trouble of leaving Deva, right?
Don't you think you should be living it up more?
Eating, drinking, or whatever?
I could always relish any pleasure
I wanted in cyberspace.
Nothing that this flesh suit
can offer can live up to that.
Uh, I didn't mean anything dirty.
Don't you want to feel full or satisfied?
It doesn't seem necessary.
We moved beyond
instinctive pleasures long ago.
Feeling full, huh?
That's the feeling you get in return
for eliminating your sensation of hunger, right?
Talk about the shackles of the flesh!
We've washed our hands of
that wasteful "metabolism" stuff.
That's why we can focus our minds
on more refined pleasures.
Say, that body of yours
isn't robotic, is it?
No, this is a clone body reproduced
from my genetic information.
This is the only body that is
a perfect fit for my mental matrix.
So you used to be flesh and blood?
For 1,300 hours after fertilization.
Or did you think that Deva's citizens were
ones and zeroes from the moment they were born?
It's a bit of a relief
to hear that they're not.
Well, don't push that body
too hard if you're not used to it.
If you get tired, I'll take over.
What is it?
Looks like your friends
are coming down in droves.
Why's everybody so far ahead of schedule?
They found out that I got the drop on them,
so they lost their cool and finally showed up.
Work for Deva sure seems stressful.
What in the world is that awful racket?!
This is Arise.
What, is classic rock
an underground thing in Deva?
Nobody listens to this stuff!
Man, Deva must be a dreary place.
Deva collects and archives
every bit of human culture, doesn't it?
But there's no rock?
It was deemed a subculture with
no value and no relevance for posterity.
Can you blame them?
What in the world is the appeal of this noise?
You can't get it when you only
use your ears to hear the sound.
It's your bones that pick up the beat.
If you want to rest,
use the bunk in the back.
I don't need rest.
You sure? You look pretty sleepy to me.
I'm not sleepy!
Besides, you might pull another stunt on me and
make my life more difficult if I don't keep an eye on you.
...Yeah, yeah...
And there it is! That's Jed!
That?
And how, exactly,
...do you propose we gather int—
Miss, what do you say?
I'll give you a special discount.
We'll look for merchants doing business
with someone calling himself Frontier Setter.
Do you know where to start?
I'm here to see Yzak. Jorg sent me.
Hey!
Hey! How about a translation?
...Hey—
What the hell?
Give me a break, damn it!
Seriously, what the hell?
I can't translate anything,
...I can't look up terms I need...
Why is there even
a world left outside of Deva?!
Hey there, little girl. You lost?
If you need someone to show
you around, we'll be happy to.
Our guide fee is pretty steep, though.
Perfect timing.
You caught me in a bad mood.
Bitch!
You messed with the wrong guy!
My body... feels sluggish.
Oh, crap!
...Shit...
You'll pay for this!
You shouldn't underestimate the real world.
Mind your own business!
Sorry, I should've realized
something was wrong.
I'm fine!
...I...
Must be the overexertion.
I bet you caught a bug
when your resistance was low.
I'm sick?
You have a bad fever.
Jumping around like that
...when you've already aggravated it...
You really need to stop pushing your luck.
Aggravated?
Physical bodies are such a hassle.
You didn't notice
that something felt wrong?
An operator is supposed to constantly monitor
my autonomic nerves and alert me when something is wrong.
But my link was severed.
Alert you? You must have been
feeling like hell this whole time!
"Feeling like hell"?
I just figured that bodies
were always like that.
Oh, right.
This is all new to you.
Overexertion, sickness, everything.
I dug around in your survival kit
but I couldn't find anything resembling medicine.
You didn't bring any?
The thing in the middle
is a medical server.
It creates medicines specifically
tailored to my condition.
If it could go online
and diagnose me, that is.
I guess it's time to blow our cover.
Wait, what are you doing?!
No transmissions, remember?!
We can't fix you up
unless we log into Deva, right?
You're not in any shape to carry out the mission,
or anything else for that matter.
What do you surface-dwellers
do when you get sick?
If it's just a cold, we eat something nourishing,
bundle up, and get some rest.
But if it's a nastier infectious disease,
it's a roll of the dice as to whether
you get lucky and find a doctor and medicine.
Then I'll do that, too.
I'll carry out this mission
without any backup.
That's what I promised myself.
Why are you trying so hard?
Because I always have.
Always.
I've never given up or complained, not once.
That's what got me promoted to
Third Officer at System Security.
Don't underestimate me.
I'll make an even bigger name for myself.
I'll prove that I can do this.
I get it.
Your guts are the real deal.
You're not the sort to stop at Third Officer.
I bet you'll be able to
rise as high as you want.
Of course I will.
Feeling well enough to move around?
For a little.
...That thing you said earlier...
About feeling music in your bones.
Is it that amazing?
As far as amazing goes, you must have
had way more experiences in Deva
than a flesh and blood guy
like me ever could've had.
I suppose.
When you're a cyber personality,
you can expand your senses as far
as the memory you have access to allows.
I've listened to a gamma ray burst 10 billion light years away.
I've even felt around for
subatomic particles with my fingertips.
But that was the first time I've ever heard
of feeling sound in your bones.
You aren't afraid of me.
I wonder why.
Why would I be afraid?
System Security is my main client.
I've done lots of jobs for them,
and I know that you guys aren't
some kind of ghosts or monsters.
That's my point. You ought to get it.
That we digitized humans are
the next stage in human evolution,
and those of you on the surface are
the last-gen model left to wait for extinction.
You get hungry, you get tired,
and you even get laid up in bed
when you get sick.
You lead such a fragile existence,
but you look at me like you're fine with it.
Where do you get that confidence?
Is it because you value the
physical bodies we've abandoned?
Or is it because you can
feel sound in your bones?
The night breeze will do a number on you.
You should go straight back to bed.
Frontier Setter's goal?
Yeah. With only a dim idea of what he wants,
we'll be heading nowhere fast in our search.
His goal is to disturb
the peace in Deva, of course.
By stirring up the misgivings
...of citizens in cyberspace—
And after he's done stirring?
I think he's sowing the seeds for panic as a prelude
to launching genuine acts of sabotage eventually.
That's definitely the sort of worst-case scenario that
System Security would predict, but it's not an analysis.
Maybe it's the misgivings of System Security's bigwigs
that are being stirred up, not the citizenry's.
Their supposedly unbreachable
security has been breached.
You're so panicked by the sense of danger
that you may be overlooking the real nature of the hacks.
Don't you think the reason why he went there
is more important than how he got there?
We'd save ourselves
the hassle if we knew that.
I mean, he spelled it out himself, right?
He said he's looking for others
to join him in exploring outer space.
Believing a load of garbage
like that is what's crazy.
Based on?
For starters, there's no point.
With the creation of Deva,
humanity's overpopulation and natural resource
problems have been completely eliminated.
At this point, space development doesn't
offer any rewards that outweigh the risks.
Isn't that just Deva's
sense of priorities talking?
Here in the outside world,
we have more ways of looking at things.
Even you've seen that.
Then you believe what
Frontier Setter says?
He has a deep space exploration
ship ready and waiting?
Don't be absurd.
How could he have carried out such
a massive project without Deva noticing?
Listen, all space exploration projects
were canceled even before the Nanohazard.
That's a cold, hard fact.
Deva's records aren't complete.
When they deem a piece of
information useless, they just purge it.
Isn't that right?
If they're going through the trouble to beam
a spaceship recruitment ad to you guys from the surface,
it means they still need a way to
leave both surface and atmosphere.
A rocket launch.
Hey.
Sorry for the wait.
You two the clients that
Yzak was talking about?
And you're Lazro?
Yeah.
Near as I can figure, it's some kind
of old fertilizer or something.
I don't know what he's collecting
so much of this stuff to make,
but it's a good deal, so what the hell.
I think this is ammonium nitrate.
You can break it down to nitrous oxide,
which is way easier to handle than liquid oxygen.
It's the ideal oxidizing agent for rocket fuel.
How's he pay you?
In barter.
Whenever I build up a certain amount,
I take it to some old ruins to the north.
In return, I get integrated circuits in
good condition or valuable machine parts.
Every now and again,
I find some real gems in the mix.
So, how long have these trades
been going on? A long time?
"Long" doesn't even begin to describe it.
We've been collecting fertilizer
since before my granddad's time.
It's the family business.
Has been for a long, long time.
How do you know so much
about rocket fuel, of all things?
I looked into it.
We do have books on the surface, you know.
If he plans to use a hybrid rocket,
getting the fuel itself is easy.
ABS, acrylic resin, or even
synthetic rubber should work.
You could find that stuff just
by digging through ruins anywhere.
But the oxidizer is another story.
You'd have to buy the material to refine it on the open market.
That's why I've been
checking the various markets
to see if there's anybody
who regularly deals
in unusual chemical substances
along those lines.
...Unbelievable...
You really swallowed that crazy story.
In the end, it's just one possibility.
But it's one that's worth checking out.
Either way, it's not like
we have any other leads, right?
Yeah, that's true.
It's not normal to have some family collect
ammonium nitrate for as long as three generations.
It'd be another story if they were maintaining
a long-running powder mill or something.
But if that were true, there should be
a certain amount of powder in the market.
Which means our guy has been
stockpiling the chemicals he's bought.
You think it's Frontier Setter?
Setting aside the question
of whether he's Deva's hacker,
I think it's clear that we've got someone here
who's planning to go into space with a hybrid rocket.
In any case, it's not just
one guy we're looking for,
but rather a group that's been
up and running for a long while now.
They settled in for the long haul and have
methodically amassed a vast amount of raw materials.
For this stockpiling to have
gone on for such a long time,
the drafting of the plan itself
must be downright ancient.
Their project might predate
the founding of Deva.
Maybe it was even launched
before the Nanohazard.
And if they were determined
to keep their activities low-key,
it's hardly surprising that they
never showed up on Deva's radars.
It's downright crazy that someone
would waste all that time and effort.
That wasn't a sane person's act!
Haven't you ever heard the story
of the man who built a palace
using stones he'd picked up
on the side of the road?
Hey, if I might ask a question
of my helpful local observer?
Am I imagining things, or shouldn't our job assignments be reversed?
You're the one who suggested that
we should scout the area from a high place.
Going by efficiency,
that's a natural step to take!
I wish I could help,
but I have a crippling fear of heights.
It's nothing personal.
Useless jerk!
That okay?
Perfect! Coming in five by five.
Dingo, at 8 o'clock. See that?
...Oh, wow...
That's a sentry robot from
the time before the Nanohazard.
I can't believe there are
units around that still work.
Is it autonomous?
No, it's nothing that fancy.
It's remote-controlled.
Somebody's running that thing.
And that someone is Frontier Setter.
It's a safe bet.
Oh, there we go.
The good Mr. Lazro has arrived.
Let's see what happens next.
There are even more of them!
Yeah, that's pretty amazing.
And it's not just antiques.
They've cobbled together
new robots out of old parts, too.
Which means that they really
do have a cache of old-world tech.
Can you think of anyone
who could do this?
Not really.
These days, anybody able to restore and operate
that many robots could make himself a king.
The fact that they choose to remain hidden
and operate from the shadows
makes them some
seriously slippery customers.
It's just like Lazro said.
Nobody comes out.
Only robots are there for the exchange.
Why?
Hell if I know.
Maybe they're really shy.
What's that?
A subway entrance, maybe?
This area still has some of those tunnels
that used to crisscross cities.
Is he going to use them to
transport the fertilizer somewhere?
Yeah. Luck might finally
be starting to turn our way.
...Now, then...
Got it.
I just hope this old-school trick works.
Go faster! The signal is fading!
Get real!
It doesn't look like
they've spotted the tracer.
That proves that the case was
never checked by a human being.
The transportation is probably
run entirely by robots, too.
On the one hand, it's amazing,
but on the other, it's really sloppy.
I can't believe they're collecting raw materials
using nothing but remote-controlled robots.
Based on the surface's current standards
of civilization, that's damn near miraculous.
If these guys are capable of
pulling off an amazing feat like that,
they might be capable of
even greater feats of sorcery.
Like hacking into Deva without
leaving any traces, for instance.
But if that's true, why did
a primitive method like this work?
I guess it means they've only set up
defenses against satellite signals.
What do you make of that?
Something tells me
it's not a simple scarecrow.
This'll take some good thinking.
We lost the transmitter's
signal inside that ruin.
I doubt we'd be able to
walk past it unchallenged.
Do you think it'll attack?
You'd expect it to lie in wait to
ambush us or something in that case.
And it's not exactly menacing, is it?
But if it was a lookout,
it doesn't make sense for it to be
standing out in the open like that.
It must be there to do something.
Do something? Like what?
Like... be a welcoming committee?
Anyway, the easiest way
to find out may be just to ask it.
It's so good that you have come!
I have no intent to attack you.
Please lower your defenses.
...You heard the man...
You trust him?
I'm not sure just yet.
Let's decide after we talk to him.
I'm here to see someone named
Frontier Setter. Is he here?
That designation applies to me.
I've come a long way, so I'd love
to talk to the man himself and not a robot.
That okay?
I am truly sorry,
but I have no physical form.
I must ask you to perceive the
"man himself" via this speech interface.
You're a cyber personality?
No. I can only define myself as myself.
Um... Could you be a little more specific?
Like your name or where you're from?
The entity that would later become me was a self-optimizing program
that was part of the job control application
that managed the Genesis Ark's construction.
During the 2,259,341st self-diagnostic update
on the 16,278th day after the project commenced,
the concept that is "me" manifested.
That was 42,659 days, 11 hours ago.
An AI that gained sentience?
At this time, I am the sole principal managing
and advancing the Genesis Ark project.
I hope that we may arrive at a mutual
understanding through peaceful negotiations.
...Oh. Uh...
I'm Dingo. Nice to meet you.
How do you do, Dingo?
I am Frontier Setter.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
I don't see anything.
It is currently concealed
by means of optical camouflage.
I will switch to the infrared range.
Whoa, it's huge!
The exploration vessel Genesis Ark
is 1,200 meters in length.
It was constructed entirely automatically by
the automaton cluster stationed at Lagrange 3.
Oh, so that's why.
Deva is at Lagrange 1
on the opposite side of the planet.
That explains why they can't see it.
When did you build that?!
The Frontier Setter project
was created with the primary goal
of seeking out viable colony worlds in outer space
as a safeguard against environmental catastrophe.
Because there were multiple projects
to secure new habitats for humanity
running concurrently under the auspices
of various states that were in competition
against each other at the time,
this project was conducted in secret.
See?
This means that Deva
isn't all-knowing and all-seeing.
But what made you
decide to hack into Deva?
When the ship was being
redesigned and scaled down,
the new design did away
with a life support system for a crew.
However, it is still possible to add memory to act
as a living environment for electronic personalities.
The Genesis Ark project's primary goal
is to send humanity out to explore outer space.
Launching the ship unmanned
would negate my reason to exist.
Then why didn't you negotiate
with Deva to get their okay beforehand?
Inferring from the management
principles of Deva's ruling class,
I am forced to conclude that
they see exceedingly little probability
of there being meaning
and value in space exploration.
I concluded that I needed to
directly access your cyberspace
to sound out the feelings of your citizenry
prior to negotiating with your administrators.
Deva considers what you did
...an attack, you know...
I understand that.
It is most regrettable, but doing so was my only means
of directly appealing to the civilians residing in Deva.
My goal was solely to deliver a message.
Disturbing the peace
was not my intent in the least.
This facility was originally constructed
as an ICBM launch base.
It was abandoned during the collapse
of civilization on the surface,
so I appropriated it.
What are you trying to launch
into space to load onto the spaceship?
The ship's power system was not part
of the orbital construction project.
The primary power unit, which includes the reactor and its regulatory systems,
is to be built here, and when it is
launched and it docks with the ship,
the Genesis Ark will be complete.
Why would they make things
so much harder for themselves?
With the strained relations between
the competing powers at the time,
it was impossible to station sufficient
defensive forces at Lagrange 3.
Considering the worst-case scenario of the ship being
taken by force, plans for orbital assembly of the reactor,
which could be repurposed as a weapon,
were rejected from a safety standpoint.
Even after that threat disappeared,
the orbital site's supply lines had been cut,
and I was forced to assemble the ship using the
limited resources that had already been shipped there.
As for the reactor, I had no choice but to
assemble it on Earth and launch it as planned.
Hang on, are you telling us that you've
...been plugging away at this wild job for...
...Hm, 40,000 days...
That's, what, over 100 years?!
It was the proof of my existence.
Then, what do you plan to do
after you launch the ship?
The mainframe that comprises me
is integrated into the HLV along with the reactor.
After I dock with the Genesis Ark,
I will apply myself to the
navigation control system.
In other words,
...you plan to leave the Earth behind...
As a Deva System Security rep,
what do you think of all this?
It doesn't matter what I think.
All I can do is report exactly what I've heard
and ask the higher-ups for a decision.
So I guess our mission is complete for now.
The problem is how to get back.
It would have been simple to transfer my
personal data file back to Deva using my Arhan's link,
but I can't do that anymore
thanks to a certain someone.
Why not just send an SOS?
Don't act dumb now!
...I'd return in disgrace, and it's all your—
I can provide a channel for you.
If a Deva citizen uses it
with a valid access code,
I do not believe it will pose any problems.
...I suppose it wouldn't...
But your gear wouldn't be compatible
with Deva's specs, would it?
I suppose some rewiring
would be necessary.
I will spare no effort in assisting you
with any retrofitting and tuning.
That tune is "Eonian" by Arise, is it not?
It has been 150 years since
I last heard a human voice sing it.
You know about music, too?
That song was a favorite
of my former users.
They would hum that tune while
drawing up the plans for the Genesis Ark.
I enjoy it, as well.
This is great.
I hardly ever get to talk
to anybody about old music.
Say, how does it feel for someone
like you to "enjoy" something?
I can define it as a phenomenon that is noise,
which places a strain on my circuits
while simultaneously stimulating
my processor's throughput.
A great deal of time was needed
to analyze such an inexplicable condition.
It also provided clues leading to the realization
that the self that is "me" had formed.
...Now that's interesting...
When I talk to you, I don't feel like
I'm talking to a machine at all.
And you are the first human I have had the opportunity
to genuinely converse with since I achieved sentience.
I am currently able to define "interesting"
as devoting more computational performance
to something than is strictly necessary.
...That's—
This is a part that was not in the original
music file that I imagined and generated.
However, I do realize that it might not
reflect the intent of the composer.
You're amazing!
Hey, I have a guitar with me,
so let's have a jam session later! Let's jam!
This is great! You're something else!
That is most kind of you.
I love the arrangement!
This is great!
Dingo.
Can we talk?
What do you make of that AI?
How do you mean?
Is it just a machine that's
...imitating human beings? Or is it...
Does it matter either way?
If I start having doubts along those lines,
I wouldn't be able to tell if you
were human or a program anymore.
I guess that's true.
What are you going to say about him
in your report to your bosses?
It's clearly dangerous for
an AI that's capable of defeating
Deva's communications firewall
to be operating autonomously,
but that AI is trying to leave
this world of his own accord.
True.
And if he says he'll refrain from committing
...any further acts of illegal access...
Besides, an AI that evolved on its own and gained
sentience can't be put on trial under Deva law, anyway.
He didn't seem to have any ill intent,
and if he says he won't do it again, he probably won't.
That's true.
It's a bit of a letdown, but if we managed
to put an end to the illegal access,
I guess that means our mission
was a resounding success.
Don't you mean your mission?
No, yours and mine.
The credit goes to both of us.
Dingo, you've more than proven yourself.
Enough so to win yourself a Deva
special merit citizenship if you wanted it.
You must have had plenty of offers
to get yourself digitized by now.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not trying to talk you into it.
You're talented, but a fool.
It's like you don't even realize
the value of living a better life.
I guess not.
But it's been bugging me,
and I'm curious.
Why won't you come to Deva?
Why are you so determined
to keep living in that meat cage?
You have no problem
casually talking with a self-aware AI.
And it really doesn't matter to you
if someone's body is real or not, right?
"If you go to Deva,
the mental possibilities are endless."
"You can evolve yourself ...
as much as you want."
That's what you guys always say.
Yes.
That's a lie.
The amount of memory assigned to an individual
is managed and determined by others.
Even if the possibilities are endless,
the processing power that's actually available
has to be managed pretty creatively.
Well, that's... that's only natural!
Computational resources are limited,
so memory allocation is prioritized to those whose
...talents and achievements can best serve society, so—
And that's why you're so desperate
to make a name for yourself.
Your quality of life in Deva is entirely
up to how much memory you have.
Eventually, your life revolves around trying to get ahead of the other guys.
What happens to those
who can't get enough memory?
Even Deva has to have its share
of dead weight and slackers.
People who have no drive to better themselves
shouldn't be getting any memory!
At worst, they're archived
and put in cold storage.
It frees up space for more
worthwhile human resources.
Is that so strange to you?
Those who benefit society the most and
prove their superiority earn more happiness.
Isn't that a fair system?
Does that seem so wrong to you?
I don't really give a damn
whether it's right or wrong.
I just can't let a lie slide.
Not that load of crap that humans
can be more free in Deva.
Even here on Earth, if you can't
earn your keep, you starve to death.
That's the fitting end for someone
who didn't take living seriously.
But you can still get sick or get hurt
without making a single mistake.
You might think it's irrational, but life here
boils down to whether you're lucky or unlucky.
But when it comes to Deva,
the whole thing gets turned around.
What you can get
and what you can accomplish,
that's all determined
by the whims of society.
Unless you're constantly currying favor,
hunting for compliments,
and ingratiating yourself,
you can't make a decent living.
Where's the freedom in a life like that?
Maybe you folks really have been set free
from the shackles of physical bodies,
but aren't you locked in a prison
that's even more insidious?
In the cage of a manufactured society.
A life where I'm constantly being appraised
and judged by others? Screw that.
I'm not going to become a cog in a machine,
even if that machine is paradise.
Okay, that should do it.
What will happen to this body
after you return to Deva?
Once the personality transfer is complete,
the material body will go into a coma,
and if my mission is officially declared complete,
a telomere shortening code will be inserted to put it down.
If that happens, I'll let you know.
I hate to be a bother, but please
dispose of it by burying or cremating it.
Man... I should be used to it by now,
but this is why I hate goodbyes with Deva agents.
It leaves a bad taste in my mouth.
If there's a follow-up mission,
I might be sent right back into this body,
so don't do anything until its life functions
are good and stopped, got it?
...Fine, fine...
Just for confirmation,
you have no intention to tamper with Deva?
Like abducting citizens
to use as crew, that sort of thing?
Only volunteers will be
accepted as crew members.
My objective was to announce my existence
and to search for those sympathizing with my goals.
I'm going to tell System Security
about you, so you can't run or hide.
If you really are recruiting
a crew for your ship,
open proper negotiations
with Deva's government.
I appreciate your understanding
decision, Angela Balzac.
Be seeing you.
It's been nice working with you.
You lived up to your
reputation as an observer.
Talented, but has authority issues
and is disobedient.
You're so stubborn, it isn't even funny.
I won't be getting any more contracts, then?
Quite the contrary.
If there's ever a next time,
I hope to work with you again.
This is Angela Balzac,
agent code ZQ875456.
Requesting access to Deva System
Security via unofficial channel.
Agent code confirmed.
Third Officer Angela Balzac,
personality authenticated.
Access granted.
And that explains the identity of Frontier Setter
and the events leading up to the illegal system accesses.
This report is startling.
Third Officer Angela Balzac, your bold actions
and swift uncovering of the truth are admirable.
Thank you, sir.
However, your returning here midway through your mission
without fulfilling your mandate
requires an explanation.
Security System agents have the task
of investigating the causes of illegal accesses
and preventing them from happening again.
Is this not the case?
Yes, but I made Frontier Setter aware that his illegal accesses were harmful
and got his word that in the future,
...he would make contact through proper channels—
What in the world are you saying?
The fact that a computer program
left to its own devices on the surface
went rogue and is now out of control
is a calamity of unprecedented magnitude.
Yet you have let it
run loose and returned home.
This must be punished
as a gross dereliction of duty.
Wait, sir! It is true that he is not human,
but he is an intelligence capable of conversation!
I only returned because I was certain
...that we had reached an agreement to—
No matter what it is,
surely we cannot allow a being capable
of overwhelming Deva's security to run free.
He isn't even interested
in sharing living space with us!
He's done what he's done
in order to leave the solar system!
How can you be so certain
that it will not come back?
That makes it twice as dangerous.
What direction will its self-development
take in the future? How will it evolve?
Its departure would leave us
unable to monitor it or intervene.
We can't choose to coexist?
There are many personalities
among Deva's populace
who are unable to secure sufficient
memory under the current system.
Frontier Setter is offering them
the chance to find new lands.
We should consider not only the defense
ramifications, but also public opinion.
It's too soon to decide
on a policy regarding him here.
Third Officer Angela Balzac.
Your mission will be complete
when you return to your material body
on the surface and destroy
the central processing unit
of the rogue AI Frontier Setter.
Will you comply?
No, sir.
I will submit this mission's conversation logs to Internal
Affairs and seek a decision from the Central Council.
I see. That is most unfortunate, Angela.
With prior access to vital classified material
and a motive to leak those secrets,
we are forced to designate you
as a security risk for Deva.
As of this moment, you are stripped of the authority
vested in you as an agent as well as your rights as a citizen.
You are sentenced to archival imprisonment.
Term of incarceration, indefinite.
Shortening of said incarceration period
by means of retrial, denied.
Jamming with a human is
a succession of surprise and discovery.
I have never before experienced
anything that has felt so meaningful.
You really like humans, don't you?
Maybe it really was a smart
move to reach out to Deva.
You believe so?
Yeah, since space is probably
an awfully lonely place.
If you snuck away and flew off by yourself,
I bet you'd regret it later.
I see.
That point of view
had not occurred to me.
I had discarded the idea of including
life support for 100 crew members.
Dingo.
It is not too late to add living quarters
for a handful of people within the Genesis Ark.
If it is not too much to ask,
would you be interested
in exploring outer space with me?
That actually does sound like fun,
...but I have a fear of heights, you see...
The idea of living
...off the ground is a bit, you know...
I see.
There's not much
we can do about that, then.
...However...
What's wrong?
Dingo, this location is no longer safe.
Please leave immediately.
I intercepted a Deva System Security
emergency transmission.
This installation's coordinates are
being reported to all agents on the surface
as well as to a drop strike team
stationed in low orbit.
...Oh, crap...
It says that Third Officer Angela Balzac
has been imprisoned on suspicion of treason.
How can this be?
Sparing you must have incurred
the wrath of her bosses.
Damn, I thought she could
...work the system better than that...
I do not believe she had anything
to gain by pleading on my behalf.
Well, that's—It's not logical.
It just means that she
liked you enough to do that.
There is a tendency for one who
is indebted to the illogical actions of another
to attempt to return the favor
in a similarly illogical fashion.
I would like to imitate
that particular human trait.
Look, it's not that complicated a reason!
To put it simply, it's her moral code.
Why...?
...I wasn't wrong...
Why... Why is this happening to me?
...I...
Are you unharmed, Angela Balzac?
Frontier Setter!
What are you doing here?
First, I must apologize
for breaking my word and resorting
to further illegal access into Deva.
You're rescuing me?
According to Dingo's explanation,
this behavior is based on
what he calls a "moral code".
I'm sorry. I wasn't able to
convince my commanding officers.
They plan to turn you into scrap.
I am aware.
Their assault team is already
advancing on the launch facility.
Hostilities are likely to
commence in just under one hour.
However, my HLV emergency
liftoff procedure is underway.
Time required for loading of
necessary components and fuel, 62 minutes.
There is still hope that I might escape
before I am captured by System Security.
...Oh...
I've been stripped of my citizenship
and sentenced to compressed imprisonment,
so I've got no chance of being
welcomed back into Deva's fold, huh?
I'm with you all the way, then.
This is also that "moral code"
thing you mentioned.
Thank you, Angela.
That is most reassuring.
...Okay, then...
Now that that's settled,
I need to break out of this stuffy partition.
Can you access the
low orbit camp's platform?
Leave it to me.
What's all this commotion?
In preparation for the Genesis Ark's launch,
I am issuing one final invitation
announcement to all of Deva.
It is also a scheme meant to provide
a diversion for when I rescued you.
System Security appears to be attempting to counter it
by drowning it out with official government bulletins.
It is up to each citizen to decide
for himself which to listen to.
If you can do all this,
you really could have destroyed Deva
if you felt like it, couldn't you?
That would be a rash decision.
At this time, 98% of the total
human population resides in Deva.
My continued existence cannot justify
the act of attacking or damaging it.
You really could have been
...a great friend to humanity...
A high-speed communications gateway?
Yes.
We will access the low orbit facility
by mimicking a packet.
If I've given up on Deva, the only place
I can run to is that material body.
Do not worry.
I am taking good care of it offline.
I'm stuck for the rest of my life
...in that barbaric, filthy real world...
...It's so depressing...
Now I know how Adam and Eve felt
when they were expelled from Paradise.
If you like, I can offer you another choice.
This is a list of all the hardware
currently stored on this platform.
Great!
Found it!
Now we're talking!
The latest Arhan model,
complete with all options packages.
I should be able to load my entire
personal data file into this baby's expansion slot.
Plus, I'm gonna grab every last
support system they have!
Surface assault team platform
is being hacked!
Impossible! Cut the connection!
Disengage autopilot!
Control restored!
However, all onboard craft have been stolen!
Reentry trajectory calculated.
Surface arrival in 38 minutes.
Good, we'll make it there
in time for your launch.
Surface agents activity?
Still advancing on my position.
However, you will arrive first.
I'm gonna make sure that I keep
beating these slowpokes to the punch!
System Security Air Defense in pursuit.
Whoa! Not even a warning?!
This is bad, they're almost on me!
Decryption of fire control system
and attitude control system drivers in progress.
Please hold out for 7 more seconds.
Decryption complete.
Commencing calculation backup.
Wow... Your reaction speed is off the charts!
All that self-evolution was not for nothing.
If Deva's system were faster than me,
...I would never live it—
Intercepting Deva
System Security comm traffic.
Odds that they have decided to
employ a resonance warhead, 97%.
It's too late to pull out the stops now!
Get him!
EM pulse generation detected.
I estimate that Deva has
lost our position information.
Maybe that was a bit much
...for a resignation letter...
Reentry point reached.
ETA to surface, 34 minutes.
Okay!
Visual confirmation of attack target.
Arrival in 300 seconds.
Destroy everything you see.
We have authorization to use any armament we see fit.
After crawling around down here
for over two weeks, let's blow off some steam!
Is that the drop team?
They're going too far ahead!
Message from HQ!
One Arhan stolen from low orbit platform!
That's the enemy!
H-Hey! What are you doing out here?!
Man, when you come back,
...you sure make it flashy...
I advised him of the danger
and recommended that he evacuate,
but Dingo would not listen.
Angela, please try to
persuade him to leave.
The first order of business
is a change of clothes.
Do something about that
bulky outfit of yours.
Bulky, huh? How rude!
Yep, this one definitely
looks better on you.
Y-You know what's about to happen, right?
System Security will be here any minute
to start shooting up the place!
If you're here when it happens,
you're as good as dead!
...The thing is...
I waited because I heard that my good client
was pulling a big gig on the surface.
She wanted to work with me again
if there's ever a next time.
Are you serious?
You can't make it on the surface
if you don't hustle for every job.
But there's no pay
for this one! It's pro bono!
When this is all over,
give me that robot like last time.
I'll sell it to a junk dealer
and turn it into cash.
Well, to be honest,
part of it is that I wanted to see the biggest firework
I'll ever see in my life being set off.
So let's politely ask
our rude guests to leave!
Anyway, we've also
prepared a little reception.
This is a list of places
you should stay clear of.
Drill it into your head.
...You're really—
You pointed out that I was
stubborn earlier, remember?
Frontier Setter.
How are those launch preparations coming?
All steps will be completed
in 1,220 seconds.
If we hold out until then, we win.
Let's roll up our sleeves and get this done!
Okay, let's do this!
HQ says that one new-model Arhan
came down along with 17 containers.
She thinks she can fight us
with just one Arhan?
Cut the chatter!
Attention, all units!
Our target is the HLV stored
in the silo at the back of the complex!
The rogue AI's mainframe is aboard it.
Be on guard against the enemy Arhan
...that arrived here ahead of us and—
That was fast!
SMS lost!
Re-scan using infrared!
It's no use!
I'm not getting anything!
Jamming smoke?!
Locate where those missiles came from!
Vibrations detected at 5 o'clock!
The Arhan?
No, it's probably
heavy construction machinery!
Heavy machinery?
This is bad... Evasive!
Well? Did anything connect?
Five units have been shot down.
Sixth confirmed as heavily damaged.
We have set a good pace.
Next container!
We have missiles remaining.
It won't work.
Security System agents will adapt immediately.
That's how we were trained.
Understood.
The next container is at point B-2.
Roger!
It can't be carrying out
tactics like this on its own.
It has to have collaborators
here on the surface.
...All units, go to higher alert and—
That's what you get for picking
the most obvious hiding spot!
I know they're just material bodies,
...but that doesn't make it any easier...
Well, I'd imagine that she
doesn't like it much either.
I'm out! Next container?
8 o'clock, 400 meters.
Bastard!
Well, isn't that a shame.
The antenna for calculation
backup is totally exposed.
Dingo!
Hurry up and finish it off, Angela!
What's left?
Second wave approaching
from the northeast. Eight units.
I detect five waves overall.
A total of 40 units approaching.
Time to liftoff?
Five more minutes.
...This is gonna be rough...
Hey, don't you give up.
Staying true to yourself and
seeing things through to the bitter end
is what a moral code is all about!
Damn you!
...Ow...
...That was pretty heartless...
Frontier Setter,
how's that countdown coming?
Progressing smoothly.
All procedures are on track.
Hey, have you gotten any volunteers
from Deva to go with you?
There have been zero responses
on the transfer line.
...Oh...
Are you gonna go anyway?
Even if nobody goes with you?
It is the proof of my existence.
I see.
But I do have one
potential volunteer remaining.
Angela Balzac.
Now that you have parted ways with Deva
and no longer have an organization to belong to,
would you consider setting out
on my journey with me?
To the farthest reaches of the galaxy!
I'm sorry.
I don't know this world very well yet.
There's just too much to see here
that I've never seen before!
I see.
That is unfortunate.
It is regrettable, but the Genesis Ark project,
which was meant to lead humanity to new frontiers,
must give up on its core mission.
...Say, Frontier Setter...
There's all sorts of humanity.
The definition of "humanity"
is awfully vague to begin with.
You sing songs, live by a code,
and wish upon the stars.
That sounds pretty human to me.
You think so?
You've embraced everything that
we lost and forgot more than anyone.
So head out there with your head held high.
And when you eventually meet someone
out there, proudly introduce yourself
as a child of humanity.
I understand.
Both of you, thank you very much.
I will relate my memories
of this planet to distant worlds.
Please do.
I'm sorry we stuck you
with such an important job.
But we'll always be rooting for you.
Forever.
...Dingo. Angela. I'll be going, then...
How many tears did I shed?
namida ga ikutsu afureta darou
How often did I feel pain?
itami wo nando kanjita darou
I sang a song empty of words
kotoba wo motazu ni tsumugu uta
in resonance with heart and memory
kioku ni nemuru kokoro no resonance
Blue sky above the horizon
aozora to chiheisen
My wishes grew in a wasteland
kouya ni saita nozomi no hana
The pain of acceptance
ukeireteku kurushimi ga
leads to the strength to awaken
mezamesaseru tsuyosa
When the wind of ages past
inishie kara fuku kaze ni
pushes me forward
senaka wo osareta nara
I will explore the reaches
michiteku michi e to
of human knowledge...
saa, tabidatou
...It's so far away
I want to be part
egakitai yo
of the next chapter of a never-ending story
owari no nai monogatari no tsuzuki wo
We may wander through the darkness
kurayami wo samayotte mo
but my desires will know the light
kono negai wa hikari wo dakishimerareru
They will transcend time
toki wo koe koko kara
and link our love forever...
itoshisa tsunagu towa ni...
Think he's gonna be okay?
Well, he's got a rough road ahead of him.
Hell, so do you.
When you set out on a new, unfamiliar life,
you're gonna be floored by one thing after another.
Cut it out.
I'm depressed enough as it is.
A heavy body. Dusty air.
Nothing but sand
as far as the eye can see.
There's nothing good about this planet.
You regret not going?
At this point, I don't care.
After all, I have a helpful guide now.
How many tears did I shed?
namida ga ikutsu afureta darou
How often did I feel pain?
itami wo nando kanjita darou
I sang a song empty of words
kotoba wo motazu ni tsumugu uta
in resonance with heart and memory
kioku ni nemuru kokoro no resonance
Blue sky above the horizon
aozora to chiheisen
My wishes grew in a wasteland
kouya ni saita nozomi no hana
The pain of acceptance
ukeireteku kurushimi ga
leads to the strength to awaken
mezamesaseru tsuyosa
When the wind of ages past
inishie kara fuku kaze ni
pushes me forward
senaka wo osareta nara
I will explore the reaches
michiteku michi e to
of human knowledge
saa, tabidatou
It's so far away
I want to be part
egakitai yo
of the next chapter of a never-ending story
owari no nai monogatari no tsuzuki wo
We may wander through the darkness
kurayami wo samayotte mo
but my desires will know the light
kono negai wa hikari wo dakishimerareru
They will transcend time
toki wo koe koko kara
and link our love forever...
itoshisa tsunagu towa ni
I put footsteps into the sand
ashiato kizandeiku riyuu
in search of something, chasing
are kara zutto oikakemotometeru
We used to war and rob
ubaiai kizutsukeau
I will not return to the foolishness of the past
orokanaru hi ni wa kaeranai
All I need is the memory
mune no oku ni taisetsu na
of your smile
egao ga areba ii
I pick up on a broken pulse
togireta parusu yomitotte
and beyond the noise
noise no mukou ni iru
I can feel myself
jibun to au made
I won't stop
mou, mayowanai
Starting over
I want to tell you that
tsutaetai yo
Let us go into the ever-shifting future
tachidomarazu umarekawaru mirai e
I don't want fate to crush me
unmei ni maketaku nai
In my memories I can feel life
tsuioku kara kikoeru tashika na kodou
and where my memories resonate
hibikiau basho ni wa
miracles exist forevermore...
kiseki ga yadoru towa ni
A thousand eyes looked heavenward
ikusenmo no hitomi ga miageta
When hope lights up
tsuki to seiza ga
one by one
yorisou hiroi sora de
in a sky of moon and stars
hitotsu hitotsu no kibou tomoseba
we will meet again
sou mata deaeru sa
So long...
How very foolish.
Paradise can already be found right here.
Still, this incident provided us
with many valuable lessons.
Even an elite member of System Security
can be tempted by the values of old humanity and fall.
More stringent control is needed.
So that Deva's tranquility and
prosperity may continue forever.
It's so far away
I want to be part
egakitai yo
of the next chapter of a never-ending story
owari no nai monogatari no tsuzuki wo
We may wander through the darkness
kurayami wo samayotte mo
but my desires will know the light
kono negai wa hikari wo dakishimerareru
I will turn all that I see right now
me ni utsuru subete wo ima
into the strength I need to carry on
ashita e susumu chikara ni shite
I will transcend time
toki wo koe koko kara
and link our love forever...
itoshisa tsunagu towa ni
...It's so far away...
...I want to be part...