One-tier
Ain't she a beauty?
Your gramps and his friends
made this doll, ya know?
Awesome, right?
Yup.
Awesome.
So beautiful!
It's the prettiest thing in the world!
You can become as good as me if you practice, Wakana.
Gross!
Why do you like girly dolls
even though you're a boy, Wakky?
I hate you!
Good morning.
You're as beautiful as ever.
Precious things that shine in brilliant colors
I'll never forget this day
My sigh flew way over the horizon
And was taken away by the waves
FIERY FLOWER     PRINCESS!
On a whim you helped me find my true self
So I skip after you as you drag me by the hand
FIERY FLOWER
PRINCESS
I'll burn your broad smile into my memories
Two shadows jumping by the water
These footsteps I hear are echoing towards the future
I'm chasing you, so brilliant and barefoot in the distance
I opened up my heart and so much came gushing out
I'll paint the blazing flames of the future in glittering hues
I've never felt like this before
Your shining eyes look straight towards your dream
I want to smile by your side and
Be myself!
Episode 1
The One Who Lives in a World Entirely Unlike Mine
Gojou Dolls
100th Edition
Golden Week Sakurako
Name
Count
Greatsword
Hilt
Count: 4 pcs
Golden Week Sakurako
100th Edition
Count: 4 pcs
Golden Week Sakurako
Name
Count
Greatsword
Golden Week Sakurako
Name
Count
Greatsword
Hilt
Count: 4 pcs
Name
Count
Greatsword
Name
Count
Greatsword
Hilt
Count: 4 pcs
Good morning, gramps.
Morning, Wakana.
Were you working late last night?
You sure you're getting enough sleep?
Oh,
I got into the rhythm of it, so...
I kept painting them, and before I'd realized,
I had made quite a few.
I still can't paint them as well as you though.
Just how many years
do you think I've been doing this?
Uh, forty seven?
48!
Let's dig in.
You can't do faces,
but your outfits are great. You're doing fine.
That's the only thing I can do.
I can't do anything else well.
You don't need to push yourself.
Just take it easy.
You're still a student.
Sure.
Speaking of that...
Have you made any friends
now that you're in high school?
Are you okay?
I-I'm okay.
What brought that question on?
Since grade school, all you've ever done
is make or play with dolls.
So I thought maybe you didn't have any friends.
Oh, I do! I do have friends!
I've always had friends.
They all have club activities to go to.
So we don't get to spend much time together.
That's all.
That's all it is.
That so?
I'm relieved.
I see, yup.
Gojou Dolls
I'm off.
Do take care.
Will do.
I really hate first period!
We'll get scolded for sure!
Hey there!
I-I'm sorry!
Wrong person!
Sorry, gramps.
I haven't made any friends in high school either.
I mean, how could I?
My dream is to be a hina doll artisan.
So all my hobbies are...
Making hina dolls and improving my doll-making.
Appreciating their beauty.
How pretty you are.
Talking to them.
Where should we
start working on you today?
With those sorts of interests,
there's no way I can talk to other people.
Did you see episode 6 yesterday?
Of Chiru 2?
It was sick!
The animation was dope as well!
In the last tournament, the coach was...
The things I love and the things
they love are too different.
'Sup!
So...
If I try to join them, I'll just end up
disturbing and unsettling them.
It'd be better...
if I just disappeared...
Yowch!
I'm sorry, Marin!
All good?
Sorries.
Are you okay?
I'm okay, I guess.
Sorry about that, uh...
Gojou.
K-Kitagawa!
W-W-Well...
We all good?
Y-Yes!
Oh, is that...
There's something on your arm.
What's this?
A bruise?
Guess not.
That's just...
It's not a bad one.
One what?!
Is that so?
All good then.
You sure you're okay, Marin?
My head made a cracking sound!
As if!
There was...
ink on my arm.
Boy, she surprised me though.
That's the first time I've talked to her.
Kitagawa is a cheerful person with many friends.
She's always in the spotlight.
She lives in a different world from me.
Listen, after school yesterday...
Whoa, gonna tell them about that?
It's rare for you to hang around after school, though.
You usually just disappear.
Marin said she was going to her part-time
job as a salon model.
I wanted to get a haircut anyways.
It was part-time work, after all!
There was this guy waiting around
after his haircut to hit on her.
Yikes, just go home, dude.
How'd he look?
He was a total hunk!
Just before we were gonna head back,
he approached us.
He was fishing for a conversation topic, but...
Say, isn't that from that whatchamacallit anime?
Such a nerd!
Hard pass from me.
You're a hard pass for me, too.
She said!
And then she left.
For real? Butchered the guy, huh?
That's rough!
The guy deflated on the spot.
Isn't that a waste, though?
You said he was a hunk.
You always give guys the cold shoulder
when they try to talk to you.
Him being hot doesn't matter.
I can't stand guys like him.
I mean, it's obvious I like the thing
if I put it on my bag, right?
It makes you wanna say "Don't go making fun
of the things people love, you prick!"
Right.
Also, don't put my cute Shion
in the "whatchamacallit" category.
There it is!
Marin's Shion obsession!
I'm telling you, that sort of thing is...
There's a person in this classroom
who lives in a world entirely unlike mine.
Sakuya
Mirai
uma
brother
Mion
Neon
Big si
It must be nice to live in a world where
other people accept you as you are.
Are you for real?
You'll do it again?
Sure. It's fine.
You saved my ass, dude!
Man, knock it off and start helping already.
What?
Gojou says it's fine, though.
Plus, I gotta get to work.
Counting on you, Gojou!
Dude!
I'm sorry, Gojou.
I'll have him buy you a juice next time.
To be honest, doing all the work myself is a pain.
But it's much better than the awkwardness
of trying to make conversation and failing.
I bet they'd have a hard time
finding a topic we could discuss anyways.
Staying quiet the entire time would also be tiring.
Let's just finish this up quickly and go back home.
Did she forget something?
What's up?
No...
Well...
What are you doing?
Exactly what it looks like.
Cleaning.
I was a bit late since I went to the bathroom first,
but I also have cleaning duty this week.
Y-You'll help?
Isn't that obvious?
I'm supposed to, right?
Where are the others?
They left.
Seems like they needed to go to work.
For real?
All of them?
Yes.
Gojou, they just push their work onto you, don't they?
They do indeed.
Indeed?!
You already knew?!
Doesn't it bother you?
Well, a little bit, yes.
Thought so!
Have you told them?
No.
But they see me as someone they can rely on,
so I guess it's fine.
They're not relying on you. They're just using you.
Being reliable doesn't mean just doing
whatever people tell you to.
That's definitely not a healthy way to live.
You need to tell people how you feel.
Gojou Dolls
Ow!
What's wrong?! You okay?!
Oh.
Sorry, I cut my finger again.
Be more careful!
Let's see. Did we have any band-aids left?
Hold on a bit.
Thank you.
It's been several days now...
You need to tell people how you feel.
...but I can't get Kitagawa's words out of my head.
She was right.
I always suppress my emotions.
But really...
even that time...
Huh?
There!
Put this on it!
Gramps, the sewing machine stopped working.
What?
Well, it's basically an antique.
It was its time.
Guess we need a new one.
I wish I had at least finished the piece.
Oh, right...
Home Ec Room
Man, this works so smoothly!
Good thing we don't have a handicrafts club.
There's no one here after class, so I can work freely.
I can even bring this.
I'll sew a cape for you today.
I hope you look forward to it.
K-Kitagawa!
I'm sorry! Are you okay?! Did you get hu—
Oh shit!
What is that?
It's all over.
So cool!
You can use a sewing machine?!
What?
The sewing machine!
Where'd you learn?!
We don't have home economics as an elective!
Well, um, my family runs a hina doll shop.
So they taught me at home.
Ah, that's why! Makes sense.
So is that a princess doll?
Eh?
Can I see her?
Here.
She's so pretty.
Her eyes are shining.
I've never
had anyone say anything nice
about the things I like.
Never before!
Did you make it?
No, my gramps made this one.
I-I still can't really make anything but the clothes.
Clothes?
You make clothes?
Um, yes.
For real?
Yes.
But I just do the sewing. Nothing complicated.
Um, could you face the other way?
Of course!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What is this?!
What's happening?!
Why is she taking her clothes off?!
What's that rustling?! What's that sound?!
Gojou.
Yes!
Wh-What is it?
You can turn around.
But—
It's okay. Look at me.
It's still a work in progress.
But still... um... what do you think?
Um...
What do you mean?
What is that outfit supposed to be?
Uh...
I kinda tried to make that dress.
On my own.
Is this a joke? Are you messing with me?
What? No, I'm not.
I seriously tried my best.
I mean, it looks nothing like the picture!
I can't even imagine how you got it so wrong.
This is the type of material that needs lining, right?
Lining? What's that?
You don't even know what lining is?!
I can't believe this.
Excuse me.
As I suspected, no backstitch, and it's all creased.
Wait! There's no lower thread on this hem!
This barely even counts as being sewn together!
And of course, you didn't leave
any margin for the seam, did you?!
And this! Why is this piece done differently?!
Also—
I-I'm terribly sorry! I got carried away!
Please kill me!
Wait! What?!
What are you doing?! Stop that!
Wh-Wh-What must I do to earn your forgiveness?
Nothing! I don't need anything!
I'm not mad! I'm really not!
Come on, Gojou, there's no need for that.
I made this because...
I want to use it for cosplay!
Cosplay?
Yup! Do you know what that is?
I want to dress up like characters
from manga, anime, and games.
It's the utmost show of support
for your favorite characters.
How awesome is that?
Isn't it the ultimate expression of love?!
You still listening, Gojou?
Yes! I'm sorry! I'm listening! I'm sorry!
Anyway, I don't have a sewing machine at home,
so I've been working on it here.
But as you can see, it's not going too well.
And I don't know anyone who's good at sewing.
Gojou!
Would you please make me clothes for cosplay?
What?
I'll understand...
I'll understand if you don't want to.
I don't think I could do much better by myself.
But I really want to be like Shizuku!
I love her so much that I want to be her!
Please help me, Gojou!
So cool!
You can use a sewing machine?!
She's so pretty.
Don't go making fun of the things people love!
You need to tell people how you feel.
Very well.
I've never made anything for people to wear before,
so I'm not sure if I'll do a good job.
But I'll do my best!
So you'll help me?
Yes!
For real?!
Yes.
Yay!
Yay! Yay! Yay!
Shizuku! Shizuku!
I can become Shizuku!
There's a person in this classroom
who lives in a world entirely unlike mine.
I never would have thought
I'd reach an understanding with her.
I'm literally moved to tears.
By the way, I'll do whatever bits I can by myself.
Though that might not be much!
Okay.
You really want to turn into that person, huh?
Yep!
She's just so precious!
Kuroe Shizuku from "The Lewdly Miraculous Lives of the
Rich Girls of the Humiliation Club at Saint Moist Girls' Academy 2"!
What did you just say?
I realized something,
I seem to be in love
By a whim of fate,
that one word made my chest tight
Ah, I shouldn't expect anything more though
Right now the two of us should just pursue our dreams
But my pure and innocent heart is being
(fluffy, fluffy, fluffy, fluffy)
Oh no, I'm staring, awestruck again
What do I do? I'm too deeply in love
I'll be true to my feelings, so please
Watch me become pretty by my side
Episode 2
Let's Get to Doing It
Next time!