Is this...
Huh?
A good-luck fairy?
Kai?
Congratulations on graduating, Bocchi.
You remember our promise, right?
We're through unless you've
made friends with all your classmates.
You really did try your best, Bocchi!
But...
I'm sorry. We're through.
See you.
Kai!
Please!
Today is July 19th.
It's the day before summer vacation,
and I'm starting to worry.
If I don't do something,
this nightmare's gonna come true!
In the summer of my first year of middle school,
I, Hitori Bocchi, have finally come to understand this.
Life really is tough...
So nervous, so scared, never able to say these words out loud
But you see
I just want
Want you to
Be my friend even though I'm like this
Life
I snooze the alarm, still asleep
My bed, warm and cozy, keeps me there
In my dreams, I open up
But life can never be that easy
Making a U-turn, so quick and neat
I'm here and you're there and we never meet
From up close you seem distant
From far away you shine like the sun
As our everyday theme song starts playing
It's a sign that we need to set off
Make some plans
Think them up
Leave behind
Doubts and fear
The first step is all you need
Just make all your dreams come true now
Can I believe in these words?
Now smile and say hi and just look—you've gained one more new friend
No, no, wait
That's not right
This is life
It won't go as you imagined
Don't rush now, take your time, make sure to just go at your own pace
And one day
Make it real
And so please
Be my friend and help fulfill my dreams
Just think—how wonderful could that be?
Don't be shy now, talk with us and not just to yourself
Gentle
Tears
I need to make at least one more new friend today.
Let's practice saying hi with a smile.
Morning.
All conversations start with a greeting.
A cheerful greeting. Cheerful!
Nako, Aru, Sotoka...
Remember when you spoke to them for the first time!
What do you want, Pukey?
Hitori?
What was perfectly executed?
All of them talked to me first!
Isn't that Aru's friend,
Yamada?
Yamada Hanako
(Tennis Club)
Now's the perfect time! Give her a cheerful greeting!
All conversations start with a greeting!
And the time for that greeting is now!
I ended up running away.
What is she doing?
It's so cool... It feels nice...
I should leave her alone.
It really is impossible for me
to start the conversation!
But I thought it might end up like this,
so I came up with a plan to let me avoid it!
And now... The time has finally come...
The time has come for me to remove my ribbon!
I must be getting better with this stuff
if I'm preparing plan Bs now.
That's Kurai from the disciplinary committee...
Kurai Kako
If she notices my missing ribbon, then...
Huh? Hitori?
Y-Yes?
Where's your ribbon?
Oh, I've forgotten it...
I see.
Please use this one, then.
It's my spare.
Thank you.
I'll make sure to wash it and return it.
That'd mean you'd have to
return it next term, wouldn't it?
Oh, right...
Can't help it.
We'll see each other during the summer break.
It'll end up like this!
Okay!
Huh? Hitori?
Y-Yes?
What's with your sloppy appearance?
Huh?
You aren't getting complacent just because
summer break is almost here, are you?
I... I...
I won't allow anything like that!
I-I-I... I-I... I-I-I...
Again?!
I hope everyone here enjoys their summer breaks.
Stand!
After everything that happened,
the term ended with no progress.
Bow.
I couldn't... do anything.
We're going home, Bocchi.
It's summer break, Master!
Where are we going? Where?
There were things I wanted to ask
my precious friends about, too...
Master?
Are you that happy?
How's your training going?
Do you want to see? I'll show you my skills!
Those two are so full of energy.
I won't lose!
Can you really win against me?
Huh?
Summer break's starting real soon,
but you seem really down, Bocchi.
I mean...
I'm not allowed to be happy right now...
What?!
I just can't... Because...
Oh, it's good.
You told me before that you liked this flavor, remember?
What's wrong? Did something happen?
I had a weird dream.
A dream?
I wasn't able to make up with Kai anymore in it.
I tried my best to make more friends...
To be friends with everyone...
But nothing worked out.
I see.
I actually planned to ask everyone
if they wanted to hang out with me...
over... the break... as well...
But who'd want to...
I shouldn't think about having fun with everyone...
Master!
Spend time with me!
That timing was impeccable!
I'll hang out with you, Master.
Hey!
You better not exclude me!
Let's have fun, Bocchi. We'll go to the beach,
and to the pool, and to the festival too!
Aru...
Autumn walks! Snowboarding! Flower viewing!
None of those things are summer events...
We'll visit tons of places, have lots of fun,
and you'll get over your shyness a little.
Then you'll make tons of friends
instantly once the second term starts!
Don't forget about me, too!
Thank you...
Then we can do radio exercises together too!
I'm not a morning person...
I know! Let's have a sleepover at my place!
Sounds good.
I won't have practice over the
Obon holidays, so let's do it then.
That sounds great!
Huh? Obon?
What's wrong?
I always visit my grandpa during Obon...
So I wouldn't be able to come...
Master!
It was just an idea, don't worry!
You see, Aru's gonna end up skipping
practice anyway, so we can do it whenever.
Stop saying stuff like that!
And so our summer break started.
Hitori
Bocchi's
Bocchi!
You should have just told me
you didn't have a proper swimsuit.
You actually showed up in your school swimsuit...
Our swimsuits match, Master!
Rakita
You too, Sotoka?!
Sorry for the wait.
And... sparkle!
You're getting way too worked up.
Stop that!
Look, it's a swimming pool!
It sure is.
Nako, it's a pool!
Yeah... It is...
Okay, everyone! Gotta exercise first!
Get warmed up!
Let's go! One, two, three, four!
...and five, six, seven, eight!
Oh, I could make this a part of my ninja training!
One, two, three, four!
Huh?
Sotoka...
Yes?
Don't stand next to me, please.
But why?
Just because!
I wanna go into the water!
You look fishy again.
Is this a new training technique?!
People are gonna stare...
Finally, we can go in...
Wait.
Don't forget to put on sunscreen.
Huh?
I want to go swim already...
I'm gonna start rubbing it in.
Sure.
Stop!
What are you even doing?
She also looks kinda suspicious.
I can do this.
My instincts are telling me
everything I need to know!
What are you doing?
Running on the water surface!
It's time to show off the
ninja arts I've been perfecting.
That's just impossible.
Say that again after you see me try!
No way!
Knew it.
I thought we'd all go in together.
Let's go, Nako.
I-I'm fine here.
Huh?
I'll watch all of you from here.
Nako...
Did you not want to come to the pool?
No, it's just...
Ah, I see. You don't like exercising too much.
That's not it.
Also, please don't force that image onto me.
There's no way you can run on the water surface.
I can! I just lack training!
Don't mention this to Aru and Sotoka.
Okay.
I'm scared of the water.
I can't swim.
What?
Let's go home, then!
That's an extreme response!
But...
You know what... Screw it!
I'll come into the pool with you.
Will you teach me how to swim, Bocchi?
Sure!
I bet I drowned in my previous life.
I'm practically certain of it.
You remember your previous life, Nako?
No, it was a joke.
There.
You're in the water.
Yeah...
Why are you so happy?
Because this is the first time
I'm able to help you with something!
Let's get started.
First you do this!
I mean... If I could, I wouldn't be struggling with this.
Let's start by floating.
If you relax, your body will float.
Really?
Hold onto that and let's try it.
Okay...
I can't! When I put my head
into the water, my body stiffens up—
Kill me now.
What do we have here?
Could it be that you can't swim?!
I can win against Nako today!
Prepare yourself!
I'll make you regret calling me a failure!
Oh, but if you call me Super
Vice-President Aru The Great,
I might consider forgiving you!
Super Vice-President Aru The Gr—
Let's continue, Bocchi.
Sure.
Continue? Continue what?
Huh? Oh, helping her to swim...
I mean, well...
That's not what I—
Um... uh...
You don't have to keep it secret anymore.
You're floating! It's working!
Now put your head underwater...
Amazing!
See? You can do it, Nako!
It's only for a little bit.
Master is teaching Nako how to swim!
Today Nako is one of her disciples as well!
That's true.
Let's do this together, my fellow disciple.
Tell us what to do next, then, Master.
Okay.
So once you're floating,
you do this flap-flap thingy with your legs.
And...
Like this!
Like this?
Perfect!
Flap-flap-flap-flap-flap...
She's an awful teacher...
I don't feel like bullying her anymore.
Meh, whatever...
Let me join you too!
No one is trying to exclude you.
You really failed to read the mood, didn't you?
Who are you calling a failure?! You can't even swim!
Stop that!
You splashed me too!
We're at a pool,
of course you're gonna get splashed!
Take this! And this! And some of that!
You're such good friends.
Huh?
What's wrong?
I'm having fun with my friends!
Isn't that obvious?
Karaoke
Not only did we go to the pool together,
but we also went to karaoke!
I've never done this before!
Summer break is such a wonderful time!
You don't need to tell the mic all that.
I was so excited for this that
I didn't sleep at all last night!
You went to the pool on no sleep?!
You're gonna make yourself sick again.
Let's go grab drinks first.
Just grab whatever you like.
Oh, a drink bar!
Wow, you pronounce that so well, Sotoka!
H-Huh? I do, Master?
You do!
Drink bar!
Drink bar...
Drink bar.
Get your drinks already.
Where are the prices, though?
Huh? It's free.
Free?
No way...
If we can drink all of these for free,
then this wonderful place full of treasured
memories of our time here is gonna go bankrupt...
All karaoke places offer drinks for free.
I'll just drink water.
I'm telling you, it's fine.
Let's get started!
The first to sing will be our
karaoke debut girl, Bocchi!
Try it!
Huh?
What should I pick?
Right. Karaoke means singing.
In front of people... In front of people...
What kinds of songs do you like, Bocchi?
In front of people...
Hey!
Bocchi!
Hey! Bocchi?
I can't!
Why...
I guess this is still a bit much for her...
How about someone else then?
I'm fine just listening.
I don't really know any Japanese songs...
Am I the only one singing?
I'm good at clapping my hands, though.
You don't have to bother.
I've learned several well-known
sporting cheer chants.
Why would you learn those?! Why not songs instead?!
Why are we even here?
Whatever. Let's hear Sotoka, then.
Sotoka.
Okay.
Here I go.
Go and get them!
What's this, a baseball game?!
You should sing to it, Aru.
Huh?
Sing us that song from the other day.
"Give up now, Aru!
You can't shine anymore, Aru!"
It's "Don't give up now, Aru!
You can still shine, Aru!"
Isn't that the song you sang the other day?
I want to hear it!
I guess I'll sing it.
Just this once, though!
Let's see...
Go and get them!
Too fast!
Yeah! Go and get them!
You just feel like saying that, don't you?!
Let's win this! Let's win this! Yeah!
I know a lot more, too!
But why?
What's wrong?
Kai...
Kai!
Bo...
No, we're through. We're through.
Kai...
Does that mean...
She's the...
Kai.
Do you still remember me?
I've made friends!
This is Nako, and this is Aru.
Hello.
I'm the best vice-president in the world.
And Sotoka is actually my disciple...
"Disciple"...?
I'm still far from being friends
with all my classmates,
but I've made friends! I have!
Why don't you say something to her?
It's fine.
Isn't that the girl you're always worrying about?
You don't run into each other all that often...
Kai! I swear on the good-luck fairy!
I'll become friends with all of my classmates!
And then... and then...
And then we'll be friends again!
Let's do our best.
It'll be fine. You can definitely...
Master...
Bocchi...
Maybe you should go talk to her.
I'm so glad...
Huh?
Bocchi made friends.
She doesn't hate me either.
Bocchi...
Kai... Kai... Kai...
Karaoke
Why'd you puke?!
Our first karaoke trip sure was an experience.
Bocchi fell asleep, too.
She did say she didn't sleep the night before.
Sotoka, want me to take over?
Nako, Aru...
What is it?
Is it okay for a disciple to be friends with her master?
Would you like to be?
Can't you quit being her disciple?
I have my reasons as to why
I want to learn the art of ninjutsu.
Family reasons.
Can't imagine what that's about.
Why don't you ask your master once she wakes up?
I will.
My dream kind of came true, but not really.
Good-luck fairy!
What's a good-luck fairy?
This thing.
She swore on this thing.
That's Master's master.
Life really isn't easy. But...
Kai, I...
I've made friends.
I have friends.
I'm new to the sound
of my new school shoes
I bow before my class
"Hope we can all be friends"
I'm new to this life
and here comes my new self
Just like seasons pass and change
There's this new me, so sweet and kind
I'll be like a comic book
You hide inside your textbook
And step by step I'll show my true self
Thought I was
dreaming when you called me your new friend and said such kind words
It all seemed just too good to be true but I tried to believe in you
And so
When I smile, it's so much wider now
It's closer to full bloom now
It's still such a strange sight to watch our shadows growing longer
But I realized that waiting for me were so many precious things
So strange, it's all making my heart beat just so fast
Can't handle these words so dear
This time I'll be the one to say
"Could you walk home with me?"
"Be friends with me?"
A
Friendly
Welcome
Home
Next time: "A Friendly Welcome Home".