It's gotten pretty cold...
That means it's time for... Shinobi Sprint!
Oh! It's Master!
Master!
Good morning!
G-Good... morning to you.
You seem different today, Master.
That's right.
I'm Super-Strong Bocchi.
You got even stronger, Master?!
Where'd that extra power come from?
It's because today's the closing
ceremony for the second term.
So closing ceremonies give you this power?
Master...?
I didn't make any new friends
during the second term...
So...
To prove to myself that I've gotten
stronger than I was last term,
I'm gonna become Super-Strong Bocchi right now!
Master...
I-In that case, I'll become Super-Strong Sotoka too!
So cold...
Dare I ask?
So nervous, so scared, never able to say these words out loud
But you see
I just want
Want you to
Be my friend even though I'm like this
Life
I snooze the alarm, still asleep
My bed, warm and cozy, keeps me there
In my dreams, I open up
But life can never be that easy
Making a U-turn, so quick and neat
I'm here and you're there and we never meet
From up close you seem distant
From far away you shine like the sun
As our everyday theme song starts playing
It's a sign that we need to set off
Make some plans
Think them up
Leave behind
Doubts and fear
The first step is all you need
Just make all your dreams come true now
Can I believe in these words?
Now smile and say hi and just look—you've gained one more new friend
No, no, wait
That's not right
This is life
It won't go as you imagined
Don't rush now, take your time, make sure to just go at your own pace
And one day
Make it real
And so please
Be my friend and help fulfill my dreams
Just think—how wonderful could that be?
Don't be shy now, talk with us and not just to yourself
First
Time
Hearing
It
Master.
What is it?
We might gain some confidence if we can show
Nako and Aru that we're stronger than usual today.
Great idea!
Nako.
Huh?
Have you noticed anything
different about me today?
Why are you suddenly asking such a girly question?
Well, there's something about me
that's made me way stronger today.
...I take back what I said.
I'll give you a hint: Look at my feet.
Your feet?
I see! You're stepping on your heels!
As of today, I'm Super-Strong Bocchi!
How does doing that make you strong?
Hey, uh...
Nako couldn't understand it, but maybe...
Aru.
Huh?
You know, I ate natto for breakfast today,
and I added mustard,
even though I don't usually have any!
You don't, huh?
Yeah!
But today I added a little bit.
I see. I usually put the whole sachet in my natto,
so next time I'll try eating it without any.
You put it all in?!
Aru's so grown up...
I'm still so weak...
Wait, what? Hey, Bocchi!
Aru.
Wh-What's up?
Wait! Sotoka...
You're coming with me!
Ah, so that's what this is about.
We need to figure out how to make
Master realize that she's super strong already.
She isn't super strong though.
I wouldn't be so sure.
Even if she hasn't made any new friends lately,
it's not like she's doing all that bad.
I wish we could make her understand that.
Any attempt at that today
is probably gonna end in failure.
Stop calling me a—
Wait, that wasn't about me.
If I wasn't her disciple anymore,
do you think she'd get it then?
Huh?
I'm not following.
Well, if I stop being her disciple
and become her friend instead,
then she'll have made a friend
in the second term,
and maybe then she'll realize
she actually is strong.
It could work.
Putting aside whether she realizes or not,
I'm sure she'd be overjoyed by that.
But wait...
What if Master only sees me as her disciple?!
Is all of this disciple business this serious?
But— ah! However— ah! Maybe— ah!
Dunno. It probably is to Sotoka though.
Still— ah! But— argh!
What do I do?!
When you really think about it,
the idea of being friends with
all of your classmates is crazy.
But she might be convinced that it's
the only thing that can prove she's changed.
Was Bocchi really that timid before?
Compared to when she first got here,
she's come a long way.
I ended up not being able to talk to Master,
and before I knew it, winter break came...
Followed by Christmas...
And then New Year's.
Turns out I was right about
it being less crowded on the 4th.
There are so many stalls here!
Where do you think they normally set up?
Oh, I know! Why don't we all buy different
food and share it with each other?
Sounds like fun.
I've never done that before!
I'll grab a candied apple, then.
And how are you gonna split that?!
I'll get a goldfish!
They're not for eating!
Wow!
It's appearing out of nowhere!
Is that ninjutsu?
He's a real ninja!
Look! We can have each of us take a bit—
I learned that when visiting a shrine,
you bow twice, clap twice, and bow once again.
Really?
Let's give it a try!
Sure!
Bow twice, clap twice, bow once.
You're not supposed to chant it,
you're supposed to do it...
Bow twice, clap twice, bow once.
Fancy seeing you here!
Wh-Why are you guys here?!
Making our New Year visit to the shrine, duh.
There's no way a member of the disciplinary
committee doesn't know how to pray.
O-Of course I do! You've got it wrong, I swear!
Hello, Kurai...
Happy New Year.
Thanks! Happy New Year to you as well.
Happy New Year!
I will become strong.
I will become perfect.
I will become friends with all my classmates,
and then go back to being friends with Kai...
I will learn more from Master...
I will learn more and master
the art of ninjutsu. Yeah.
Let's see...
I pray for good fortune.
Seriously?
You don't have any dreams or anything, Nako?
Not really.
You know, Nako told me about her dreams before,
but she won't say what they are.
Hey, Bocchi!
Oh really? What you hiding from us, huh?!
You've made me oh so curious!
Come on, tell us!
Fine, I'll tell you. My dream is...
Your dream is...?
To be the perfect version of myself, I guess.
You want to be perfect?
Seriously? That's so silly—
Wait! That's my dream!
Huh? Kurai?
Are you leaving already?
I didn't come here with you.
I made plans to see my relatives
after I was done here.
See you.
I'd like to be friends with Kurai one day.
Master, I...
Huh? What is it?
I... No, if I...
Oh, it's Onaka and Kurie.
Everyone's here to pray now
that the new year's started.
I haven't apologized yet for
what happened in that cooking class.
You spilled your group's
flour all over the place, right?
I'm going over to apologize.
Sure.
I feel like I need to become a little stronger!
Actually, Sotoka, did you end up
asking her about becoming friends?
What? You still haven't?
I-I'm very sorry!
I said it!
You're miles away from them!
Look, it's Hitori!
Happy New Year.
H-Happy... Year!
You came to pray as well?
Y-Yes...
Um...
U-Um... When we made pancakes... I...
Oh, I know!
We should go have pancakes sometime.
I'm up! Let's go right now!
R-Right now?
I didn't mean today!
We can decide on a date together.
Let's talk about it later.
Huh?
You don't wanna go?
W-Well...
It's just...
What is it?
I'd like to go,
but could we become friends, then?
Oh wow.
Master!
I'd really like to be friends with you both!
Sounds good to me!
Like, we're already pancake pals, aren't we?
Let's hang out soon, yeah?
Great job, Bocchi.
I'm so happy for you, Master.
Oh, I got a message from Kai!
"Bocchi hasn't been crying, has she?" she asks.
Wait, Kai?
How does she have your number?
We exchanged numbers
in secret at the karaoke place.
"Bocchi's doing great." Send.
Hitori?!
What's wrong?!
No way! She's fainted!
Come back to us, Hitori!
She's still prone to fainting though...
Wait for me, Kai.
Who's Kai?
Good grief...
Gotta snap this sleeping Bocchi and send it to Kai!
What is this?!
My... My...
My cotton candy has returned to me!
Oh wow!
She just made new friends! Two of them!
Kai...
Hold on. That's a summer kimono, right?
And isn't it one meant for guys?
Aren't you cold?
Nah, I'm good.
We need to go pray!
I pray that Bocchi doesn't cry too much.
Hitori
Bocchi's
The term's just started and
you're already back at the origami?
Can't take any breaks from my training.
Oh! Master!
Hitori.
Morning.
Morning, Hitori.
M-M-Morning, Peko, Ito.
Morning.
Morning, Nako.
Did you have your pancake date yet?
Huh?
Oh, no, not yet.
I don't get it! It just doesn't make any sense!
Hm?
Aru please you've gotta help me I'm begging you I don't know what to do anymore I feel like I'm going to go insane!
Whawhawhawhawhawhawhawhawhat? What? What? What? What? What?! What?!
What's your problem?!
Something terrible's happened.
I can tell.
Why am I here?
I know you're not busy, so help us out.
So, what's up then?
I noticed Master being all friendly
with Onaka and Kurie.
That makes sense.
They did become friends recently.
But it feels like she's putting
even more distance between us now!
Well, you're her disciple, and she's your master.
But she's known me for
so much longer than those two...
Maybe it's just a matter of habit for her now.
She wants to respect your relationship.
Have you told her you want to be friends yet?
Is being her disciple that important to you?
It's because of what she told me
when we first talked.
Sotoka?
Yes?
I'll do my best.
So after I've taught you everything I can,
then...
Then?
Could you be my friend then?
I feel like I shouldn't ask to be friends
before she's taught me everything.
That's quite the predicament.
But what exactly is "everything"?
I... don't really know, to be honest.
Give us something to work with...
Then there's nothing you can do.
Hold on a sec.
All we need to do is get her
to act friendlier towards you, right?
That shouldn't be too hard, should it?
Not at all.
She just made new friends,
so there's a chance she'll
be friendlier towards you too.
You think so?
Have you talked to her since the shrine visit?
I haven't...
Then how about you go talk to her?
Trust our Bocchi!
That was so cringe...
Shut your mouth!
You're right.
It'd be weird for her to treat me differently.
She's probably already noticed that herself.
Master!
Huh?
Oh, it's you!
I'm going home...
English?!
Goodbye, everyone.
Hey, cheer up! I'll do something about this!
Really now?
You're helping, you know!
Bocchi.
Do you have a moment?
Hi, Aru!
Um... How are you?
Great. What about you?
Same.
Oh, actually!
How's Mieru?
Mieru?
Ah, you mean my sister!
Why is she bringing her up now?
Oh, um... She's not around anymore.
Huh?!
She had to go someplace far away.
We'll never see her again.
But don't worry, it's for the best.
Aru...
Shut the hell up, you idiot!
You too, Bocchi?!
Wait, why are you crying?!
I'm the one in pain here!
You remember what this was about, right?
I haven't forgotten, don't worry.
You know, I wanted to talk to you about Sotoka.
About Sotoka?
Yeah.
She told us that she really wants
you to treat her like a friend.
Do you not like the idea?
It's not that.
It's just... Sotoka is my disciple, not my friend.
Realistically, she's pretty much your friend, though.
You get too hung up on the formalities.
She wants the two of you to be real friends.
So why not just do it, eh?
You know, I was really happy
when you and Nako called me Bocchi.
So I was hoping that Sotoka would
one day start calling me Bocchi as well.
This problem's easily solved, then.
I'll go get Sotoka!
Aru, wait!
What's up?
Thank you.
Good grief...
Bocchi and Sotoka can be real pains someti—
Ow!
The realest pain of all has gotta be you, Aru.
Well, whatever.
We should get moving too.
Huh?
We wouldn't want anyone to get in the way.
Sorry for the wait.
Did you bring her here?
Master...
What's that?
Oh yeah, she's forgotten how to
speak Japanese, but ignore that.
It's rather hard to ignore.
N-New shuriken.
Great!
If you'd like, we could make
these new shurikens toge—
Let's make these together, Sotoka!
Sure!
B-Bocchi!
You can drop the English accent.
And with that...
It's comple—
It's done!
It's doneth.
That's aweso—
That's... awesome.
I didn't know such shurikens exis—
Didn't know you could make these.
I've prepared more for you.
I have more in stock. In store. Storage?
We shall collect all types of shuriken together!
Let's collect them. Stock them?
Let's do that! Let's... do that?
Let's do collecting!
How can you be so bad at this?!
So how have we ended up back here?
Sotoka's still bothered by something,
so we should get to the bottom of it.
But Bocchi's been friendlier to you, hasn't she?
I've stopped calling her "Master"...
You have?
And what's wrong with that?
Keep calling her by her name.
But...
She said you two could be friends
once she'd taught you everything, right?
She did...
Then maybe she's already done that.
Deep down you know that,
and that's why you want to be friends now.
Nako...
Thanks.
Nako, Aru...
I'll be right back.
I'm going to graduate!
How come you have all the good ideas?!
Where is everyone?
Maybe they went home without me and—
Master! I'm Super-Strong Sotoka!
Um... Hi, Sotoka...
As of now, I am no longer your disciple.
What?!
Is it because I'm too weak?
No! The opposite!
It's because you're strong!
Huh?
You made Nako smile when she failed her test,
and when Aru wanted to go home
to change her uniform,
you gave her the courage
to come to school as she was.
Seeing all the things you did for them...
It made me care more about friendships than ninjas!
You've taught me everything you could.
That's why I came here to graduate
and become your friend.
Sotoka, you...
Open the shuriken, please.
I may love ninjas,
but I love you more.
"I may love ninjas,
I may love ninjas,
but I love you more.
but I love you more."
I may love ninjas,
but I love you more.
This is...
Master.
Yes?
Please be my friend.
You're...
You're the first person to ask me that!
And with that, Master became my friend.
S-So... toka!
B-Bocch... Master!
Y-You can call me Bocchi now!
You can relax around me, M-Master.
Why do the two of you seem
even more stressed out now?
Wait, is that...
Yep! I finally figured out how to make it.
Let's give it a try outside.
Yes, Master!
Wait for me, Master!
Master!
Things were meant to change,
but the two of them seem the same.
I think that's fine.
No matter how you look at it, they're good friends.
I'm new to the sound
of my new school shoes
I bow before my class
"Hope we can all be friends"
I'm new to this life
and here comes my new self
Just like seasons pass and change
There's this new me, so sweet and kind
Do you know that one show
where they chased their dreams?
Now step by step I chase mine as well
Thought I was
dreaming when you called me your new friend and said such kind words
It all seemed just too good to be true but I tried to believe in you
And so
When I smile, it's so much wider now
It's closer to full bloom now
It's still such a strange sight to watch our shadows growing longer
But I realized that waiting for me were so many precious things
So strange, it's all making my heart beat just so fast
Can't handle these words so dear
This time I'll be the one to say
"Could you walk home with me?"
"Be friends with me?"
From
To
Clicking
Tapping
Next time: "From Clicking To Tapping".