Let me explain the situation.
Urachi is trying to erase all abilities from Sakurada,
while I'm planning to protect them.
In other words,
our opinions are polar opposites.
That's why I summoned Urachi
to talk things through.
But I had no intention of listening to Asai.
I just played along,
planning to capture him.
And that's how I decided to kidnap Urachi.
Wait a second.
I'm so lost.
How does talking lead into kidnapping?
I wouldn't be able to negotiate with him
if we stuck to proper methods.
That's why I had to make sure
Urachi wouldn't disappear on me
and bind him to a chair, forcefully if necessary.
Kei, I'm on Director's side.
That's another reason I wanted you to drive.
What?
You were on Urachi's side before the reset as well.
You believed abilities shouldn't exist.
So if I have to convince you both anyway,
it's more efficient to convince you together.
Your logic is crazy.
If Director tells me to stop the car, I will.
I have no choice then.
Let's take a classic hostage.
Kei, you're going too far.
You're right, I really don't want to do this.
It's unfortunately a necessity, though.
There's no way it's necessary.
Director.
What is it?
It's just as you're saying.
It seems I've become Asai Kei's accomplice.
You're siding with him?
For now. Seems like I have no other choice.
So basically, you're prioritizing your job
as a teacher over your job with the Bureau?
This has nothing to do with me being a teacher.
I don't get it.
Even if he can't stab you,
he sure can stab himself.
If I stopped the car,
he'd become a hostage himself.
Of course I'd rather avoid such measures.
He really hates violence, you see.
I'm sure of it.
Doing things you hate is difficult.
And adults are responsible
for looking after children.
If either of us has to make a difficult choice,
the adult should go first.
Let's begin, then.
I
used
to
say
there
was
a
novel
I
loved
That
I
kept
on
a
shelf
and
never
opened
up
"See,
this
is
how
you
stay
true
to
yourself"
Showing
off,
proud
of
just
being
me
People
around
me
Try
to
sound
mature
and
take
some
wise
words
They
use
them
as
if
those
words
belonged
to
them
Showing
off
the
fake
wisdom
they
had
stolen
So
I
laughed
at
them
But
actually
my
sense
of
self
that
I
kept
on
a
shelf
Was
no
different
from
what
I'd
been
laughing
at
And
the
truth
is
that
I
already
knew
But
no
more
lies,
it's
time
For
my
heart's
reset
I'll
myself
So
I
told
myself
somewhere
deep
down
in
my
heart
Even
if
they
might
talk
behind
my
back
Why
should
I
care
when
I
don't
turn
around?
You
can
choose
To
follow
the
path
someone's
already
walked
But
wouldn't
you
rather
leave
footprints
yourself?
You
believed
your
own
dreams
and
chose
a
path
So
it's
the
right
one,
just
trust
in
your
heart
It'll
all
be
fine
The door has disappeared.
We've been trapped here.
I've made a hole in the gas tank of the Bureau's car.
Can I ask you to take care of that next?
Unlock those two bikes.
Are we stealing them?
We should be getting out of here soon.
Aren't you trying to save the world?
Those bikes are in a no-bike-parking zone,
so no one can complain if we take them.
I'm not trying to be good,
I'm trying to save the world.
I don't see the difference.
If someone hits you,
being good means not resisting,
while punching them back is
a step towards saving the world.
Isn't that a pretty subjective definition of "saving"?
Those who wish to save the world know
what's right for the world to be saved.
The Bureau members used some kind of ability.
Let's hurry.
No choice now.
There they are!
Around twenty seconds until my ability activates...
Will I not make it?
Look into their eyes.
Five...
Four... Three...
Two... One...
Zero!
Stop that!
Be quiet!
What?
Nice, Sakagami, Oka Eri.
I'd rather use my ability myself, though.
Too bad no one ever looks me in the eyes.
Well, can't blame them.
There we go.
Everyone ready?
Let's go!
You're sounding awfully cute.
Warn us next time you want
to do something this crazy!
What are you here for?
To meet someone.
Not you, though.
You're not running away?
It's not my job to run away.
Job?
You mean what Asai Kei instructed you to do?
Yes, that's right.
You put too much faith in him.
He got rid of you.
I don't understand.
If you're the only one he left behind here,
isn't that the logical explanation?
I'm sure he knew you'd
be captured by the Bureau here.
There's nothing wrong with me getting captured.
Also, I won't get captured.
Even alone, I'm capable of capturing you.
But it's not just the two of us here.
You probably can't take on two ability users.
That's true.
Seems like you're the one who
has to deal with two, though?
I see not everything always
goes as Asai Kei planned.
Do you really think you can convince me?
Yes, of course.
If I explain what you gain from my plan,
you'll agree with me for sure.
Well, whatever.
I'm a victim of a kidnapping.
Can't wait to hear what you have to say.
Have you ever heard of the plank of Carneades?
Yeah.
It's a skeptical thought experiment
about making life-or-death choices.
When a ship is wrecked,
everyone aboard gets thrown into the sea.
One man somehow succeeds in grabbing
onto a plank floating on the surface.
But the plank can support only one person.
And then another reaches for the plank.
If he grabs onto it as well, both with drown.
That's why he pushes the other man off.
And so one man drowns, while the other is saved.
Do you think that's the right decision?
In my opinion, yes.
One of them surviving is better than both drowning.
I also believe that humans should always
give their very best to survive.
I see.
What about you?
Please don't tell me you'd find
a way for both of them to survive.
That's exactly what I think.
Both of them surviving is the best possible outcome.
Your answer shows only that you're
looking away from the nature of the problem.
It's the foolish answer of someone
who doesn't understand the premise.
The premise?
Yes.
You can't do the impossible.
In the thought experiment of
Carneades' plank, one of them has to die.
That's the premise of the problem, an absolute rule.
You should be able to understand that much.
I know one similar story.
A certain boy had a special ability.
Anything he touched with his right hand
would stop changing, as if frozen in time.
One day, a man appeared before him.
A man who protects the rules of the world.
However, if the man died,
the rules of the world would change,
and humanity would fall into chaos.
To prevent that,
the man had no choice but to have
his time stopped to never die.
And so the boy stopped his time,
to protect the rules of the world.
He chose to sacrifice one man
for humanity to live in happiness.
And here's the problem.
Did he make the right choice?
So what is it?
He stopped the time of one man
for the good of the world.
Do you think he made the right choice?
That's a cruel joke.
What Kagaya did was right,
and he didn't have a choice to begin with.
The Bureau enforced it.
Then let's imagine Kagaya's guilt prevented
him from stopping your father's time
and that he opposed the Bureau's decision.
Would you think of that as evil?
If killing a person for the absolute happiness
of everyone else is too difficult,
if making the decision to sacrifice
someone is too much,
would you call that evil?
Yes, it is evil.
Because it's not the right decision.
If you're giving up to your weakness or kindness,
that's foolish and harmful to society.
Your beliefs are strong.
Strong and righteous.
But, Urachi,
can you ask of all humanity to be as strong as you?
You're very strong.
Now you need to learn how it is to be weak.
Honestly, I don't think there are
wrong answers to a problem like that.
You should choose whatever
you yourself find acceptable.
My answer is to save both.
You said it's the foolish answer of someone who
doesn't understand the premise of the problem.
I'm sure you're right.
But if you thought about it more realistically,
you'd focus more on something completely different.
What you really should consider
is how to prevent such an accident
from happening ever again.
And in case it does happen again,
you should be prepared so that
you can save both of them.
Asai,
what are you even talking about?
About the abilities in Sakurada, of course.
I'm saying we should think how to
save everyone in the upcoming future.
Who is everyone?
Kagaya, your parents,
and you as well.
I'm happy even now.
If abilities disappear, all the more.
What about the other three?
What can be done to make Kagaya
stop feeling guilty towards you?
Release my parents from the ability binding them.
Exactly.
That's obviously impossible!
My father's ability must be
protected no matter what.
Without it, the world would be thrown into chaos.
That's true.
But what matters is his ability, not him.
We just need to take the ability from your father.
Urachi,
you should just have Sakagami
copy the ability of your father.
Once it's transferred onto another person,
Kagaya would then lock that person,
and your father would be free.
That changes nothing.
It just means someone else would have
to be sacrificed instead of my father.
What if it's not human?
For example,
what if we try to copy the ability onto a cat?
A cat?
We'd sacrifice a cat instead of a human.
Both Kagaya and your father would be saved.
That's impossible.
There have been no cases of anything
other than human using an ability so far.
Also, Sakagami Yousuke's ability...
Yousuke
Like I thought, he can copy only to humans.
Why do you think it's not possible
to copy to anything other than humans?
Because they have will.
Sakurada's abilities don't activate
unless you wish for them to.
Cats don't possess the will to use an ability.
I have a friend who has an ability
to share her senses with a cat.
With it, we can give a cat the
same will a human possesses.
So what?
Even if you assume nothing goes wrong,
and both my parents and Kagaya
get a happy ending,
what will that prove?
You can't say anything about abilities
just because they saved someone once!
Cherry-picking examples
where everything went right
is no reason to approve of abilities!
Then...
How many people would have to be saved
for abilities to be allowed to exist?
Saving how many people would prove their worth?
It's not the problem of a simple number.
People can't rely on such
an unreliable thing as abilities!
You have to accept all the despair and trouble
and live without turning
your eyes away from reality!
You're the one turning your eyes away from reality.
Abilities are part of our reality,
yet you force them out of your life,
pretending they aren't there.
You're the one trying to run away
and shut yourself in your own world!
Asai,
who knows, maybe what
you're saying really is right.
But no matter how right you are,
my heart won't budge.
I still consider abilities to be evil.
It's an undeniable fact I can't do anything about.
It's just as I thought...
I cannot convince you.
Yes, I knew that.
I'm sorry, Urachi.
I actually wasn't trying to convince you.
Thank you, Tomoki.
Hm?
Are you done?
Almost.
Listen, Kagaya.
There's people who can be saved
with abilities, and can't without.
Kei figured you're more important
than Urachi Masamune.
You have to make a choice.
If you can save the person you want to save,
it is the right choice to do that.
If you can solve an old and still relevant problem,
Kagaya, what will your decision be?
Kei always says one thing.
Abilities aren't some special powers.
They're part of us humans,
just like our limbs or our words.
No matter how we use them,
the nature of the world doesn't change.
We can do what is possible,
and we can't do what is impossible.
The same way a mother pats her child's head,
we use our abilities.
Kei said it's nothing more than that.
Asai Kei simply wishes for the world
around him to become a better place.
Kei is never wrong.
Not because he's smart,
not because he's exceptional,
but because his absolute memory
lets him never lose sight of what he considers right.
That's why he can't be wrong.
Please decide if the outcome he suggests
is one you consider happy or not.
It's calling Asai Kei.
Urachi Masamune is with him.
It's what we decided together.
You're bringing us pure salvation.
We knew from the start you'd be born
and that's what let us live happily.
So if you ever feel guilty about this,
you really shouldn't.
Take pride in what you're doing.
Because you're putting your ability to the right use.
Asai Kei,
I will support you in this matter.
Thank you very much.
Put Director to the phone.
It's me.
I see.
I understand.
Asai, did everything go as you planned?
Yeah.
Where did I go wrong?
Was it ignoring Kagaya's feelings?
Your insensitivity towards his feelings
seemed to me like it extended to your own.
My feelings?
Yes.
You trusted Kagaya.
I'm sure it was a very strong, subconscious trust.
That's why it never occurred
to Kagaya to side with us instead.
When did you notice that?
During a time you don't know about.
While the abilities were gone from this town?
Yes.
We erased that with a reset.
During that time, I talked with you.
We had a nice little two hour long chat.
Unaware of abilities, you were an ordinary
man working for the government.
During those two hours,
I got to understand you better
than you can imagine.
You're completely different than me.
I would never think of such an inefficient method.
Urachi.
I want to supervise abilities.
I want to join the Bureau, gain a lot of authority,
and rebuild the ability supervising system
itself according to my ideals.
So, Urachi, please lend me a hand.
I need you for that.
What are your ideals?
I want to fight all kinds of misfortune.
If possible, get rid of all of it.
Do you really think...
Do you really believe that such an absurd,
childish dream would come true?
Of course it wouldn't.
Still, I want to right all wrongs one by one.
Even if my ideals are eternally distant,
I want to keep moving towards them.
Urachi.
I think we're very alike after all.
What differs about us is only
the beginning and the end.
I'm sure we can still understand
each other a little bit better.
Even if not fully, I'm sure we can
understand each other enough.
That's why, Urachi,
let's be on the same side, even if only formally.
You know, Asai, I hate shaking hands.
There's a lot of other things I hate.
Meetings with too many participants,
childish hopes and dreams beyond reason,
other people's hands...
I hate all of that.
And to be honest,
I also hate putting things in my pockets.
I wonder if Kei is free tomorrow.
Where should I invite him?
We get a day off because of the school festival,
so I guess somewhere where we can relax.
What is this...
Stop! Stop, please!
Goodbye.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong from the start.
I'm sorry, Kei.
I don't think it was all really for you.
I'm sorry.
Next Episode
I want you to play a game with me.
I'm sure I can't save you.
It's stupid, isn't it?!
That's so absurd.
Weren't you waiting for me to come meet him?
Give up.
It truly is my true happiness.
Hey, give me Asai Kei.
Thank you.
On such a cold dark sky of grey
Rises the sun, which breathes life into it
A scenery so plain and so mundane
And yet it seems to break my heart, it's so dear to me
As the time never stops passing by
You get lost while searching for
Pure like the rays of a morning star
What we all yearn for the most
In what colors bliss is dyed
Struggling against all your past mistakes
At last from the answer you found kindness fills your heart
More beautiful than anything you know
And you find it behind a dark veil of sadness
If I closed my eyes and stopped my thoughts
If it were so simple to just
Lock your own heart
How lovely life would be
But I believe you have the key
To let my soul be free