September 1st
Friday
First Day of the Second Semester
This is Murase Youka.
She will be your classmate starting today.
She's one year older than you guys.
Mentioning my age wasn't necessary.
Is that so?
Anyway, be nice to her.
Sera, you'll be in charge of her.
Yes, sir.
The
flow
of
time
makes
a
continuous
sound
(so
close
your
eyes
and
feel
it)
It's
a
melody
that
invites
the
coming
future
(which
begins
today)
What
kind
of
world
is
waiting
for
me?
(Who
is
calling
me?)
I
tried
asking
myself
for
an
answer
(in
my
heart)
Here,
in
the
middle
of
ideals
and
reality
(I'm
searching
for
them)
The
hands
of
the
clock
are
being
constantly
moved
(as
I
turn
them
back)
I'll
do
anything
to
erase
all
sadness
(over
and
over
again)
Even
if
it
means
going
back
down
the
passage
of
dark
stairs
(to
recreate
the
past)
There's
something
I
want
to
protect
no
matter
what
(I'll
protect
you)
I'll
say
that
out
loud
(and
try
resetting
again)
Believing
that
fate
will
bring
us
together
again
Marble World and Candy Resist
April 10th
Monday
Entrance Ceremony
Close your eyes.
Think of what you deem the purest.
That is your purity.
There are plenty of things in
this world that are as pure as that.
Where are they?
They're everywhere!
As long as you have purity within your heart,
you'll be able to find things
that are just as pure anywhere.
But it probably isn't smart to live
searching only for pure things.
Huh?
A service club at Ashiharabashi High School?
Yeah. I'll be the club advisor
and you guys will be the members.
So we're being monitored?
Don't you two want to help others
with your combined abilities?
What are you going to do, Haruki?
I'll follow your lead, Kei.
Yes?
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Asai Kei
Reason for joining club
Name
Club Member Application
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Reason for joining club
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Reason for joining club
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Reason for joining club
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Reason for joining club
Here is my membership application.
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Reason for joining club
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Reason for joining club
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Reason for joining club
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Reason for joining club
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Reason for joining club
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Reason for joining club
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Haruki Misora
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
would like to join
the Service Club.
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Reason for joining club
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
the Service Club.
1-E
Haruki Misora
Club Member Application
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Reason for joining club
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Class
Thanks.
Still, he sure was in a rush.
I mean, making us bring the applications
immediately after the entrance ceremony.
You're going to continue with the
Service Club even in high school?
Yeah. I have my reasoning for doing so.
But if I were to give a reason,
it's because it'd be troublesome not to be in it.
Still, I'm pretty sure there's no reason for you
to be in the Service Club without my ability.
The same goes for you, too.
Our abilities don't have any value on their own.
Besides, if anything, I want to be in the Service Club.
Why is that?
When you're in the Service Club, you can gain
access to info regarding special abilities.
I want to learn more about them.
But also because I want to get
to know our advisor better.
You mean, Mr. Tsushima?
Yeah. I kinda like the guy.
Don't you wanna join the Service Club?
I do, as long as I'm there with you.
Sorry. I made you wait, didn't I?
Not at all.
Congrats on your enrollment.
Thank you. It's good to see you again.
Everything that comes out
of your mouth sounds sarcastic.
That hurts. I was being honest.
Is your name officially written this way?
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Asai Kei
Reason for joining club
Yes, I always write it like that.
Why?
My name can be difficult to spell for some people.
It gets messed up pretty often if I don't do it.
Whatever.
Anyway, I've accepted these.
Welcome to the Ashiharabashi
High School Service Club.
The way you're smiling is kinda sinister, you know.
I know.
When I think about it, there's so many
bad things I could do with your abilities.
So, Mr. Tsushima...
Why'd you want us to submit our membership
applications right after the entrance ceremony?
I just wanted to make you guys
club members right away.
In order to assign us club duties?
Yeah.
You guys are best suited for it.
This happened about two hours ago.
At around 11:30 a.m, we found a female student
collapsed in front of the school gates.
That's around the time
the entrance ceremony ended.
Right.
A parent found her and immediately
took her to the infirmary.
She didn't take part in the entrance ceremony.
This was found on the ground right next to her.
Take a look at it.
That's the student who collapsed
in front of the school gates.
Hello. It's nice to meet you.
I'm sorry, we're the only ones eating.
Oh, that's okay! Don't worry about me!
I've got this instead.
A strawberry-flavored Candy Candy.
Do you like Candy Candy?
Yeah. I've liked sweets for a long time.
Anyway, is it okay for high schoolers
to stop at a café on their way home?
It's fine since we're doing this for the Service Club.
Huh? Really?
Yes.
Haruki and I have been in the
Service Club since middle school.
If it's for the Service Club,
most things count as part of our club activities.
And if we get a receipt,
the cost is deducted from our club's budget.
I see.
Why is she inside a marble?
She possesses that sort of ability.
She has the ability to enter the reflected
scenery in things like mirrors or glass shards.
Sera Sawako
I guess it's more like she's in the reflection
of the marble rather than inside the marble.
Her body is asleep on a bed
in the infirmary right now.
Sera has used her ability twice in the past.
She's used it at a rate of
about once every two years.
Is that correct?
Yeah, probably.
"Probably"?
I guess I never really felt it.
I see.
Sera Sawako uses her ability without realizing it.
It isn't done consciously.
Does that mean there's
a switch deep within her mind?
Would it be best to reset?
Well, that's what we were ordered to do.
I think there's something
else we can do before that.
What is that something?
I guess it'd be speaking with Sera first.
With me?
Yes.
There's something I'd like you to tell me about.
Why did you use your ability?
"Why"?
Abilities in Sakurada don't work
unless the user wishes for them to.
You wished to use your ability at some point in time.
Before we reset, we'll need to make
certain what your reason was.
Otherwise, you'll end up in that marble again.
Um...
Sorry, I have no idea.
Before I realized, I was stuck in here.
It's okay to tell me one thing at a time.
Can you recall what you did step by step?
Um, I think I woke up at around 5:30.
You wake up quite early.
I've always been like that.
Whether it's for field trips or sports events,
I'm the kind of person that wakes up early.
And today it was because
of the entrance ceremony?
Yeah, probably...
When I woke up, I changed into my
uniform like usual, ate breakfast...
Should I tell you what I ate for breakfast, too?
Yes, please. Just to be safe.
So, in other words, you were late
because you were looking into the marble?
I guess it all started when I missed my bus.
Well, I would've made it in time
even with the next bus.
But I thought it'd be fine.
You mean, it'd be fine to be late
for the entrance ceremony?
I thought skipping out on just
the entrance ceremony would be fine.
You end up hearing the same old thing
at every ceremony you go to, right?
It's smarter to wander wherever
you feel, like the shopping district.
But you still made it to the school gates.
Yeah. I was pretty half-hearted about it.
When I was in middle school, I was kind of a
dedicated student, so I'm not used to playing hooky.
For some reason, I decided to look at the marble
in front of the school gates, and ended up like this.
Do you like marbles?
Huh? Yeah, I sort of do.
What do you like about it?
Maybe how carefree they are.
"Carefree"?
Yeah. The view is squished
and warped, and also inverted.
It's like they're making fun of the world.
I don't think they're making fun of it...
Anyway, I thought that kind
of thing about them was nice.
Yes? This is Asai.
Why haven't you reset yet?
Haruki saved around noon two days ago.
We can still reset up until noon tomorrow.
Your duty is just to reset and report
what happened in the past.
Yes, I'm aware of that.
Why aren't you resetting immediately, then?
Well, I want to thoroughly
understand Sera beforehand.
I want to understand her problems
to learn why she used her ability.
What are you going to do with that information?
I'm going to resolve her problems with
a method that's appropriate for her.
I'll do everything according to your intentions.
My intentions?
If you wanted us to reset immediately,
then there was no need to have us meet Sera
or give us detailed information regarding her ability.
You're going to reset once you're satisfied, huh?
Yes, that's right.
Then it's fine.
Hold on. I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Please give me Sera's middle school
classmate's contact information.
Well...
I guess they've passed so far.
Sorry if I'm a bother.
I don't feel like you're being a nuisance.
You and Asai are sort of strange.
In what way are we strange?
I feel like you two aren't normal.
Your relationship is weird.
What do you mean by "relationship"?
We're classmates, right?
It doesn't seem right to speak politely.
Is it better to speak casually?
Well, I guess it'd feel more comfortable.
Fine, let's do it.
Huh?
I won't get hung up on how I talk.
Does that sound okay?
It's weird. Why are you talking like that?
I tried to imitate Kei.
He speaks like this.
It's fine to speak politely!
That seems unnatural... and a little scary.
Is that so?
You really aren't normal.
You're weird, but in a good way.
It makes you seem sort of special.
"Weird" can be used to describe
something uncommon.
I think uncommon things are special.
That's not what I meant!
I probably used to be weird myself,
but I wasn't special at all.
I don't understand.
You know, when I was in middle school,
I was always called by a weird nickname.
But that nickname wasn't special in the slightest.
I wanted to ditch that name as quickly as possible.
Why did you want to ditch it?
Because it's something I didn't need.
April 11th
Tuesday
Ashiharabashi High School
I'm pretty sure of it.
Morning, Kei.
Morning.
Did you get to know Sera better?
Probably. In our own way.
Did you change the way you speak?
Yeah.
Yesterday, Sera said it was weird for me
to speak politely since we're classmates.
Oh, I see.
Asai, you're okay with this?
I think it suits her well.
Thanks. I tried to copy the way you speak.
But Sera said it was unnatural and scary.
I don't think it's scary.
It's just who I am.
If you compare this to the way I normally speak,
which do you think is better for me?
There are upsides to both, but I guess the
way you normally speak is more natural.
I see. I'll speak as I always do, then.
Shouldn't you guys hurry?
Our homeroom class is about to start.
Not at all. It's totally fine.
How so?
We decided to skip school today.
Wha—
Akamatsu Park
Is this okay?
What do you mean?
Being absent from school.
The day after the entrance
ceremony isn't a big deal.
You're okay with this, Misora?
Yes.
Why?!
Because Kei decided it.
Can you really call that a reason?
Of course.
Sorry.
I'll try to get out of here on my own,
so you and Asai should go to school.
Why do you care so much about school?
I mean, you skipped the entrance ceremony.
That's different!
I needed to do that.
What do you mean?
They say that there is something pure within
the heart of a child who loves pure things.
Something pure?
Yeah.
That's what my homeroom teacher said
in my third year of elementary school.
Sera?
Huh?
You're still here?
I'll be going home in a bit.
Thank you for doing that.
It's nothing.
I just like pure water better.
You have something very pure within your heart.
Something pure?
Yes.
There is something pure within the heart
of a child who loves pure things.
Close your eyes.
Think of what you deem the purest.
That is your purity.
A very pure object that exists
only within your heart.
I'm sure what you thought
of doesn't exist in this world.
Still, there are plenty of things in
this world that are as pure as that.
Where are they?
They're everywhere!
Tucked away in the blue skies,
in the sound of the wind,
and even in the words you say.
As long as you have purity within your heart,
you'll be able to find things
that are just as pure anywhere.
I don't have anything like that.
You do. I'm sure you do.
Try comparing something you've seen or
thought of with the pure thing within your heart.
Once you do that, you'll be able
to find nothing but pure things.
Really?
Yes. Now, open your eyes.
This is thanks for changing the vase water for me.
You mustn't lose the purity within your heart.
As long as it's not lost, you'll be able
to find nothing but pure things.
I believed that all this time.
She was a good teacher, huh?
I think it's okay for an elementary schooler to
believe what an elementary school teacher says.
But even when I became a middle schooler,
I still believed what she said.
Is there something wrong with that?
Of course there is.
I was never absent or late
when I was in middle school.
That's amazing.
It's not!
Don't give me a standard response.
All you get for perfect attendance is a certificate!
That thing is just card stock.
I think people who can skip school
whenever they see fit are probably smarter.
Is that why you didn't show up
to the entrance ceremony?
It was just coincidence that I missed the bus.
But I wondered what would
happen if I didn't go to school.
That's why I tried occupying myself by going
down to the park and the shopping district.
Did you have fun?
No.
I thought that I was doing
something that isn't pure.
I had this sense of guilt.
But a carefree life is something
I simply wanted to obtain.
Really?
Yeah. That's probably why I went into the marble.
The view is squished and warped, and also inverted.
I went into a marble because
it was making fun of the world.
I don't think that's the case.
Why do you think so?
I spoke to one of your classmates
from middle school yesterday.
Huh?
And I heard all about you.
Everyone called you by the same name.
"Student Monitor"...
That's what everyone called me.
I always believed that abiding by
the rules was the pure thing to do.
I never broke the rules,
and when someone did, I warned them.
After about a month,
the "Student Monitor" nickname spread.
People stopped talking to me during breaks
and asking me to hang out with them after school.
I was just simply choosing pure things!
But no one else seemed to care about them.
Everyone said that your greatest
trait is your responsibility.
Yeah, so I'm going to get used to being carefree.
But I don't think that's what you want.
Why?
I heard all sorts of things.
Three strawberry-flavored ones
and two ramune-flavored ones...
making a total of five Candy Candy.
I accidentally brought them to school,
so I left them with my homeroom teacher.
In your middle school, you weren't allowed
to eat candy inside the building.
Your plan was to actually eat it at school, wasn't it?
Yeah.
But you weren't able to eat them in the end.
Despite your many failed attempts to break
the rules, you never used your ability.
But this time was different.
It's the opposite of everything
you've done in the past.
You were late for the entrance ceremony.
You actually broke the rules,
and that's why your ability activated.
In the place where you were found collapsed,
you wanted to try something—
to see how the world looks in a marble.
The hands indicating it was noon were turned
upside-down, and it looked like it was morning.
You wished to be in that world, right?
You wanted to escape to a world
where the entrance ceremony hadn't
started yet and you weren't late.
Everything is upside-down in here.
The school, the clock... Even I am upside-down.
But if both the clock and I are upside-down,
it doesn't look upside-down to me anymore!
Which means that being inside
the marble doesn't change anything.
Yeah.
I'm sure I wished for it, but I didn't
like it and couldn't take it anymore.
I'm not smart.
If it's so painful it makes you want to escape
into a marble, you don't need to give up your purity.
It's okay to be more selfish and
protect it, even if it isn't smart.
That's true,
but it's too late!
No, we can still make it in time.
Haruki, time to reset.
Reset.
Huh?
10 | Sakurada Station
Close your eyes.
Think of what you deem the purest.
That is your purity.
There are plenty of things in
this world that are as pure as that.
But it probably isn't smart to live
searching only for pure things.
Ashiharabashi High School
Excuse me.
What's wrong?
Huh?
You've been staring at that for a while.
Um, I was thinking that I want to eat it.
You should eat it right away, then.
It's against school rules!
Do school rules need to be obeyed?
I don't think they really matter.
Then, it'd be best for you to eat it now.
I will.
Why are you crying?
I don't know!
I see.
By the way, it isn't against the rules to eat candy.
We're always simply standing in a rain of eternal sadness
Huh?
Eating and drinking isn't allowed
during class, but outside of that, it's fine.
That is why I need that warmth of yours
Also, I think school rules should be obeyed, after all.
Life is but a dream we never wake up from
We repeat it over and over, praying for salvation
The purity is still inside of me.
I kept waiting endlessly for your signal
To make sure you wouldn't disappear all by yourself
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Haruki Misora
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Asai Kei
Reason for joining club
That concludes my report.
So, do you think you've resolved Sera Sawako's problems?
Ah, it doesn't matter where I am or what I'm doing
I'm not sure.
There's a possibility that it will happen again.
My heart can't go against your will
Well, I got the gist of it.
You can go home now.
So I'd follow you even to the ends of the world
Yes, sir. We'll take our leave.
I fell in love with you at the dawn of our new world
Thank you for listening to my selfish request.
"Selfish request"?
Yes. We didn't reset until the very last minute.
But we kept pushing the hand of the clock backwards
Well, I look forward to working with you.
And lost not only time, but our smiles as well
I just don't get that guy.
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
I
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Name
Asai Kei
Club Member Application
4 / 10 / 2017
would like to join
the Service Club.
Class
#
1-E
Reason for joining club
Haruki Misora
Relying on them is for the best, huh?
You're the one who brought it back
And taught me that even lies can be meaningful
Here's another problem child.
A student who's bound by her own ability.
The student who plays hooky, Murase Youka.
Next Episode
You lost your ability?
My special ability is to recreate the past.
I've gotten weak.
Call me "Witch," if you must.
...about the Swampman.
Hey there!
I made sandwiches.
I'll take Haruki Misora's reset ability.