I'll leave Sakurada, forget about my ability,
and live out the rest of my life.
It'll just be a week, though.
Do you want to know your own future?
Yes.
Even if it's something painful?
Yes, please.
You're going to be involved in something big...
Something involving my successor.
Does such a person exist?
The Bureau has been looking
for one for a long time now.
But no matter how much they looked, they couldn't
find anyone with the ability to see the future.
However,
you know someone who does possess it.
You've met that person a little over two years ago.
Is your successor...
Is the future-seeing ability user a girl?
Yes.
A slender girl with short hair, big eyes,
and about the age of a middle schooler.
Yes.
Is it the girl who died two years ago?
Correct. And you will run into her again.
Two Years Earlier
It's been two weeks since
the second semester started.
As well as two weeks since
Souma Sumire left this world.
She won't be coming to this rooftop anymore.
The
flow
of
time
makes
a
continuous
sound
(so
close
your
eyes
and
feel
it)
It's
a
melody
that
invites
the
coming
future
(which
begins
today)
What
kind
of
world
is
waiting
for
me?
(Who
is
calling
me?)
I
tried
asking
myself
for
an
answer
(in
my
heart)
Here,
in
the
middle
of
ideals
and
reality
(I'm
searching
for
them)
The
hands
of
the
clock
are
being
constantly
moved
(as
I
turn
them
back)
I'll
do
anything
to
erase
all
sadness
(over
and
over
again)
Even
if
it
means
going
back
down
the
passage
of
dark
stairs
(to
recreate
the
past)
There's
something
I
want
to
protect
no
matter
what
(I'll
protect
you)
I'll
say
that
out
loud
(and
try
resetting
again)
Believing
that
fate
will
bring
us
together
again
I also stopped spending time on the rooftop.
I always end up getting cold
feet when I reach the door.
I don't get any opportunities to meet
Haruki Misora anymore, either.
The last time I saw her was about a week ago.
We were summoned to the staff room
and encouraged to join the Service Club.
I haven't seen her since
we submitted our applications.
Or, to be more precise, I've been avoiding her.
When I'm sad, it rubs off on her.
I don't want to see her until
I can smile like nothing's wrong.
But it's been two weeks already.
It's a good time to change how things stand.
A young boy hurt a girl he was
friends with using his ability.
It seems he doesn't understand
quite how it works yet.
I'd like you to use Haruki's reset to put
the world back to before he hurt her.
And then after that, report the whole story
to me using your absolute memory.
The Bureau will take things from there.
I understand.
Where is Haruki?
I don't think her homeroom's been let out yet.
Or so I'd assume.
I see. I'll fill her in later, then.
It's your first task in the Service Club.
Good luck.
Kei, I can't use my reset ability.
You mean to say you don't have a save?
No, I saved around 5 p.m. two days ago.
What's stopping you, then?
I don't know.
I just get the feeling I wouldn't be able to.
Why don't you sit down for now?
Should I?
I'm not forcing you.
You should do what you want to do.
Haruki is changing.
She'll be feeling a lot of things from now on.
She'll learn them from you.
You were able to save two days ago, right?
Yes.
I believe I was.
How can be so sure?
I don't have any qualms about saving.
But I don't feel like I can reset in the first place.
What's the difference between them?
You ordered me to save.
Did I?
Yes.
You told me to save once every three days.
Kei, give me the order to reset.
I feel like I can do it if you tell me to.
Why won't you order me to reset?
Thinking ahead, it'd be best
if you're able to reset on your own.
If you absolutely need my orders,
it might pose a big obstacle sometime in the future.
I was sure he'd just tell me to reset right away.
Has he come to hate my ability?
I can easily see that being the case.
My reset most likely had something
to do with Souma Sumire's death.
Kei has been avoiding me ever since she died.
Even though he'd wanted my ability so much before.
Even though I'd decided I'd use it for him.
Now I understand.
You can't use Sakurada's abilities
unless you truly want to.
I decided to follow Asai Kei,
but he no longer wishes for
me to use my reset ability.
Not acting in accordance with his
wishes is the wrong thing to do.
I'm sure that's what I assumed
somewhere deep in my mind.
That's why I can't reset anymore.
Souma Sumire died as a result of a reset.
She was alive in the previous timeline,
but she died in the current one.
I've taken the ability to reset too lightly.
For the most part, everything went the
same way as it did before whenever we reset.
The contents of the newspaper never changed.
Neither did the results of sport matches
nor changes in the stock market.
The same accidents in faraway cities
would happen again as well.
That led me to believe that the future
doesn't change just because we reset.
I'd figured the only exception was me
retaining my memories from before the reset.
But Souma Sumire died,
and I had nothing to do with it.
I don't know why she did,
but it means unforeseen accidents
are not out of the equation.
That's why I couldn't tell her to reset.
Is resetting the right thing to do?
Kei probably can't come to terms with it.
But I'm sure tomorrow he'll tell me
to reset like nothing ever happened.
That way, we can carry out
our tasks in the Service Club.
We can help someone.
For that reason alone,
Kei will eventually choose to reset.
And that means resetting is the right thing to do.
Reset.
It seems I was right.
Something deep within me doesn't want to reset.
It's probably those things called
"emotions" getting in the way.
Every time I look at you,
it makes me think of two identical white boxes.
You're facing two white boxes in a white room.
You have to open one of them,
but you don't know which is the right one.
I don't understand.
I'm basically saying that's how
uniform the world is to you.
If they were different colors,
you could pick the one you like more.
If they were different shapes,
you could even pick based on that.
But the only thing that's ever in front of you
are two completely identical white boxes.
That's what Souma Sumire said.
But that isn't the case right now.
I see resetting and not resetting
as two very different choices.
There's an obvious distinction.
The logical choice would be to reset.
Kei would choose that too.
But my emotions are getting in the way.
Kei also hates the ability.
Reset.
I...
I'm scared of Kei hating me.
I'm from the Bureau.
How did it go?
The Bureau determined that Souma Sumire's death
was an accident unrelated to any abilities.
Why?
The connection between her death
and Haruki Misora's ability isn't clear.
It should be.
She was alive before the reset.
You're the only one claiming that.
Are you saying that I lied to you?
The Bureau determined that
we can't rule out that possibility.
Shouldn't you be able to investigate
if I'm telling the truth?
I cannot answer that.
If I'm able to prove that I am,
will you save Souma?
No.
I'm sorry, I didn't make it clear.
Even if what you're saying is the truth,
the Bureau won't get involved in this.
It's been determined Souma Sumire's death
happened separate from the usage of any abilities.
I see.
Please tell me one last thing.
If the Bureau put their resources into it,
would they be able to bring Souma Sumire,
someone who died two weeks ago, back to life?
I cannot answer that.
If you're an organization that
oversees the abilities in Sakurada,
wouldn't you know of an ability that can save her?
I cannot answer that.
Reset.
Reset. Reset.
09 | Agasa
Are you crying?
Hey. What are you doing here?
I came here to see the sunset.
That so? Why, though?
No reason, really. I just kinda felt like it.
I see.
Want a Kit Kat?
Yeah, sure.
Here.
Thank you.
Did you know that a girl died around here?
Yeah, I did. She went to my school.
Really? What was her name?
Souma Sumire.
How do you spell that?
"Souma" spelled S-O-U-M-A,
and "Sumire" spelled S-U-M-I-R-E.
Put it all together and you get "Souma Sumire."
I can tell you were pretty close.
Your girlfriend, maybe?
No, why would you think that?
Most people wouldn't remember someone's full
name just because they went to the same school.
And being able to effortlessly spell her name
like that tells me you were more than just friends.
I just happen to have an ability like that.
Like what?
I can remember anything and everything.
Oh yeah?
So what brings you here?
A girl slipped and fell into the river.
If it's dangerous here, it should be made safer.
Made safer? Do you want to put up
some kind of railing or something?
That's what I had in mind.
To steal your words: I have an ability like that.
What kind of ability?
I can build fences in just a few minutes.
You build fences?
I can also tear up clouds
and make a hole in the moon.
Not that I've ever done that,
but I think I'd be able to.
You're not making any sense.
I don't expect you to understand.
Want some Koala March?
No, thank you.
But they're so good!
If I eat too much, I won't have any room for dinner.
Right.
I'll eat them all by myself, then.
I wanted to put railings in dangerous places.
But you know...
I climbed all the way to the top and
couldn't find any place dangerous enough.
Then I found you.
And that made me wonder if the girl
who died here actually committed suicide.
That came out of nowhere.
How is me being here at all related to Souma?
You just kinda looked like you were ready to die.
The wind is strong, the sunset is beautiful...
It seemed to me like you were ready
to die for trivial reasons like that.
So I tried to put two and two together.
For whatever reasons, a girl... I mean, Souma died,
and knowing that, you, her boyfriend,
decided to commit suicide to follow her.
You couldn't be more off.
Really?
But everything went according to my script,
up to how you effortlessly spelled her name.
For the record, what would you do
if I really were here to die?
I'd save you, of course.
That's what the Kit Kat was for.
Did you think a Kit Kat was going
to change my mind about dying?
I find it hard to believe anyone would want
to die after eating something that good.
And I guess it meant "take a chill pill" too.
A pill in the guise of a candy bar?
"Have a break." That sort of meaning.
I'm going to head home.
Thank you for the Kit Kat.
What's your name?
Asai Kei. What about you?
Ukawa Sasane.
Want some Koala March?
Reset.
I'm scared of Kei hating me.
Is that phone strap some sort of memento?
No, not really.
But I really can't see you as the
type to use that kind of thing.
It was originally a keychain.
My parents were rarely ever home.
So when I got my own key,
my mom put this thing on them.
Was that before you came to Sakurada?
Yeah.
I threw away my house key
when I decided to live in Sakurada.
Yeah, uh, that's what you call a memento.
Is it?
Duh.
I threw away my key,
but what was I hoping to get in exchange?
I don't even have to think.
I'm here because I was drawn to Sakurada's abilities.
I'm sorry, Kei.
I couldn't reset on my own after all.
I'll give you the order, then.
Let's reset.
Kei.
Are you sure you want to do this?
Of course.
Resetting is the right thing to do now.
Don't you hate my ability?
Hate it? Why would I?
A reset killed Souma Sumire.
Souma Sumire died in an accident.
Our reset had nothing to do with it.
She died, and that's the end of it.
Wouldn't she be still alive if we hadn't reset?
That might be true.
But does that really matter?
If it's too dangerous an ability,
don't you think we shouldn't use it?
It's true that we might change
someone's future by resetting.
We might ruin someone's life
and never even know it.
But at the same time,
it has an equal chance of helping someone.
Let's say there's a man who
hurt himself and started bleeding.
Do you think it's wrong to save him?
No.
So that man is saved,
and he goes on to eventually meet
a woman and build a happy family.
Do you think that's wrong?
No.
But if you hadn't saved him,
the woman might've gone on to meet someone else.
She might have had an even happier family.
The life of the child who was supposed
to be born into that family
might've been indirectly
taken away by saving the man.
It's not limited to just abilities.
Every action of every person
is constantly changing the future.
If you think that resetting is the only
thing interfering with the future,
that's nothing but conceit.
If you changed the future to save one person,
but ended up making someone
else suffer in the process,
would you not feel sad?
Of course I would.
There's no better outcome than making
someone happy at no one else's expense.
And even then, you still want to reset?
If at all possible, I'd love to be able
to create nothing but happiness.
In the same way that God makes miracles,
I want to make people happy
without hurting anyone.
But I lack the power to do that.
Still, I don't want to sit by and do
nothing just because I'm powerless.
Even if I do hurt someone,
all I have to do is save more people than that.
I also think that's the right thing to do.
That's why I want you to help me, Haruki.
I'm sure Kei thinks that from the bottom of his heart.
Even if all his other words
were lies to make me reset...
Even if most of what he said were
just empty words to persuade me...
At the very least, the last part was from his heart.
I understand.
Kei, give me the order.
Haruki, it's time to reset.
Reset.
September 1
th
Wednes
day
Tues
Wednes
Mon
Tues
Second Time
I did the same things as before the reset.
I ate the same food,
read the same book,
and went to sleep at the same hour.
It's tiring to repeat what I already did once before.
Makes me feel like I'm acting in a boring play.
But resetting made me afraid
of changing the future unnecessarily.
September 14th
Tuesday
Second Time
Okay, I get the full story.
I'll report that to the Bureau.
Good job.
And so ended our first task in the Service Club.
The boy, who was supposed to use his ability,
and the girl, who was supposed
to get hurt because of it,
should be safe now.
But someone else might be
suffering because of this reset,
and we'll never even know about it.
I'm not sure if we did the right thing.
What killed Souma Sumire wasn't our reset.
It's my fault for making Haruki
reset for no real reason.
But still, if we can save someone by doing it,
I think we should keep using her ability.
I was hurt because of Souma's death.
But how I felt also hurt Haruki.
It hurt her deeply enough to make
her unable to use her ability.
I can think of only one way to ease her pain.
I'll bring Souma Sumire back to life.
I don't know if that's even possible,
but there are countless abilities in Sakurada.
I can't say for sure it's impossible
to bring a dead girl back to life.
Kei.
What's wrong?
We reset.
I'll tell you everything now.
I see.
But first, there's something I want to give you.
What is it?
It's nothing special.
Next Episode
Reviving a dead person...
If you're going to bring Souma back to life,
I'll do anything to help.
Is it broken?
You seem happy for some reason.
I think it's okay to just pray for that happiness.
Hello, Kei.
We're always simply standing in a rain of eternal sadness
That is why I need that warmth of yours
Life is but a dream we never wake up from
We repeat it over and over, praying for salvation
I kept waiting endlessly for your signal
To make sure you wouldn't disappear all by yourself
Ah, it doesn't matter where I am or what I'm doing
My heart can't go against your will
So I'd follow you even to the ends of the world
I fell in love with you at the dawn of our new world
But we kept pushing the hand of the clock backwards
And lost not only time, but our smiles as well
You're the one who brought it back
And taught me that even lies can be meaningful