Sagrada Reset
April 27th
Tuesday
Please come to the rooftop of the school's
south building after school on April 28th.
Signed, Souma Sumire.
Hey, Tomoki, there's a pretty
strange girl in your class, right?
A strange girl?
Oh, yeah! You mean that weird chick with long hair.
She's kinda like you.
Like me?
She hardly ever talks and always
has this blank look on her face.
It's like she's not interested in anyone around her.
Her name's Haruki Misora.
If you ask me, I'd say I'm pretty
talkative and expressive.
And my name is Asai Kei.
What's so similar about us?
The atmosphere around you.
It's like you both lack genuine feeling
whenever you do something.
Is that how you see it?
Hell, yeah!
So, what's this about Haruki?
Oh, she's not the one I wanted to ask you about.
It's Souma Sumire.
You know, the one with short hair.
Oh, that's the class rep of my class.
I've talked to her a few times.
And earlier today, I found a letter in my shoe locker.
It said she wants to meet me
on the rooftop tomorrow after school.
She's totally gonna ask you out!
So, whatcha gonna do?
I'll check it out.
I have no reason to refuse her invitation.
April 27th
Tuesday
You see, that's a perfect example
of how you simply go with the flow!
April 2
th
day
Tues
Wednes
Hey, you're in Class 2-1, right?
Yes.
Do you happen to know Souma?
Oh, great.
She told me to meet her up here.
Do you know where she might be?
No.
Hey, what's your favorite food?
I don't have one.
What's your least favorite food?
Do you think we're alike?
It depends on your definition of "alike."
By the way, why are you here?
If you want to be left alone, I can just leave.
I'm here because Souma Sumire
told me to come here.
It's not that I want to be alone.
I wish you'd said that when I brought Souma up.
Do you talk to her often?
The classmate I talked to the most when
I was a first-year was Souma Sumire.
Oh, so you are close.
You're already becoming the person I've
talked to most since I became a second-year.
Reset.
That girl...
April 27th
Tuesday
Second Time
If you ask me, I'd say I'm pretty
talkative and expressive.
And my name is Asai Kei.
What's so similar about us?
The atmosphere around you.
It's like you both lack genuine feeling
whenever you do something.
Yeah, we do.
Hell, yeah!
So, what's this about Haruki?
Uh... Is something wrong?
Oh, it's nothing. I was just thinking
I didn't have much of a chance.
This place is called Sakurada.
It's a town tucked away in Japan,
where about half of the people
possess special abilities.
There are a vast range of abilities.
While they generally defy the laws of physics,
they are pretty much useless for the most part.
There's a reason why people
with abilities live in Sakurada:
If someone leaves Sakurada,
they end up forgetting about their ability.
Being unaware of an ability you can use
is no different from not having one at all.
I possess the ability to relive the past
in my mind with all five senses.
I can always remember the things I've seen,
heard, and thought with absolute accuracy.
So far, my ability has only been effective enough
to say that I've got a better memory than others.
However...
April 27th
Tuesday
April 2
th
Tues
Wednes
day
Second Time
Hey, where should we go?
The place we went to last time!
Sounds good. Let's go!
Yeah, let's!
Good afternoon, Asai.
What are you doing, Souma?
Doing my class rep duties.
In a place like this?
It doesn't matter where I do them.
As long as it isn't on the rooftop
of the south building.
Don't you think it's a bit rude when you ask me
to come somewhere and then not show up at all?
My bad.
Is it part of the class rep's duties
to set me and Haruki up?
She doesn't have any friends she's close with.
I just simply thought that if I have
you two meet, you'd become friends.
And what about you?
I'll try, but I don't think it's possible.
We're not compatible at all.
Like you wouldn't believe.
Why me, of all people?
Because you're compatible.
You two are really alike.
You're identical in how you
both lead very proper lives.
Not in that we both lack genuine feeling?
If you ever wanna get closer to Haruki,
I don't mind helping you out.
Is there any real point to that?
There is. There's a huge meaning
to you two being together.
Like, say for example, resetting.
Reset.
Oh, so this is the second time.
Is resetting your ability?
Yes.
I can restore the world to as far as three days back.
So you can basically rewind time?
No. I just rearrange everything to its past state.
Since I rearrange things,
I strictly reconstruct the world of the past.
So it's not as if you're erasing time.
It's really just a reset.
Even human brain cells get
rearranged to their past state.
Because of that, people lose
their memories of that time.
I see.
However, my ability has three restrictions to it.
First of all, I can't use my ability
to reset if I didn't save beforehand.
The save expires after 72 hours.
Secondly, I can't save until 24 hours
have passed since a reset.
So basically, you can't repeat
the same time over and over again.
And lastly, the biggest restriction out of the three:
resetting personally affects me, too.
All my memories of that time also disappear.
Even the memory of the reset itself disappears.
Spring is almost over.
Summer starts next weekend.
Oh, really? Summer is always
much sooner than you think.
Well then, let's spend our summer here.
We can meet up as much as we want
and talk about all sorts of things that can
help us understand each other better.
Is there any point in doing that?
Who cares if there's a point or not?
We'll just be hanging out like sparrows that
are only on a power line to rest their wings.
I don't like doing things without any purpose.
I guess.
Then, let's assume there's an android among us.
An android?
They look just like humans.
Even if you were to hold their hand,
kiss them, or check their blood,
you wouldn't know that they're artificial.
So, who among us is that kind of android?
What's the point of this?
It's just a simple question.
Who's an android?
We're all just ordinary humans.
Just think about it.
Who would you expect to be an android?
Anyway, let's make figuring
that out a reason to meet up.
And then, at the end of summer,
we'll tell each other our answers.
Resetting, huh?
It's an interesting ability, but it's not very useful.
Yeah, that's true.
You simply experience the same time period twice.
On top of that, you're not aware
that it's the second time.
Normally.
Huh?
It seems like resetting doesn't affect my memory.
I think my special ability preserves it.
Seriously?
Until now, I sometimes had this feeling as if
my memory and sense of time were doubled.
I think it might have something
to do with Haruki's reset ability.
You should totally reset after memorizing
the winning lottery ticket numbers!
I'll do that when I'm completely
desperate for money.
Totally saw that coming!
You always take the high road.
But I'm sure it can be used for good.
Yeah.
It might break the rules of this world, after all.
Reset.
Oh, I don't have a save.
Um...
Do you happen to know my mom?
No, I don't.
Where did you lose sight of her?
Please tell me what you've been doing up until now.
I was at the hospital for a checkup.
Please tell me your name.
Kurakawa Mari.
Please let go.
Let's work together.
Together?
I won't lose my memory even
if you use your reset ability.
So if we team up, we can redo the past.
We can overcome any problem together.
I don't want to.
Why not?
Because I abide by the rules.
Rules?
It's a guideline for me to decide on things.
For instance,
if it has a probability of causing a negative
effect on my surroundings, I refuse to reset.
Will it cause a negative effect if we work together?
It's a possibility.
How so?
Because you're the only one
who can exploit resetting.
When I do a reset, I lose my memory of that time.
I wouldn't even notice your lies.
You have too much initiative in this situation.
Plus, I don't have any basis to trust you.
Haruki.
You used your reset ability on this rooftop
after school on April 28th, right?
Yes. Probably.
I'm curious why you did it.
It was probably because a girl was crying.
Whenever I see someone crying, I reset.
That's pointless.
Even if you reset, she'll end up crying anyway.
It being pointless isn't a reason
for breaking the rules.
Haruki...
I'm sure I'll be able to earn your trust in due time.
Not once have I ever trusted anyone.
Is that so? Then, I'll be the first.
Did you two warm up to each other?
I can't say. It's kinda difficult.
Oh? So even you can admit when things are difficult.
I started to wonder if she truly had anything to say.
Kei, why do you want to get closer to Haruki?
To get my hands on her reset ability.
Kei, you're the kind of person that always gives
self-deprecating answers to such questions.
It's caused by your extremely
strong sense of justice.
I'd say it's on the same level
as clean-freaks or perfectionists.
I don't think I'm that righteous.
God once placed a curse on one young man.
It was a curse that shot pain throughout the man's
entire body when he came across a sad person.
Wow... That sounds terrible.
In order to avoid his pain, the young man
reached out to all the sad people.
And?
God then made a copy of the
young man and created a fake.
The copy had no will of its own,
so it did the same thing the original did.
The fake also reached out to all the sad people.
God gave the two names of their own, you know.
What kind of names?
He chose the names Good and Hypocrisy.
So who do you think got which name?
The real young man is Hypocrisy. The fake is Good.
Why is that?
The real one helps others for his own good.
You don't even have to think
about who's genuinely good.
The fake is only following the real one's lead.
That isn't a problem.
Doing things for yourself isn't genuinely good.
That just shows how upright you are.
Your sense of justice is so strong that
you can't even admit you're righteous.
If there's even just a little bit of impurity within you,
you'll end up thinking like you're a villain.
Haruki Misora is what you'd
consider to be an ideal human.
She's the only being that can be what
you consider to be genuinely good.
Let's find out about Haruki's past.
We might find out how she
became the way that she is now.
How?
I know someone with the perfect ability for this.
I think he'd probably be willing to help us out.
What do you usually do to have fun?
I've been talking to this one person a lot lately.
Today, we talked about trust.
Trust?
It was about if it's possible
to accept a person's judgment
under circumstances when there's no logical basis.
Okay...
He said he would earn my trust.
So, that person likes you, huh?
Likes?
I like you. And I like my mom, too.
But my mom doesn't like me. It's because I'm a fake.
What do you mean by "fake"?
Do you want to be liked by your mother?
Yeah. Very much.
I'm here to pick you up, Mari.
Let's go home.
Who is this man?
He's Mister Tsushima.
Are you Haruki?
Yes.
I heard about you from Mari.
She said you always spend time with her.
Thank you for that.
Who are you?
I'm like her stand-in guardian.
Why isn't Mari's mother coming to pick her up?
She will. She's just a little late, that's all.
We need to get going, Mari.
Okay.
Where's Souma?
She's meeting someone, so she'll apparently be late.
Your hair's really pretty.
And since it's pretty, it might be best to cut it.
I don't get what you mean.
It doesn't feel real.
Your pretty hair makes you
seem way too otherworldly.
Is that a problem?
Maybe.
Asai Kei, there's something I'd like to ask you.
What is it?
Is it sad to be unloved by your mother?
Well, yeah, it would normally be sad.
There's a girl named Kurakawa Mari.
She wishes to be loved by her mother.
Do you know of a way to make that happen?
You want to help her, right?
I don't really know.
But I decided to be on her side.
Following your own rules?
No.
Why, then?
I'm not sure.
If you want to help that girl out
no matter what, then I'll help out.
But if you're helping the girl just for the sake of it,
then I don't want to.
I can't do anything to force you.
Kei! Haruki!
Let's go to the student council room.
Nice to meet you. I'm the student
council president, Sakagami.
His ability is a pretty interesting one.
What? You haven't told them yet?
Nope.
B-Basically, my ability is copying the ability
of the person I'm touching with my right hand
to the person I'm touching with my left.
I want you to copy Kei's ability of absolute memory to Haruki.
We'll make you remember your childhood times.
Why?
Because I wanna know.
I'm really interested in your past.
Is that so? All right, then.
Hold on.
Memories have tremendous power.
It might distort your personality, Haruki.
Is there a problem with that?
I understand. If there are any problems, let's reset.
August 12th    Thursday    3:15 PM
First Time
Save.
Go right ahead.
Okay, here we go.
If Asai uses his ability while we're like this,
Haruki will get the same effect.
Haruki, what day do you want to remember?
Well... Let's go back to when I was 5 years old.
Got it. I'm starting now.
What's wrong?
I was crying.
Always.
Always?
I cried very often...
Whenever I heard sad news,
or even if something broke.
Why did you cry?
Because it was sad.
What was sad about it?
Everything about it was sad.
It's sad that everyone will die someday.
It's sad that everything will break someday.
Everything about those obvious rules is sad.
The natural way of things is sad, huh?
Yes.
That's why you became unable to choose.
That's why you created rules.
Yes.
If anything and everything is tied to sadness,
then there's no point in having choices.
No matter what you choose, it changes nothing.
That's why you became unable to choose.
You can't choose anything, and yet,
you must choose something.
That is why you created rules for your own actions.
Yes.
I want you to tell me one thing, though.
Who's the one who's sad?
I don't know.
Haruki Misora, what you were
missing was your sense of self.
The young Haruki didn't even realize
that what she was sad about was herself.
If there wasn't any difference between
a death you saw on TV and your own,
then you wouldn't know how much
sadness there would be in the world.
It must be very painful to live, feeling all the sadness
of the world as if it affects you personally.
After getting your feelings worn down by sadness,
you become unable to do anything, right?
And yet, she still decided to keep going.
She created rules to make the right decisions.
She was forcing herself to try
and help even if she was unable to.
And to always make the right choices,
even if it meant losing her emotions.
I think only Haruki, who doesn't have
a sense of self, can remain righteous.
If there really is a person out
there who we can call "Good,"
I'm sure it'd be Haruki.
But Haruki isn't able to help anyone.
People would rather get help, even from a hypocrite,
than to be watched over by a good person.
I guess.
Also, I think the ones who can save people
are selfish hypocrites like you, Kei.
There's no way. I'm not even a hypocrite.
Right.
You're kind to a fault,
and that uprightness of yours causes you
to worry too much about your own malice.
You're unable to believe that you're right,
yet you continue to be righteous.
I don't get what you mean.
Let's prove it, then.
Prove it?
I'll have you act as if you're a good person.
August 13th
Friday
August 1
th
Fri
Satur
day
I'm surprised. I wouldn't expect swings to suit you.
Can you really say that about swings?
Probably. They definitely don't suit me.
You're Kurakawa Mari, right?
Yeah.
Nice to meet you. I'm Asai.
I go to the same school as Haruki.
I'd like to ask you something.
What?
Did you know that a little girl named
Kurakawa Mari died seven years ago?
Kurakawa Mari died seven years ago.
She died?
When the doctor performed a C-section on Mari's
mother, Mari had already stopped breathing.
Mari, if Kurakawa Mari died,
then who might you be?
Next Episode
You choose, Haruki.
Are you going to hand Mari over to the Bureau?
My job means doing things I don't want to do.
What do you want to do with Haruki Misora?
I remembered all of the sadness
I was supposed to feel soon.
Let's go erase the girl's tears.
We're always simply standing in a rain of eternal sadness
That is why I need that warmth of yours
Life is but a dream we never wake up from
We repeat it over and over, praying for salvation
I kept waiting endlessly for your signal
To make sure you wouldn't disappear all by yourself
Ah, it doesn't matter where I am or what I'm doing
My heart can't go against your will
So I'd follow you even to the ends of the world
I fell in love with you at the dawn of our new world
But we kept pushing the hand of the clock backwards
And lost not only time, but our smiles as well
You're the one who brought it back
And taught me that even lies can be meaningful