I'd rather you not talk about that old man to Mytyl.
Why? It's possible he's what we need to save her.
Is it really possible, though?
She's afraid of that man.
What is your wish?
I'm the god of this world,
so I'll grant any wish of yours.
If you're claiming to be the god, can you tell me
the difference between a god and a demon?
A god grants salvation and demands nothing.
A demon grants power and demands your soul.
But don't you take away their freedom
if they ask you to grant their wish?
I don't take anything from them.
By being given one thing, you can lose another.
If you're caught in a paradise granted
to you by a god and can't get out,
how is that any different
from your soul being stolen?
Those are words that could destroy this Eden.
It'll be time soon.
I
used
to
say
there
was
a
novel
I
loved
That
I
kept
on
a
shelf
and
never
opened
up
"See,
this
is
how
you
stay
true
to
yourself"
Showing
off,
proud
of
just
being
me
People
around
me
Try
to
sound
mature
and
take
some
wise
words
They
use
them
as
if
those
words
belonged
to
them
Showing
off
the
fake
wisdom
they
had
stolen
So
I
laughed
at
them
But
actually
my
sense
of
self
that
I
kept
on
a
shelf
Was
no
different
from
what
I'd
been
laughing
at
And
the
truth
is
that
I
already
knew
But
no
more
lies,
it's
time
For
my
heart's
reset
I'll
myself
So
I
told
myself
somewhere
deep
down
in
my
heart
Even
if
they
might
talk
behind
my
back
Why
should
I
care
when
I
don't
turn
around?
You
can
choose
To
follow
the
path
someone's
already
walked
But
wouldn't
you
rather
leave
footprints
yourself?
You
believed
your
own
dreams
and
chose
a
path
So
it's
the
right
one,
just
trust
in
your
heart
It'll
all
be
fine
I spent all day yesterday walking around the town.
And today I heard from the Bureau
about Tyltyl and Mytyl.
That's how I've more or less reached a conclusion.
Asai,
do you think this world is right?
I don't think it's right.
But I don't think we have a say in it.
I hate this world.
And I've been wondering why.
I saw a poster long time ago.
There was a picture
where everyone held hands
in a circle around the Earth.
And in my heart, I felt that such things were right.
Katagiri Honoka is isolated from people.
The way she secludes herself in her own world
and creates her own god
is what you find problematic, isn't it?
In my heart, I feel that such a thing is disgusting.
This world is all Katagiri has.
If she can't wake up in reality,
this is her only way to be happy.
You've got me wrong.
I'm not against the ability
to create a world inside a dream.
The problem is creating Tyltyl and becoming Mytyl.
That is warped and disgusting.
I don't know
if this case should be solved high-handedly, though.
But I know.
This world wants to be saved.
Why do you think so?
It's the only reason a monster
would destroy the town.
The truth is that Katagiri Honoka, who created
this world, also hates it, or at least I think so.
Please wait!
I won't.
I'm going to fix this world.
I'll destroy it and return it to a blank state.
And what good will that do?
Won't Mytyl remember that she's Katagiri Honoka?
Then she can start over and create a proper world.
Ukawa, I respect your strength.
But I've never once thought you were righteous.
If I had to compare...
I've never once thought you're
a better person than Haruki Misora.
Asai, I really hate to say this,
but I strongly believe my sense
of what is right is better than yours.
You're reckless, Ukawa.
What happened to people
who were in tall buildings?
They'll be fine.
Getting hurt inside a dream
doesn't affect your real self.
What just happened?
Ukawa erased all the buildings.
That's absurd.
Ukawa has an ability that can alter a world.
She can do anything she imagines
as long as it doesn't affect living beings.
You sure erased everything nicely.
I did, including the written copy of the Script.
Is that a problem?
It'd have been better if you'd waited a bit longer...
Doesn't matter.
I wish you'd left at least a bed to sleep
in for when we want to go back.
Hi, morning.
Could you place a lock on this?
If you used Kagaya's ability on me,
would I not get affected by resets?
I don't want to lose my memories of today, if possible.
Generally, using his ability on people is forbidden.
I see.
Do you hate that dream world?
It reminds me of something I absolutely hate.
Which is?
This place.
It reminds me of the real Sakurada.
One Hand Eden, a paradise of easy life.
Reminds me of this strange town, full of abilities
that let you achieve results just by wishing for them.
You sure hate abilities.
It's not as much hate as fear.
There's no way I could approve of an individual
possessing a power that could destroy the world.
The nameless system verified that
Ukawa Sasane is harmless, though.
And who'll verify if the nameless system is correct?
You hate your own ability, am I wrong?
The ability to completely see
through the feelings of others.
Is something wrong with that?
This is where your value lies, in my opinion.
Ability users are supposed to hate their abilities.
It's as though the world ended.
I have a hypothesis.
The real hospital is at the east end of Sakurada,
but in the dream world, east and west are reversed, so it's at the west end.
I've been thinking about
why it's like that all this time.
Have you reached an answer?
My theory is that the directions
might not be reversed at all, actually.
We might be out above the sea right now.
In that case, I might know what's
on the other side of this wall.
The dream world's real Sakurada?
It'd all make sense that way.
This was probably a replica
of the town that Tyltyl made.
What are you going to do?
Tyltyl! I want to meet you!
Could you let us through?
It really was here.
STOP
CHISECHOU
TYLTYL
Are we getting on?
Of course.
TYLTYL
Is that the god?
I wonder.
Welcome. I've been waiting for you.
Are you the god of this world?
Yes, I'm Tyltyl.
I was created as the false god of this world.
Here.
If we're going to talk, you should sit down.
Haruki!
Beautiful.
Do you mind if I visit you in the hospital in reality?
I want to meet you again.
That's impossible.
No one is allowed to visit me in the hospital.
The Bureau decided so.
You should just forget about me and live on.
And what are you going to do?
I'm not going to do anything.
As long as this world stays the same,
I'll spend my days alone here watching the sky.
What do you think will happen to this world?
Who knows.
It's for the god to decide.
Why did you confine yourself in your
office and keep using your ability?
It was comfortable.
It was comfortable to spend my life
looking at the truth in solitude.
Were you happy like that?
Yes, solitude brings me happiness.
Where is Kei?
You're not in danger.
Don't worry about it.
Please tell me.
He's somewhere you can't reach on your own.
Don't worry, you'll meet him again soon.
You can sit down for now.
Welcome to the dream world.
Here you can have anything you wish for.
Now, tell me what your wish is.
I do not have any.
You're strongly bound by a certain young man.
That's true.
And being bound by that young man,
your simple self has become
so much more complicated.
I do not understand.
Without you realizing, your real self
has diverged from how he defines you.
The truth is that you have a lot you'd wish for,
but you started hiding
behind a mask of selflessness.
You have two selves that contradict each other.
I know a spell that'll awaken the other you, though.
Let's try it.
If you don't do anything,
Souma Sumire might end up taking away Asai Kei.
Asai Kei will long for Souma Sumire,
and won't even turn your way.
You should take your time talking this through
with your other self, who knows what you wish for.
You hate me.
But that's a contradiction.
Since you don't really have anything,
you shouldn't be able to hate anyone.
What have you done?
I sent Haruki Misora to see another me.
Another you?
Come on, sit down.
Welcome to the dream world.
Here you can have anything you wish for.
What is your wish?
I have two things I'd like to ask you for.
That's pretty greedy.
First, please let me read volume 407 of the Script.
That's not your wish, is it?
My dear Sumire told you to do so.
You know Souma Sumire?
She's the only friend I have.
So what's your second wish?
I want to know what'll happen
if Souma Sumire leaves Sakurada.
Could you let me test that here, in the dream world?
Specifically,
I first want you to get help from a girl called Oka Eri,
and rewrite Souma's parents' memories.
Make them forget that Souma died two years ago,
and move their house out of Sakurada.
Would that be possible?
Of course it is.
But to me, this world is my reality.
Yeah, I guess so.
You should understand then.
You can't use the people
of this world as guinea pigs.
That's not true.
I know that you're actually sacrificing
a whole town's worth of people.
I need you to do the same thing for me.
Tyltyl,
if this world is important to you,
why are you letting a monster run wild?
Was it Mytyl who created it?
Is there something wrong with that?
Indeed.
I've finally learned the truth about this world.
You know nothing!
It's not just Mytyl that is Katagiri Honoka.
This whole world is her.
Why do you hate me?
You're worthless to Kei.
So I'm not as polite when I talk with myself...
But I was created from within you.
Essentially, you wanted me to exist.
You didn't actually want
Souma Sumire to be born again.
Because with Souma Sumire's future-seeing
your reset ability would lose its value to Kei.
You were afraid of that.
Yeah.
But it doesn't matter anymore.
Kei chose to revive her, so I follow him.
When Kei decided to take
Souma Sumire outside of Sakurada,
it made you happy.
Because your reset ability will remain useful.
This isn't about me.
If Kei chose so, I approve of it.
But I don't like that.
It might be better for Souma Sumire
to remain in Sakurada.
Why?
I'm sure that Kei wants to be with Souma Sumire.
And since I genuinely wish for Asai Kei's happiness,
the right thing to do might
be to keep Souma Sumire here.
What you actually hate,
what you actually fear deep in your heart
is the possibility that you yourself might not be
prioritizing Asai Kei's happiness over anything else.
This emotion of wanting to monopolize him
is what you very emotionally hate.
Both me and you are emotions.
You were in your little Eden.
You were protecting yourself
in a very easy to live place.
Now, tell me.
Tell me what your wish is.
Tyltyl,
I finally understand what I myself wish for.
What is it?
I want to grow.
I want to be of greater value
than anyone or anything else to Kei.
That's why I have nothing to ask you for, Tyltyl.
I see.
Now I know why there is a monster.
Mytyl wishes for it.
Why do you think so?
If nothing attacked, she wouldn't need to be protected.
Mytyl wants to be protected, am I wrong?
No, you're not.
Mytyl... Katagiri Honoka is lonely.
Her ability was originally only
to talk with people inside a dream.
She just wanted a connection with
people who were sleeping next to her.
But the Bureau has taken away even that from her,
and she became truly lonely, all alone.
And having lost all connection with people,
Katagiri created a god and an enemy.
That's right.
The monster and I were born,
and she became Mytyl, unaware of anything.
Do you think this world is wrong?
It's definitely not right.
The means and the end don't match at all.
You can't create both the hero and the villain
yourself if you want to connect with people.
In the end, she's still all alone.
She keeps claiming this place is Eden.
And yet, somewhere deep
in her heart, she knows it's a lie.
As much as she might pretend to have
forgotten everything, she's aware of her solitude.
You love her.
Of course.
I was created to.
That's why I can't save Mytyl.
I can't erase her solitude.
I'm never able to do the one thing I was born for.
That's why you created the reversed Sakurada.
You knew that place would be destroyed by Ukawa.
Did Souma tell you?
Mytyl is currently crying in that destroyed town.
She doesn't understand why
I'm not coming to her rescue,
and so she's crying in her loneliness.
Once her tears run dry, she'll think.
What can she do to end her loneliness?
Where is the Eden that has
been protecting her all this time?
Mytyl knows nothing outside of that
little town surrounded by a white wall.
But Katagiri Honoka
knows that this world is far bigger than that.
Once Mytyl regains all of
Katagiri Honoka's memories,
she'll step outside that wall, right?
I want to believe that she will.
Will that save Mytyl?
I don't know.
But she can't stay the way she is now.
This world is a little bit too sad.
Tyltyl,
I can't become a god.
But I might be able to help Mytyl
make some friends at least.
I might not be able to do much,
but I'll try to make this world her real Eden.
That's why I ask of you, Tyltyl.
Will you help me with my experiment?
I get it. I will.
Even I want to grant someone's wish at least once.
Volume 407 of the Script...
Sakurada... abilities...
The Bureau...
"The first year..."
I'm sure this is what Souma wanted me to know.
Kei.
Hey, where have you been?
I was meeting Tyltyl.
I see. Did anything happen?
Tyltyl asked me if I had any wishes,
and I answered that I have none.
What were you doing?
The same as you.
Tyltyl asked me what I wished for as well.
Did you ask him for anything?
I did.
He promised he'll help us test Souma's case.
In return, I'll resolve Mytyl's problem.
Mytyl's problem?
It seems that this whole world is Katagiri Honoka.
So someone forcefully destroying all of it,
even if it's because this world isn't right,
is something I can't approve of.
What is that?
That's Katagiri Honoka.
She wants to open her eyes.
That's why the monster has so many of them.
She wants someone to take her hand,
which is why it has so many of them.
She's all alone, lonely, so scared
that it makes her scream inside,
and so it does aloud.
To summarize, I'd say that the monster
is Katagiri Honoka's very emotions.
What is it doing?
It's looking for the blue bird.
But it can't find the blue bird this way.
Next Episode
The future I see isn't absolute.
What are you plotting?
It's been a while, Souma Sumire.
I can't save you.
It's fine. You're not alone anymore!
Please... save me!
On such a cold dark sky of grey
Rises the sun, which breathes life into it
A scenery so plain and so mundane
And yet it seems to break my heart, it's so dear to me
As the time never stops passing by
You get lost while searching for
Pure like the rays of a morning star
What we all yearn for the most
In what colors bliss is dyed
Struggling against all your past mistakes
At last from the answer you found kindness fills your heart
More beautiful than anything you know
And you find it behind a dark veil of sadness
If I closed my eyes and stopped my thoughts
If it were so simple to just
Lock your own heart
How lovely life would be
But I believe you have the key
To let my soul be free