Minami?!
Yeah... When I came to, I was like this.
How do you think this happened?
I don't know. Maybe it's your ability?
You do live in Sakurada, after all.
Do you know what might have caused it?
I went to the haunted mountain
to look for the vampire...
But I can't remember what happened after that.
Asai, you're in the Service Club, right?
The
flow
of
time
makes
a
continuous
sound
(so
close
your
eyes
and
feel
it)
It's
a
melody
that
invites
the
coming
future
(which
begins
today)
What
kind
of
world
is
waiting
for
me?
(Who
is
calling
me?)
I
tried
asking
myself
for
an
answer
(in
my
heart)
Here,
in
the
middle
of
ideals
and
reality
(I'm
searching
for
them)
The
hands
of
the
clock
are
being
constantly
moved
(as
I
turn
them
back)
I'll
do
anything
to
erase
all
sadness
(over
and
over
again)
Even
if
it
means
going
back
down
the
passage
of
dark
stairs
(to
recreate
the
past)
There's
something
I
want
to
protect
no
matter
what
(I'll
protect
you)
I'll
say
that
out
loud
(and
try
resetting
again)
Believing
that
fate
will
bring
us
together
again
I'm amazed you came here
in the middle of the night.
Yeah! I don't remember anything, though!
For a ghost, you sure are cheerful.
Of course! I'm a ghost, you know!
It's so unrealistic, and it feels special, doesn't it?!
It's Haruki. Looks like she's here.
Really?! I'll go show her my ghostly self!
Shall I add you to my collection, too?
Are you alone?
Yes. Kei went on a picnic with some girl,
so I followed him here.
That must be tough to deal with.
It really is.
We found Minami's body.
Did she die?
She was killed.
The suspect turned himself in this morning.
His name's Yoshii Ryouji.
But he goes by "Hitsuuchi."
Yoshii is an absolute clean-freak,
and he can't force himself to eat anything.
Instead, he possesses an ability that allows him
to convert information into nourishment.
Yoshii used to suck information
directly from the person.
He only took a small amount.
It was enough only to leave
the person out cold for a while.
That's how the rumor of the vampire came to be...
Yoshii created an environment
to collect information more safely.
That's how the informant
known as Hitsuuchi came to be.
But he ran into some trouble,
and that environment was destroyed.
And then went back to sucking
information directly from people again.
That's what happened last night.
The victim was Minami Mirai.
No matter how much he sucked, the amount
of information she had wouldn't diminish.
So, Yoshii accidentally ended up sucking too much,
and Minami died along with
the information she had.
The ability to die while retaining information...
If you put it another way,
it's the ability to turn into a ghost.
Are you going to revive her?
Yeah, I guess.
Minami didn't seem all that sad, though.
Actually, she seemed quite
happy over becoming a ghost.
The truth is, it doesn't matter
what Minami is thinking.
She was alive before the reset.
Are you thinking about
what happened two years ago?
I can erase whatever I call.
Right hand. Stone.
Your point?
Right hand. Human body.
I've decided to kill you both.
How am I supposed to respond to such a threat?
Did you expect me to agree?
No one would accept a death threat
and let themselves get killed.
Full body. Gravel.
She calls out what part of the body she wants
to activate, and then the object to erase.
She can reuse a body part while the call is in effect.
The new call also retains the previous call's effect.
She's wary of Haruki?
But she's only coming after me.
Let's end this now.
Murase, do you know what a MacGuffin is?
How do you know about that?!
I knew it. Murase Youka and
the MacGuffin are connected.
Where is the MacGuffin?
Beats me. I just know its name.
Very well, then.
Is there a time limit for the effects of her ability?
Right hand. Human body.
Begone!
Haruki, reset!
Full body. Ability.
Reset.
July 1
th
Satur
day
Fri
Satur
Thurs
Fri
Third Time
It's July 13th. The time is 12:59:15.
Looks like you reset.
Was it before we went to the festival?
We still haven't gone to it yet.
I'm glad to hear that.
You liar.
It's disappointing to hear that from a guy.
Haruki.
Um...
You liar?
Hey, not bad!
It'd be best if you said that while scowling
at me from above a bit more, though.
Kei?
You don't have to do that.
You said it was a done deal, didn't you?
I don't believe I did.
You will tomorrow.
You think I can take responsibility
for what I said in a previous timeline?
What in the world is going on?
Don't worry about it.
Even though Minami is dead?
She's alive... in this timeline, at least.
I'll deal with Yoshii.
I was nearly killed by Murase.
I'll deal with that, too.
One more thing.
What is a MacGuffin?
A person who possesses the MacGuffin is able
to control all the special abilities in Sakurada.
It's an urban legend.
Rumors of it spread about two years ago.
So it doesn't exist?
No. An object called "MacGuffin" does exist.
It's a small black stone that's about this big.
Where is it?
The staff room. It's in my desk drawer.
That concludes our discussion.
Don't be late to class.
I'm thinking of telling Minami about
what happened before the reset.
Do whatever you want.
Good morning, Kei!
This time, I've got a message from Friday,
July 14th, which is yesterday for you.
I believe you made an important appointment—
July 15th
Saturday
Third Time
Good morning.
Morning.
Nice to meet you, Murase.
You don't need to keep up the act.
Why are you here?
Tsushima called me here.
Do you want to kill me?
Why would I kill you?
I was just kidding.
That's a sick joke.
She doesn't remember anything
from the previous timeline?
By the way, are you done with saving the cat?
I wanted to test whether or not I could
cancel out your abilities with mine.
I remember the request I made regarding the cat.
You both aren't a threat.
She remembers things from two resets ago.
That means that just the latest
reset was a reset for her.
Why is that?
What do you want?
The MacGuffin was stolen.
I'm gonna have you guys get it back.
You were in the Service Club, too, Murase?
In name only.
This guy has given the Bureau
the most trouble these past two years.
He's your senior.
Is that true?
Shouldn't we be focusing on the MacGuffin?
The thief's identity takes priority.
We have a suspect.
The thief is most likely Yoshii Ryouji.
It's Hitsuuchi.
Tell me more of what
he mentioned earlier about you.
I said something selfish a long time ago. That's all.
What's your objective?
We want to revive a girl.
We're looking for an ability
that can make that happen.
I failed in the end.
Are you trying to do something similar, Murase?
Hairpin -Plum Red-
Tsumami Workshop - Tortoiseshell
I will take down the Bureau and rebuild it.
There are countless abilities in Sakurada.
If they're used well, people will be even happier.
But those in the Bureau
just observe what's going on.
Asai, would you join forces with me?
Let me think about it a little.
First, we need to find Hitsuuchi.
That's easy.
Right hand. What is obstructing me from Yoshii.
It's this way.
That's amazing. So you can even use it like that...
It's strange, isn't it?
This is the way to Yoshii's house.
You know where it is?
Yes. I went three days ago.
The hole in the wall...
So, it was actually a trace of
Murase searching for Hitsuuchi.
But...
Hey, Kei. It's been a while.
Or should I say, nice to meet you?
It's the first time I've heard
your actual voice, huh, Hitsuuchi?
Hey, you! I had quite an ordeal since
you disconnected my phone line!
It's your fault! Hand over the MacGuffin!
I can't hand over what I don't have.
I'll disconnect your phone line again!
Wait. I'm pretty sure he's telling the truth.
Who stole it, then?!
I don't know.
But someone might've picked it up by chance.
You might know that someone, Hitsuuchi.
Yeah. In that case, I might know who it is.
She said she'd bring the MacGuffin.
How much of the previous timelines do you know?
Everything you told Tsushima.
I did something really bad.
Even though the reset erased everything?
I still did something bad.
If you think so, then maybe you did.
Yeah.
Thanks.
That's why Hitsuuchi is still helping us despite
knowing that Minami stole the MacGuffin.
Oh, you're here, too, Misora!
Are you Misora's friend?
No, I'm not.
She's Murase the Revolutionary.
No, I'm not!
I've got something for Asai, you know.
That means you've got the MacGuffin, huh?
Could you show it to me?
Here it is. It just looks like
an ordinary pebble, though.
Oh, yeah? Well then, I'll take it.
No. I promised to give it to Asai.
It's pointless for him to have it.
I think the same would apply to you.
I'm special, you know.
I possess an especially powerful ability.
That doesn't matter.
I've admired abilities for a long time.
Asai is special. Misora is also special.
But I can't see what's so special about you at all.
Shut your trap!
I'm going to take it from you.
Try me.
Index fingernail. Human body.
If you want to join forces, call me.
You don't have to go after her.
Kei...
This is kind of bad.
I wanna ask you to do some work.
Is it for the Service Club?
No, it's a request from me.
I've got a student that's playing hooky.
Her name's Murase Youka.
Please brief me.
Murase had an older brother
who was once part of the Bureau.
He died in a car accident
in the summer of last year.
So, Murase thought that if the Bureau
used special abilities effectively,
they could've saved her brother
with someone's ability.
She always said that she would
never forgive the Bureau.
Again and again and again.
She'd just say the same thing repeatedly.
Because she viewed the Bureau as her enemy,
you told her about the MacGuffin
to entice her to go after it.
Yeah, that's right.
Why did you approve of the request to save the cat?
I wanted you two and her to connect.
She relies only on her ability.
She needs an opponent
that she'll lose to completely.
I don't really have a way to persuade her...
Murase hurt Minami.
It was just a scratch.
She intentionally hurt someone using her ability.
The Bureau will deal with it severely.
She crossed a line that should never be crossed.
I can only think of one method to persuade her.
And I don't want to do that.
Please send Murase a message.
What should it say?
"Let's join forces and take down the Bureau.
I'd like you to come to the Kawaharazaka's
riverside tomorrow at 11:45 a.m sharp."
Hey, what's up, Kei?
I've got a favor to ask.
Hello. Would you like some?
There's no mayonnaise on it.
Murase probably just wanted
to get something across.
The same goes for Mr. Tsushima.
But that didn't go well for the two of them.
I love messages.
I want to send a lot of happy and
trivial words from person to person.
What if it's something sad?
I'll figure out how to word the message.
If it's something that should be said,
I'll use the right words to do the right thing.
But when it gets across, the recipient will be sad.
That's true...
But I believe it's still better than
the message not getting across at all.
You don't need to be afraid.
I'm sure you'll do just fine.
What did you come here for?
I was thinking of climbing up a tree.
Because I'll be doing something awful tomorrow.
If you don't want to do it, then don't.
I have to do it no matter what I think.
And to be honest, I don't really feel that guilty.
And?
I just wanted to climb up to some high place.
In order to see the distant view.
You should just be honest
and say you're having a hard time.
I think I'm being very honest, though.
You should tell Haruki.
I'm sure she'll be happy about it.
And she'll have a better answer for you than I do.
The truth is, I didn't want to do that.
I'll bring cream puffs next time.
Come again sometime.
Seeing you vulnerable is quite entertaining.
It's not something to boast about,
but I am vulnerable for the most part.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
You're ten minutes early.
Is that so?
I'll be honest. I ate one takoyaki.
"One"? You mean, one food tray?
No, just one ball.
Who ate the rest?
Nonoh did.
You've been spending a lot
of time with other girls lately.
And tomorrow, I'll be seeing Murase.
I'm going with you.
Yeah. I'd be glad if you came along.
Also, this isn't a substitute for takoyaki, but...
What is this?
How did you...
Uh, I mean, thank you very much.
It doesn't look weird, does it?
Nah, I think it looks great.
I've got a favor to ask for tomorrow.
July 16th (Sunday)
There's something I need
to ask you no matter what.
Did the cat really get into an accident?
Who cares about that?
It's important.
It's more important than anything else.
There was an accident. The cat died.
Happy?
Yes.
I was thinking about becoming your ally.
Really?
However, let me test your ability.
If you pass the test, I'll follow your lead.
But if you can't pass it,
I'll have you take down the Bureau my way.
And what is this method of yours?
I'll have you come to school.
And you'll take school seriously,
graduate, then work for the Bureau.
After that, I'll give you one suggestion
after another for the correct method,
and you'll change the Bureau.
In the end, you're no different from Tsushima!
You're wrong. You just need to pass the test.
If you make me give up with your ability, you win.
Let's do this, then.
Haruki, save.
Save. It's July 16th, and the time is 11:48:17.
Bang.
Index fingernails. Human body.
Are you stupid?!
Knives are way scarier than this.
Right hand. Human body.
You'll lose your whole hand next!
That would be a problem.
Full body. Gravel!
The truth is, you didn't care about our abilities.
You just wanted us to reset to save your cat, right?
This has nothing to do with the cat!
Why did you decide to take it in, then?
Did you know that Minami Mirai died?
The girl who stole the MacGuffin?
She was killed by Hitsuuchi on Friday night.
Who was the one who brought
the MacGuffin yesterday?
The same Minami.
On Saturday at noon, we reset for the
second time after you attacked us.
You had no idea, right?
Why would I attack you guys?
You wanted us to reset Minami's death.
You thought that by attacking us,
we would reset for sure.
Lies! My ability can cancel out the effects of a reset!
If you don't wish for it, your ability won't activate.
You wanted a reset yourself.
You wanted to forget Minami Mirai's death.
I'm not that weak!
Full body. Human body.
Now, you can't even touch me!
The same goes for you.
If you touch me, I'll end up dead.
I don't care what happens to you!
Isn't this a fight to become allies?
Enough with this! I don't need allies!
Don't move.
Haruki.
Full body. Ability.
Don't you realize?
This is where you were standing when you saved.
You're wrong. You're two steps off.
If you reset, you'll appear two steps away from me.
I can attack you immediately after a reset!
I have just one thing to say.
What is it?
Haruki can't reset without my orders.
What the hell does that—
Murase...
It's okay to give up.
Ding-dong-ding-dong!
This is a message from this morning
that will be delivered on July 16th:
It's the message that you've
been waiting for from Asai Kei!
Haruki, reset.
Reset.
Second Time
Bang!
Sorry.
I don't remember anything.
I know. But I'm still sorry.
I give up.
That cat is getting along just fine.
He's taking a nap with Nonoh.
I was happy about the request to save the cat.
From the bottom of my heart, I thought,
"I really want to live doing this sort of thing."
Savings dogs, cats, and if possible, people as well.
From now on, let's work toward that.
On rainy days, let's share our umbrellas
with a person who's soaked.
If there's a puppy that's lost its way,
we can find its mother.
We can give milk to a starving cat.
We can even dress up like Santa
and hand out presents for Christmas.
Anyway, let's just do things
that will make us smile together.
Yeah...
It'd be nice to do that.
I'm sure things will go just fine,
just like it did for that cat.
It's okay. Enough time has already passed.
Next Episode
Marble World and Candy Resist
Congrats on your enrollment.
Hello. It's nice to meet you.
Do you like marbles?
It's like they're making fun of the world.
...said it was weird for me
to speak politely since we're classmates.
Because it's something I don't need.
Why are you crying?
I don't know!
We're always simply standing in a rain of eternal sadness
That is why I need that warmth of yours
Life is but a dream we never wake up from
We repeat it over and over, praying for salvation
I kept waiting endlessly for your signal
To make sure you wouldn't disappear all by yourself
Ah, it doesn't matter where I am or what I'm doing
My heart can't go against your will
So I'd follow you even to the ends of the world
I fell in love with you at the dawn of our new world
But we kept pushing the hand of the clock backwards
And lost not only time, but our smiles as well
You're the one who brought it back
And taught me that even lies can be meaningful