Thrall to LF-03.
Restarting Permet link connection test.
In three, two, one...
Interconnect established.
Currently on Layer 31.
Please commence calling.
Roger.
Calling Layer 31.
No abnormalities detected in GUND Format.
Connect to Layer 32.
Calling Layer 32.
Callback confirmed.
Connect to Layer 33.
Error. No callback.
Retreat to Layer 10.
Attempting to call Layer 33 again from Layer 10.
Error. No callback.
Calling Layer 33.
LF-03 to Thrall.
Requesting an increase to the GUND Format score.
Negative. That would go
against the test's objectives.
We don't have time. I'm executing it.
Hold it.
Elnora.
Let's wrap things up for today.
I haven't entered the danger zone yet.
Let me increase the level
and attempt to call Layer 33 aga—
The test ends here, Elnora.
Understood.
Test complete.
Start analyzing the Permet influx values.
Roger. Starting analysis.
Any abnormal fluctuations?
You're too eager.
Oh, Dr. Cardo.
If you can't clear it, then no one can.
We have to prove that the GUND Format
is safe as soon as we can.
If not, we're at the whims of the council.
It won't mean a thing if your body doesn't hold out.
But—
Besides, someone's here to pick you up.
Huh?
Mama!
Eri!
Mama! Papa's waiting!
Let's go eat cake!
I thought I told you not to come in here!
Is she still sleeping?
Yeah.
Fast asleep.
She's gonna get a spanking
if she doesn't wake up soon!
Lfrith is still an infant.
A baby?
Exactly. A newborn who can't even turn over.
Everyone here helped with her birth.
Right now, your mother is
teaching her all kinds of things.
Huh.
Then she's my little sister!
How old are you now, Eri?
Four!
As of the 20th, the Front 3rd Autonomous Sector
has approved a budget to purchase Gundam-type
mobile suits manufactured by Ochs Earth.
Ochs Earth's weapon system has raised major
concerns regarding bioethical issues for its pilots,
eliciting calls for accountability from the company,
as well as the Mobile Suit Development Council.
The GUND Format was originally constructive:
a medical technology meant to assist with physical
dysfunctions caused by the environment of space.
However, Vanadis Institute,
the project's lead researcher,
was bought out by Ochs Earth.
The GUND Format was then repurposed
for military mobile suits.
Its pilots, however, are regularly exposed
to data storms that wreak havoc on the body.
Imagine, if you will!
A gigantic frame 18 meters tall,
moving with inorganic mechanisms,
controlled by forcibly linking it to a human body.
The strain a pilot must bear is unfathomable.
The public fears an arms race,
as the buildup of mobile suits may prompt Earth
to expand their military, accelerating tensions—
They're sure saying all they want
about our products, huh.
Papa! I'm back!
Welcome back.
Looking good. Sorry for making you do all this.
It's nothing to apologize for.
Eri helped out, too.
I made that over there!
Amazing. It's beautiful!
Eri, why don't you go grab a party hat for Mama?
Okay!
Layer 33 again?
If I don't clear it soon,
we're all going to be in trouble.
I'm sorry.
This wouldn't've happened if the higher-ups
weren't in a rush to roll out Lfrith.
We got the sponsor we needed.
Thanks to you, Nadim.
I just hope the Council stays put until the deadline...
The press conference is in one hour.
This is it for Ochs Earth.
This is what happens when
Earthians get ahead of themselves.
Hopefully, it'll be as easy as you say.
We don't know if Dr. Cardo Nabo will comply.
Will it really go smoothly?
Is this not exceeding the capacity
of a private enterprise?
What are you worried about at this stage?
There's nothing wrong with overachieving.
We didn't ask for your opinion, Delling.
It'll be too late if we let Vanadis
complete their Gundam.
We, the Mobile Suit Development Council,
must come to a decision.
For the peace of all humanity...
we must purge the witch.
Cake! Cake! Yummy cake!
I'm putting the candle in now.
Oh?
Oopsie.
Mama?
Sorry about that. Give me a sec.
Mama's GUND always breaks.
I guess it does.
But without this tech,
Mama wouldn't be alive right now.
That's why Dr. Cardo is more than a mentor to me.
She's my savior.
The old granny's amazing!
Eri.
The doctor isn't the type
to mind what people call her.
Still, it's disrespectful.
HQ?
Eri, can you give your papa a minute?
Whaaat!
Papa has work.
Sorry, kiddo.
No fair!
I want papa now!
What's going on?
The Council is having a press conference.
But we should still have time!
It's Delling.
He's behind this.
The ex-military guy?
We don't know what they're trying to pull.
You guys watch out, too.
Folkvangr to transport ship Begavent. Control 173.
This is Begavent. Communicating with 173.
Distance to gate entrance, 22.
Trajectory confirmed.
Please enter Gate Three.
A ship's here.
Wendy, gimmie a hand with the cargo.
Tarrifs are way too high lately.
It's pissing me off.
They aren't gonna ship it for free, you know?
The Spacians are monopolizing trade to bits.
I'll make it worth your while.
Okay?
That's cheap.
Found it, Eri!
This one, right?
Eri?
Wake up already!
You make Papa and Mama worry all the time!
Even on my birthday!
That's unfortunate.
Granny?
You came here by yourself again?
Elnora must be tired of scolding you.
I guess...
Is she important to you too, Granny?
Indeed.
Why?
What about those two over there?
This one's special.
Special?
In order for you and your family
to continue living in space,
a suitable body is required.
Though not a weapon like this.
Lfrith embodies the future we envisioned for GUND.
A door to a new frontier
for all humanity.
I don't get it.
Then, do you want to try talking to her?
Come, Eri.
Try putting your hand there.
Lfrith recognizes you now, Eri.
Try telling her that there's nothing to fear.
Hello, my name is Ericht Samaya!
Do you like cake?
Today's my birthday!
I wore a party hat, too!
What's wrong?
The Council is holding a press conference.
Right this minute?
Ochs Earth was left out.
Got it. I'll be right there.
Eri, can you get back on your own?
Yeah.
Don't make you mother worry.
Okay.
The cake has strawberries on it.
Oh yeah, and Mama...
Ulysses is in position.
Ready at your command.
Raid everything,
including the headquarters as planned.
Has the Council approved?
Leave that to me.
We, the Mobile Suit Development Committee,
hereby announce that we have decided
to freeze the development of
all Gundam-type mobile suits.
Furthermore, the Council will forcibly seize
the company that developed them, Ochs Earth,
which acted under the authority
of business administrative laws.
Ridiculous.
We're the scapegoats?
Any ships scheduled to dock?
There's one transport ship.
Stop them.
Don't let them in!
In order to protect the order
and the ethics of mobile suit development,
we have decided to establish
an auditing organization, Cathedral.
Allow me to introduce
the supervising head of Cathedral.
Mr. Delling Rembran.
The acquisition was a sham!
Money was never on the table. They intended to use forc—
Yamaoka!
Dammit!
Those narrow-minded Spacians...
Elnora?
Eri?
HQ to all Dominicus units.
You are to seal off the Folkvangr's
surroundings immediately.
Not a single shuttle may escape.
Nyla?
Wendy, run for it.
Now!
Nyla!
The alarm?
Elnora!
The Council crossed the line.
I can't find Eri!
She's missing?
You go get Eri.
I'll sortie a Lfrith.
It's too dangerous!
It's all over if the enemy gets here!
Trust in the GUND-ARMs that you guys made.
Are you sortieing, Manager?
I can't reach Wendy.
I'll slow them down.
Secure us an escape route in the meantime.
Will we see reinforcements from HQ?
Don't get your hopes up.
LF-01, launching!
GUND Format Permet score Two!
Identification matches target mobile suit.
Roger. Commencing mission.
It's fast!
This must be a Gundam!
Permet score Three!
He dodged it?!
Impossible!
Sure has been a while, yeah?
The target is using peculiar swarming weapons.
Don't go in alone.
Wendy, is that you?
I have to avenge Nyla!
I see.
I'll lure the enemy away.
Second Gundam-type mobile suit
detected at port side in our travel path.
That matches our intel.
Keep your guards up.
Kenanji.
Deploy Beguir-Beu.
Roger.
Throughout my experience on countless battlefields,
I have arrived at but one conclusion...
Weapons only exist to kill others.
There is not a single excuse for them.
The simple act of holding a weapon for killing
is a sin in and of itself.
However, the mobile suits made by
Vanadis and Ochs Earth go a step further!
They take the lives of both the pilot and adversary!
They serve not as tools, but as a curse on us all.
Wendy!
Don't raise your score any higher!
The punishment for taking a life
must be administered by humans, not machines.
Lyla, I'll avenge you!
People must be killed by people.
We should at least be allowed this dignity
in the foolish act called war!
Get back, Wendy!
That custom unit is serious business!
Why can't I move?!
GUND Format Link suppressed.
So begins the end of the Gundams.
Nyla.
Wendy!
We must pull the trigger ourselves
to understand the value of the life we take
and the weight of our unforgivable sin.
Lest we forget what it means to wage war
and kill human beings!
Dr. Cardo Nabo.
Your life ends here.
Humanity, born in the cradle of Earth,
is far too fragile to venture beyond.
Like the way one clothes a newborn babe,
it is only by donning the GUND
that we may survive out in space.
That's just an excuse for a
technology that demands sacrifice.
You understand nothing.
When you lot plunder GUND,
you snuff out our own future!
Eri!
Mama!
Mama! Mama! Mama!
It's okay now.
Everything's okay.
HQ to all units.
We've successfully neutralized
Cardo Nabo and all key members.
Retreat as soon as preparations to
detonate the front are complete.
I repeat, HQ to all units.
Doctor...
Why did you have to die?
We've successfully neutralized
Cardo Nabo and all key members.
Mama?
Retreat as soon as preparations to
detonate the front are complete.
A callback from Layer 33?
Whose vitals were used to authenticate...?
Mama.
Did she wake up?
Powerful electromagnetic waves
detected within Folkvangr.
It's an unregistered Permet ID.
There was another one?
One, two, three!
Mama, Mama!
They're pretty, like candles!
They are.
You've got skills, but...
You're still just a Gundam!
Elnora, is that you?
Nadim?
Papa!
Dammit! Let go of me, Gundam!
Elnora, you need to escape.
Don't you dare! I'm goi—
You're not escaping alone!
Please survive.
For your sake, for Ericht's sake, for everyone's!
I love you, Nadim.
I love you too, Elnora.
Permet score Four!
Papa! I'm back!
Welcome back.
Papa, what's a birthday?
It's a day where we celebrate the day you were born, Eri.
How do we celebrate?
Hmm...
Happy birthday to you.
It's Papa!
Cut this channel.
We can't. The source is thought to be the Gundam.
Happy birthday dear Ericht.
What's going on?
Happy birthday to you!
Thus,
we, Cathedral,
hereby repudiate
all Gundams.