Building No. 2 - The Twins' Homework
...Delivery!
Honey?!
As I'm playing a horror game, I sense...
a presence!
Stare...
Anna!
Huh?
Stare...
Is someone peeking?
Is that you, Haruki?!
Hey!
Oh, Uzuki, Satsuki.
What are you two doing?
What's this?
Yayoi-oneechan's bras are
padded inside.
Just kidding.
Actually, her favorite color
is pink so she
has lots of pink underwear.
Yayoi-oneechan's bras are
padded inside.
Just kidding.
Actually, her favorite color
is pink so she
has lots of pink underwear.
Yayoi-oneechan's bras are
padded inside.
Just kidding.
Actually, her favorite color
is pink so she
has lots of pink underwear.
Yayoi-oneechan's bras are
padded inside.
Just kidding.
Actually, her favorite color
is pink so she
has lots of pink underwear.
Yayoi-oneechan's bras are
padded inside.
Just kidding.
Actually, her favorite color
is pink so she
has lots of pink underwear.
Yayoi-oneechan's bras are
padded inside.
Just kidding.
Actually, her favorite color
is pink so she
has lots of pink underwear.
Yayoi-oneechan's bras are
padded inside.
Just kidding.
Actually, her favorite color
is pink so she
has lots of pink underwear.
Yayoi-oneechan's bras are
padded inside.
Just kidding.
Actually, her favorite color
is pink so she
has lots of pink underwear.
Yayoi-oneechan's bras are
padded inside.
Just kidding.
Actually, her favorite color
is pink so she
has lots of pink underwear.
Yayoi-oneechan's bras are
padded inside.
Just kidding.
Actually, her favorite color
is pink so she
has lots of pink underwear.
Yayoi-oneechan's bras are
padded inside.
Just kidding.
Actually, her favorite color
is pink so she
has lots of pink underwear.
"Yayoi-oneechan's bras are... padded inside."
Hey! Why are you writing this down?!
Yayoi, what's all the commotion about?
Mutsuki-nee! Uzuki and Satsuki are—
Step
We're doing our homework!
Work!
Our homework is to write about our family.
That's why we're watching everyone.
Don't tell me you're just writing
whatever you want about us.
We're still collecting ideas for it!
For it.
You don't have to make us
sound interesting, you know.
Aww...
Just give it your best.
Okay!
We'll say what we're gonna write out loud.
Please listen!
Okay.
Let's see...
My brother Haruki
is the only boy in our family.
He's glued to his games and never exercises
and is a really big scaredy cat—
Stop right there!
Write some cooler things about me!
Cooler things?
An evil god is sealed within my right arm!
I must not allow it to reawaken!
...is something he yells every now and then
because he's trying to save the world!
I think that's really cool!
Stop! No more!
Next up is Yayoi-oneechan!
She's really good at sports,
and she's the ace of the basketball team!
But she's also really violent.
I think it's bad that she'll
just suddenly hit Haruki.
But it's probably her way of showing affection.
Basically, she's a tsundere.
If only she was more honest—
The two of them get along well.
Yup.
And finally, Mutsuki-oneechan!
Slim
Curvy
She's perfect to the point where
any girl would be jealous of her.
Curvy
She can be a little scary sometimes,
but she's actually really nice.
And she's also really good at cooking,
sports, and studying!
She's my role model!
I love my family a lot.
I'm done!
Me too.
We're home!
Home!
Our essays got full marks!
Marks!
That's great.
Sounds like a wonderful family.
But what is your
brother fighting against?
What exactly is this evil god?
Sounds like a wonderful family.
But what is your
brother fighting against?
What exactly is this evil god?
Sounds like a wonderful family.
But what is your
brother fighting against?
What exactly is this evil god?
Sounds like a wonderful family.
But what is your
brother fighting against?
What exactly is this evil god?
Sounds like a wonderful family.
But what is your
brother fighting against?
What exactly is this evil god?
Sounds like a wonderful family.
But what is your
brother fighting against?
What exactly is this evil god?
Sounds like a wonderful family.
But what is your
brother fighting against?
What exactly is this evil god?
Sounds like a wonderful family.
But what is your
brother fighting against?
What exactly is this evil god?
Sounds like a wonderful family.
But what is your
brother fighting against?
What exactly is this evil god?
Sounds like a wonderful family.
But what is your
brother fighting against?
What exactly is this evil god?
"Sounds like a wonderful family.
But what is your brother fighting against?
What exactly is this evil god?"
We forgot to erase it.
Everyone at school really liked you.
arigatou arigatou mainichi arigatou
I'll tell you thank you every day
otome no kokoro e tanoshiku akaruku
The road to growing up is filled with fun
arigatou arigatou sekai no minna ni
Though I want everyone to know that I'm grateful
otome no hajirai choppiri itazura
I act childish to hide how shy I really am
I'm Nakano Mutsuki.
Building No. 3 - Mutsuki's True Self
Building No. 3 - Mutsuki's True Self.
Look forward to it!
Building No. 3 - Mutsuki's True Self