Building No. 11 - Yayoi the Caretaker?!
Don't just leave me here...
What are you doing at this hour—
I can't... move.
Are you sick?
I think so...
I got up to go to the bathroom,
but then I didn't feel too well.
Now I can't make it back.
I can't believe you.
Here, have my pillow.
Good night.
Thanks for bringing me back to my room.
Not like I had much of a choice.
You have school tomorrow, right?
I'm fine now, so you should head back to bed.
Okay...
Good morning!
Morning!
Good morning.
Go wash your faces, you two.
Huh? Haruki's not here?
Here?
He caught a cold even though he's an idiot.
I can tell you're lonely
without him sitting next to you!
You!
I-I'm not!
Haruki!
Give me a call if you need anything, okay?
Sounds like they've left.
Honey, why are you wearing
a maid outfit, pray tell?
There's a perfectly legitimate
reason for this, you see...
What?!
Why is the guy next door wearing one?!
Well?! What's the story?!
Uh oh, I need to use the bathroom.
B-But my body refuses to move...
I don't need to use the bathroom...
I don't need to use the bathroom!
I really hope I don't wet my bed.
Hm? Yayoi...
Don't wake up without warning!
Your yelling is making my head spin.
What time is it?
It's already past three.
You skipped out on your club activities?
It just happened to be an off day.
It makes me happy
to see you back so soon.
U-Um...
Can you take me to the bathroom?
Occupied
S-Sorry to make you do this...
It's no big deal.
The others aren't back yet,
so it's just going to be me looking after you.
You just need to rest.
Wh-What are you doing?!
I-I was going to wipe away your sweat!
Your cold will only worsen
if you're drenched in it.
I'll do it myself!
Wait, I just need to do your back.
We're home!
Home!
Haruki? Yayoi?
They're kissing!
Kissing!
Don't be stupid! You're mistaken!
They kissed!
Yayoi, you mustn't kiss someone with a cold!
Kissed!
You've got it all wrong!
They kissed! They kissed! They kissed!
I can't do this... I'm at my limit.
ashita no koto wa wakaranai kedo
We don't know what tomorrow will bring
kyou wa kitto ii hi ni shiyou
So let's try to make today a good day too
Don't wanna.
Building No. 12 - Haruki's Bond With His Sisters
Building No. 12 - Haruki's Bond With His Sisters.