This nonstop rain is depressing...
Morning, Ohta.
Oh, morning, Tanaka.
Man, the rain makes it so humid. It's killing me.
I don't think humidity's the problem here.
You're absolutely drenched.
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
After school I sit next to a window
And the spring breeze entices me to sleep
So I shut an eye against the dazzling world
While the sun makes the scenery dance upon my eyelids
I whistle vaguely at the blue sky
And I get more of a spring in my step
I remove my earphones in a bustling corner of the city
And look into the distance, where I hear a voice
Let's bask in the glowing sun
Ever so gently
Starting another day as usual
Napping in the sunshine
In this cozy place with you
With all these feelings booming in my heart
Episode 6
The Sick Tanaka-kun
My sister told me to take an umbrella
because there was an 80% chance of rain.
So I left home with one...
It won't be necessary for this amount of rain.
It wasn't raining very hard when I left the house.
But with every passing moment...
I'll make it.
And before I knew it, it was raining cats and dogs.
Your umbrella must've felt miserable,
being so close, yet unable to fulfill its duty.
I don't really like umbrellas to begin with.
My hands get wet every time I open or close them.
There's no place to put them on buses and trains.
Also, I tend to forget them somewhere,
and I have to buy a new one every time.
Well, I guess they can be a pain,
but I think they're generally useful tools.
If you think back, I'm sure there have been
several occasions where they've helped you.
Helped me...
Oh, yeah...
One day, when I had nothing to lean against,
the umbrella supported me firmly as a cane.
I could hear the umbrella's
pride shattering just now.
It sure is pouring.
I know it's cliché,
but how nice would it be to share
an umbrella with the person you love?
Oh, gosh... I'm thinking about it so much,
it's starting to look like he's actually there.
A soaking wet Tanaka-kun...
That's actually him!
T-Tanaka-kun, what are you doing?!
Tanaka!
You disappeared on me!
What are you doing out here?
The bodies of insects and birds
conveniently evolve to keep them safe, right?
So I thought, if I kept standing out
in the rain like that, I might...
Tanaka has acquired the
special ability "Rain Barrier"!
...be able to achieve a very
convenient constitution, too.
If mankind had that kind of latent potential,
it would've been unlocked
long ago by our ancestors,
who survived the age before umbrellas.
In any case, your hatred for umbrellas
runs a lot deeper than I thought.
Well, they're such a pain.
I see now.
He was talking about a "rain barrier"
because he doesn't want to use an umbrella.
Using an umbrella might be bothersome,
but if you catch a cold from
being wet, you'll feel worse,
and that could be even more bothersome.
That's a good point.
Okay, I'll use my umbrella properly.
You're serious, Tanaka?
Nice job, Shiraishi!
Y-Yeah... I'm glad.
I just remembered another thing
I hate about umbrellas...
People always grab mine
and take it home by mistake.
I go in a different direction from here,
so could you take over, Shiraishi?
B-But... I...
God, Buddha, Ohta-sama...
Shiraishi-san, can I scoot closer to you?
No...
I'm afraid any closer might be bad
for my heart, so that's no good!
Okay...
This is awful...
I panicked and rejected him flat-out.
But...
Being this close is more than enough for me.
My shoulder's freezing...
I want to move further under the umbrella...
Morning.
This again?
You realized too late that it was a downpour?
What happened to your resolve from yesterday?
No...
With today's rain, I thought if I just
dodged between the raindrops,
I could make it here without getting wet.
But it was beyond my capabilities.
I must train in either Iga or Koga, or perhaps...
It's about 500 times easier to just use an umbrella.
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun Is Always Listless
Whoa, that's awful, Tanaka.
I barely recognized you.
Master...
Morning. What's up?
Morning, Ohta...
You sound terrible. Are you sick?
Seems like it...
Master! Master!
U-Um, are you okay, Tanaka-kun?
Is it because you were out in the rain?
Master! Master!
My throat hurts a little, that's all.
You gave me good advice,
and I still got sick. I'm sorry.
Don't worry about that.
I'll take you to the nurse's office
if you're not feeling well.
Thanks, but I'm fine.
I don't want you to catch it,
so you'd best stay away.
If you start feeling really bad,
I'll take you to the nurse's office.
Everyone spaces out when they're sick.
Tanaka is sluggish to begin with,
so he'll probably move even slower.
I'd better keep an eye on him...
A-Are you okay, Tanaka?!
His movements are actually more violent than usual.
I feel as though my strength is
gradually depleting against my will...
You can't do anything about
those coughs that crawl up on you.
Judging by your voice,
it's really taking a toll on your throat.
You should try to avoid talking
so it doesn't get worse.
But if you can't speak,
I wonder how we should communicate...
That won't be a problem...
Huh?
What?
Between you and me,
lip reading should suffice.
Tanaka, do you know which part
of your body that mask is covering?
Lip reading is difficult, so let's
communicate through writing.
Okay.
Such tiny handwriting...
Wait, is this kanji right?
Sorry, could you hang on a sec, Tanaka?
I'll look it up real quick. Let's see...
You can just talk
normally, you know.
Oh, no, Ohta. I forgot
my Japanese History textbook.
Seriously?
Why don't you ask Echizen in the class
next door if you can borrow hers?
Oh, no, Ohta. I forgot
my Japanese History textbook.
Someone else,
if possible...
But we don't know anyone in
the other classes except Echizen...
... True.
Oh, hey, Tanaka. What's up?
The name "Echizen" takes so much
time to write. What a pain.
What are you doing?
You should change
your surname to
"Ohta" or "Tanaka"
A proposal from you?
Not in 1oo years!
-Echizen
A proposal from you?
Not in 1oo years!
-Echizen
How did a conversation about
a Japanese History textbook lead to that?
A proposal from you?
Not in 1oo years!
-Echizen
A proposal from you?
Not in 1oo years!
-Echizen
A proposal from you?
Not in 1oo years!
-Echizen
No idea...
A proposal from you?
If communicating through writing
is too hard, we could try gesturing.
In this case, my comprehension skill
will be vital to understanding you...
Try something so we can practice, Tanaka.
Tired.
Sleepy.
It's working pretty well. Nice, Ohta.
Yeah, this is going great.
It's easier than I expected.
Won't you need a method to convey
other messages besides those two?
Is he trying to awaken a new ability
again because he's too lazy to talk?!
Tanaka has acquired the
psychic ability "Telepathy"!
It's easier to just talk, so I'll talk...
I-I see... So you gave up on telepathy.
Huh?
Tanaka... Is it just me or is your
skin more radiant than usual?
I've been wearing a mask, so my breath
must have moisturized my skin...
I see. That's an unexpected effect.
Also, I actually figured out a new game
I can play while wearing a mask.
It's quite fun.
Oh?
I guess you discover new things
when in unusual circumstances.
I'm glad you were able to get
something out of being sick.
Morning, Tanaka.
Oh, good.
You're not wearing a mask,
so I assume you're feeling better?
Yeah. Morning, Ohta.
What's wrong, Tanaka?
Your usual listlessness is gone.
Are you coming down with
something other than a cold now?
Oh, yeah... I'm not wearing a mask...
Whoops...
Lately, I've been making weird faces
under the mask where no one could see,
so my facial muscles have become more active.
My cold might be gone,
but I'm going to wear the mask today, too.
Well, um... It's nice to see
that side of you now and then...
It might take a few more days
for him to completely return to normal.
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
The power of a common cold is frightening...
What should I do? I had no idea!
You should change
your surname to
"Ohta" or "Tanaka"
Is it going to be me or Ohta? It's your choice.
To think... Those two love me so much,
they actually want to marry me!
Tanaka didn't seem like
he was interested in me at all.
If anything, he seemed to think I was an annoyance...
And Ohta is a childhood friend.
It's too late for me to see him as a man.
I just can't!
Who's that?
That long skirt...
Is it you, Echizen-san? What are you doing?
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
Sorry, but a "no fighting" decree
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
has been issued this week in the Tanaka Kingdom.
No Fighting
Decree
Tanaka
Wha— No!
I'm not gonna fight. I'm a girl.
Oh, so you've changed your mind, Echizen?
I hope we don't have heavy snow tomorrow...
Does that mean you like me just the way I am?
That reminds me.
Echizen, I've been thinking...
If you want to challenge Tanaka again,
how about a thumb wrestle?
It's peaceful, but determining the winner is simple.
Good idea. It's like the epitome
of an energy-saving match.
Right? It requires technique more than strength.
B-But...
If Ohta or Tanaka were to grab my hand now...
I caught you.
I'll... I'll...
I'll die from my heart bursting!
Is thumb wrestling that
life-threatening in delinquent society?
To think Ohta and Tanaka,
two guys who are polar opposites,
would propose to me...
Which type is the best fit for me?
Kind
Reliable
Will probably
treat me like
a girl
Will probably
treat me like
a girl
Echizen, I...
Don't treat me like a girl!
Beats him up out of embarrassment
Listless
Unreliable
Not even sure
if he'll treat me
like a human
Not even sure
if he'll treat me
like a human
Echizen-san...
Treat me more like a wife!
Beats him up out of sheer anger
I have no choice but to change myself...
I can... I can do it...
I can be a normal girl...
E-E-Ecchan?! What are you doing?!
You scared me.
You can't do that, Ecchan.
This skirt is important to you.
Myaano...
That's right...
If my surname changes,
Myaano will have to call me by a different name...
M-Myaano...
If my surname changed to Tanaka
or Ohta, what would you call me?
Um... It's Ecchan because you're Echizen,
so if you're Tanaka, you'll be Tacchan.
If you're Ohta, you'll be...
Occhan?
No...
I can't handle Myaano calling me
the same thing people call old men!
I guess it's Tanaka, then...
Speak of the devil! There's Master!
Master! How are you feeling?!
I'm feeling very energetic!
Yeah, I can see that.
Also, I'm pretty much never energetic.
Myaano is small, so her height
difference with Tanaka works well.
I'm nearly the same height as Tanaka,
so I wouldn't look cute next to him...
I wish I were short and cute like Myaano...
Why?! Ecchan, you look so cool and gorgeous!
I admire people who are tall and strong, too.
Huh?!
R-R-Really?
It's n-not like h-hearing that
makes me h-happy or a-anything...
Wh-Wh-What's wrong, Ecchan?
You're stuttering like crazy!
In fact, I'd like her to aim for Ohta's level...
I see.
I guess I don't need to be concerned about height.
Watch out!
Are you okay, Echizen?
What is this sense of safety?
I fit perfectly in his arms...
His hands are so big...
Wait, isn't his face kinda close?
This body temperature or whatever
it is I'm feeling can't be good...
Echizen!
Why'd you run off without any warning?
Here, grab my hand.
Don't... This is nothing—
Ow...
Don't try to move so much.
What if you have a sprained ankle?
P-Put me down! Put me down right now!
Hey, Echizen! Stop flailing!
Are you okay?
Seriously, what's gotten into you, Echizen?
You're acting strange today.
Did you eat something weird?
I-It's because...
Y-You guys asked me to
use either Ohta's or Tanaka's name!
Hold on, Echizen. What are you talking about?
Huh?! You're gonna play dumb
after asking me something that important?!
Sorry, I seriously don't know. Please enlighten me.
You bastard! You're making a girl say it?!
A man should be more assertive!
If you do, I'll obey and follow you...
She's surprisingly old-fashioned...
Ohta or Tanaka...
Echizen-san, are you talking about
what I wrote when I was sick?
You should change
your surname to
"Ohta" or "Tanaka"
You should change
your surname to
"Ohta" or "Tanaka"
You should change
your surname to
"Ohta" or "Tanaka"
Y-Yeah, that!
You just popped that out of nowhere!
I see... You've been concerned over
something like that all this time?
Oh, I shouldn't call it "something like that." Sorry.
A-As long as we understand each other, it's fine...
I'm truly sorry I disrespected your precious surname
just because it has so many strokes
that I was too lazy to write it.
Huh?
So that's what happened.
Yeah.
So I thought it'd be easier if you changed your name
to something easier to write, like Ohta or Tanaka.
I had no idea you were
that fond of your own surname.
I apologize.
So...
Is he telling me he was just too lazy to write it?
Don't worry.
"Echizen" isn't so bothersome
to write when I'm not sick.
Yeah, Echizen. Tanaka was sick that day.
Please forgive him.
It wasn't a marriage proposal at all...
I just had the wrong idea about everything?!
Echizen is a good surname.
Don't say such damn misleading things!
Oh, there's a simpler way
of referring to her without
having her change her name.
Yeah.
Ecchan.
Wha—
I see. "Ecchan."
It's easier to say out loud, too. "Ecchan."
S-Stop that! Don't repeat it!
Ecchan, my mom said to come visit us sometime.
Ecchan. It has a nice ring to it. Ecchan.
Ecchan.
Everyday life is like a bothersome cat
How I wish I could ignore it and do as I please
I discreetly retreat into my own world of music
Maybe I have a talent for daydreaming
That so-called happiness
What exactly is it?
I tried acting on my own desires
Will I understand it now?
Dramatic listlessness
I want to put my life into its hands
Maybe a positive attitude is better
Is trying my best the right thing to do?
I can't hold a poker face
Everyday life makes me dizzy
My dear listlessness
Once more
It's Valentine's Day!
Was it you?
Huh?
Are you the culprit?
It's Lady Macarons!
Thank you for always
taking care of my brother.
Next time, Episode 7:
Next Episode
Tanaka
Tanaka-kun's Valentine.