Cultural Festival
Haunted House
Regarding our attraction
for the cultural festival,
Haunted House
based on the results
of the committee meeting,
our class, 1-F, will be doing
the haunted house as we requested.
Hell yeah!
Every class wanted the haunted house!
We would like to assign tasks now,
so please write your name on
the board if you see one you want.
Which one do you want?
What do you wanna do, Kicchan?
The cultural festival's a school event
that gets everyone especially excited.
There'll be lots of food stands, too.
I can't wait. How about you, Tanaka?
He's erasing all traces of his presence!
The cultural festival...
A time when the entire school is enveloped
in mysterious, youthful energy,
from preparation to the actual event.
The one ranked #1 on the list of school events
that I don't want to participate in, right?
So that's what a cultural festival means to you?
Yeah.
That's why, to avoid having
to do any troublesome work,
I've been training hard to conceal my presence,
for the past two weeks.
Two whole weeks?
Talk about dedicated.
If people with motivation take on all the work,
there shouldn't be anything for me to do.
Haunted
House
Tanaka-kun, Ohta-kun.
Haunted
House
Ghosts
Haunted
House
Ghosts
Haunted
House
Ghosts
Haunted
House
Ghosts
Haunted
House
Ghosts
Haunted
House
Ghosts
Yamane
Haunted
House
Ghosts
Yamane
Haunted
House
Ghosts
Endou
Yamane
Haunted
House
Ghosts
Chihara
Endou
Yamane
Haunted
House
Ghosts
Chihara
Endou
Yamane
Haunted
House
Ghosts
Chihara
Endou
Yamane
Haunted
House
Ghosts
Chihara
Endou
Yamane
Ghosts
Chihara
Endou
Yamane
The only roles left are for ghosts,
Ghosts
Chihara
Endou
Yamane
Ghosts
Chihara
Endou
Yamane
Ghosts
Chihara
Endou
Yamane
Chihara
Endou
Yamane
Chihara
Endou
Ghosts
so we'll leave those to you, okay?
Sorry! Everyone's so excited,
all the other tasks filled up right away.
We got the starring role.
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
After school I sit next to a window
And the spring breeze entices me to sleep
So I shut an eye against the dazzling world
While the sun makes the scenery dance upon my eyelids
I whistle vaguely at the blue sky
And I get more of a spring in my step
I remove my earphones in a bustling corner of the city
And look into the distance, where I hear a voice
Let's bask in the glowing sun
Ever so gently
Starting another day as usual
Napping in the sunshine
In this cozy place with you
With all these feelings booming in my heart
Episode 11
Tanaka-kun's
Cultural Festival
All right everyone, we're gonna give it
our all to scare the crap out of them!
Yeah!
I'll do my best to make scary ghost props!
We're counting on you.
Katou and Shimura,
construction's probably going to be tough,
but good luck.
Just leave it to us.
The layout for the haunted house is done,
so let's have a meeting!
Got it.
I wanna go home...
So I'm playing the role of ghost...
I'm not too confident in my acting skills.
I hope it works out.
You'll be fine!
Don't be so tense. Let's just have fun!
He's right, Ohta-kun!
You'll be fine!
Oh, right...
You think so?
This is the perfect situation
to make use of my training,
Why are you so worried?
Ohta! We need you to be strong!
and fade out.
But...
Look at Tanaka!
He has no presence at all, just like a real ghost!
Amazing, Tanaka!
You've already practiced for this?!
Just what I'd expect from Master!
You're totally gonna kill it!
What do I do now, Ohta?
My training has backfired on me...
At this point, you might as well just dive in.
As long as you belong to a class,
you have to take on some kind of work.
Besides, take a look, Tanaka.
I brought all the black curtains I could find!
We don't have enough paint.
Can someone go buy more?
Yeah. I've already asked the teacher
about that, so we're fine.
Playing a ghost might be
easier than the other jobs.
Now that you mention it...
I see...
Now that I know I got the easiest task,
I'm beginning to think I might be able
to sort of, maybe try my best.
Can't you just say you'll try your best?
Having an actual
out-of-body experience
so only my spirit has to participate
might not be a bad idea.
My body could relax at home,
and it'd be perfect for the haunted house.
Ohta...
Uh, just do the best you can
in your living body, okay?
Tanaka, you're good at hiding your presence,
so you can jump out suddenly to scare people.
Okay.
Let's try a simulation.
It'll look something like this...
Tanaka, you stand there.
Whoa, this is scary...
Tanaka, he's here! The customer is here!
You're here already? What a surprise...
Welcome.
He's the one who's surprised,
and he gave me a warm welcome...
Um...
Urashimaya?
Wrong line! I'm not Urashima Taro at Ryugu-jo!
He's no good at anything
other than hiding his presence.
How about a ghost inside a well?
When a customer walks by,
the lighting crew can put a spotlight on him.
He can just sit there!
Well (temporary)
Looking good.
This will be your post, Master!
What's wrong, Ohta?
I'm concerned.
If we use this setup, I'm afraid...
It'll be fine. You're such a worrywart, Ohta.
Okay, I'll turn on the spotlight!
...Tanaka will fall asleep.
What the—?!
Whoa, that was fast!
It's dark, cramped,
and there's no one else around.
Those are ideal conditions
for his sleeping spots.
We have no choice.
Eyelid eyes!
Now Tanaka can do his job even while he's asleep.
This might make people laugh
after the surprise wears off, though.
This is the first thing they'll see when they walk in,
so something that's just
typically scary might be better.
Huh? Sorry.
Did I fall asleep?
What the heck? That's really scary!
Nice, Tanaka!
Next, we'll use this.
Hands popping out from an old shoji door!
That sounds fun! I wanna try!
Even when you know it's coming, it's quite a shock.
This is something even I can do.
How's this?
Uh...
Yeah...
Your default setting is a little high.
Huh?
Unfortunately, your hands are outside
the average person's field of vision.
You're so tall...
No good, huh?
Tanaka-kun!
I borrowed this costume from the drama club.
Can you try it on?
'Kay...
There.
Oh, good. The size looks about right.
Since you're a ghost,
should it be right-over-left instead,
to indicate you're wearing a burial kimono?
You know, for realism's sake.
I see...
Like this?
He just naturally, so naturally,
exposed his bare body!
It's okay! He was wearing underwear!
He was wearing underwear!
Is this right?
Uh... Yeah...
I ended up being left with the most
important part, the grand finale.
I wonder if I can handle it...
Wow, that's amazing.
You look very imposing, so you'll do fine.
Yo.
Echizen...
I heard 1-F is doing a haunted house.
Let me guess, you guys are playing the ghosts?
You're both more into this than you look.
Essan! Ya finish the sign?
Yeah, it's drying right now! I'll bring it later!
Got it!
I'm glad...
Echizen-san, you have friends
other than Miyano-san.
Yeah. I thought you were
the lone wolf in your class.
C-Cut it out!
Don't gimme that look like I'm
your damn kid or something!
Heave!
Ho!
Whew...
All right!
All done!
It looks just like the real deal!
Great work, Katou-kun and Shimura-kun.
Oh, don't mention it.
To me, this is nothing.
It's all thanks to everyone's hard work!
Room of Terror
Let's bring some people in for a rehearsal!
Ghost crew, please stand by!
A bath...
A bath.
It literally just looks like a bath.
It's pretty comfortable.
N-No problems here...
Scary!
Why are you getting scared by this?
Okay, all that's left is Ohta's grand finale.
I present the construction
crew's pièce de résistance.
Behold!
The main stage of 1-F's haunted house!
Isn't it awesome?! Isn't it terrifying?!
Ohta, you'll lie in wait right here,
and when someone comes close, move suddenly!
Yep. People will think you're all tied up,
but then you start chasing them
out of the blue, taking them by surprise!
Amazing! It's like a real haunted house!
Exit
Okay, let's start bringing customers in.
Ghost crew, we'll be counting on you!
What's wrong, Ohta? Why did you come out?
We're gonna rehearse,
so you need to get back to your post.
I'm sorry...
I couldn't say it,
but I'm actually...
terrified of ghosts.
With that face?!
Tanaka-kun Is Always Listless
Th-Then why did you agree to play a ghost?
You should've told us.
I felt bad that someone would have to
take my place for my own selfish reasons...
And honestly, I thought a
cultural festival haunted house
would look more fantasy-like,
so it wouldn't bother me.
I was too naïve.
My knees are actually weak just from
walking through it to get out here.
With that face?!
Takoyaki
Ohta can't do this, then!
What should we do for the grand finale?
Takoyaki
The festival is tomorrow...
I understand.
I'll resolve this one way or another.
Cultural Festival
~ Grab! The Light of Youth!! ~
Wait, Essan!
I can't! I can't do this anymore!
C-Calm down. We're almost at the exit!
Look there...
I'm a cat girl demon!
I'll curse you all!
Y... Y...
You're waaay too cute, Myaano!
She's so cute!
Send me that picture later?
What's going on?!
The harder I try, the more people smile!
I think people are enjoying our new type
of haunted house with comic relief at the end.
All's well that ends well, I guess!
Reception
Ohta-kun!
How's the reception work going?
No problems here.
I'm so grateful to Miyano for taking my place.
Hey, we're having people
fill out a survey after they exit,
and they voted Tanaka-kun the scariest.
Seriously? That's amazing!
I see... I won't be able to see him
at work since I can't go in there,
but Tanaka must be working
extra hard to make up for me.
Yeah. We should support him in any way we can!
1-F Haunted House
On break!
Will be resuming at 13:30
Okay, let's take a one-hour break!
On break!
We'll resume at 13:30. Don't be late, everyone!
What do you wanna eat?
I heard there's a crêpe stand.
Wanna go?
Where's Tanaka?
Tanaka!
We're locking up the classroom, so come on out!
We're taking a break until 13:30.
If you wanna check out the
food stands, now's the time.
Welcome!
They expect me to take
a break with all this ruckus?
First things first. I should find Ohta
and have him take me somewhere quiet.
Sorry, Ohta-kun,
but the decoration fell from up there...
Oh, leave it to me.
Ohta, can you give us a hand, too?
Yeah, sure.
Looks like this is a bad time...
Oh, well.
I guess I'll have to find
someplace to rest on my own.
Please? Can you take my place for just 30 minutes?
Maid Café
Caramel Ribbon
I really want to see the drama club's play!
Maid Café
Caramel Ribbon
Jeez, fine...
Only for 30 minutes, though!
Thanks!
Welcome to Caramel Ribbon!
Will it be a table for one, sir?
Go home...
Go home! Forget everything you just saw!
Essan, calm down!
It's a ghost!
How scary!
Whoops...
It's too late now,
but this costume makes me stand out.
I should probably hide somewhere.
Ow.
Tanaka isn't back yet...
Yeah.
Sorry. I wasn't watching him.
However!
I already accounted for such a possibility.
Katou! Go change!
Roger!
Yay, I get to be a ghost!
You arranged for a replacement?
Talk about thorough.
I didn't anticipate needing one for you, though...
Sorry...
Reporting a lost child.
A little boy about three years old,
wearing a blue T-shirt,
is waiting in the faculty room.
If you have any information on this boy,
please come to the faculty room.
Ohta, can you go retrieve Tanaka before
they make an announcement about him?
If people find out our ghost is lost in the school,
our haunted house's beautiful,
hard-earned reputation's gonna tank.
You're right... I'll go now.
So many people everywhere, as I expected.
This crowd density will tire
Tanaka out in two seconds flat.
Shaved Ice
Melon
I'd better find him quick.
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Shaved Ice
Melon
Strawberry
Tanaka!
I'm coming...
to save you!
Do not use the rooftop
during the cultural festival
No good...
I came all the way here as my last hope.
This world no longer has any place
where I can rest in peace.
Black Curtains
Store in chemistry room
Nice...
This is taking longer than I thought.
I didn't expect to encounter so many temptations.
Hey, Tanaka! If you're here, answer me!
Tanaka?
Tanaka?!
O...
Oh...
Ohh...
Ohhhtaaa...
Huh?
Hey, Ohta...
What's wrong? Are you okay?
It looks like Ohta's in trouble,
but I can't carry him by myself.
I shouldn't just leave him here
while I go get help, either.
All I can do is wait until someone comes.
Wait...
What time is it right now, anyway?
It feels like it's only been about ten minutes,
so I guess we're still fine...
Whoa! This is where they've been?
Hey, wake up, Tanaka! Ohta!
We're starting to pack up!
That thing! Where did that thing go?!
Are you still half-asleep?
Let's finish packing up and have a party.
Shimura... Katou...
Huh? What's up, you two?
The ghost role...
I took over. Now that was fun!
Sorry to slip out midway.
Sorry...
Nah, you guys worked hard all morning,
so don't worry about it.
But you do need to help pack up!
Got it.
Okay...
Good work, everyone! Cheers!
Cheers!
Tanaka-kun Is Always Listless
Nothing's more relaxing than a typical day.
It's true...
They said there was a
white shadow in the pictures
the Photography Club
took during the festival.
Kicchan said there are rumors that it appeared
in the empty classroom, too.
What?
I knew it.
I didn't want to believe it, but they're true...
The school ghost stories...
Consecrated Salt
You should stay away from the rooftop.
That's where I saw it!
Really? Then I might have seen it, too.
Here, take this pile of salt!
Okay.
How scary...
Everyday life is like a bothersome cat
How I wish I could ignore it and do as I please
I discreetly retreat into my own world of music
Maybe I have a talent for daydreaming
That so-called happiness
What exactly is it?
I tried acting on my own desires
Will I understand it now?
Dramatic listlessness
I want to put my life into its hands
Maybe a positive attitude is better
Is trying my best the right thing to do?
I can't hold a poker face
Everyday life makes me dizzy
My dear listlessness
Once more
A girlfriend?! Him?!
How dare you take the first step up
the stairway to adulthood before me?!
Don't say a word.
My feminine appeal is gonna burst!
I know it's weird to ask this
of you out of the blue, but...
Next Episode
Tanaka-kun's
Happiness
Next time, Episode 12:
Tanaka-kun's Happiness.