Bond, if this is too much...
No, I'll do it.
Hey, Bond!
Get a hold of yourself!
Bond!
Kotarou!
Following the path of pain
kutsuu no michi wo tadori
Was too much to continue moving forward
ashi wo tometa darou
My time was frozen
kooritsuita toki mo
Keeping my distant memories out of reach
ima wa tooi kioku wo kasunde
If there are no sacrifices
nanimo gisei ni
Is that the definition of strength I can try to achieve?
sore wa tsuyoku nareru no ka to
But I lack even the courage to let go of your hand
nigitta mama no te mo mada hodoku yuuki ga motenakute
I'll become a hero
eiyuu ni naru
I've learned that
narenai kara
For me that's impossible
sono koto ni kidzuiteta
If nothing else, I'll wish for the strength I need to protect you
semete kimi wo mamoritai sou negau
I'll forge my body into a blade
kono karada wo tsurugi ni kaete
And take the path full of obstacles
are wo deta michi wo yuku
I moved forward by defeating even my own weak self
yowakatta jibun sae kiritaoshi susunda
I wonder if I'll ever reach
itsuka todoku no darou ka
The future you wish for
kimi ga nozomu mirai ni
I'll protect you until the very end, when we welcome that day
sono hi wo mukaeru made wa boku ga mamorinuku yo
Bond, we reached town.
Episode 20
"Moving On From a Standstill"
Luis?
R-Right.
Put these away, newbie.
Don't get cocky, you yellow monkey.
You don't even have a useful ability.
Next time you pull this crap, I'll kill you myself.
I'll help.
Oh...
Thanks, Luis.
Cheap meat might be tough,
but it has a unique taste.
Right, Bond?
We have another mission tomorrow.
Be sure to eat up.
Yeah.
I...
I killed...
I killed a...
I... I...
Kotarou.
Yasmin?
No dying.
Guardian had several fronts,
one of them being a private security firm.
Basically, it was a mercenary group
comprised of superhumans.
In the six months after I pretty much fled from Japan,
I experienced a lot of firsts.
My first war zone.
My first sight of true poverty.
My first time feeling the
bloodlust of a real, live human.
Get these done too, newbie.
But you should maintain your own guns...
Monkeys shouldn't speak.
But the superhuman tendency to discriminate
against those with inferior abilities
was the same everywhere, I found.
Sheesh. Leaving their weapons
in the hands of others?
Don't know if they're ballsy or stupid.
I'll help once this is done.
Luis, uh...
Sorry about last night.
It doesn't bother me.
In fact, I got to hog two meals.
No complaints there.
There was one more first I experienced in this country:
having a true comrade-in-arms.
Whoa there, Midou.
Close one.
Damn, Bond got me again!
Pincer attack, Tenjin!
You got it, Tenma!
Hey, no hands!
Cheating!
Luis, pass!
Bring it!
We often played with the local
kids when we were off duty.
They were always smiling, even though
they lived in a time of war and poverty.
Just watching those smiles offered me salva—
Look, guys.
A spring in his shoe!
What a cheater!
No fair, Bond!
Get him, everyone!
Hey, wait!
Sorry!
Spur of moment!
Sorry, sorry!
What are you guys doing to Bond?!
Yasmin?
B-But...
I don't want to hear your excuses!
Crap! Yasmin's mad!
Yasmin...
Uh, saved me.
Thanks.
She's mad, all right.
Can't say I blame her, after what I did.
You only play with Midou and boys.
No fair.
Er, give this, and you forgive?
Only this time.
A chocolate bar!
Why does only Yasmin get one?
No fair!
I want one too, Bond!
Not you too, Luis!
I don't get rationed a lot of sweets, y'know...
Halfsies.
You sure?
Thanks, then.
Life in this country's painful.
But we all halfsies the pain and live.
Yasmin...
Let's halfsies, Kotarou.
Yummy!
Y...
Yeah.
Why did you come to this country, Kotarou?
I ran away here.
Lots of people say the same.
They don't look it.
They think they can stay strong while raising hell.
But they're scared and anxious.
How about you? Why'd you come here?
I was in track and field since childhood.
Was expected to represent my country
in javelin and bring home a medal.
But then...
Men in black showed up?
Well, it's more money than a medal.
Not a bad deal for a poor guy like me.
Luis...
And what was your story?
Bond, are you tired?
Not at all.
Your smiles fill me with energy.
Okay, then.
Is school fun for you all?
Kids enjoy school lunch.
I'm learning programming on computers.
That's good.
Before, you say you want to learn programming.
I'll use computers to feed everyone lots of food.
You fighter.
Thanks to person who donated it.
There are kind people.
There really are.
Bond, join us!
Gimme a hand here.
I can't beat them by myself!
Okay, let's do this.
After running away to this land,
I'd come to a standstill yet again.
While I did some good here and there,
that was but the price I paid to avert
my eyes from my smoldering depression.
And just like that,
I entered my second year of life as a mercenary.
The goal of this mission is to wipe out
the forces stationed in the factory that's
manufacturing a new type of narcotic
and blow the whole thing up.
Also, daemons have been spotted
in the factory's vicinity.
Can't we just carpet bomb the place?
The problem is that
the factory is close to the border.
We don't want to wake up the neighbors.
What are those plots of land along the roads?
Farms.
They're growing grains,
which will provide useful cover.
We'll infiltrate from here.
Once you occupy the factory,
confiscate the narcotics and their ingredients.
If you encounter any Gaia fanatics, shoot to kill.
We're not capturing the summoners?
Kill a summoner, and their daemons stop moving.
We can support other teams that way.
Oh, I see.
Each team is to assign
the appropriate members
and equipment for their roles.
Dismissed!
Luis, Bond, come with me.
Team Valiant is in charge of the direct assault.
Sir!
We've never had such
a large-scale mission before.
Let's visit the school tomorrow.
Yeah, sounds good.
Let's go, Kotarou.
We can see them again after the mission.
Yeah.
Split up into two groups
and neutralize all enemies.
Roger.
Damn it!
What the hell?
I've never seen a daemon like that!
Shit—
Bond!
We can't beat that.
Let's take out the summoner.
Got it.
Where could the summoner be?
He should be at a safe distance
and have protection.
Bingo.
No...
Yasmin?
Kotarou.
I didn't realize until I fired...
I shot them...
Class needs money.
We can all communicate with djinn.
All of you?
You mean you tried to reduce
the consumption of life force
by contracting with one large daemon together?
A-Are you going to kill us?
Stay quiet.
Four lightly wounded by stray bullets.
Four dead.
Two on the verge of death.
They can be saved if they
receive immediate treatment.
I went and did it again...
You couldn't have known in that split second.
They were so young!
This is too awful!
This is Valiant 4.
We've neutralized six summoners.
Captain!
What's with the glare?
Are you going to say killing
wounded kids is wrong?
Yes.
You useless punk.
We've secured the factory.
We withdraw before dawn.
Yes, sir...
Whatever you're trying to do, don't!
I'm sure that ability you just tried
to use eats away at your life.
Don't use it.
I knew that those two would get killed.
But I still did it.
That was the only way to save Yasmin and the rest.
Yes, it was.
Fuck this...
Fuck it all to hell!
I won't accept Guardian's methods.
I could never accept
superhumans who discriminate against,
look down upon, and walk all over people.
Let's go.
I feel the same way.
This place will be bombed soon.
The neighboring country
was the narcotic factory's client.
And they were going to carpet bomb
the place to destroy the evidence.
Yasmin, if you can't run...
No! I'm okay!
Here it comes.
That's a glide missile.
It turns everything within
300 meters into a sea of flames.
It's only a matter of time until
they start firing those here.
Luis, what are you...
This is how I use these.
He took it out.
I'll guard the retreat.
Take the kids and go.
Go?
What about you?
I'll be right behind you once the route's secure.
Do as Luis says
Stop Luis and take him along
Stay here
Do as Luis says
Stop Luis and take him along
Stay here
Do as Luis says
Stop Luis and take him along
Stay here
Do as Luis says
Stop Luis and take him along
Stay here
Do as Luis says
Stop Luis and take him along
Stay here
Do as Luis says
Stop Luis and take him along
Stay here
Do as Luis says
Stop Luis and take him along
Stay here
Do as Luis says
Stop Luis and take him along
Stay here
Do as Luis says
Stop Luis and take him along
Stay here
Do as Luis says
Stop Luis and take him along
Stay here
Do as Luis says
Stop Luis and take him along
Stay here
Do as Luis says
Stop Luis and take him along
Stay here
Do as Luis says
Stop Luis and take him along
Stay here
Do as Luis says
Stop Luis and take him along
Stay here
Do as Luis says
Stop Luis and take him along
Stay here
Do as Luis says
Stop Luis and take him along
Stay here
Do as Luis says
Got it.
I once hit a friend of mine.
It was a trivial fight.
But he died from it.
I see.
I volunteered to come here to punish myself.
But I've had enough of living this way.
I'm going to quit standing still.
I think I'll do that, too.
I'm going ahead.
I'll be waiting.
Yeah.
Keep at it! We're almost there!
We made it...
That's enough!
Run, Luis!
You can't do that, man...
Yasmin?!
Midou!
Tenma!
Tenjin!
No...
They need proper treatment, ASAP!
Can I really cross this wasteland
without any weapons, supplies, or wheels?
I'm a traitor with nowhere to go.
Can I really protect these kids?
Leave us here.
Yasmin?
I don't think we'll make it.
So leave us and escape, Kotarou...
Rewrite
Don't
Never.
I see.
This ability converts my life force into power.
Fine. Take all you want.
I've decided to live the way I want.
For Luis, too.
I promise I'll save you.
Wait for me.
See you, Luis.
You look awful.
I apologize for my late return.
I got separated from the others
due to the carpet bombing.
Yeah.
You're Team Valiant's sole survivor.
Just when we'd wiped out the summoners...
We have plenty of replacements.
Return to active duty once you sort out
your team's personal belongings.
Yes, sir.
Once I decided to stop standing still that day,
a lot of things fell into place.
Even in this country,
there was a city that was relatively safe.
I gave Yasmin part of my savings
and had her relocate there with the others.
While they were summoners,
they were only being used because they were poor.
And there were many, many more like them.
As for me...
I improved after that mission
and started doing things solo.
I used the freedom that gave me
to take in any summoners
I found that were being exploited.
I also took in superhumans
before Guardian could find them.
In order to prevent Guardian from finding out,
I had to stay away from the place.
But Yasmin and the rest took care
of everything in my stead.
As a result,
a group comprised of both summoners
and superhumans was born.
Simply put, human nature was the reason
Gaia and Guardian were at odds.
But I felt like that same human nature
could also allow them to co-exist.
And nobody could convince me otherwise.
And then,
around two years after I left Japan,
I got a call from Esaka-san.
Is that you, Kotarou?
I just wanted to check on you one last time.
Are you going back to Japan?
I see.
Everyone's sad because
you never come to see us.
I don't want to cause you any trouble.
But this is your home.
Hearing you say that is more than enough.
All I ever wanted was a home, a place to belong.
Then... Then why?
Of course, I'll keep sending you money.
Gotta say though, your asset
management brings in more money
than I do these days.
That's not it!
That's not what I...
That's not what we want!
There was a beautiful sky, filled with stars,
on the night we parted with our friends, too.
Say, Yasmin.
Have I been able to move
on without standing still?
I-It's all thanks to you
that we can live with smiles on our faces right now.
Isn't that enough?
Thank you.
Kotarou...
Kotarou!
The world you live in
nemuru koto no nai
Is one that never sleeps
anata ga tatsu sekai wa
And it's still so pure
mada muku na mama de
If I can leave something
moshi kono daichi ni
In the ground here
nanika wo nokoseru no nara
Let it at least be some kind of a trace
semete omokage wo
I can't even do a simple thing like gaze at the sky
sora wo miageru sonna kantan na koto mo
So I close my eyes
yurusarezu hitomi tojiru
I was only ever looking
tada hitotsu dake
For one thing
mitsukete hoshii no
Sunken in memories
kioku ni shizumu
Feelings of love
itoshisa wo
At the ends of time
ikusen no hate
I hope you stay safe
tadoritsuku anata ga
Until we meet again
sukuwareru you ni
It's fine as long as my song reaches you
kono utagoe todoku kagiri