Step aside, Kotarou-kun.
Kotori...
If Salvation comes to pass,
the Key will return to the planet,
and I'll lose my druid powers.
And if that happens...
Because I'm probably a daemon
who's only alive thanks to your powers,
I'll die?
I wouldn't be able to bear that.
You're the only hope I have left in this world!
It'll be fine.
Druids have ways to prevent the Key
from returning to the planet, even if it dies.
So I won't let you be erased.
I'll prove it to you.
Prove...?
If I really were a daemon,
I wouldn't be able to defy my master.
So I'll go against your wishes to prove that I'm not.
My wishes?
You want to get away from all
this Key and druid stuff, right?
I won't let you.
I'll force you to make the most difficult choice.
Are you saying I should continue to suffer?
That's right.
Because I'm not a daemon.
I'm Tennouji Kotarou, the person.
No you're not!
You are a daemon!
The Kotarou-kun I knew wasn't cheerful at all!
He was moody, unsociable,
cold, not nice at all...
and he didn't save me!
You're a daemon.
One created by my desires,
given the kind of personality I wanted.
A daemon...
Say, Kotori.
The Key must've been
a huge burden on you, right?
Wrong!
I'll fight your weakness.
If you're gonna waver from your duty,
then I'll protect the Key.
So please...
Let's stay together until the very end.
You really aren't nice at all.
Tell me.
What?
What is Salvation?
Is it something that'll make
the world a better place?
It's ruin.
Kaga—
Shizuru?
Kotarou-kun...
The Key...
Kotarou...
Proof...
Proof... Proof?
Hey, what do you mean by "proof"?
How do you know my name?
Hey.
Hey! Hey!
I have to go.
But where?
A hill?
Oh, right.
That hill.
Episode 14
"Three Cups of Coffee"
I have this faint inkling
that a myriad of times that aren't now
and countless places that aren't here
came together to form this one night.
And I'm positive I'll find her there.
"Her"?
Who's that supposed to be?
Hey, you th—
So this is as far as I get tonight.
Get going, Shizuru.
What am I supposed to do without you?
I won't have anything left!
The look on your face is saying it'll be all right.
I can change.
I'll change so much,
no destruction or whatever will beat me.
And I'll be waiting for you, right here.
No...
No, no, no!
No!
Don't worry.
You'll always have a place in my heart.
So please find me,
even if I go a little overboard
with the changes, okay?
Kotarou...
Kotarou!
If only time would...
We should hurry.
I love you.
I love you more than anyone or anything.
I feel the same, Shizuru.
Later.
Let's meet again...
next time.
All right.
I have to say, this is quite the pleasant night.
H-Hey...
Are you alone?
Aren't you lonely staying here all by yourself?
Don't you wanna talk to someone once in a while?
I'm Tennouji Kotarou.
I'd prefer if you'd just call me Kotarou.
What's your name?
If you don't mind,
could we kill some time with a friendly chat?
Er...
What are you doing?
Oh, I know! Homework, right?
Okay, let me help—
Is that my...
It's really lively here.
Well, the Harvest Festa is coming up.
The Harvest Festa?
Wanna go together?
The mess with the Gaia
extremists has been cleared up.
Surely we can take some time off to relax.
Yeah!
Damn, my girlfriend is a total cutie!
What's that over there?
Hey, Chihaya!
There sure is a lot of stuff here.
Excuse me.
I'll take this one.
You like it?
W-Well, yeah.
Like it?
I can't see it clearly enough to answer.
But I guess it's kind of cute.
Oh, good. I thought it'd look great on you.
C-Can I really have it?
Yeah. To commemorate our first date.
Thank you very much.
You're taking it off?!
I can't see it well when I'm wearing it.
And it's kind of embarrassing...
R-Right...
But hey, that's how it usually goes.
I-I guess.
Hey! Now I can't even see it!
What's the problem? At least I'm wearing it.
C'mon, gimme a little peek.
Oh, fine.
Nice, I see 'em.
My memories are at their clearest
just before I wake up.
Over and over and over,
I try to talk to the girl, get killed,
and dream about my memories.
We're getting married.
Thanks for everything.
Tennouji Kotarou & Kotori
In one such memory,
I had a family with Kotori.
It was bliss.
However...
Cheers!
In another memory...
And this guy was like,
"I'll flatten you and drown your rotten corpse!"
Really? That guy sounds like such a riot!
I'd somehow gotten to know an OL living in Setagaya,
Hamada Michiko-san, and married her.
And in another, me and Akane-san,
Akane-san of all people,
were in an adult relationship.
I also found myself in a paradise
beyond my wildest dreams!
I mean, she's dynamite by herself,
but there were two of her! Two of her!
The ruin of civilization.
Gaia's remnants.
Idola's daemons.
Hunters.
At times,
I lived as a soldier
in a world straight out of some LN.
This is a memory of fighting Gaia's mad dog.
In the end,
was it never possible for us
to come to an understanding?
Oh, right.
I even have a memory of racing down
a highway at night with Shizuru,
enacting a chase scene right out
of a Hollywood blockbuster.
But this is where the contradiction rears its ugly head.
These memories are so inconsistent,
they couldn't possibly be from the same life.
It's like I've been reborn countless times
and lived different lives each time.
That's absurd.
But I can't come up
with any other way to explain
my inconsistent memories.
So I stop racking my brain
and focus on the task ahead of me.
Yes,
the terrifying task of talking to this unshakable girl.
This is something I must do.
Because it's the only thing I have to cling to right now.
Hey.
And yet, of course, I failed again.
Man, I'm running out of things to say.
Maybe I should just try a bolder method.
Like attacking her or something.
Nah, that won't do.
Socializing calls for a friendlier approach...
In terms of trying to attract her attention,
isn't this just like hitting on a girl?
I can't seem to get you off my mind.
I'm sure we'd make a great couple.
So there's nothing to fear, baby.
Hey...
Why don't we start going out?
My love is unstoppable!
Je t'aime.
No!
Play with adults, and you'll get burned.
I'm melting away!
I'm not getting anywhere!
Killing me just for trying to approach her?
This goes way beyond playing hard to get!
Oh, come on!
Yeah, yeah, I know.
Nothing's changed.
Even here, everything I do is pointless.
I just wanted somewhere to belong.
I wanted to mean something to someone.
I was scared of being left alone.
That's right!
That's why I started the occult club, too!
What's wrong with that?
Everyone's like that!
So why have I been singled out
and hauled off here?
Why am I the only one...
in this god-forsaken place?!
I'm a puny guy.
Some small-time guy who tried
to get through life curled up
into a tiny ball. That's all.
So why...
Why won't you leave me alone?
Go ahead.
Kill me.
Help me not think about anything anymore.
Turn me back into nothing.
Please.
What's your deal?!
Who the hell are you?!
Did you...
just say "Kagari"?
K-Kagari?
I-I've been wanting to ask.
Have you always been alone?
And, although I don't remember it,
we've met before, haven't we?
And not just once or twice, either.
I don't know if I should call you
a hard worker or what...
Oh yeah, I know it's a bit late to ask,
but what is this thing?
What the hell is this?
A theory?
This whole thing was
a super-dense mass of information?!
Is this a theory of life?!
There were battles revolving around the Key.
I took part in those battles, at times as part of Gaia,
at times as a member of Guardian,
and at times as...
Some considered the Key Earth's messenger,
sent to punish humanity for its hubris,
and some considered her Earth's immune system.
But in the end,
everyone perished without learning
anything about the Key.
Are you researching a way to destroy the world?
Humanity ruined the environment too much,
so you're going to destroy it?
Figures.
Kotori?
Hey...
All by yourself in such a lonely place again?
Akane-san?
What the heck?
Looking awfully thin there.
Lucia?
Did she run away?
Oh, right.
I can't touch her unless it's through a cloth.
Is this...
There's no fish or charcoal to use it with.
You're always such a nice girl, Shizuru.
This place is way too big for just two people.
This is all she had, huh?
I thought this town was deserted,
but I was mistaken.
Those were signs and vestiges of life.
I bet it's all connected somehow.
After that, I got killed countless times,
and gained in return
this comfortable distance between us.
I actually quite like it.
After all, since we can't communicate,
there are no lies or lip service in this relationship.
It's a completely pure connection
I built with my own hands.
It seems Kagari's research
isn't proceeding too smoothly.
Is there anything I can do to help?
Why don't you take a break?
It's good!
I'm a human, not a tree!
Crap, I spaced out for months!
Did your research hit a brick wall again?
Uh, here you go.
I don't actually want to drink this muddy water,
but you left me no choice!
As if.
Uh, are you...
You weren't asking for seconds, huh?
Trying to win me over with a drink like that?
I suppose that's the best an inferior
human could hope to think of.
As if.
And yet again, time passes without feeling like it.
I-I'll make some right away!
H-Hey...
Welp, I'm dead again.
Kagari?
A-Are you sure?
Are you telling me...
three cups of coffee was all it took
to break down the final barrier between us?
We're not friends,
lovers,
family, or anything.
Forget all that.
We can't even talk to each other.
And yet...
Even though it's so thin that
it could snap at any moment,
there was something that connected us.
I've found my answer.
I wouldn't mind risking my life for this right here!
That's right, Kagari...
You never were...
some incomprehensible being!