Bloody pathetic.
You housebroken dogs in
your sheltered environment,
yappin' about "justice" when
you know shit all about war...
I'll crush you all!
That's why I've stayed alive
in this fucked-up world!
Should we retire for the time being?
Wait.
I can keep going!
Distracted as you are right now,
you will not learn a thing.
I shall now make my rounds through the forest.
Damn.
He saw straight through me.
Good... memories...
Guess I'll head to the
Harvest Festa for a change of pace.
Little by little, the ripples drew apart from one another
sukoshizutsu hamon wa hanarete itta
And before we knew it, they no longer overlapped
itsu shika hitotsu mo kasanaranaku natta
But it's okay as long as you're here with me
sore demo ii kimi to itara
When did I start feeling this way?
konna kimochi itsu kara idaita
This is the love story of a certain boy
tada hitori no shounen no koimonogatari da
To protect you till the end of time
eien ni kimi wo mamotte miseru
I'll etch this upon my heart
kono mune ni kizamikomu
When did it start being just the two of us, again?
itsu kara futarikiri ni natta n da kke
But it's okay
mou ii ka
Just smile
sonna koto waratte yo
On the eve of this world's end
owaru sono hi ni wa
Denied.
I figured as much.
Aw, why not?
What's the problem?
I can't say I don't understand.
And here I thought I could go to a festival
with friends for the first time...
Next year, for sure,
let's go around the Harvest Festa
with everyone from the occult club!
With Shizuru and Prez, too!
That sounds great.
Yeah, really great!
It certainly does.
I'm sure Shizuru will be delighted, too.
That's right!
I'll have to drag my BFF, Yoshino, along with us.
And of course, Kagari, you'll join us—
Kagari?
She's been a bit quiet today, hasn't she?
What was that noise?
No way!
What's wrong, Kotori?!
The barrier's been broken from the outside!
What?!
Yo.
So you were here, huh.
Why, you...
Is your little friend from Guardian here, too?
Or did she kick the bucket already?
You're the one who hurt Lucia!
I shoved a skewer through
her belly and barbecued her good.
I grilled her just right, didn't I?
You bastard!
Wow, you had a trick like that up your sleeve?
Guess I'd better show you my hand, too.
Wh-What is it? An earthquake?
Bit of a waste to use it on shitters like you,
but come on, have a little taste of this!
Chibi-Moth! Everyone!
Show them what you're made of!
You had a summoner kicking around, too?!
What the heck is this monster?!
You bastard!
Yo.
Back from the grave I see, hunter.
This time, I'll be sure to put you down for good.
Chibi-Moth, help us out!
What're you doing?!
We're running away!
He shouldn't be able to keep
that daemon animated for long!
Besides...
This place is done for.
Kotori.
She's right! Let's run away, quickly!
That thing's bad news!
Easier said than done...
It's all right.
The trump cards are on their way.
Huh?
A gun?
Get 'em good, big guy!
Wha—
Let's go, while we have the chance.
Wait!
Why are Keisuke-san and Rikako-san...
Why are your parents here?!
Huh?
Come on, hurry!
Wait!
Kotori, listen to me—
They're just daemons now!
You ain't going anywhere!
I don't understand any of this complicated stuff,
but I believe that we need to run for now!
Got it!
With this, we can protect our family.
Yes. You are right, dear.
Huh?
Let us go, dear.
Yes, let's.
No way...
That's not possible...
I mean, they're both already...
Dad!
Mom!
Get the fuck outta my way!
I should have known better
than to extend myself so.
Chihaya-san, please be safe!
We won't let you interfere with Midou!
Gaia's Apex...
Shall we see if you're truly as
powerful as the rumors say?
Kilimanjaro and Krivoy Rog?
I daresay they're a tad insufficient
to pit against me.
These damn small fry ate up my time.
We'll be counting on you.
Yeah!
Bayern Knights of the Green Sword...
Move out!
Guess I'm leaving now, too.
But first, I would like to make something clear.
You and Lucia-chan aren't thinking
of doing anything stupid, right?
I see.
Good, then.
Well then, Shizuru-chan,
you be a good girl and watch over the place.
You're our ace in the hole.
Don't forget.
You're a member of Guardian.
That day ten years ago...
The first daemons I created
after becoming a druid
were my dad and mom.
They could move and could even talk.
But those were only reflexive
movements from when they were alive.
They were nothing but tools!
And I just used them at my
convenience, right to the very end...
I'm sorry.
I was with you,
but I never noticed.
Not to mention,
I couldn't even remember the accident...
It's fine.
There isn't a single thing you
need to apologize to me for.
Kotori?
Are you all okay?!
Yes! We're fine!
I see.
You bastard!
Go on without me!
I'll stop this guy!
Don't be stupid!
What are you saying?!
You can't do it on your own!
I'll be fine!
I'll definitely meet up with you later!
You'd better not be lying, okay?!
I know.
Sacrificing yourself for others?
How touching...
It makes me wanna hurl!
I won't let you lay a finger on Kagari!
Kagari?
Oh, you mean the Key?
True.
I'm sure hunters would go into a frenzy over that,
but the one I'm here to kill is you!
Why the hell are you so obsessed with me?!
It ain't just you!
You pieces of shit in this country
spend every day with your heads in the clouds,
and it makes me wanna grind you all into dust!
Smarts, don't it?!
A peace-loving dumbass
couldn't possibly endure this!
He's getting destroyed!
How is that man still alive with
two daemons that powerful in tow?
Yeah, it hurts.
But, unfortunately for you,
enduring pain is the one thing
that jerk Sakuya instilled in me!
You fuckin' brat!
"Bull's-eye!" as they say.
Damn!
I see. Talk about a real monster.
The newbies would be no match for it.
Hunter reinforcements?
Is that...
Don't me tell you're all...
Kiddo?
Gen-san!
That's most likely the Key.
I'm not sure why we can see it, though...
Oh?
If we can see it, destroying it'll be a piece o' cake!
Like hell it will!
Sorry about this...
Take the Key and get the hell outta here!
Wh-Why are you helping us?
Shit!
Why the hell did I make that stupid promise?
I'll burn you all to ashes, hunters!
L-Let's get out of here!
Now's our chance!
Yeah...
You're just doing whatever
the hell you please, eh, Gaia?
Pot callin' the kettle black much, hunter?!
Come on, what's the matter?!
The world always works this way!
The weak have everything stolen from them.
That's why I'm gonna destroy it!
Damn.
End of the line, huh?
No, Midou.
You have to get along with everyone.
But he's such a total scatterbrain.
Jeez...
Damn, I wanted to see it so badly...
To see this whole goddamn world
shatter to pieces...
Forgive me.
We allowed the Key to slip away.
Also, that kid we decided to keep
an eye on was with the Key.
Understood.
Continue to pursue them.
Tennouji, you're...
I'm sorry, Touka
If you let that thing live, it'll destroy the world.
Protect it with all you've got,
and then fall into despair!
Kagari.
What is the Salvation?
Who is the "you" you're looking for?
Hey, keep it together!
You're all battered and bruised!
Oh no, they caught up to us!
Please stay away!
It's all right.
Huh?
I thought about it lots and lots.
I'm not sure if this is the right thing to do, but...
Why are you here?
Well, I am a member of the occult club.
Shizu...
Shizuru!
Ow...
Was it a dream?
Not at all.
Good morning, Kotarou-kun.
You woke up sooner than I expected, Kotarou.
I see.
You came for us.
Shizuru healed yours and Lucia's wounds.
I see.
Thanks, Shizuru.
We should be safe here for now.
Here?
Wait...
What?! Where the heck are we?!
A Gaian facility called the
City of Stone, apparently.
Um...
Another world was created
on the flip side of our own via a Gaian technique,
or something like that.
It's being used as a storage place for daemons.
I only vaguely remembered this place,
but we managed to take refuge here somehow.
Oh.
So, what about Kagari?
She has been acting that way since this morning.
Why are you so determined to destroy humanity?
For generations,
the saint's soul and memories have been
transferred into our descendants.
You do not seem to have been consumed by it yet,
but it has surely been engraved upon you already.
Because the saint lost hope in humans?
With each successive generation,
our despair is sharpened and refined.
We do not hold a single happy memory
which could make up for it.
But I do.
You mean that farce at the school
we sent you to on a whim?
Just try and fight it, then.
Try to fight the continuous chain
of despair which I pass to you,
and you pass on to Shimako...
The groundwork has been laid perfectly.
The time is right.
For this song to resonate throughout the world,
we need to drag the Key
out into the world of the living.
Then...
After the Observer Tree appears,
the choir will head for the sanctuary.
I'm about to head there myself.
Yes.
I will go, too.
Do as you please.
Hand.
Trunk.
This sure takes me back.
Now, if only she were here...
You mean Prez?
Hey, Kagari!
You've been way too quiet today!
Did you run out of feecof or something?
You actually...
You actually have realized it, haven't you?
This is the real Kagari.
She isn't a living creature.
She's simply a phenomenon
designed to cause the Salvation,
taken human form.
She's no different from a daemon.
But until just recently,
she was saying whatever she wanted,
causing people problems,
and getting all happy calling
crappy coffee delicious!
Kotarou-kun...
It didn't work.
Kagari?
I couldn't find any.
Couldn't find what?
Good memories involving mankind...
I couldn't find any.
What is the meaning of this, Kashima?!
You ordered all the summoners
to sortie into the city?
Are you trying to start a war?!
No.
I'm simply putting an end to everything.
Wait!
Where are you going?!
A fitting place to welcome the end.
Don't tell me you're going to let the Key...
Stop it!
The Key should be nothing more
than a tool to monitor destruction!
Who would actually wish
for the world to truly end?!
Sakura...
Those who know naught of true despair,
who are merely discontent with life,
are nothing more than petty nuisances.
Now, Key.
Come forth.
Kagari!
What came over her all of a sudden?!
What is it, Chi?
Um, don't you hear something?
Something?
Probably some sort of song...
That's right. This is...
What is this?!
The tree!
What is that?!
That's...
Did I underestimate the enemy a little too much?
I must return to Chihaya-san's side at once.
This is...
Huh?!
What the—
That tree is...
Huge!
What in the world is going on?
Hey! What the hell is that?
This is bad, isn't it?
Is this Kazamatsuri?
Someone summoned all of us
from the City of Stone to Kazamatsuri.
Wh-What is it now?!
Daemons, Kotarou!
It can't be!
They're showing up in front of ordinary people?
Look at that!
What is it this time?
The forest is spreading!
Has it begun?
The time of Salvation is upon us.
Humans...
May your end be pleasant.
natsukashisa mo kieta yume
Losing myself in a dream where even nostalgia lost form
Episode 12
The Song of Destruction
mayoi kono te ga samishiku kaze wo nadeta
Lonely, I reached out with my hands to feel the wind's gentle caress
kotoba wo shiranai mama naraba
The names of those emotions still eluded me
kono hitomi wo tojiru koto mo
Even closing my eyes for eternity
kantan datta no ni
Should have been simple
hajimete fureta nukumori
But I felt warmth for the first time
chiisaku mebuku kodou ni
A tiny soul began to bud within my heart
tomadoi wo oboeta
And I learned of bewilderment
anata no koe sagashite mugen no michi wo yuku
Walking on the path of eternity, searching for your voice
hoshi no hajimari wo shiru tada sore dake
I'm led to the time when stars are born, nothing more
kuchi ni nokoru nigami mo hiroku mada ki ni naru
This bitterness that lingers inside my mouth tempts my curiosity
itsuka deau anata he saigo ni hohoemi wo
So I'll offer you one last smile before we meet again