What a beautiful morning.
I guess this is all thanks to the army
of talismans that Prez gave me.
You have my eternal gratitude!
And now, there'll be a few words
from each committee
regarding the Harvest Festa
scheduled to begin next month.
Th-This is a notice from the
Spread the Green Committee.
Leading up to the Harvest Festa, um...
W-We are recruiting helpers to place
potted herbs around the shibby!
Uh, what the hell is a "shibby"?
Er, um, this is volunteer work,
so you won't be paid!
Yosshi!
The Harvest Festa's gonna be a blast!
Don't talk to me.
We're talking the biggest, week-long
event in Kazamatsuri, Yosshiino!
School's out for the duration!
I know!
Wanna go around with me, Yoshiino?
At least pick one idiotic nickname and stick with it!
Truly pathetic.
A wolf would only waste away
at a banquet set for herbivores.
He shot me down.
Still,
this year's Harvest Festa is
shaping up to be a lotta fun!
Our stars are only an illusion of the shattered night
hibiwareta yoru ni ikuseisou no sora
On the sky many months and years old
utsuru bokutachi wa maboroshi
I wish to leave behind my past self
moshi kanau no nara kinou to wa chigau
Kanbe Kotori
And have my true self here instead
hontou no boku wo kono chi ni
The proof of our existence vanishes beyond the horizon
bokura ikitekita koto kanata e kieteku
Your life comes to a standstill like a rusted rail
sabitsuita reeru kimi wa tada tachitsukusu
So long as this blue fire flows through my arm
ima kono ude ni nagareru aoi hi ga aru nara
I'll be able to take your hand and stop you
furikaeru kimi no te wo hiite
Vowing to stars born of ashes never to let go
mou nidoto hanasanai to hai no hoshi e chikau yo
I will rewrite this poem
kakikaeru kono uta wo
Episode 3
Welcome, Supernatural Phenomena
Better check the blog before class!
Good morning.
Y-Yeah, morning.
Now remove yourself.
Oh, sorry.
I'll be leaving at once...
Wait, why?!
Who the hell are you?!
My, how unusual.
There are two gentlemen here.
Greetings, my fair lady.
How do you do?
My sincerest apologies for
barging in unannounced.
Where the hell were you during morning
assembly? Too busy being the princess?
I just pulled an all-nighter on the battlefield.
Well, care to explain the uniform?
Oh, it seems Chihaya-san entered my profile
on the order form for some reason.
She is still wearing her old uniform as a result.
I see.
So that's the story behind it.
By the way, who is he?
Oh, this man is Chihaya's—
Excuse me!
Ohtori?
Huh?
Why are you here, Sakuya?
Well, you forgot something important,
so I came to deliver it to you.
Ah, my lunch box!
I forgot it?
Yay, thank you so much!
Hey, you.
Yes?
Who might you be?
My name is Tennouji Kotarou.
A pleasure.
I am Ohtori Sakuya.
So you're Ohtori's...
Older brother.
Nah, Sakuya's just Sakuya.
You've forgotten the cover story, haven't you?
O-Oh, right...
Chihaya-san is a paragon of integrity.
For her to lie would simply be...
Who is this guy, then?
Due to various circumstances,
I now wait upon Chihaya-san hand and foot.
So you're like some sort of butler?
I suppose that is not too far off.
If I had to say, I am Chihaya-san's...
knight in shining armor!
Anyway, you're also an "Ohtori-san"?
Oh, things could get confusing
if you had to call us both that.
Why not simply go with "Chihaya" and "Sakuya"?
The great Chihaya-san would never allow
some lowlife to call her by name—
I don't mind, really.
I would expect no less of you.
Your warm benevolence extends even
to the most undeserving of lowlifes.
Then, Chihaya—
Acting a little too familiar, aren't we?
Are you at the top of the leaderboards
for world's rudest person?
You're like an open book.
Kotarou, classes are starting!
Why don't you hurry along?
I'm going to take a nap.
At least act like you're going to class,
even if you're just pretending!
Transmuting an "absent" into a "present"
is child's play for my dark magics.
Yeah, yeah.
The dark magics called authority, right?
Shall we then, Chi. Ha. Ya?
Yeah. We'll be off!
Um, Tennouji Idiotarou-kun, was it?
It's "Kotarou", actually.
On a personal level, I hate you.
What the hell was with that butler guy?
And hey, does this mean
Chihaya's some high-class girl?
Yeah, really can't see that.
Okay, for this one... Konohana.
Yes, sir.
Hey, why do you think
Class Rep always wears gloves?
Shut up.
What do I care?
But rumor says
she's a clean-freak who doesn't
like touching things directly.
Wait.
If she really were a clean-freak,
I doubt she'd agree to be class rep.
You've got a point.
It doesn't seem like she avoids
interacting with others.
Maybe she has some other reason for it?
Huh? What would that be?
Maybe her gloves are seals to contain
her secret cursed powers!
Wh-What's with that?
You've experienced it yourself, haven't you?
K-Knock it off.
Don't say any more!
I'm not like the others.
I have secret cursed powers...
Stop it!
I-Inside of me...
Stop it, Tennouji!
The evil dragon awakens!
Quiet down, you two!
Here we go, guys!
It's the new-and-improved
occult club's first group activity!
These cookies are great!
Chi, you have too many in your mouth.
I'll take this one!
Would you like more tea, milady?
Yes, please.
Prez.
Butler or no, isn't letting an outsider
enter the grounds against school rules?
It's fine.
My magic severs this club room
from the academy's control.
What sort of logic—
By the way, I have prepared this as well.
Thank you.
You're won over too easily, Class Rep!
Hey, why am I the only one left
out while you all have tea?!
A tsuchinoko?
Yeah.
A submission to the blog says a bunch
of people have spotted one on campus.
Do you think it'll be tasty?
You're planning to eat it?!
A tsuchinoko is just an obese snake.
Depressingly realist!
Well, it's not like I was particularly
convinced that it was real, either.
But something tells me it wouldn't be
so strange if a tsuchinoko did exist.
And in the event I prove that
paranormal phenomena do in fact exist...
Those glorious mammaries are mine for the taking!
Kind sir, I descry a most wicked look in your eye.
A-Anyway, I would like to make this
the occult club's first investigation!
Hey, tsuchinoko...
Ack!
That cry just now!
And this magnificent texture, both soft
and at the same time perfectly firm.
Could it really be a tsuchinoko?!
Can we discuss this like adults?
Tennouji Kotarou!
Despicable, despicable, despicable!
Filthy, filthy, filthy!
You irredeemable pervert!
Let's get out of here, Shizuru!
Farewell, Kotarou.
Oh, found the tsuchinoko.
What? Capture it!
Damn! Stay still, damn it!
Gotcha.
Chi-chan is awesome.
That's the Chihaya I know!
Not a lot of brain, but made up for in brawn!
You're totally insulting me, aren't you?
You're not getting away!
No way.
You really caught it?
Um, you're not from this school, are you?
I am a UMA hunter.
My name is Tsukuno.
You're a professional?
No, I actually work as a clerk.
I just really wanted the bounty for the tsuchinoko.
Furthermore, the reward will fund
my vacation abroad, a brand-name purse,
designer clothes, and some new boots
from this winter's collection.
Kotarou-kun, this rumor was a total sham.
Oh no, I must be getting back to work.
Well then, my like-minded friends, do excuse me.
Good work.
You did well.
Looks like we achieved our goal.
Um, then...
Tsuchinoko
Sighted on Campus?!
Complete
Tsuchinoko
Sighted on Campus?!
Complete
Tsuchinoko
Sighted on Campus?!
Complete
Tsuchinoko
Sighted on Campus?!
Complete
Tsuchinoko
Sighted on Campus?!
Complete
Tsuchinoko
Sighted on Campus?!
Complete
st Occult Research Club Activities Report
Tsuchinoko
Sighted on Campus?!
Complete
st Occult Research Club Activities Report
Tsuchinoko
Sighted on Campus?!
Complete
st Occult Research Club Activities Report
Tsuchinoko
Sighted on Campus?!
Complete
st Occult Research Club Activities Report
Tsuchinoko
Sighted on Campus?!
Complete
st Occult Research Club Activities Report
Tsuchinoko
Sighted on Campus?!
Complete
st Occult Research Club Activities Report
Tsuchinoko
Sighted on Campus?!
Complete
st Occult Research Club Activities Report
Tsuchinoko
Sighted on Campus?!
Complete
Who'd have thought they'd still
have cutlet sandwiches left?
Lucky me!
Shizuru's eating, too?
Come to think of it...
Let's eat lunch in the courtyard, together.
Shizuru.
If you're about to have lunch,
do you want to eat with me?
We promised the other day, right?
Kotarou, you remembered?
In that case...
Do excuse me.
Well then, without further ado...
Chow time!
What's that?
Broiled saury?
Unfortunately, I can't hand this over.
Not even to you, Kotarou.
If you've been looking forward to it,
then just eat it yourself.
I'll help myself, then!
She looks so happy, I almost feel envious of the saury.
What's up?
My eye is kind of itchy.
Hold up.
Should you really be rubbing it directly like that?
That could make the infection worse.
It's not an infection.
What is it, then?
You won't tell anyone?
Sure, if you don't want me to.
It's okay if it's you.
Huh? Wait, this is weird.
Why do we have a nice mood going?
Um...
Well...
It's pretty.
I think it's pretty.
You're so cute, Shizuru.
Sorry, sorry.
Okay, I'm stuffed.
Steel
Aluminum
Time to head back to the classroom.
Tennouji Kotarou!
Class Rep?
Can you not tell the difference
between aluminum and steel?
Also, rinse out the inside
before you throw it away!
W-Will this do?
Wait. It'll take up too much space
if you throw it away as-is.
Use this.
Wow, that's pretty cool!
It uses the principle of leverage.
It can crush steel cans, too.
You should try it out.
Take that!
Steel
Oh, this feels awesome!
There's plenty more to go.
All right, bring it on!
Take that!
And that!
I feel used.
When you consider it payback for yesterday,
I'd say you got off lightly.
What are you doing, anyway, Class Rep?
Sorting for recycling purposes, of course.
The Earth's resources are finite.
On an individual level it may seem
as though they're unlimited,
but they will run out one day for sure.
The accumulated, irresponsible
waste of each individual
threatens to consume the Earth
itself even in the present day.
Is this normal for a clean-freak?
I'd say this is more like she genuinely cares
about order and environmental problems.
In a way, I'm not only the representative
of a tiny world known as a class,
but rather, the whole Earth—
Ahem.
Sorry.
I just said a bunch of embarrassing things,
so please forget them.
Don't be silly. What's embarrassing about it?
We mustn't avert our eyes from
environmental issues, right,
Class Rep?
No, correction: Earth Rep!
I-I told you, stop that!
What are you saying?
The Earth Rep's pearls of wisdom
are anything but embarrassing!
Stop it!
Don't say any more!
We must immediately spread the message
to all people throughout the world!
Oh, my esteemed Earth representative!
T-Tennouji...
Kotarou!
Why?!
The Earth Rep is not to be trifled with.
To think I'd be bedridden
in the infirmary until this late.
I-It's her!
That's a massive dog!
Is it chasing her?
Damn!
I'm honestly scared,
but I'll be in trouble if she pops up again.
So I need to confirm a few things for myself.
Rewrite complete.
No, superpowers do exist.
Oh, do elaborate.
Perhaps you have superpowers?
Man, if I'd just told her about this,
I could feel her up on the spot.
My rewritten physical abilities
won't go back to normal.
Keeping this hidden again is gonna be a pain.
I won't catch up unless I kick it up another notch, huh?
What should I do?
It's way too quiet here, even for night time.
Not to mention, this atmosphere
is somewhat familiar.
I sensed that thing and tried
to corner it here, but what's this?
I ended up catching a stray cat, too.
Since you're after that thing,
you're a hunter, I take it?
Not good.
I don't know why, but this guy's bad news!
Now that's a riot.
Is every hunter in this peace-addled country
this useless?
Feeding time.
Eat to your heart's content!
Run, run!
S-Someone help!
What was that thing called again?
That was no ordinary dog.
Based on the report...
...ia diehards...
...took severe damage to his...
A daemon, huh?
That's right.
That was a daemon!
Oh, you all right, kid?
I see you're awake.
Um, why am I...
Oh, we found you passed out in the park,
so we decided to help.
Is that so?
In the park...
Th-Thank you very much.
So, what in the world happened?
You don't look particularly calm.
I was being chased by this weird dog...
Almost like some sort of daemon.
You were attacked by a... daemon?
Huh?
Where did it show up?
Don't worry. We'll slay it.
We're basically pros when it comes to
taking down these daemon things.
U-Uh, slay it?
What's your affiliation?
A-Affiliation?
Um, the Kaza High Occult Research Club, I guess?
I see.
Anyway, have something to eat.
Uh, what did you mean by
"daemon" and "slaying it"?
I was referring to a game.
Huh?
We're online game enthusiasts, you see.
We often mix up games and reality.
Ugh, they're old losers.
But we've heard that a number of
unidentified animals exist in Kazamatsuri.
Maybe you saw one of them.
For real?!
Um, I'm actually looking for stories like that.
Could you fill me in?
Feel free to drop by my shop sometime, then.
Oh, pardon me.
I'm Esaka.
I run a small antiques shop in this city.
Esaka-san, was it?
Yes, definitely!
My intel will prove more useful
in practice than any strategy guide.
Um, I'm not talking about a game.
Oh, you came, missy?
Give me the usual, Gennady.
You got it!
Yo.
Friend of hers?
She's an underclassman from
school I'm somewhat close to.
Here ya go. Thanks for waiting!
Shizuru, are you a regular here?
Gennady treats me to ramen all the time.
Were you a regular, too?
No, actually...
Maybe Lucia hit you too hard?
I'm starting to think so, too.
Wait, no!
Look, that thing got me good!
I don't see any injuries.
Huh?
Wait, what?
You're right!
You must have been dreaming.
Was it really a dream?
But my abilities have definitely been rewritten...
I'm starving!
Gen-san, gimme some grub!
Oh, the boss and the little missy are here, too?
Ah, it'll be crowded like this.
All of you, put the tables out thataway!
Man, you're such a slave driver.
They're all regulars.
Oh, a fresh face. You the little missy's boyfriend?
What was that?
I won't let any man have
the little missy as long as I live!
Huh?
No, Shizuru and I aren't—
She lives in that run-down
apartment all by herself.
A working student, huh?
I wish there was something
I could do to help her out.
So much has happened tonight
that I can't make sense of it all.
Oh my. Imagine running into you here.
Out on a night stroll fretting
over your scalp, Gobaldo-kun?
I-I'm not going bald!
And what are you doing out so late?
Chihaya-san desired some ice cream
available only in convenience stores.
You really are a butler, huh?
But don't you think you're
spoiling her a little too much?
I'm her knight, Nobody Sleazebag-kun.
Did I do something to you?
You seem to be out to get me for some reason.
The moment I laid my eyes upon you, I felt as
though I had come face-to-face with my destiny.
Yes, like fate had drawn
us together to be enemies.
Huh? You're not making any sense.
Oh, it is exactly as I said before.
I simply hate you.
dekakegiwa no amazora kaerigake no kitakaze
Rainy skies when I leave, north wind blowing when I come home
itsudemo kimama ni subete aiseru tsuyosa ga hoshii
Give me the courage to cover every inch of this whimsical world with my love
kyou mo isogigachi na hitonami wo miokuru you ni
Fresh tree leaves sway, as if bidding farewell
osanai konoha ga yureteiru
To waves of rushing people
mata hajimaru yo
So it begins, once again
saa bokura mo sorosoro ikou
Come on, it's about time we went too
ikue ni mo kasanaru sekai de toki no nagare ni mi wo makasete
In this stratified world, we entrust ourselves to time's steady flow
kono saki mo itsudemo futari no ayumi wo tsudzukete ikou
Let's walk towards our future, step by step, always just the two of us
eien nante nozomi wa shinai tatoe chippoke demo kamawanai
I don't need an eternity, I'm happy with something small
tashika ni, ima koko ni bokura ga iru koto
But at this very moment, there's no doubt that we are here
sore ga shiawase
And what is happiness but this?