Today I'll go with a normal Lunch Combo A.
But sneaking out for some Italian
at Saizuriya wouldn't be bad, either!
What are you after?!
My life?
My chastity?!
It's my first time,
so be gentle!
Calm down. It's me!
That voice...
Is that you, Lucia?
I'm going to release you now.
B-But keep your eyes closed until I say it's okay.
Got it?!
You have to!
All right.
O-Okay.
Open your eyes.
I-It's a maid uniform.
Got a problem with that?!
Uh, want me to take you to the infirmary?
You're the one who told me to serve you
a homemade lunch in a m-maid uniform!
O-Oh, the maid uniform part was obviously a joke.
I've made a huge mistake!
Yay, I'm so happy you kept your promise!
And it looks great on you! So lovely!
R-Really?
Yeah, it's super cute.
Huh?!
Cu... Cu...
No!
You jerk!
Why?!
Our stars are only an illusion of the shattered night
hibiwareta yoru ni ikuseisou no sora
On the sky many months and years old
utsuru bokutachi wa maboroshi
I wish to leave behind my past self
moshi kanau no nara kinou to wa chigau
Kanbe Kotori
And have my true self here instead
hontou no boku wo kono chi ni
The proof of our existence vanishes beyond the horizon
bokura ikitekita koto kanata e kieteku
Your life comes to a standstill like a rusted rail
sabitsuita reeru kimi wa tada tachitsukusu
So long as this blue fire flows through my arm
ima kono ude ni nagareru aoi hi ga aru nara
I'll be able to take your hand and stop you
furikaeru kimi no te wo hiite
Vowing to stars born of ashes never to let go
mou nidoto hanasanai to hai no hoshi e chikau yo
I will rewrite this poem
kakikaeru kono uta wo
W-Well, since you went to all the trouble,
I shall help myself to your lunch box!
Episode 6
Occult Club Activity Log
Sure...
Wow!
So this is a girl's homemade lunch,
the stuff of ancient legend!
Q-Quit spouting stupid
nonsense and eat it already!
Okay.
Thanks for the meal.
H-How is it?
Yeah, it's tasty.
I love the simple warmth that's
characteristic of home cooking.
R-Really?
Thank goodness.
But to be honest,
I got Shizuru to help me make that lunch.
Shizuru?
A little, mostly with the seasoning.
My sense of taste has been abnormal
ever since my body became this way.
That's why she was able to eat that
super spicy parfait like it was nothing?
Shizuru's been helping me out since forever.
Um, at Guardia—
Sorry.
Um, have you been with Shizuru
at that "G" organization all this time?
Yeah.
Shizuru can generate a medicine that
neutralizes my poison within her body.
As such, Shizuru has been my one and only,
precious friend all this time.
Your friend, huh?
So, I'm sorry,
but I ended up telling her
about your special power, too.
Oh, I see.
Don't worry.
I have no intention of telling
anyone other than Shizuru.
Not Touka-san, or the organization.
Shizuru's wish is for you to live out a peaceful life,
far from the clutches of the organization.
I see.
Shizuru's too kind.
She is my one and only friend, after all.
Hey.
Huh?
I told you this the other day.
You have me as well, now.
Not to mention the rest of the occult club.
Do you think Ohtori-san will forgive me?
I wouldn't be too worried.
She's been wanting to apologize to you, too.
It'll be all right.
I'm right here with you.
Yeah.
Thanks, Kotarou.
Sure!
Did you just call me "Kotarou"?
Wh-What's wrong with me calling you by name?!
Wh-Why are you snapping at me?!
I'm very sorry, Ohtori Chihaya!
Huh?!
Hey, what's all this about?
An apology, of course!
I sincerely apologize for being
so nasty to you the other day!
That's not what I meant!
Oh, jeez, what was the point
of me fasting since this morning
to work up the determination to apologize to you?!
I'm starving!
Why don't you hurry up and apologize too, then?
You have a point!
I'm sorry, Konohana-san!
I was out of line!
Mhm, it's great that you were
able to apologize, huh, Chi-chan?
Here, eat to your heart's content!
This bread is yummy!
By the way...
This has been bugging me for a while.
What is it?
Why have you been clinging to him all this time?
Because we're friends, naturally!
What do I do with this girl?
She's oblivious to how much
distance friends should maintain!
Sh-Shizuru-san?
What are you doing?
It's no problem.
I'm friends with you, too.
Hey, Lucia-san?!
What the?
My arm's getting buried! My arm!
To think I would be so utterly bested...
I'm sorry, Kotarou.
Why are you apologizing?
I'm pretty sure there's demand
for chests like yours, too!
Shizuru, thanks for being
considerate about the "G" incident.
Sure.
I want you to be free.
I see.
If that's how it is...
All right!
Let's get out there and start occult clubbin'!
"Somewhere in Kazamatsuri
lies a legendary, holy sword
that only a true hero can pull out."
Someone submitted that info to the blog,
and we went out in search of it!
Case 1
The Legend of
Kazamatsuri's Holy Sword
Hey!
This is just a candy shop!
Thank you. That will be a million yen.
Starfish Cutter!
And they're enjoying themselves!
Looks like it was a bad lead.
Kotarou, there's a holy sword right here.
This is the holy sword, Excalibur!
They say it's been stuck here for around ten years,
and nobody's been able to pull it out yet.
That's a legend, all right.
Exactly.
However, today I shall be the one
to lay that legend to rest.
Papagatero!
Who the hell is that?!
I don't give a damn about you right now.
I'll sink these fangs I've been
sharpening for the last ten years
into this holy sword, right here and now!
I pulled it out!
The legend!
Don't break it!
Case 1
The Legend of
Kazamatsuri's Holy Sword
SOLVED
Case 2
Panic! The Laugh That
Echoes From the Darkness
Thriving Business
Case 2
Panic! The Laugh That
Echoes From the Darkness
SOLVED
Case 3
The Ogre Who Lives
in the School Building at Night
Case 3
The Ogre Who Lives
in the School Building at Night
SOLVED
The Dinosaurs Vs. The Yayoi People
Case 4
The T-Rex Lived
Until the 2nd Century!
SOLVED
The subject of this weekend's quest
is this lead which was sent to our blog!
A modern day utopia? I saw a rainbow paradise at the Tsumugi River Basin!
So in other words, a picnic in the forest?
Sakuya, Sakuya!
Fill up my lunch box with rolled omelet
and octopus-shaped wieners!
Of course.
I shall prepare lunch boxes
for five on the day of your trip.
He casually ignored me!
On the contrary,
Slowtarou-kun, I wanted to give you
the special opportunity to harvest
and savor fresh, local ingredients.
'Twas a butler's display of consideration.
Let me see.
Podostroma and gyromitra
mushrooms are in season right now.
I highly recommend them.
A murder plot that doesn't dirty your own hands?!
A utopia, huh?
Are you sure it's not just another bad lead?
No! I choose to believe in our contributors!
So, anyone interested, please raise your hand!
Pass.
I guess I'll pass.
I'll pass.
Surprisingly, I'll pass.
"Ass" indeed.
Wait a second, you crass butler!
Yes?
I...
Don't let these traitors
pressure you into a decision.
Come on, tell me how you really feel!
Kotarou...
Got it.
If possible, I don't really want to go, either.
Okay, it's settled!
Tomorrow, on Saturday, we're going on a quest!
Got it?!
If we're going to the forest, we'll need a bodyguard.
Sorry, I fell behind schedule!
You're late, Kotarou.
This was your idea, so don't be late!
Lucia's sudden lovey-doveyness died down, huh?
Not sure if I should be relieved or disappointed.
Sorry about that.
So, what are you up to?
Kotori brought a dog as a bodyguard.
It's so cute!
Wow, a dog?
Look, Chibi-Moth.
Say hi to Kota-san.
Moth!
Isn't this a mammoth?
I think I've seen it before in the forest.
Yes, I did pick him up in the forest the other day,
but as you can see, he's a dog.
H-He is?
Chibi-Moth is as strong as they come!
Yeah, around three Yoshinos, I'd say.
I feel bad for Yoshino.
Uh, there's no way he's three
times as strong as Yoshino.
Chibi-Moth, go all-out for a sec.
Are you trying to kill me?!
Sorry.
But, if he's this powerful,
he'll be the perfect bodyguard for us in the forest.
Something's sticking out of him!
Look, this thing's totally a mammoth!
Huh?
There's nothing there.
Did you hit your head or something?
It's not good to make strange
accusations just because you lost.
Kotarou, have the courage to admit defeat.
Unsightly.
Forget it. I'm done.
What did you bring for snacks?
I've got candy.
I have salted rice crackers!
Sweet natto.
Woffers.
Woffers?
These.
Oh, jam wafers?
Yeah, woffers.
Huh?
Boss, you know that stupid girl, right?
Shouldn't you take her side?
I neither saw nor heard a thing.
What is it?
Oh, what a pretty river.
What course are we following?
Let's see.
This is where we are.
From here, we'll take a shortcut through
the forest and head downstream.
You really prepared ahead of time.
Of course.
Right now, I'm a pretty reliable guy!
How promising.
I have my full trust placed in you, of course.
Oh, dear. It seems I dropped my emergency flare.
You don't trust me in the slightest!
It looks so clean. I bet it tastes great.
Stop it.
Cut it out.
Huh?
If you drink raw river water,
it'll give you a stomachache.
It runs through a village upstream,
so you're better off not drinking it.
Oh, there could be wastewater mixed in.
Yes, that could be quite dirty.
Gulp, gulp, gulp...
I just said not to drink it!
Good taste!
Well, it shouldn't be a problem for Shizuru.
How irritating.
You don't like bugs, Prez?
I don't think anyone likes them.
There sure are a lot more bugs once
you go just a little ways into the forest.
Obviously.
They use insecticide around the city
and the outskirts of the forest adjacent to it.
Huh?
This is Mother Nature's true form.
Not that humans can deal with it.
You don't want to live in a city
swarming with insects either, do you?
Well, that's true,
but kind of wrong, too...
It's unavoidable.
Life and living aren't always beautiful.
People only accept what is beautiful.
The greenery close to us is fake
and unnatural to the core.
But couldn't you also call that
a product of human progress?
Improving our habitat in order
to survive seems only natural to me.
Even if the things we humans
so arrogantly call "improvements"
end up causing a fatal error
in the environment and Earth itself?
Even so, humans will—
Now, now.
Calm down, you two, and let's admire
these Hercules and Caucasus beetles.
So they live in Japan, too!
Kazamatsuri really is something.
You okay?
Yeah.
The greenery is just a little thick here.
Now that you mention it...
The smell of the greenery is suffocating.
The bugs disappeared at some point, too.
A daemon!
An orthrus appeared!
Wait a second, Shizuru!
A-A daemon?
Like a raccoon dog?
I think he's telling us to follow him.
Got it!
Lead the way, Chibi-Moth!
Um, doesn't something smell weird?
Huh?
You're right. This is awful.
Oh, you found them?
All right!
This is the utopia?
Don't get any closer, Kotarou!
Lucia! Shizuru!
Jeez, we were worried about you two!
Never mind us. Look at that.
Kotarou-kun, this used to be a forest.
Is this a tree that's rotting away?
Toxins most likely permeated
all the way into the soil,
drying up and rotting the forest.
Kotarou, look at this.
The orthrus.
It was alive until just a minute ago.
It was walking and everything.
But now...
The UMAs in Kazamatsuri...
Don't tell me the unidentified animals
we've been hearing about have all been...
It appears the toxins
that seeped into the ground caused birth defects.
Was it caused by wastewater?
Most likely.
So, what will you do?
Didn't you come here to investigate this?
Well...
Orthrus, rest in peace.
Anman.
"Amen," right?
Okay, let's go home before it gets dark.
Kotarou-kun, you didn't take a picture?
I guess not.
Are you sure?
Wouldn't "We found the source of the daemons"
be a huge scoop for the occult club?
That kind of thing's too much for me to handle.
We can't make news fodder
out of this just for fun, can we?
What is this?
I feel like I've seen this before...
What's wrong, Kotarou?
You're breaking out in a heavy sweat.
If you're tired, we can rest for a bit.
Uh, no, I'm fine—
It's her!
Kotarou?!
I never thought you'd follow
me all the way out here—
Kotarou-kun! Kotarou-kun!
What the hell was that?!
Kotarou!
Kotarou-kun, this way is—
A-Are you okay?
You look pale.
Y-Yeah, I'm fine.
Sorry, let's head back.
Yeah...
What are you doing?
I should ask you the same thing!
I was feeling restless at home,
so I figured I'd at least write down
what happened this afternoon,
even though I don't intend to publish it.
All right, done!
Twenty points.
After what we saw, "Chemicals that
damage the environment are bad"
is a very simple conclusion.
If we're being honest,
environmental damage is inevitable
with lots of humans around, isn't it?
There's nothing we can do about it.
You're right.
Accelerating environmental destruction.
Resources on the verge of exhaustion.
And yet a segment of humanity
continues to indulge in their pleasures
without any sense of impending danger.
Honestly.
I wonder what they plan
to do when the day comes?
"The day"?
The point of no return.
It refers to the instant in time after
which we can no longer turn back.
The day the Earth is beyond
saving isn't all that far away.
You mean, humanity will go extinct?
Unless we migrate to another planet, yes.
That's science fiction.
Just how long...
do the lot of you plan to keep on
living in your little dream?
I-I...
What are you scared for?
How foolish.
Why did you decide to write
this down in the first place?
Hoping to find a job in an
environmental organization?
It's nothing that serious.
It's just...
I do believe there are people
truly trying to protect the world.
I didn't think it would hurt
to at least do what I can.
In that case, I happen to know of a good method.
Huh?
Remove the source of the pollution.
Oh, like factories and stuff?
Not that.
The answer is very simple.
Huh?
Just get rid of the humans.
Sleep isn't making my fatigue go away.
Hello?
This is Inoue.
The occult club went to investigate
the forest yesterday, didn't it?
Hey, Inoue.
Do you have me wiretapped or something?
I would never!
I just have a world-class spy—
Hey, what'd you just say?!
Did your investigation have to do with
the Rainbow Swamp, by any chance?
Rainbow Swamp?
That's what I call it.
I see. That fits.
We suspended the investigation, though.
It was too heavy for us.
True.
Given what's causing it,
this would fall into our territory.
Do you know something?
I got my hands on some juicy intel.
I was thinking of going to check out the forest.
What's this intel you got?
You'll have to wait and keep your eyes
peeled for the next front page to find out!
Yeah, yeah.
Well, be careful, anyway.
Thanks.
See ya!
Now, then...
Who is it?!
Who's the spy?!
You're Tennouji-kun, right?
I am. Why?
Um, I'm from the newspaper club.
I heard you're close to Inoue?
I'm not sure you'd call us close.
More like she messes with me...
Oh, that reminds me. She called me on Sunday.
Really? What did she say?!
Huh?
That she was about to head to the forest...
Inoue hasn't come home for the
past three days, since Sunday!
What?!
dekakegiwa no amazora kaerigake no kitakaze
Rainy skies when I leave, north wind blowing when I come home
itsudemo kimama ni subete aiseru tsuyosa ga hoshii
Give me the courage to cover every inch of this whimsical world with my love
kyou mo isogigachi na hitonami wo miokuru you ni
Fresh tree leaves sway, as if bidding farewell
osanai konoha ga yureteiru
To waves of rushing people
mata hajimaru yo
So it begins, once again
saa bokura mo sorosoro ikou
Come on, it's about time we went too
ikue ni mo kasanaru sekai de toki no nagare ni mi wo makasete
In this stratified world, we entrust ourselves to time's steady flow
kono saki mo itsudemo futari no ayumi wo tsudzukete ikou
Let's walk towards our future, step by step, always just the two of us
eien nante nozomi wa shinai tatoe chippoke demo kamawanai
I don't need an eternity, I'm happy with something small
tashika ni, ima koko ni bokura ga iru koto
But at this very moment, there's no doubt that we are here
sore ga shiawase
And what is happiness but this?