A short while passed after that,
and I found myself setting foot
in a whole new environment.
Actually, I just mean that I started high school.
Following the path of pain
kutsuu no michi wo tadori
Was too much to continue moving forward
ashi wo tometa darou
My time was frozen
kooritsuita toki mo
Keeping my distant memories out of reach
ima wa tooi kioku wo kasunde
If there are no sacrifices
nanimo gisei ni
Is that the definition of strength I can try to achieve?
sore wa tsuyoku nareru no ka to
But I lack even the courage to let go of your hand
nigitta mama no te mo mada hodoku yuuki ga motenakute
I'll become a hero
eiyuu ni naru
I've learned that
narenai kara
For me that's impossible
sono koto ni kidzuiteta
If nothing else, I'll wish for the strength I need to protect you
semete kimi wo mamoritai sou negau
I'll forge my body into a blade
kono karada wo tsurugi ni kaete
And take the path full of obstacles
are wo deta michi wo yuku
I moved forward by defeating even my own weak self
yowakatta jibun sae kiritaoshi susunda
I wonder if I'll ever reach
itsuka todoku no darou ka
The future you wish for
kimi ga nozomu mirai ni
I'll protect you until the very end, when we welcome that day
sono hi wo mukaeru made wa boku ga mamorinuku yo
Episode 18
"Superhuman Qualities"
Even after deciding to quit Martel,
I took part in meetings with my parents.
My plan was to gradually fade away
instead of leaving with a bang.
Not very brave, I know.
I'm a coward.
Are you the Tennoujis' kid?
Kashima Sakura, Martel's linchpin.
A luminary whom the more zealous members
of the organization even called a saint.
Your parents asked me to talk to you.
About skipping meetings?
No. Just to have a little chat.
Let's see...
Are you enjoying school?
School?
She hit me with a barrage of trivial questions.
But they were peppered with some curious words.
Night.
Forest.
Daemons.
Hunt.
Superpowers.
She seemed to be sounding me out.
I get the gist of it now.
You're at an age where you have
a lot on your mind, yes, Kotarou?
Right...
Answer this one last question for me.
What do you usually do when you encounter
something you find unacceptable?
What do you mean?
Do you strive to change yourself
or your environment?
Or something else entirely, perhaps?
I...
Dunno
Go with the flow
Give Up
Improve my environment
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
Improve my environment
Go with the flow
Give Up
Change myself
Dunno
I don't know. I've never given it much thought.
Is that so?
You must be a stray.
Thank you, come again!
Today's chocolate tart was amazing.
Indeed.
I daresay it was on par with the one
I once had at the Creme Chantilly.
I guess we've covered pretty much all
of the famous pâtisseries in town now.
Indeed we have.
Uh, Esaka-san.
Thank you for always
hanging out with me like this.
Tennouji-kun.
Yes?
A friendship free of any vested interests
is a most rare and valuable thing.
Yeah, ones born out of
self-interest feel awfully hollow.
Indeed.
Today might mark the end
of this relationship, though.
There's something I'd like to talk to you about.
Would you hear me out?
Tennouji-kun, I want to recruit you.
You ought to join our organization.
As a superhuman, you belong with us.
"Superhuman."
That's what he said.
People with abilities like mine.
Esaka-san was one of them,
and he was part of an organization
that fought daemons.
What I saw in the forest that night was actually real.
All of my monster hunting
suddenly felt totally childish.
It was embarrassing.
Earth-Saving Hunter, my ass.
That night, I had an argument with my parents.
I told them again that I wanted
to leave Martel, this time for real.
We yelled at each other
till the late hours of the night,
and my thoughts eventually came to a head.
Or came together, I should say.
It's me.
I want to leave home.
If you're running away like a child,
you'll get no help from me.
But if you're leaving as a man, I accept.
I am.
You'd best be prepared.
Things will only get tougher from here.
And so began a period of upheaval in my life.
Hey, morning.
Good morning.
Uh, going on a family trip?
That's right.
Pero's death had left Kotori scarred badly.
They must be doing this to lift her spirits.
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Wait and watch
Say nothing and send them off
Stop them
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Wait and watch
Say nothing and send them off
Stop them
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Wait and watch
Say nothing and send them off
Stop them
Wait and watch
Say nothing and send them off
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Wait and watch
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Wait and watch
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
Say nothing and send them off
Wait and watch
Talk with them, pretending to be nice
Ignore them
Stop them
For some reason, I got the feeling I should stop them.
Um, do you really have to go today?
Why do you ask?
I don't know...
Why, indeed?
What?
I learned a lot from how you live your life.
I wanted to thank you for that.
Where's this coming from?
That's all.
See ya.
Wait!
Where are you going?
Soccerbat practice.
It's a new sport where we play soccer with bats.
You're lying.
Are you coming back?
Damn, she's sharp.
I decided to quit Martel, too.
But my parents wouldn't stand for it,
so I'm running away to a relative's place.
Oh.
Harvest Festa...
They hold that "Harvest Festa" thing here, right?
Yeah.
Show me around.
Why me?
I don't have any friends, so you show me around.
Can't say I follow that logic.
Just do it!
Pushy one, aren't you?
Fine.
I'll show you around once I'm back.
It's a promise, okay?
Cross your heart, hope to die.
Bye.
Say hi to your parents for us.
I will.
I make a friend just as I'm leaving.
Bit ironic when you think about it.
We cross a few mountains and end up in a town,
where there was an organization
with no official name.
But everyone just called it...
"Guardian."
Is this the stench of sewage?
Reality stinks.
Living as you did, in the highest stratum
of society, you tend to forget that.
Tennouji, you've left Kazamatsuri behind now.
Never forget that.
Got it.
This is as far as I can take you.
Go on in. I've told them you're coming.
You're not coming?
Do you want to be a soldier who
needs his hand held all the time?
No.
Get some basic training and start
turning yourself into a man.
Right now, you're not even halfway there.
Excuse me...
Nobody home, huh?
Hey.
Wait...
There you are.
Come this way.
O-Okay.
People who couldn't live a decent life
because of their special abilities...
Like me.
But, man...
These guys are all crazy strong.
Guess I should go with that.
If I hit the pedal, I can step it up as much as I want.
I just need to will it, and it'll happen.
I've never needed any training at all.
Which middle school are you from?
Nah, I should wait and see.
Second.
Second? My friend goes there!
That guy...
For real?
For real!
Don't I know him from middle school?
Gather round!
Due to its nature, there are strict restrictions
on info about our organization.
In this facility, you will undergo physical training,
and at the same time, strive to obtain
special skills in the art of hunting.
Training will be harsh.
In the worst-case scenario,
some of you may even die.
Stay focused at all times.
Each and every one of you
has outstanding powers.
Maybe you had to keep them
hidden in normal society,
but here you can show them off to their fullest.
Learn how to use them in a manner
befitting superhumans.
Any questions?
Yes.
You're... Tennouji?
Esaka-san recommended you, didn't he?
Uh, what exactly do we do here?
Put simply,
we eliminate daemons and keep
their existence a secret from society.
I suppose
you can consider it similar to what
you used to do in the forest.
So they did know about it.
Isn't he...
And so, we began training.
We spent the first two weeks marching.
Then came the core workouts,
practical exercises,
and theoretical lessons.
The class on daemons was the most interesting.
I learned that every daemon has a summoner:
people who create and use daemons.
As a group, they were referred to as "Gaia,"
and they were at odds with Guardian.
Gaia... People who control daemons.
In the end, this was a clash of people, of ideologies.
Sounds awfully complicated to me.
Hey there, Mighty Hero.
Imamiya?
What's with the hero stuff?
Well, you have real combat experience.
I gotta respect you.
Though it's a bit weird that you
were hunting daemons in secret.
What do you want?
It may not last long, but it seems
we're teammates starting today.
I expect great things from you.
Even Mikuni, the freak elite,
has got his eye on you.
Just so you know, I'm not that strong.
Come on, don't be so modest!
Didn't the Esaka-san recommend you?
I shoulda made friends with you in middle school.
We met in passing a bunch of times, right?
Did we?
Anyway, let's do this, partner.
Whatever.
Want me to buy you something to drink?
They put me on a pedestal, like so, but...
I will now announce the results
of the recent practical exam.
First, Mikuni.
Second, Kurokawa.
Third...
In the very first exam, I ranked 22nd out of 22.
I was a total scrub,
and my reputation tanked immediately.
21st, Nagai.
Last place, Tennouji.
Wh... Wh-Wha...
Hey there, Mr. Fibber.
Where's my dummy knife?
Get it yourself.
Huh? You're beyond useless, man.
If you ain't got no ability,
shouldn't you find other ways to contribute?
You listenin'?
Ow!
The hell was that for, Nishikujou?
Aren't you ranked sixth from the bottom yourself?
Hey, I'm technically the best on the team.
The best on the worst team.
Nishikujou Touka.
Another of my teammates.
Quit picking meaningless fights.
Okay, okay.
Let's go, Nagai.
O-Okay.
And there's Nagai.
She was also one of my teammates.
Sorry. I've really done it now.
I think his name was Mikuni.
An elite at the top of the class.
He did that with his bare hands?
I hear Esaka-san brought you here?
That's quite something, isn't it?
Sorry, you'll have to explain.
Esaka Sougen,
a veteran hero everyone in this trade knows.
Looking at your grades, I just don't get it.
Why did Esaka-san recruit someone like you?
Was there a special reason of some sort?
Even if there was,
how is it any of your business?
Do you think I'm too much of a scrub to be here?
Of course not.
Well, scrubs have to be more wary than others.
So you're saying there is a reason?
You're trying too hard to read into it.
And it's giving you away.
Coaxing information out of people
clearly isn't your strong suit.
Also, it looks like being a condescending
ass is second nature to you.
Them's fighting words.
You're nothing but small fry.
No argument here.
I was small fry who couldn't even
beat the girls in combat training.
So you're a slasher.
Secret's out, huh?
Superhuman abilities are broadly
classified into three types:
Poaching-Type
Poaching-types that specialize in hunting,
Slashing-Type
slashing-types that specialize in cutting,
Tainting-Type
and tainting-types that can control
the body's circulatory organs.
By the way, I have the tainting-type
ability to control blood.
Oh, yeah. You never were good at shooting, Nagai.
You wouldn't be a poacher.
Hey, please don't tell anyone.
I won't.
I have no one to tell.
I'm sorry.
I'd end up in last place if I lost to you.
Completely hopeless.
You're like an open book.
Seriously, man...
You've got no power or speed,
so at least use your brain.
Damn it.
Maybe I really should use it...
The power that gives me whatever power I want.
Hang on.
If controlling bodily fluids is my special ability,
then what is that thing?
That power to enhance
my physical abilities as I please.
I guess you could call it
the power to rewrite myself.
The power that'd make me as strong as I desired...
Something's off.
It's way too convenient.
If I rewrite my abilities enough,
then forget Imamiya and Nishikujou,
I could easily surpass Mikuni, too.
How does that power work? What's the cost?
It feels dangerous.
I probably shouldn't use it too often.
Esaka-san.
Tennouji?
How are you doing?
Not too good.
What are you saying, you fool?
I feel like I'm letting you down.
Did you see my grades?
I did, but your rank at the moment
doesn't matter in the least.
We're not looking for people with good grades,
but those who'll be useful.
Useful?
Allow me to train you a little.
You probably shouldn't be so partial to me.
And why is that?
It looks like you're pretty popular.
If someone like me kept you all to myself...
Quit putting yourself down.
You'll become a bottom feeder down there.
I'm sorry.
It seems I need to retrain you from the ground up.
Your bleeding has stopped.
Well, that's my ability.
You're honest.
I don't mind if you know about it.
Honest to a fault.
I won't attack.
Come at me.
That's all, huh?
Ten bouts, and I lost all of them...
Only when you go all-out
and hit your absolute limit
will your skills improve.
Do you want to go one last time?
I... do...
Good.
From the left
Take a step back
Jump
Go head-on
From the right
From the left
Take a step back
Jump
Go head-on
From the right
From the left
Take a step back
Jump
Go head-on
From the right
From the left
Take a step back
Jump
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Go head-on
Jump
Take a step back
From the left
From the right
Successive attacks at vitals
Use feints and see what he does
Look for an opening and surprise him
Invite an attack and counter him
Go stealth and stake it all on one big attack
Successive attacks at vitals
Use feints and see what he does
Look for an opening and surprise him
Invite an attack and counter him
Go stealth and stake it all on one big attack
Successive attacks at vitals
Use feints and see what he does
Look for an opening and surprise him
Invite an attack and counter him
Go stealth and stake it all on one big attack
Successive attacks at vitals
Use feints and see what he does
Look for an opening and surprise him
Go stealth and stake it all on one big attack
Invite an attack and counter him
Look for an opening and surprise him
Use feints and see what he does
Successive attacks at vitals
Go stealth and stake it all on one big attack
Invite an attack and counter him
Look for an opening and surprise him
Use feints and see what he does
Successive attacks at vitals
Go stealth and stake it all on one big attack
Invite an attack and counter him
Look for an opening and surprise him
Use feints and see what he does
Successive attacks at vitals
Go stealth and stake it all on one big attack
Invite an attack and counter him
Look for an opening and surprise him
Use feints and see what he does
Successive attacks at vitals
Go stealth and stake it all on one big attack
Invite an attack and counter him
Look for an opening and surprise him
Use feints and see what he does
Successive attacks at vitals
Go stealth and stake it all on one big attack
Invite an attack and counter him
Look for an opening and surprise him
Use feints and see what he does
Successive attacks at vitals
Go stealth and stake it all on one big attack
Invite an attack and counter him
Look for an opening and surprise him
Use feints and see what he does
Successive attacks at vitals
Go stealth and stake it all on one big attack
Invite an attack and counter him
Look for an opening and surprise him
Use feints and see what he does
Successive attacks at vitals
Go stealth and stake it all on one big attack
Invite an attack and counter him
Look for an opening and surprise him
Use feints and see what he does
Successive attacks at vitals
Go stealth and stake it all on one big attack
Invite an attack and counter him
Look for an opening and surprise him
Use feints and see what he does
Successive attacks at vitals
Go stealth and stake it all on one big attack
Tennouji.
Yes?
Something felt different
in that last move of yours.
I racked my brain to come up with that plan.
Did you use your ability?
No. Not at all.
I see. A coincidence, then?
It felt quite nasty.
Was my attack a good one?
No, it was trash.
Keep your attacks simple and bold.
Don't turn everything into a gamble
or a psychological battle.
Simple but effective use of power is the basis
of combat and the secret to success.
Got it.
Let's call it a day.
I read up on Esaka-san.
The Bayern Knights of the Green Sword
are the strongest group in Guardian.
They're the ones who saved me
in the forest that one time.
And Esaka-san is their leader.
I focused on training during the day
and read instructional books at night.
I'd never been so serious about anything before.
And, four weeks later,
my teammates and I
were ready for the last stage
in basic training, the mock battle.
Taking on lion dancers should be a piece o' cake.
They're basically giving us a handicap.
Are you kidding me?
That team only went in three minutes ago...
Team Imamiya, you're next. Bring it.
Listen, you'll die if you don't focus.
Be careful!
We gotta do this.
I'm seriously counting on you guys!
Man, this pisses me off.
Nobody can beat them.
Am I really superhuman?
Oh, Mikunicchi.
Way to go.
Human elite really are a cut above.
Two lions? They beat four instructors?
In The Tortoise and the Hare,
if the hare hadn't slacked off,
the tortoise would've never caught up.
And the world was full of hares that didn't slack off.
Congrats!
Grats!
On the last day of basic training,
a small party was thrown for us.
Listen up, rookies.
Your job is to run around on the job
and cause trouble for everyone.
Oh, please. I shine when it's for real.
Stop hitting on me. This is not the time.
What's wrong, Tennouji?
You should be celebrating, but you seem gloomy.
Esaka-san.
I've learned a lot here,
but I don't think I've improved much.
You're awfully negative.
But it might be better than being conceited.
I got a little better,
but the others have shown
much more improvement.
Listen to me, Tennouji.
There are many ways to live and prove useful.
If everyone were a "hero" like Mikuni,
the organization would crumble.
Even at your current ability,
you can be a fine soldier.
You've got the right stuff.
Thanks.
We'll be carrying out a major
operation in Kazamatsuri soon.
I'm sure a lot of people from this facility
will be asked to take part in it.
In Kazamatsuri?
That town has long been a holy place to Gaia.
Esaka-san.
By the way, Esaka-san...
I don't see Nagai around.
She quit.
It seems she felt she'd hit her limit.
She did?
Many superhumans don't take setbacks too well.
I hope you don't break.
The world you live in
nemuru koto no nai
Is one that never sleeps
anata ga tatsu sekai wa
And it's still so pure
mada muku na mama de
If I can leave something
moshi kono daichi ni
In the ground here
nanika wo nokoseru no nara
Let it at least be some kind of a trace
semete omokage wo
I can't even do a simple thing like gaze at the sky
sora wo miageru sonna kantan na koto mo
So I close my eyes
yurusarezu hitomi tojiru
I was only ever looking
tada hitotsu dake
For one thing
mitsukete hoshii no
Sunken in memories
kioku ni shizumu
Feelings of love
itoshisa wo
At the ends of time
ikusen no hate
I hope you stay safe
tadoritsuku anata ga
Until we meet again
sukuwareru you ni
It's fine as long as my song reaches you
kono utagoe todoku kagiri