One day, I realized I had nothing.
The pockets I once thought filled with happiness
The pockets I once thought filled with happiness had actually been empty from the start.
had actually been empty from the start.
I had never put in the effort
to fill them with anything,
I had never put in the effort to fill them with anything, so that was only natural.
so that was only natural.
But I couldn't understand even that.
My whole life I've just been walking
along an aimless, empty path.
My whole life I've just been walking along an aimless, empty path.
And then one day, before I knew it,
I felt like I had lost a great deal of time.
I have to rewrite it all.
I'll do things better next time.
I have to go.
The deserted city brings out
my boyish sense of adventure.
My body feels extremely light.
Maybe I could even fly.
Yeah, right!
Oh, so nights are quite bright.
Hey, you there.
What are you doing in a place like this—
You've gotta be kidding me...
Ow ow ow...
Wait, that was just a dream?
It seemed awfully real, though.
I feel like I've seen that girl somewhere before...
Could she be my lover from a past life?
Or maybe a fated rival?
Yeah, right. Who am I, Yoshino?
That reminds me,
wasn't there something I agreed to do today?
Who could it be at this hour?
My daughter, Kotori, has not come home.
Please, bring her back for me.
Right away, madam.
This is Madam Rikako,
the mother of my childhood friend, Kanbe Kotori.
A mere plebeian such as myself
would not dare defy someone so classy.
Kazamatsuri City Park
To be honest, this isn't the first time
I've gone to pick up her lost daughter.
The forest has always been
a popular playground for children.
But these days, Kotori's the only one still going.
She still plays in this forest all by herself.
I find that just a little bit saddening.
Hey, Kotori!
Kotori-san!
Oh, just a cat?
Don't scare me like tha—
Oh, it's just a...
Just a...
What is this creature?
I swear I've seen something like this before...
I know!
This thing is actually...
Just an ordinary mammoth!
Okay, then.
Kotori!
Kotori—
Jeez.
Hey.
Wake up, Kotori.
Come on, get up already.
Not gonna work, huh?
If that's how you wanna play...
Behold, Kotori.
Spare change, your favorite!
Here.
How's that?
Attagirl.
This way, this way.
Yeah, right this way!
She's like a zombie.
Okay, this way...
Kotarou-kun?
Morning.
Morning...
Um...
I'm home!
It's nighttime!
It's dark!
You fell asleep in the forest.
Um, does that mean you
carried me all the way here?
Something like that.
I see.
Sorry for the trouble.
You know, I had this amazingly happy dream.
What was it about?
I was at the vending machine
buying juice, and then...
coins just kept pouring out of the change slot!
Your happiness sure comes cheap.
Anyway, your esteemed mother
was very worried about you.
Shouldn't you head in now?
Yeah, I will.
Kotori...
See you tomorrow.
Yeah!
Good night!
Oh, and thanks for today.
Sure.
Guess I'd better head back, too—
Was someone watching me just now?
Something about tonight is giving me the chills.
The best option at times
like these is some solid shuteye!
Sleep!
Go to sleep, Kotarou!
Wh-What the hell?!
Was I dreaming?
Sorry, Kotarou-kun.
Go on without me again today.
I'm running a little late.
Gotcha.
I'll go on ahead, then.
Sorry about that.
It even left a mark.
All right, time to go.
The city of Kazamatsuri is currently
undergoing experimental afforestation.
There are various research facilities,
corporations, and so on in the city
which proactively tackle environmental problems.
This city is peaceful,
affluent,
and positively filled with greenery.
And in such a blessed city...
Let's live our once-in-a-lifetime
youth to its fullest, Yoshino!
In a way that'll make us forget
all about some bad dream!
Huh?
This guy with the wicked glare
first thing in the morning
is who you could call the one
and only delinquent in our class,
Yoshino Haruhiko.
For some reason,
he can't stand the very sight of me.
Ignoring me, huh?
I'm gonna give him a piece of
my Dead End Knuckle for sure.
And he's saying something alarming!
Hey shithead!
You fuckin' with me?!
Huh?!
C-Calm down!
Why are you so angry today?
Are you being serious?!
D-Did something happen, again?
In that case,
I'll use my fist to smash apart the door
your memories are locked behind!
Wait!
I'll open it up by myself!
Tennouji, I challenge you to a duel!
Sorry, Yoshino.
I don't really know much
about card games and stuff...
I meant in the fighting sense!
That's too bad, Yoshino.
We've built up such a delightful
friendship as besties.
How could we ever hit each other?
I don't recall ever being "besties" with you!
And today, I'll beat that fact into your very bones!
Sounds like you're serious.
Very well.
I accept!
Meet me behind the school building after school.
I'll give you a taste of "The End" right there!
Sure.
But just so you know,
I'm not the sort of guy to be "ended" that easily.
I wouldn't have it any other way.
Don't you dare forget this
flame-forged promise between men.
Of course not.
Sorry, Yoshino.
My memory's a bit shoddy.
Is that so?
Then I'll give you plenty of time
to remember it in the hospital!
Stop this, Tennouji Kotarou,
Yoshino Haruhiko!
If you do not cease your disruptions
in this sacred garden of learning,
then I, your class representative,
Konohana Lucia, won't stand idly by!
Okay, Konohana-san.
N-Nishikujou-sensei!
When did you get here?
The bell has already rung, you know.
Huh?
So take your seats, please.
Yes'm.
Curse you, Tennouji!
I'll remember this.
Why is it always me?
Oh, good morning, Kanbe-san.
Oh, m-morning.
And you know!
After that, Aizawa-kun from Class E
started going out with
Tsukimiya-san from Class C!
For real?!
Hey, Tennouji.
Anyone who disses me pays the price.
Even if it happened to be
God himself!
"Even if it happened to be God himself"?
You're fucking dead!
Make your peace!
In ten minutes, I'll flatten you
and drown your rotten corpse
in a sea of fresh blood!
"In ten minutes, I'll flatten you
and drown your rotten corpse"?
Son of a bitch!
What am I going to do with myself?
Even though I took an afternoon...
no, evening nap in the forest yesterday,
I totally overslept this morning.
Fall really makes you fall asleep, huh?
By the way, what are you two talking about?
It seemed like fun!
Let me join in.
This is none of your business.
It is a matter between men.
Talk about old-fashioned.
That kind of thinking is really
behind the times, you know?
She's right.
Say no to bullying!
Screw you!
I'm the victim here. We made a promise
between men and he stood me up!
Quit making such a big deal
out of a promise to hang out!
It was a duel!
Good, good.
You're like two bees in a pod.
You mean "peas"...
Don't make me laugh!
Who'd be friends with this loser?
I hear this sort of thing happens a lot lately.
Hook up!
Shack up!
Cut it out!
I'm gonna puke!
Lube up! Lube up!
Stop it, goddamn it!
Kotori doesn't have any friends.
Yoshino is also an outlaw in this classroom.
Unlike these two, I'm quite chatty with others,
but I don't exactly fit in myself.
That's why...
Ooh la la!
It's getting steamy in here!
Why are you on her side, asshole?!
What if people start shipping YoshiTen?!
Yoshino, you're quite the expert on this.
Leave me alone!
That's why I really feel
we'd be able to have a lot of fun
if we hung out together as friends.
My body feels kinda heavy...
That ghost last night
was the girl I saw in my dream
the other day, wasn't she?
Did I do something to get myself cursed?
Basking in the beauty of
Mother Nature really puts me at ease.
What the hell's a cardboard box doing here?!
Ow ow ow...
What the heck?!
Huh?
Uh, are you all right up there?
I am not all right!
I can't move!
O-Okay, I'll help you out,
so hold on a sec.
What's wrong?
I-If you look at my panties, I'll get mad!
Uh, I wasn't planning to,
but they're kinda exposed from this angle.
Please don't look, whatever you do!
Uh, I kinda have to look up to help you.
Then help me without looking up!
I'm saved...
How'd you end up there, anyway?
Actually,
I may not look it, but I'm a transfer student!
I managed to make it this far somehow, but...
I totally fell!
Um...
W-Well, don't worry about it!
These things happen!
I feel so humiliated!
A-Anyway, why don't we head to school?
I just need to carry this for you, right?
Up we...
I-It's heavy!
This thing weighs a damn ton!
Is something the matter?
N-No, nothing at all.
I just wasn't holding it right.
Um, your face is beet red, your veins are bulging,
and your arms are trembling.
I'll carry it myself.
I'm quite strong!
No!
That would hurt my pride as a man!
But I don't want you dropping it,
so I think I'll carry it after all.
I implore thee, milady, have mercy!
Give me one last chance!
Jeez, what's with you?
Please let go!
Ow ow ow...
What was that for?
S-Sorry.
Is something wrong?
I was right. Those are cherries.
Huh?
Wh-What do you mean, "I was right"?
So you did see them before!
I told you, I couldn't help you without looking up.
Thank you so very much for saving me!
But I hate you regardless!
Well, no biggie. It's not like we know
for sure that she'll join my class.
Ohtori Chihaya
Ohtori-san, please introduce yourself.
I-I'm Ohtori Chihaya. I just transferred here.
Ohtori Chihaya
P-Pleased to meet you!
Her uniform isn't ready yet,
so she'll be coming to school like this for now.
Like most transfer students, you'll be sitting
in the last row, beside Tennouji-kun.
Ugh.
Ugh?
Over here, right?
Okay,
I have a message for all of you
regarding next month's Harvest Festa,
so please take a handout and pass
the rest to the person behind you!
Hey, Cherr—
If you want to take part in any part-time
work or extracurricular activities,
be sure to submit an application in advance.
It's also recommended
you do extracurricular activities
Oh, no,
I, Tennouji Kotarou,
such as volunteering for
the duration of the festival.
sometimes get cherry confused,
so please keep that in mind.
We'll be going on break for a week,
but these are extracurricular lessons in a way,
Pleased to meet you, for what it's worth.
so be sure not to slack off too much.
But I still hate you.
Now, moving along...
Let me see that for a second, young lady.
Keeping a whistle clean is a good thing,
but it won't work if it's waterlogged.
You washed this before
you used it, too, didn't you?
Here.
Impressive as always, Kotarou.
Many thanks!
Warning.
No running in the hallways.
Did I just go from savior to offender?
I'm part of the Dissiplinay Committee.
I think you mean "Disciplinary."
That's it!
This Nakatsu Shizuru girl who I happened
to run into at some meeting before
is a cheerful underclassman who
occasionally messes with me like this.
So, what happens when I receive a warning?
You get punished according to regulations.
The regulations don't say anything about it!
Since you're in the Disciplinary Committee,
why don't you deliver my sentence?
Let's eat lunch in the courtyard, together.
Wait, did you do all this just
to ask me to eat with you?
But I'm sorry.
I've already finished my lunch for today.
I see.
Another day, okay?
Okay, Kotarou, it's a promise.
You got it.
See ya!
Ensnaring a Disciplinary Committee
member and covering up his crimes...
What are you jotting down? That's slander!
I'm Inoue of the newspaper club.
The newspaper club?
I've never seen any school newspapers.
That's because it's an online newspaper.
So, why does a newspaper club member
have business with me?
Tennouji-kun, is it true you
paid your way into our school?
You don't beat around the bush, do you?
I've never heard such a ridiculous rumor before.
"He vehemently refutes the accusations."
Why do I feel malice oozing out of your words?
I got in purely on merit.
Verify your facts!
"It's all been covered up perfectly"...
T-Talk about a twisted personality.
This is the true spirit of journalism!
Try and dig up dirt on me all you want.
I'm as clean as a whistle!
I'll do just that.
I'll have you in tears, confessing things
left and right before long!
What was that all about?
Inoue Scoop Memos
If someone sees this, there's a (HIGH) possibility
I will have to shut them up, permanently!
List of suspicious people at school:
3rd Year "Witch" Senri Akane,
president of the occult research club
Possesses authority far beyond that of a mere student
Extremely dangerous to make contact with (Plan carefully!)
2nd Year "Messiah" Tanuma Imako
Suspected to be the messiah
Under gag order?
Consider interviewing medical personnel
1st Year "Scissor Girl" Shinsaibashi Hitomi
Possibly repeating the school year
This girl is seriously bad news.
Under gag order?
Consider interviewing medical personnel
1st Year "Scissor Girl" Shinsaibashi Hitomi
Possibly repeating the school year
Possesses great athletic ability
but refused to join any sports clubs
-> 9/1 Transferred (No explanation why)
2nd Year "Gray Boy" Tennouji Kotarou
Lots of irregularities in his history,
like he has no background at all?
Possibility of a direct interview
2nd Year "Gray Boy" Tennouji Kotarou
Lots of irregularities in his history,
like he has no background at all?
Possibility of a direct interview
This girl might actually be really bad news...
Okay, then, Kotarou-kun.
I have a meeting for the
Spread the Green Committee,
so I'll see you tomorrow.
How enthusiastic.
Well, best of luck.
Hey, Ohtori.
Wh-What is it?
Please don't randomly speak to me!
If you don't have any plans after this,
how about I show you around town?
H-Huh?
Why would you do that?
Unfortunately, we've had our disagreements,
but I sincerely bear you no ill will.
Anyway, consider it my way of saying sorry
and atoning for my sins.
Wh-When you put it that way,
I have to say I'm sorry, too.
But I hate your big mouth,
and that will never change!
Oh, I'll make sure not to say
anything about your cherry—
A-Anyway, I have plans to meet up with
someone I know today, so I can't go with you!
Goodbye!
See you tomorrow!
She just transferred here,
and she knows someone already?
It's been a while.
You did well to make it here alone.
Why are you treating me like a kid?
The important part begins now,
so be sure to avoid standing out too much.
Yes...
By the way, does it seem like
you'll be able to make any friends?
Friends?
Is it okay for me to make friends?
Why not? It shouldn't be a problem.
Close encounters of the supernatural
kind night after night?
I wonder if the witch
could do something about it.
Witch?
Didn't you know?
She's kind of an underground
celebrity in this academy.
They call her the Underworld Don,
the Academy Witch, and stuff.
Sounds kinda fishy.
Apparently she has a command over magic,
superpowers, curses, spirits, and so on.
That's a lot of fingers in a lot of pies.
She rarely shows up for class,
but no matter how much time she takes off,
she's never held back or expelled,
and always advances to the next grade.
So mysterious!
How could a student have that sort of influence?
This isn't some manga we're in.
What is that?
"Third year, Witch, Senri Akane.
President of the occult research club.
Possesses authority far beyond
that of a mere student," huh?
Say,
want to go look for this witch?
It's not often that you
suggest something like that.
Is this love?
What, with someone whose
face I don't even know?
Desperate times call for
desperate measures, is all.
Okay.
Huh?
Let's look for her.
If you think it's a good idea,
then I think we should do it.
Besides, you might just end up
meeting someone special.
Thanks.
What's the plan?
Do we head out right away?
No, it'd be lonely if it was just the two of us.
We might be mistaken for a couple, too.
That doesn't sound too bad, actually.
No debauchery. Let's keep it PG.
That so?
How cold.
Let's hire a mercenary, then!
Yoshino...
Let's go on the adventure of our dreams!
I'll kill you.
And so, the two of them set off on
the adventure of their dreams alone.
How are we going to search for the witch?
We'll just have to ask everyone,
from top to bottom.
That's what I thought.
She's nowhere to be found!
Maybe she's hiding using magic or something.
If that's true, then it's all over.
I've heard the whole story!
Y-You're, um...
The so-called information broker in class...
Yamada-kun!
It's Suzuki!
That aside, how could you
be so distant, Tennouji-kun?
Now, please accept this.
Is this an occult club report?
Kazamatsuri High
Occult Research Club
Said to have been published in secret and
passed down among students for generations,
this is loot with a storied history.
I hope it proves useful in your quest.
Yeah, it's plenty!
Thanks, Satou!
Yeah, but it's Suzuki, Tennouji-kun!
Lovey-dovey?
Not even close.
Based on the report we got from Tanaka,
this is the place.
You mean Suzuki-kun.
Please excuse us!
It's dark!
Um...
Lights... lights...
Hey, is somebody here?!
I think that switch was around here...
The House of Wax!
What a pointless gimmick.
What the heck is this?!
You can hardly call these school facilities!
Maybe we have the wrong place?
No, all the books on the shelf
are related to the occult.
What should we do?
It doesn't seem like anyone is here.
It's evening already,
so it's possible nobody will show up today.
Want to leave a note?
I guess I should.
I'm looking for the witch to discuss
something occult related.
Please get in touch.
2-B Tennouji Kotarou
Damn, it won't turn on!
Evil thrives in the darkness!
I gotta get out of this room!
Wait, it won't open?!
Th-Theranden!
Theranden = "The veranda, then."
I have no choice!
Damn it!
A spirit field?!
Crap!
Open!
S-Someone!
Help me!
Help me! Kotori!
Kotori...?
Huh?
I guess I have quite the powerful sixth sense...
Excuse me.
Nobody home, huh?
I hope they at least saw the note.
You will die
in two days
It's addressed to me.
A questionnaire?
I don't see the point of most of these questions.
Q25) You have power and are discontent with this world. Tell me, do you wish to change this world? Or do you wish to change yourself?
The World
Myself
What is this, a zen riddle?
If I were to change something,
would it be the world or myself?
I...
Wanna drop by the arcade on the way home?
Yeah!
Wanna settle the score from the other day?
Let's grab a bite to eat first.
I'm gonna die if I don't eat something soon!
Kotarou!
Huh?
Wh-What is it, Ohtori-san?
Uh, why the pause?
Well, you did just call me
by my first name all of a sudden.
Uh...
So, what is it?
U-Um, about what you said the other day...
The other day?
What was that?
See you, Kota-san.
Yeah.
Spread the Green Committee activities again?
Do your best.
Looks like she wants to say bye to you, Kotori.
You don't need to provide running commentary!
I see.
See you later, Ohtori-san.
Y-Yes!
Goodbye, Kotori-san!
Come on, Kotori-san.
What are you supposed to do when someone
addresses you by your first name?
O-Oh, right...
Um, Chihaya-san.
Yes!
Then, Chi-chan!
Yes?
Oh, right.
Kotarou-kun, why don't you
show Chi-chan around town?
Oh, that's right!
You did mention that the other day, Kotarou.
Since you offered, I don't mind going with you.
Oh.
Yeah, I did say something like that.
By the way, Kotarou-san.
Yes?
She's calling you "Kotarou"?
What about it?
You two should go together, then.
See you, Chi-chan!
Oh, you too.
Goodbye!
Hey, what's with that?!
Coming or not, Ohtori-san?
C-Coming!
Say, Ohtori.
Why'd you choose to move
here at this time of year?
Well...
Because it was the perfect time of year to do so?
Huh?
Summer is too hot,
and winter is too cold.
What a wishy-washy reason!
A tour around town would never
be complete without coming here.
The Martel Group's Japanese headquarters, right?
Oh, you knew about it?
I mean,
it is a famous international environmental group.
What next?
Well...
I'm hungry, so I was thinking
of heading home for the day.
Yeah, the sun does look like it's going to set soon.
Um, thank you very much for today.
It was kind of fun.
Glad to hear it.
Take care on your way home.
Okay, then.
See you at school tomorrow...
Subject
(No Subject)
To K.T.
Tonight at midnight, classroom 2-A
Make sure you come alone
Refer to the map below for your entry route
From the Academy Witch
Being in the school at night
really gets one's blood pumping.
Hello?
Wait, nobody's here?
To K.T: Go to 1-C
I see.
So that's what you've got planned!
To K.T: Go to classroom 3-B
To K.T: Go to classroom 2-D
To K.T: Go to the library
To K.T: Go to the connecting hallway
Sugar-free, black
I get what she's doing,
but the witch is making me run around too much.
Was I imagining things?
What the hell?
What the hell is going on?
What the hell is she?!
Hang on.
Has this hallway always been this long?
In that case!
Damn!
Open!
Open up!
Is someone there?!
What the hell were those things?
This is insane...
Or at least I would like to say that.
Well, if superpowers exist,
the existence of ghosts, UMAs and other
supernatural phenomena isn't too surprising.
Either way,
my meeting with the witch can wait
until I find a way out of here.
Damn it!
How long is she going to keep chasing me?!
Ow...
Huh?
What is this?
Hey!
Seriously?!
Hey! Hey!
Damn it!
What should I do?
Give it to me...
Damn, another supernatural phenomenon?
Should I hit the accelerator?
I won't make it in time!
Give me your blood!
Curse you!
What is this thing?
A plant?
No, an insect?
Not to mention, it talks...
It hurts so bad!
Hey, are you all right?
It was a ruse!
Your blood is mine!
You nincompoop!
What are you trying to pull?
We're not allowed to let humans see us,
and here you are, attacking one?
Now there's another one.
Greetings.
My name is Pani.
Huh?
Oh, my regards.
I am Tennouji Kotarou.
My! What a polite, nice guy!
And yet Gil-chan here is so rude!
But the air was filled with the delectable
aroma of blood, so I couldn't resist the urge.
Looks like I scraped myself somewhere.
So, you're Pani and Gil?
Do you two have to suck blood to live?
That's just Gil-chan's hobby.
We can survive perfectly fine on water and light.
You're almost like plants...
Give me blood...
Jeez, fine.
Blood, blood...
Here.
Yummy blood!
Get your mouth off my finger!
I'll lick it all up!
Get off of me!
Wow, you're a real nice guy, mister!
All right!
With this, the contract is thus formed!
Let's get along!
Huh?
I want no part of it.
Shot down?!
Heck, better late than never.
What are you two, exactly?
We were born from dumped garbage.
Garbage?
Yes, garbage.
By the way, why is the atmosphere
getting fishier by the second?
Do you really know where the exit is?
Ack!
O-Of course!
We're not lost or anything!
Guess this is what you call
letting the cat out of the bag.
Jeez!
We followed you because you said
we could count on you, Gil-chan!
This kind of looks like the sort of place
the final boss would show up.
What was that just now?
This is bad.
We got lost and wandered right into its nest!
H-Hey, what is "it" supposed to be?
What the hell is that?
I have to hit the accelerator this time...
No, I can't.
I bet that won't be nearly
enough to handle this thing!
Don't worry.
It's still asleep.
Let's leave this place,
and be careful not to wake it.
Y-You two, be quiet.
Whatever you do, don't make any loud noises!
Got it?
Whatever you do...
Gil!
Gil-chan!
I'm. So. Sorry!
We're done for!
We're gonna die!
Not good, not good!
If it lands a single hit, I'll be going home in pieces!
You chased me all the way here?
Hey, behind you!
Damn it!
Hey, let's get out of here!
Wha—
Wh-What the hell am I witnessing?
This is bad!
The dimension is collapsing!
Please hurry up and get away from this place!
Ow...
A mannequin?
Huh, everything's back to normal?
Oh, yeah!
Gil! Pani! Are you okay?!
Was I dreaming or something?
For now, I've got to hurry to where the witch is.
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
To K.T:
Carry the Colonel
to the Room
E-Excuse me...
Miss Witch, are you here?
Wh-What?
Welcome, gypsy,
to my mystical room.
Episode 1:
The World or Myself?
hibiwareta yoru ni ikuseisou no sora
Our stars are only an illusion of the shattered night
utsuru bokutachi wa maboroshi
On the sky many months and years old
moshi kanau no nara kinou to wa chigau
I wish to leave behind my past self
hontou no boku wo kono chi ni
And have my true self here instead
bokura ikitekita koto kanata e kieteku
The proof of our existence vanishes beyond the horizon
sabitsuita reeru kimi wa tada tachitsukusu
Your life comes to a standstill like a rusted rail
ima kono ude ni nagareru aoi hi ga aru nara
So long as this blue fire flows through my arm
furikaeru kimi no te wo hiite
I'll be able to take your hand and stop you
mou nidoto hanasanai to hai no hoshi e chikau yo
Vowing to stars born of ashes never to let go
kakikaeru kono uta wo
I will rewrite this poem