Little by little, the ripples drew apart from one another
sukoshizutsu hamon wa hanarete itta
And before we knew it, they no longer overlapped
itsu shika hitotsu mo kasanaranaku natta
But it's okay as long as you're here with me
sore demo ii kimi to itara
When did I start feeling this way?
konna kimochi itsu kara idaita
This is the love story of a certain boy
tada hitori no shounen no koimonogatari da
To protect you till the end of time
eien ni kimi wo mamotte miseru
I'll etch this upon my heart
kono mune ni kizamikomu
When did it start being just the two of us, again?
itsu kara futarikiri ni natta n da kke
But it's okay
mou ii ka
Just smile
sonna koto waratte yo
On the eve of this world's end
owaru sono hi ni wa
It's already been three days
since that incident in the forest.
I haven't seen any of them since...
Or even heard from them.
And Inoue still hasn't been found, either.
No entry for students
Our everyday lives have come to an end.
Kanbe-san, Konohana-san,
and Ohtori-san are out sick again today.
There seems to be a cold going around,
so please be careful, everyone.
Lucia and Shizuru are members
of a secret organization called Guardian,
while Prez and Chihaya are members
of their enemy organization, Gaia.
That's why they disappeared.
That much makes sense.
But why Kotori? She had nothing to do with it.
The Harvest Festa is coming soon.
Stay focused,
and act responsibly as students
of Kazamatsuri Academy.
That will be all.
Hey, is Kanbe absent again today?
Huh?
Y-Yeah, looks like it.
It's not just her,
but Konohana and Ohtori, too.
Everyone who hangs out with you.
It's just a coincidence.
There's a cold going around, remember?
If you really are in trouble...
Huh?
Forget it.
No answer
I'm begging you, call me
Canceled
There's one other thing that bothers me.
Is there more to my power than
just rewriting my physical abilities
and enhancing myself?
I did it!
I think they're around here somewhere...
Where are they?
Found them!
Let's see just how sharp they are.
I-It sliced right through them!
I totally gotta try this out on all sorts of stuff!
Huh?
Did I leave the window open?
Tennouji...
Kotarou...
Wh-Why are you here?!
S-Stay away!
Stay away from me!
This is... an emergency.
Huh?
Hey!
She wasn't a ghost?
I have something to announce
regarding Inoue-san from Class 2-A,
who went missing a few days ago.
We were told that as of a few days ago,
Inoue had been admitted to
a hospital the next town over.
Special Offer
Free of Charge
Feecof
It's delicious!
We were only told about this now
because Inoue's memory was foggy,
and it'd taken some time to identify her.
While her memory hadn't cleared up yet,
the fact that she hadn't sustained
any physical injuries was a silver lining.
However, it was such a huge shock to her parents
that Inoue's whole family
ended up leaving Kazamatsuri.
Crap.
If she saw this...
Lucia would get mad at you,
Kotarou.
Sh-Shizuru?
Wh-Where have you been this whole time?
I came to say goodbye.
Wh-What the heck?
That's all.
There's no need for you to worry about a thing.
So please, lead a happy life.
Wait, Shizuru!
The occult club was a lot of fun. I loved it.
Shizuru!
What?!
What the hell?
Did someone break in?!
It was her, huh?
She's not here?
I sense something strange in... here!
Here!
Take that!
Over here!
It was a feint!
My name is Kagari-chan.
Okay...
To be blunt, that's all I remember.
So you're an amnesiac ghost?
I'm not a ghost. I'm Kagari-chan.
However,
I believe I was on some sort of important mission...
That is why I need to find myself.
I need to find myself.
Don't tell me...
You want my help?
What a strange dream.
Yeah, I knew it!
What are you up to?
Uh, I'm going to school.
Crap. What am I gonna do about her?
You should help me out instead
of bothering with school right now.
Don't be unreasonable.
Search for yourself by yourself.
I don't know how.
Go on a trip or something.
That's it!
Sorry, but could I get you to leave
the room for a minute?
Are you trying to hide something from me?
Won't you please leave for me?
What in the world have you been
doing for the last five minutes?
Simply being a modest gentleman.
Do not concern yourself over it.
More importantly, behold! The Internet!
Humans manage to shop and find
their way through life on the Internet.
Canceled
Today
No answer
I guess even at times like these, you get hungry.
What?!
Why can't I go into the classroom?
You're not in this class, are you?
Hurry back to your own homeroom.
What the hell is she doing?!
Wait. Everyone else can see her this time?
I found on the Internet that Tennouji Kotarou
was attending someplace interesting,
so I got jeal—
Tennouji?
I found that unforgivable and transferred in.
She knows him?
Huh?
Say what you will,
common sense dictates that suspicious
people should be sent to the staff room.
Don't think badly of me.
Yoshino-kun got destroyed!
That transfer student's strong!
It's the birth of a new gang leader!
What do you think you're doing?!
It's your fault for being mean
and leaving me behind.
No matter how much you
super-duper totally love me,
you should be more straightforward about it.
Hold on. What did you just say?
I know that human males tend to be mean
to the females that they like.
Say what?
I learned all about humans on the Internet.
Have I left you utterly speechless?
Next, I will learn about myself
in this institution you call a school.
Schools will only teach you academics.
How petty...
Um...
I'll show you around the building,
so try to make do with that.
Kay-o!
Way to go, Tennouji Kotarou.
"K-Kay-o"?
Just Kotarou is fine.
Saying the whole thing is annoying.
Okay, Kotarou.
By the way, what's with that uniform?
These clothes are part of my body,
so I can transform them freely.
I'm fabulous down to my very core,
so praise me, human.
Yeah.
I knew you definitely weren't human.
First, this is the cafeteria.
As you can see, this is where
people eat their meals.
I see.
It's a place where you sate
your appetites by devouring
other lifeforms that inhabit the same planet.
Uh, well, you're not wrong...
In that case, I desire shi-su!
There ain't any.
Why'd you suddenly start having worldly desires?
What is that?
Oh, that's a self-service coffee machine.
Feecof?
Special Offer
Free of Charge
Feecof
It's delicious!
Th-This is... myyum!
They have a reputation for using
such abysmally cheap beans
that you wouldn't want to drink it, even for free...
I'm positive this must have come from
the hands of a renowned feecof artisan!
Who created this feecof?!
I am asking for the hostess!
I would like to give my compliments directly
to the human who made this—
Sorry for the disturbance!
I rushed out of there without thinking
and ended up skipping afternoon classes.
Your love will come across as oppressive
if you're too mean, Kotarou.
As a sign of your love, you should offer me
three months' salary worth of feecof.
How much do you wanna drink?!
It's been a while since I've done something like this.
I-Inoue!
Why are you here?
Are you okay? Wait...
What happened in that forest in the first place?
U-Um...
Oh, sorry.
I'm glad you're safe.
Who were you again?
Huh?
I'm sorry.
I can't remember.
You know me?
Yeah.
You appointed me as your rival.
What were we rivals in?
Chasing after the mysteries of Kazamatsuri.
You were in the newspaper club,
and I was in the occult club.
Wow!
I was in the newspaper club?
Mysteries, huh?
Could it be?
A memory card?
I haven't checked what's on it,
but apparently I was holding onto it tightly,
refusing to let go,
even when I was unconscious.
Something tells me I need to give this to you.
Huh?
But I'm sure what's on this is—
It's okay.
I'm pretty sure this is what I came here to do.
Take care.
Yeah, bye bye.
Inoue!
About our competition...
You win!
Um...
Yay!
A piece of that human's heart has been destroyed.
Huh?
And yet, she accomplished
her objective all the same.
She entrusted it to you?
I didn't know you could do that.
The Kagari-chan exploration party has returned!
Don't loiter around my house so much.
It is quite spacious.
For you to own this all by yourself,
you must have done something
quite underhanded.
Don't make me sound so shady.
My parents are the ones who built it.
By "parents," you mean your genetic contributors?
I have not seen any sign of them.
They're busy with work.
They're researchers,
and they mostly stay over at work.
It's a corporation associated
with the environmental protection agency
known as the Martel Group.
It appears you have returned, Senri.
Yes.
My apologies for having been
out of touch for so long, Suzaki-san.
There was never any need for you,
the next saint, to attend school.
In future, please know your
role and act accordingly.
Accursed girl...
Are you finished...
with greetings?
Very well, then.
Now, please get started.
So then, regarding the Key's movements.
We haven't been able to pin down its location
since we detected its presence
in the city the other day—
O-Oh?
I'm back, Shimako.
Akane-san, it's absolutely
filled with cobwebs here!
I was planning to clean them up later!
An elementary schooler's excuse,
if I ever heard one.
Is the meeting over?
Yes.
Call it a meeting if you like,
but I was just put on wheelchair
duty the whole time.
It's been like that all the time lately.
When a saint is knocking on death's door,
they keep their successor close at hand.
And she's abiding by that old custom.
In other words,
Kashima Sakura's days are numbered?
More importantly,
where is the item I asked you for?
Right here.
This is it!
I've been waiting for this!
I was in such a hurry that
I couldn't bring it with me!
At last, I have returned...
to the motherly embrace of cyberspace!
Such unbecoming, vulgar words
from the next Martel... no, Gaia saint.
Still, I'm sure it never occurred
to Tennouji and the others
that the club room and the
Martel Japanese headquarters
were connected via a hidden passage.
Club activities were a lot of fun.
They may be our enemies,
but I'm glad we became friends.
Um, are Kotarou and Kotori all right?
I mean, they found out our secret and everything.
In regards to that female
student from the other day,
Lady Akane found out what happened to her
and sheltered her without any further incident.
There is a danger that as a witness,
a mark has been placed upon
Tennouji by both sides.
Um, what about Kotori?
Kanbe is...
No, never mind.
I don't have any conclusive proof yet...
It appears we will need to take
some precautionary measures.
I'm counting on you, Lucia.
It sacrificed its mobility
without so much as a struggle.
Did it underestimate us?
Now, Shizuru.
Exact your revenge.
This is goodbye.
Looks like it's all over, huh, Shizuru-kun?
Gramps.
It's over, but this isn't the end.
You're right.
Esaka-san, what about the summoner?
I struck him with my sword, but he got away.
That was fine work, you two.
You've grown.
Shizuru-chan!
You did it!
You're not hurt or anything, are you?
Ahem.
W-We have finished cleaning up
the daemons in this area, Instructor!
I mean, Esaka-san!
It has been some time since I retired,
but our enemy has become quite sloppy.
Kazamatsuri is holy ground
for the followers of Gaia,
so various summoners gather here.
Do you suppose this is due to the Key?
There seems to be little other reason
for such an abundance of daemons
to be deployed to the city and forest
before the Harvest Festa.
Esaka-san,
I am most grateful that all of you veterans
have returned to the front lines.
A storm is coming.
Steel yourselves.
Yes!
Now,
I've got a job for you two.
If I recall, you are Gil-san and Pani-san, correct?
This is awesome!
The crude sin you committed
against Chihaya-san...
Try as I might, I can't seem to change from the same old me
senobi shite mo kawarazu boku wa itsumo kono mama
It appears you will finally be able to make up for it.
After getting stranded in the forest,
"But you're fine the way you are," you say with a smile
"keredo sore ga suki" to hohoemi kakeru kimi
Inoue left behind notes
detailing her close encounters with the
many daemons and mysterious robed men.
And...
Her declaration that organizations
likely lurked in the underbelly of Kazamatsuri,
Rainy skies when I leave, north wind blowing when I come home
dekakegiwa no amazora kaerigake no kitakaze
accusations of the danger they posed,
and admitting that the occult was real,
Give me the courage to cover every inch of this whimsical world with my love
itsudemo kimama ni subete aiseru tsuyosa ga hoshii
all must have amounted to
a concession speech to her, in a way.
She must have been so upset.
Please switch with me.
Fresh tree leaves sway, as if bidding farewell
kyou mo isogigachi na hitonami wo miokuru you ni
The next part of the web comic
I am interested in came out.
Hey, don't mess with it from the side.
Huh?
What is this?
To waves of rushing people
osanai konoha ga yureteiru
Something about this place bothers me.
So it begins, once again
mata hajimaru yo
Huh?
Is this actually your birthplace or something?
Come on, it's about time we went too
saa bokura mo sorosoro ikou
Sorry for not responding.
I caught a terrible cold and will be out for a while,
but no need to worry!
In this stratified world, we entrust ourselves to time's steady flow
ikue ni mo kasanaru sekai de toki no nagare ni mi wo makasete
What's this idiot telling such an obvious lie for?
But...
You're okay, huh?
Let's walk towards our future, step by step, always just the two of us
kono saki mo itsudemo futari no ayumi wo tsudzukete ikou
Kotori...
Make sure you get better.
Want me to nurse you and wipe away your sweat?
I don't need an eternity, I'm happy with something small
eien nante nozomi wa shinai tatoe chippoke demo kamawanai
No debauchery. Let's keep it PG.
But at this very moment, there's no doubt that we are here
tashika ni, ima koko ni bokura ga iru koto
I have to hurry.
And what is happiness but this?
sore ga shiawase
natsukashisa mo kieta yume
Losing myself in a dream where even nostalgia lost form
Episode 8
My Name Is Kagari-chan
mayoi kono te ga samishiku kaze wo nadeta
Lonely, I reached out with my hands to feel the wind's gentle caress
kotoba wo shiranai mama naraba
The names of those emotions still eluded me
kono hitomi wo tojiru koto mo
Even closing my eyes for eternity
kantan datta no ni
Should have been simple
hajimete fureta nukumori
But I felt warmth for the first time
chiisaku mebuku kodou ni
A tiny soul began to bud within my heart
tomadoi wo oboeta
And I learned of bewilderment
anata no koe sagashite mugen no michi wo yuku
Walking on the path of eternity, searching for your voice
hoshi no hajimari wo shiru tada sore dake
I'm led to the time when stars are born, nothing more
kuchi ni nokoru nigami mo hiroku mada ki ni naru
This bitterness that lingers inside my mouth tempts my curiosity
itsuka deau anata he saigo ni hohoemi wo
So I'll offer you one last smile before we meet again