Monitoring Tennouji Kotarou and Kanbe Kotori?
What? You grown attached to them or something?
They both witnessed the daemons in the forest.
There is a risk Gaia will go after them.
Well, you've got a point.
We need to keep an eye on Tennouji just in case.
What about Kotori?
That schoolgirl is missing, actually.
She is?
I-In that case, I'll at least take
care of Kotarou personally—
Nope.
That ain't happening,
what with your cover blown and all.
However!
If there were some elite super agent
whose cover was still intact,
who knew Kazamatsuri like
the back of his own hand...
What do you think?
There's someone that
remarkable in this organization?
Little by little, the ripples drew apart from one another
sukoshizutsu hamon wa hanarete itta
And before we knew it, they no longer overlapped
itsu shika hitotsu mo kasanaranaku natta
But it's okay as long as you're here with me
sore demo ii kimi to itara
When did I start feeling this way?
konna kimochi itsu kara idaita
This is the love story of a certain boy
tada hitori no shounen no koimonogatari da
To protect you till the end of time
eien ni kimi wo mamotte miseru
I'll etch this upon my heart
kono mune ni kizamikomu
When did it start being just the two of us, again?
itsu kara futarikiri ni natta n da kke
But it's okay
mou ii ka
Just smile
sonna koto waratte yo
On the eve of this world's end
owaru sono hi ni wa
Episode 9
Fate Begins to Turn
I finally got in touch with Kotori.
May as well relax for once and take a bath—
Huh?
Kotarou.
I need to talk to you.
Hey now! Think about where we are, first!
Whoops, my bad!
Me, of all people...
It slipped my mind that humans have
a custom of being naked while in the bath.
On that note,
I need to talk to you.
He—Wai—N-N-No!
Kagari-san, you pervert!
I've seen this guy's face somewhere before.
He is quite a nice guy!
Excellent!
Hey. What happened to all that stuff
about searching for yourself?
This house is far too small
for a big shot such as myself.
As part of my search for myself,
you must take me to the stylish and trendy city.
I was under the impression that the cafeteria's
feecof was the pinnacle of quality,
but this is superb, too!
Yeah.
I more or less understand
how your palate works now.
This is one of my precious days off, too.
What am I doing?
Found him!
There he is.
I HAVE TAKEN THE LIBERTY OF CLOSING
THE SHOP FOR BUSINESS TODAY.
PLEASE
FORGIVE
ME.
Man, he's off today?
I figured Esaka-san would be
well-versed in unusual subjects.
Oh, well.
Let us ask my fans for information about me.
And who would they be, exactly?
A number of people have been following
us ever since we set foot in the city.
I am positive they are what you
would call "fanatical groupies."
Seriously?
She's right. I do get the feeling someone is there.
Could this have something to do
with the incident in the forest?
Why are we running away?
It said on the internet that fanservice is
important for those who aspire to be idols.
I'm revoking your net privileges starting today.
He spotted me?
He ran away!
Was his intuition always that good?!
Let's head him off from above!
This way!
Battle Kick!
What school you from, punk?
That the only damn thing you know how to say?!
Y-You!
Ain't you the King's—
Let's leave it at that.
Th-The King!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Don't call me your king.
Why, you ask?
For I am but a lone wolf without a pack—
Y-You're Tennouji!
Oh? If it ain't the Yoshing.
Don't randomly mash those names together!
You're playing around with
a different woman already?
Talk about living the high life.
It's nothing like that.
Sorry, but I don't have time
to argue with you right now.
It seems we're being chased.
Did something come up?
Something like that.
So, yeah, later.
Wait up.
Amateurs end up wandering through
this trash heap of a labyrinth forever.
Take a right at the end of the alley.
A world of light suited to you softies awaits.
What is this Yoshing person talking about?
Hey, that nickname's starting to spread!
Don't get the wrong idea.
The one who will end your pathetic life
will be none other than I.
D-Damn you're cool, King.
Thanks, man.
Get out of here already.
Also, Kotori really did catch a bad cold.
She finally got in touch with me yesterday.
Like I care.
This thing's... a dog, right?
There's no opening.
Whoever makes the first move will lose!
Gil-chan, I am sure he is right below us!
Dive bomb!
Oh, dear. I should have known better.
What are these bugs?
No.
They're talking daemons?
You're open!
You damn mutt!
Who are you guys?
This is territory claimed by the abyss,
where light does not reach.
Come again?
However, even the deepest depths
of darkness has its own order.
Fighting a dog is disgraceful, old man.
Huh?
The hell you talking about?
And what do you mean, old man?
I'm still in my twenties—
Go to Hell!
Yoshino must have pulled
through for us somehow!
Kagari!
Hey, what's wrong?
Kotarou...
I ran out of feecof...
Caffeine addiction?!
I want it...
I want it!
C-Call the cops...
Stop it!
We're in public, and there's a lotta people around!
Stop saying extremely misleading things
that'll destroy my social standing!
What a drain...
Oh, please go ahead.
Huh?
Lucia?!
What are you doing here?
I-I could ask you the same, Kotarou!
I've been worried about you!
You all disappeared at the same time!
For your sake, this is for the best.
Shizuru said the same thing,
but how could I accept that?!
We're all friends from the occult club!
Is it ready yet, Kotarou?
Hurry.
I want it right away...
Wait.
This isn't what it looks like!
You're having plenty of fun even
without the occult club around,
aren't you, Tennouji-kun?
You're suddenly acting like you don't know me?!
To be serious for a second,
both we and Gaia are treating you
and Kanbe Kotori as subjects
requiring special care.
But, as long as nothing of note happens,
surveillance of you will be dropped eventually.
So forget about us already,
and lead an ordinary life.
Good work!
Did anything happen on your end?
No. Nothing in particular.
Really?
Nothing out of the ordinary in my area, either.
Now we just have to wait for
our senior colleagues to report in.
Esaka-san and the others
are all former members of the
Bayern Knights of the Green Sword, right?
Yes.
They are Guardian's greatest warriors.
When I was still a trainee,
he would occasionally help out as an instructor.
But...
Having them return to active
service does give me hope.
Another way to think of it is...
Gaia has become so active
that they had to come back.
I'm satisfied.
After spending all day roaming the city,
I finally understand.
This canned coffee reigns supreme!
Oh, I see.
So, how's your memory coming along?
Jeez...
I guess it's about time we headed home, then.
Hey, I remember you.
Y-You're...
And here I thought you were
just some shitty hunter.
Hey.
How'd you take down my dog?
Are you a member of Gaia?
What the hell else would I be?
Are you really from Guardian?
Who are you?
Kotarou is my minion.
I won't allow him to be harmed.
Kagari!
You're pissin' me off.
Outta my way, woman!
Stop!
Hey, hey. What do we have here?
You sure are a lot tougher than you look.
Who the hell are you, you bastard?
Interesting.
Go.
Hey. What's with the girl?
She doesn't look like one of
Guardian's superhumans to me.
Huh?
That reminds me.
I've sensed her somewhere before...
I get it.
Looks like I reeled in the one that got away!
What's going on?
It's gotten really hot for some reason!
Come out, Fogo.
Ch-Chibi-Moth!
Why are you here?
Are you telling us to run away?
Got it!
I'm legging it as fast as I can.
Don't bite your tongue!
Damn punk.
You think I'm just gonna let you flee?!
Adios!
How's he so fast?
This is gettin' kinda fun!
I ended up using my newly rewritten powers in public,
but at least we'll be okay now.
That was impressive.
I really am no ordinary person.
I definitely have some grand mission,
like saving this planet.
Yeah, I'll bet.
Did that guy from this afternoon
make it all the way here?
K-Kotarou!
She's scared?
S-Sorry to intrude!
The feecof beans I secretly ordered online
and hid in the fridge were safe!
I'm definitely revoking your net privileges.
Wait a sec.
I vaguely remember seeing
that bug somewhere before.
Who the hell you calling a bug, ya jerk!
I'll teach you a thing or two for lookin'
down on us, you rotten little brat!
So, is there anything else you'd like to say?
I'll bow down before you, so please help me!
Not this life again.
This apartment is even smaller
than the previous one.
So you are those mysterious
creatures from before.
Hey.
You're daemons, right?
What? You got a problem with us being daemons?!
No.
I'd just seriously like to ask you
about Gaia and daemons and stuff.
Ask all you like, but we are
nothing but discarded daemons.
We do not know very much.
Not very useful, are you?
What the heck!
You're awfully cold for someone
I formed a contract with!
A contract?
Oh, you mean that?
I'm a super useful daemon!
We followed you around all day today,
and you didn't notice at all!
Oh, really?
You two were there, too?
Spill the beans! What were you up to?!
We were ordered to keep an eye on you!
Ordered?
By who?
W-Well...
Chibi-Moth!
What are you doing here?
Who is it?
Kotori!
Kanbe Kotori
Yes, hello?!
Kotori!
Kotori, is that you?!
Kotarou-kun, please.
I want you to come to the forest right now.
Along with that girl.
Huh?
What do you mean, come to the forest?
Sorry.
I've been watching you two
through Chibi-Moth's eyes this whole time.
Through Chibi-Moth?
Since you were marked by Guardian and Gaia,
I was sure you'd be dragged into it all
if they uncovered her true identity.
You knew about Guardian and Gaia?
I didn't know that Chi-chan and the others
were organization members, though.
You'll tell me everything, right?
Yeah.
I'll tell you everything I can.
Here?
But there's nothing—
Huh?!
Hurry inside!
It'll close right away!
Is this really the forest?
And there are daemons...
Sorry for rushing you!
They would have found this place
if I didn't close the barrier right away!
Kotori!
It's been a while.
Welcome to Kotori-san's secret base!
Secret base?
I feel as though I know this place.
Well of course. You were born here, Kagari.
But what a surprise.
You were like a ghost at first.
And now, you're so human.
Kotori.
You could see Kagari from
the very beginning, couldn't you?
Yeah.
I could see her all along.
Why didn't you tell me?!
It wasn't something I could bring up easily.
Does that mean you know everything about me?
Except for what you were up to
whenever you escaped this place.
I've been waiting to meet a human like you!
Huh?
It appears my journey to find
myself has reached its finale!
Oh, thanks for your help.
You can go home now.
She cast me aside?!
You really are a completely different person now.
Damn you!
Let me out of here!
There are treaties against abusing prisoners!
Are these all daemons?
Yeah.
They're all daemons I created,
so they're not dangerous.
You created them?
And that little one is actually a daemon, too.
I made him look like a dog with a
technique that disguises his appearance.
Kotori, what were you doing in this forest?
If you use daemons, does that mean...
We may share the goal of safeguarding the Key,
but I'm not with Gaia.
And naturally, I'm not with Guardian, either.
I'm a druid.
A druid?
Hey, do you know about mistletoe?
If I recall, it's a parasitic plant that grows on trees?
A long time ago, a summoner sealed
all his knowledge into some mistletoe
and left it for future generations.
He did that so he could pass on his knowledge,
and his duty, to one who was worthy.
It was ten years ago, I believe.
Deep within the forest,
by sheer coincidence, I met that mistletoe
and became a druid.
That's when I gained the knowledge,
and had a number of wishes granted.
An accident ten years ago?
Why do I have no recollection
of such a thing happening?
And, in exchange for those wishes,
I was bestowed with a duty:
To protect the Key.
To protect Kagari.
We call that individual the Key.
I see.
Kagari was the Key?
You even knew about the Key?
Uh, kind of.
So ultimately, what am I, Kagari-chan?
Or should I say Key-chan?
Key-chan?
It might be best if you saw for yourself.
Gaia and Guardian have been fighting
over the Key for a long time now.
All so they can fulfill the same goal.
The same goal?
To save this world.
Save the world?
Right now, Kazamatsuri City
is in a volatile situation
due to an individual who holds the key
to Earth's survival or its destruction.
What's going on?
This is where I met that mistletoe,
and also where Kagari was born.
It's a power spot.
This place is...
When we came to the forest with the occult club,
you wandered over here, remember?
That happened because Kagari
carelessly lifted the barrier.
I was so surprised!
Now, come over here.
It looks just like that power of mine.
Oh, you'll melt if you touch it, so be careful.
This is the energy of the very Earth itself.
The Key is born from here, in human form,
as an avatar of the Earth.
Did you remember anything?
It looks like it would feel great to soak in.
You'll melt if you do that!
Kotarou-kun, do you remember
the rainbow-colored swamp?
That was actually caused by this power spot.
It wasn't environmental pollution?
Thanks to this,
I can control lots of daemons
without sacrificing my lifespan.
Your lifespan?
Practitioners control daemons
by chipping away at their own life.
The stronger, or larger the number,
of daemons you control,
the more life they consume.
B-By the way, why was Kagari
born from here again?
I don't know all the details.
But, depending on the Key's final ruling,
they say Salvation will occur.
Salvation?
Nobody's ever witnessed it,
so we won't know until it happens.
Sorry to drag you into all this strange stuff.
Kotori.
What are you talking about?
Aren't we...
I love you!
I want you to go out with me!
Thank you.
I'm very happy.
But I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry!
Aren't we best friends?
Kotarou-kun...
Besides, this is irrefutable proof of the occult!
Right here's my ticket straight
to Prez's sweet boobs!
Come to papa, my sweets!
Jeez...
No debauchery. Let's keep it PG.
Kagari?
I can hear a song.
Huh?
Are you all right?
natsukashisa mo kieta yume
Losing myself in a dream where even nostalgia lost form
I've been getting terrible headaches lately.
Well, yeah.
Anyone would if they listened
to that weird singing all day.
I hate that song.
mayoi kono te ga samishiku kaze wo nadeta
Lonely, I reached out with my hands to feel the wind's gentle caress
By the way, any updates regarding
what we discussed before?
Um, it will probably happen this evening.
Get it done ASAP.
kotoba wo shiranai mama naraba
The names of those emotions still eluded me
The situation's only going
to go downhill from here.
Does that mean...
A bloodbath between hunters and summoners
is about to take place very soon.
kono hitomi wo tojiru koto mo
Even closing my eyes for eternity
kantan datta no ni
Should have been simple
Not only did you lose the target,
you came back all roughed up?
What do you want me to do?!
hajimete fureta nukumori
But I felt warmth for the first time
Where in the world did Kotarou and Kotori go?
I couldn't exactly use my powers
on ordinary citizens!
Leave it at that.
chiisaku mebuku kodou ni
A tiny soul began to bud within my heart
Now that Gaia's using the Harvest Festa
to bring in a large number
of summoners to Kazamatsuri,
tomadoi wo oboeta
And I learned of bewilderment
we have no time to waste on unknown factors.
Starting now, we will shift
our full focus to locating the Key.
anata no koe sagashite mugen no michi wo yuku
Walking on the path of eternity, searching for your voice
Steel yourselves.
We are looking at something more serious
than a minor skirmish this year!
Yes, sir!
hoshi no hajimari wo shiru tada sore dake
I'm led to the time when stars are born, nothing more
Splendid. I believe I have
some idea of the location.
But there's some sort of barrier!
kuchi ni nokoru nigami mo hiroku mada ki ni naru
This bitterness that lingers inside my mouth tempts my curiosity
You cannot enter unless
it is opened from the inside!
That won't be a problem.
Thank you for your hard work.
Leaving her side right now
does fill me with much worry,
itsuka deau anata he saigo ni hohoemi wo
So I'll offer you one last smile before we meet again
but this, too, is for Chihaya-san's sake.
Prepare yourself, Kotarou-kun.
I finally caught you.
Shimako, you're a genius at hide-and-seek.
You're preparing something like this?
You really do intend to bring
an end to this world, don't you,
Kashima Sakura?