After taking the first step, you'll be dying to know
Our story doesn't begin without a little curiosity
Even if I say that my schedule is all hectic, I'm still excited
It's a little sucky sometimes, but it's better than being bored
A colorful calendar means I have no time for surprises
I make my way through each day, having lots of fun
If you want to truly feel that fulfilling thrill
Then don't forget this!
After taking the first step, you'll be dying to know
Love, the future and your dreams can't begin without a little curiosity
Don't be troubled or be hesitant
You are who you are
If you don't stand out you won't get your chance
So stand tall on your tippy toes
Let's make something happen that we'll never forget!