I wonder if following the theory of love is the right thing to do...
I undo my ponytail and sigh in the mirror
I wonder how I look in your eyes
I can feel exciting things coming, just like in those girly comics
I put on my usual facade, wondering if you can see through me
Even though you were closer than anyone else
Even though we were getting along better than anyone else
For some reason, until yesterday the distance between us was somewhat painful
According to the theory of love, a girl grows up every time her heart skips a beat
I'm not a child anymore, and yet I don't know how to react when you praise me
"Don't make me worry", you say, as you take my hand and never let it go
Let's fall into eternal love, to the sound of our pounding hearts