"When I was lost in that village,
with nowhere to go,
my parents found me and took me
back home to the USA with them."
That fantasy was what
kept my world afloat.
My parents wish the best for me
and provide me with familial warmth.
So I don't need any memories of my past life,
or of my previous name.
So why...
Where am I supposed to
take my first step towards?
Ru
Ha
Ka
Chi
BLOSSOM
into
the
scent
of
rain
until
I
was
breathless
Straight
ahead
chased
the
rainbow
in
the
distance
Will
I
ever
reach
Countless
colours
merge
together
to
become
harmony
suddenly
born
strange
song
with
building
a
bridge
of
echoes
to
far
away
could
make
our
own
rainbow
from
here,
where
we've
come
then
the
colours
in
it
would
be
ours,
ours
only
million
nameless
hues
tion
would
form
its
gradient
rainbow
Let's
not
fear
the
pain
and
push
open
the
door
bathe
in
the
light
of
youth
THE EXIT GAME
October
After Narushima-san joined us,
so did a bunch of other experienced players,
and we went from five members to ten, but...
Let's stop here for today.
Excuse me!
What is it, Homura?
Um, I think I'm holding the band back.
I'm the least experienced one here.
I don't want to disappoint Narushima-san.
As such, could I ask you to give me
some private lessons, Kusakabe-sensei?
I don't think that's what
Homura-san needs right now.
She has to start from scratch and learn the basics under a specialist flute instructor!
We're seriously aiming for Fumon Hall,
so please make the lessons
as hard as possible!
I'll ask someone I know.
Kaneko Flutes
Hurry up, Narushima-san!
Gosh, you're so pushy.
My arms can't handle this weight...
Help me, Kamijou-kun!
O Romeo, Romeo!
Wherefore art thou Romeo?
You've got the wrong person.
I'm the White Fairy!
Juliet, I'm over here.
Put your heart into it, Maren!
What is this farce?
"Romeo, Juliet, and the White Fairy", apparently.
What are you doing here?
Narushima-san, too.
Helping out the drama club.
They get to use the stage in exchange for
helping an amateur theatre group clean up.
Are you done?
What, you wanna work for us too?
What gave you that idea?!
Nicely expressed.
You're a once-in-five-years talent.
The drama club welcomes you!
All right! Retreat in fifteen minutes!
He's Nagoe Shunya, the president
of the drama club, and my classmate.
I may be the hero who
resurrected the drama club,
but I'm a first-year like you.
No need to be polite.
Who would?
Nagoe.
Sorry, I don't think I can do this after all.
Got it. I'll get someone to stand in.
My bad.
Why is Maren in the drama club?
Maren?
Maren Sei.
A Chinese-American.
Sei's his name, and Maren's
how you say his surname.
So you say Maren's name as Sei Maren?
These two want to steal my Maren.
"Steal"?
Don't make us sound like
something we're not!
Do you know Maren, Narushima-san?
We were in different junior highs,
but we met during joint practice
between our concert bands.
He plays the sax.
His father's a former saxophonist,
so his skills were a cut above the rest.
Plus, he was a good teacher,
kind to those around him.
He would always give us solid advice.
Why would a guy like that
join the drama club?
Because I'm his best friend,
and I recruited him when he wasn't in any clubs.
He doesn't seem to have
any acting talent, though.
Why did he give up the sax?
He was completely unlike the Maren
I knew back there, too.
I'm not his counsellor.
But you're his friend, aren't you?!
You seem awfully worked up.
Is he special to you or something?
What the hell?
You got the hots for him?
No way!
The oboe is in love with the sax.
And so is the horn.
If the higher-register trumpet
and sax aren't played well,
the oboe and horn won't get to shine.
Maren used to say his dream was
to share the stage with his father.
He wouldn't give up the sax just like that.
There has to be a reason.
He started acting weird during spring break,
after we graduated junior high.
So what happened?
Beats me.
I told him to join the concert band as soon as we started high school.
But he didn't.
Yeah.
How about asking him
to join one more time?
It won't work.
Not unless his issue is resolved.
"Issue"?
Besides, I was the one who
asked him to try acting.
I can't just turf him out to join a different club
without putting him on stage even once.
If only we could set the stage for the drama club,
the concert band, and Maren to all be happy.
What could Maren's issue be?
A broken heart, maybe?
Or maybe his parents banned him from
playing the sax because his grades dropped.
He's not you, you know.
Maren's always placed
in the top ten of his grade.
Besides, he's from a family of musicians.
Look at this. I borrowed it from Nagoe.
Maren's parents, apparently.
Whoa! They put out an album!
Huh? His parents aren't Asian?
Maren's adopted.
And he's known that from a young age.
Oh...
What are you writing?
A play with a happy ending for all.
I had a little brother?
My real hometown?
My real parents?
In secret?
Why?
Heihaizi...
He plays the sax too?
Why me?
Because of my legs?
I was abandoned?
Was I abandoned?
Was I abandoned?!
No!
How are your flute lessons going?
Rough.
I should quit the flute and play
beer bottles or something instead.
What about fingering and chord practice?
Practicing hard at home
has become a habit of mine.
Our band is full of nice people,
so taking tough classes will help—
It's complete!
I'm off to the drama club.
Now we'll all be happy!
Wait, Haruta!
Drama
Club
Atelier
Cool story.
My masterpiece!
Do you think so little of theatre?
At least this is way more interesting than
"Romeo, Juliet, and the White Fairy"!
You what?!
I've been meaning to say this for a while,
but you're terrible with words.
I mean, you call your club room an atelier!
Haruta, that's going too far.
Look who's talking.
The useless noise your band
makes disturbs our practice!
Especially the flute.
Say what?
Don't you sense anything
from being insulted like this?!
Calling it "useless noise"
is going too far, isn't it?
It is!
Pull yourself together, Homura-san!
Also, Chika-chan and I have
more acting talent than you.
Oh? You're writing cheques you can't cash.
Very well.
We'll take you on at theatre.
Bring it.
Calm down, both of you.
There's three of you, huh?
Then we'll go with me,
our star actress over there, Fujima Yaeko...
Call her Maya.
Fujima-san, help me stop those two.
Right now, she's following my orders
and method acting as a wolf girl
who was taken in just six months ago.
She's the real deal!
We'll give you a handicap and
pick Maren as our last member.
I can't do it.
That's exactly why you'll be a handicap.
The time: 1PM on Saturday.
The drama club versus the
concert band in an acting contest.
Is that all right, Sensei?
Kusakabe-sensei?!
Challenge accepted.
12:50pm on Saturday
I can't do this!
No way!
Enough of that, okay?
The competition will be
a simple unscripted skit.
The premise will be fixed, and we have to
play a role that suits the situation.
And then exit within the time limit.
"Exit"?
Getting off stage, basically.
Yes, I call it...
the "Exit Game".
BLOSSOM
"Exit Game"?
Make up whatever reason you like.
Use your imagination,
and find a way to make your exit.
And the opposing team will prevent it.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
Let us show you an example, then.
Teacher's Farewell Party
Leave before the closing speech!
Sensei's speech will start any minute now.
Teacher's Farewell Party
Leave before the closing speech!
Um, my stomach hurts, so I'll be leaving.
Teacher's Farewell Party
Leave before the closing speech!
What are you saying?
Lots of Sensei's doctor friends
are here at this party.
Have one of them take a look at you.
Nagoe just prevented
Fujima-san's attempted exit.
Ah, I see.
I'll give it a shot, too.
Teacher's Farewell Party
Leave before the closing speech!
Huh? Fujima-san?
You're Fujima Yaeko-san, right?
Long time no see!
Leave before the closing speech!
Well, isn't she a good sport.
Chika-chan's got guts, if nothing else.
Ring-ring! Beep!
Teacher's Farewell Party
Leave before the closing speech!
Hello?
My mother got into a traffic accident?!
Got it. I'll be right there.
Sorry, I have to leave immediately.
Leave before the closing speech!
Hello, this is Fujima.
What was that?
Leave before the closing speech!
Homura-san's mother didn't
actually get into an accident?
Leave before the closing speech!
Sure, I'll let her know.
Aren't you glad, Homura-san?
I see.
You understand the rules now, right?
Here's the actual theme
for the contest, then.
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
Can you exit your hideout with fifteen minutes
left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
"Counterfeiters!
Can you exit your hideout with
fifteen minutes left until the statute of limitations expires?!"
The time limit is fifteen minutes.
And, as a special rule today,
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
Victory Conditions
the drama club and the concert band
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
Victory Conditions
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
Victory Conditions
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
Victory Conditions
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
Victory Conditions
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
Victory Conditions
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
Victory Conditions
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
Victory Conditions
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
OR
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
Victory Conditions
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
OR
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
Victory Conditions
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
OR
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
Victory Conditions
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
OR
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
Victory Conditions
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
OR
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
Victory Conditions
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
OR
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
Victory Conditions
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
OR
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
Victory Conditions
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
OR
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
Victory Conditions
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
OR
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
Victory Conditions
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
OR
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
Victory Conditions
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
OR
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
Victory Conditions
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
OR
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
Victory Conditions
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
OR
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
have to make Narushima and Maren,
respectively, exit to win.
- Nagoe and Fujima make Narushima exit.
- Kamijou and Homura make Maren exit.
Victory Conditions
Wait, does that mean I'll be bullied by
those two demonic drama club members?
Do your best, Narushima-san.
We're the ones who have
to do our best, Chika-chan.
We have to make Maren exit first.
If we establish any
additional facts during the skit,
they'll be written on this board each time.
My, it's starting to rain.
Additional Premises
- It's raining.
Basically, any careless statements
will further limit our options.
Additional Premises
I see.
Are you ready?
Best of luck!
Don't lose!
Listen up.
I'm going to bring a dog at the start.
Also, there's one thing we absolutely
cannot say during this skit.
Let's get this show on the road!
Big trouble, everyone!
Haruta's gone!
Where the hell did he go?
Come on in. This way.
Where'd you run off to, Haruta?!
Kamijou-kun, what's with the wet poochy?
When I went to take a look outside,
I found her trembling in the cold,
so I brought her along.
A dog?
You think we can fawn over a dog when our
statute of limitations expires in fifteen minutes?
But Fujima-san is a poochy lover, isn't she?
Come here, Poochy.
You must've been cold.
Talk about a good sport.
Man, we did not need that premise.
Additional Premises
- It's raining.
- Poochy has been brought into the hideout.
Don't carelessly step outside.
We're good. Nobody's found us.
We just have to hide and wait
for the clock to tick over.
My only concern is that,
among us six counterfeiters,
there's one Chinese person
who lacks motivation.
Hey, Maren is American.
Take it back.
Chinese is fine by me.
- Among the six counterfeiters is a
Chinese person.
By the way, we all had plastic surgery, right?
Yeah, because there were
wanted posters of us everywhere.
Maybe there's an undercover cop here who
switched places with one of us during surgery.
The possibility certainly exists.
It must be you, Narushima!
In order to win, the drama club
must make Narushima exit.
It begins...
The Drama Club's bullying of Narushima-san.
The real Narushima would be
wearing prescription glasses.
But I am!
They could be fake.
Here. You can have these back.
What is this?!
I knew it.
You're an impostor!
Give me back my glasses!
Get out of here, impostor!
I'm not an impostor!
This isn't a smart strategy.
You should make your target
exit of their own free will.
That's what you're thinking, right, Maren?
We don't have time for that!
The statute expires in five minutes!
What are you talking about?
It's 12:10PM now.
There's one hour and five minutes
left until it expires.
It's 1:10PM right now!
Are you saying my watch is out of whack?
No. Both my watch and yours are accurate.
Because this hideout is in...
Suzhou, China.
Why?
Suzhou?
We smuggled ourselves into Suzhou, China.
The time difference between
China and Japan is one hour.
So it's 12:10PM in Suzhou right now.
Nagoe's watch, which says it's 1:10PM,
is set to Japan Standard Time.
Isn't that right?
I-I guess.
Why Suzhou?
There are other places at a
one-hour time difference from Japan.
There's a reason for that.
It has to be Suzhou.
- Everyone has had plastic surgery.
- They are in Suzhou.
That aside, we're facing a more
pressing issue right now.
- Everyone has had plastic surgery.
Wh-What do you mean?
The extension of the statute.
The time we spend
outside Japan doesn't count.
We're in a world forever stuck
fifteen minutes before the statute expires.
So you mean we'll never be free?
Right.
As long as we don't leave here and go back
to our hometown, time will stay frozen.
Thinking time will erase our sins
is nothing but egotism!
We'll have to spend the rest of our lives
trapped here with that burden!
What's gotten into him?
However, aside from us six counterfeiters,
there's someone unrelated here.
They have nothing to do with this,
so I want to let them go free.
What do you mean?!
There are only six people here!
Allow me to introduce you
to our Chinese member, Pu Chi!
- One of the members is a Chinese person called Pu Chi.
Wait, "Poochy" wasn't a dog?
By the way, it was Pu Chi
who smuggled us into Suzhou.
Thanks, Pu Chi.
So that's why...
Also, there's one thing we absolutely
cannot say during this skit.
What is it?
The word "dog".
Among the six counterfeiters,
only one is Chinese: Pu Chi.
Maren, you said "Chinese is fine by me" yourself.
That makes you the person
unrelated to the crime.
So we'll set you free right here and now.
If there's someone you want to meet, or a wish
you'd like fulfilled, you should go home.
Go home where?
Outside this hideout lies Suzhou.
My family is not here!
I suddenly got a letter from my little brother.
The only thing my real parents gave me.
Everything I was trying not to
think about became reality.
I see.
You're worried that we'll
throw you out empty-handed, huh?
There we go.
Nagoe...
That's...
I'll tell you the combination
for this suitcase now.
I know. It's 2099.
And what does it mean?
Huh?
2099.
If you read it in Chinese,
it has a double meaning.
It means, "Love you forever".
Love You Forever
That combination was your parents'
way of expressing their feelings.
You weren't born into this world unwanted.
What's wrong with having
two homes and two families?
That's who you are, Maren.
Don't tell me...
You put on this skit just to tell me that?
Go home and see for yourself.
Thank you, Nagoe, Kamijou-kun.
Maren Sei has exited the stage!
So the concert band won?
Looks like it.
Well done!
You knew that this contest was all an act
for Maren's sake, didn't you, Sensei?
Sorry. Kamijou-kun asked me for help,
and we came up with the plot together.
You stole the march on me again!
Well, you looked busy with the flute lessons.
Sensei.
Do you know something about Maren?
What was that about
two homes and two families?
You should hear that from
the man himself someday.
Heihaizi, or "black child".
That's what children born in violation
of the One-Child Policy were called.
Since he was the firstborn, he normally
wouldn't have been given up for adoption.
But Maren was born with a leg disability.
Maybe his parents were hoping
Maren's new family would help heal his legs
when they put him up for adoption.
Yeah.
I hope he gets to meet his little brother.
Me too.
world
is
still
grey,
but
it's
star
ting
to
chan
words
hang
in
the
air,
pat
ches
of
colour,
hi
ra
drif
ting
thro
ugh
the
world
hide
my
heart
in
doubt
tries
to
figure
out
whe
ther
to
say
'yes'
or
'no'
Some
times
we
lose
each
other
in
our
fanta
sies,
tired
to
walk
clear
of
them,
lody
won't
stop
fuzzy
trian
gle
is
a
circle
of
love,
tur
ning
on
ward
What
ever
for
mula
we
try,
can't
solve
it
an
shin
ease?
An
xious?
mony
might
seem
cont
radic
tory,
will
keep
gui
ding
ards
a
new
future
look
for
the
answer
days
that
are
to
come
Haruta's sister?!
You're a disgrace!
I'm not coming back home!
That apartment's a bit problematic.
Exorcise it right now!
VERNACULAR MODERNISM
It's Vernacular Modernism.