My hands tremor
As I lift up yet another
I take this final heavy step
To search for some form of hope
A wave of serenity makes my woes fade
As if there's nothing to worry about
It's almost like my fears have gone away
I don't want to lose anything anymore
Is this feeling something like love?
It's so transient, I'm not sure if it's real
If this is what love is supposed to feel like
Then I have to keep on going
We can overcome this struggle
Because as long as we're together, we'll be unbeatable
I'll rise up as many times as I need to
Because I want to protect you for all eternity
I'll remake this small, small world
And light the way toward the path we chose
So even if you're scared
Everything is gonna be okay