Why... did it turn out this way?!
I know I said I wanted to do
something we'd always remember...
But this is...
This is...
Nice reaction, Inoue-san!
I got some great pics.
If Inoue was able to get through
without chickening out,
we should be able to make it even scarier.
I... I did the best I could...
This isn't memorable...
Culture
Festival
It's traumatizing!
Culture
Festival
The Legendary
Culture
Festival
The Legendary
Culture
Festival
The Legendary
Culture
Festival
The Legendary
Our story is starting, now let's walk together
so that these miraculous days never end.
Yes! Let's go now.
After our boundless dreams.
When I lay out the map of my future,
my heart starts throbbing, telling me to make my move.
Sometimes I'll inevitably end up
shedding a few tears,
but let's keep our eyes on the future.
The curiosity that's driving me
right at this moment is still a mystery,
but I do know that I want to find out the answers with you.
Our story is starting, now let's walk together
so that these miraculous days never end.
Yes! Let's go now.
Our harmony resounds throughout the world.
We'll never forget to wear our smiles
with everything that makes this moment shine.
Yes! Go my way.
We'll keep dreaming on and on.
Culture
Festival
Okonomiyaki
Okay, bring that over here.
Careful carrying that. Don't hurt yourself!
Okonomiyaki
Welcome to our ultra-realistic haunted house,
brought to you by Amami-san and her sixth sense!
Haunted House
This will become a culture festival legend!
Just give me normal memories.
Come on, Inoue-san.
We've got a cute mascot. Meow!
W-Well, I guess this is all right...
Or so it looks, until...
Boo!
Yay!
I-Inoue-san...
Amami-san, I'd like your advice about the interior.
Oh, sure!
Um...
Excuse me for a moment.
She seems happy...
Well...
Ready to get back to work?
If we don't finish today,
we'll end up spending the night here.
That sounds cool.
With Amami around,
the school at night should give me
all kinds of blog material.
Haunted House
Wow, she's going all-out to
make sure everything is done on time.
She really doesn't want to spend the night here.
I'm exhausted...
You worked really hard, Inoue-san!
Huh? What is it, Amami-san?
Really? That's great to know.
Thank you!
Talking to nobody again...
Who are you speaking to now?
This kind soul was telling me about
a Japanese sweets shop nearby.
He seems to love sweets.
But...
He has a big hole where his stomach should be,
so even if I leave an offering, he can't eat it...
Was he the one who just screamed?
Dad?
Amami's...
...dad?
Yes...
He's got white hair?!
H-He's been through a lot...
What brings you here?
I just finished work, so I came to pick up...
Oh, I should introduce myself.
I'm Amami Asahi.
I'm an archaeology professor at the university.
Hibiki... My daughter tells me
you're all good friends to her.
Um, may I ask why you were screaming?
Oh, er...
Hanazuka Prefectural High School
Sorry, I got a message.
Sweet! A ghost picture I can put on my blog!
A-Again?
Yeah, see?
I guess your actions
answer the question for you?
And her response is the same?
I'm embarrassed to admit it,
but I can't handle that sort of thing...
No way!
Even though you're living with Amami-san?
It's true...
There's something white on your shoulder.
There's a black shadow at your feet!
Of course there is.
I can't believe a jumpy guy like this
has a daughter with a sixth sense.
Um, I'm told my mother
also had the same ability...
Wait, so you inherited your
sixth sense from your mom?
I suppose so.
This "sixth sense" or whatever you call it is ridiculous!
I-Inoue-san?
I-I'm not apologizing!
Huh?
Come to think of it, I first met
my wife at this intersection.
A pigeon?
In a place like that—
I'm on my way!
Wait!
The pigeon wants to say something!
If you jump into the street now, you'll get hit by a car!
Coo-coo-coo-cooo, coo-cooooo!
If you jump into the street now,
you'll get hit by a car
The first words she spoke to me were in pigeon.
If you jump into the street now,
you'll get hit by a car
That's a new one.
If you jump into the street now,
you'll get hit by a car
Who are you?
This little guy called out to me.
He told me a reckless young man
was trying to save his lifeless corpse.
Um...
Yes?
I'm...
I'm Amami Asahi!
And, u-um...
Er, well...
You are...?
You can call me Yuuhi.
Yuuhi-san...
But Asahi-san, you mustn't be so reckless.
If something were to happen to you...
I'm so ashamed.
...all the people behind you would be devastated.
Pardon?
And that was where our relationship started.
That's a hell of a way to start a relationship.
A wimp like him married a woman with a sixth sense, huh?
Wait, is that...
It didn't even take a week.
That's what turned his hair white?!
Caution
Slasher
Murder
Site
Caution
Slasher
Murder
Site
So what pick-up lines did you use?
Slasher
Murder
Site
Caution
Slasher
Murder
Site
Caution
Slasher
Murder
Site
Oh, come on...
Well, if you must know...
You don't seem reluctant to share at all.
The sunset is beautiful,
but it's also sad, don't you think?
What?
Because when the sun sets...
It means we must part.
Wow, what a poet!
And then? What did she say?!
This moment when evil spirits run rampant,
as light sinks into the darkness...
This is when my true ability comes to life, as well!
When dusk falls?!
Was your wife's sixth sense
even stronger than Amami-san's?
Yes.
Sometimes she even made predictions.
You foul, lecherous cat!
How dare you do that to an innocent girl?!
I wonder what she saw then.
Check out this choice selection of babes!
Let's see those pant—
Huh?!
Caution
Slasher
Murder
Site
Um, did you just...
No, it was nothing important.
Anyway, things seem rather lively tonight.
Indeed! I'm walking home
with my friends and my dad.
Oh, I'm sorry I don't have an offering today.
You're a kid. Don't worry about that.
You only get so much allowance, right?
Indeed.
Ah, I get it now.
You know the old saying about how girls tend to fall for people who resemble their fathers?
Wh-Wh-What are you implying?!
And what does that reaction mean?!
I had a great time this evening.
I haven't spoken to any of
Hibiki's friends in a long time.
Well then, you're in luck.
Our culture festival is tomorrow.
The classes will be running food stalls.
You should come visit!
That's right, it's tomorrow.
You're sure it's all right if I drop by?
Amami helped out every step of the way, so I think that it'll turn out great.
You did, Hibiki?
Yes.
I see. Then I'll be happy to go.
We'll be waiting!
Yep. Ready to go home, Hibiki?
Yes. See you all tomorrow.
Can we buy Mom some Japanese sweets
for an offering on the way?
I found out about a really good place...
Hey, by the way...
Do you think Amami told her dad
that our class is doing a haunted house?
Accessories
Today's Quitters
Talk about a fierce pace.
We really are gonna be a culture festival legend.
Right?
No one needs a legend like this.
Yeah, maybe.
Amami only asked the ghosts
to help oversee things, but...
I didn't expect them to be so enthusiastic
that they'd join the cast on the day.
I can't take this! Why do I have to
dress up like a ghost too, anyway?
I had you work out here because
you're too scared to work inside.
Don't complain.
Here, go hand out all of these flyers.
Oh, fine...
Haunted House
Cursed Garden
All of them.
All you people think it's
hilarious to see me scared!
It is surprisingly difficult
to intentionally scare someone.
Something just ran by under my feet!
That dead old guy smiled at me!
Someone's whispering in my ear!
The others have already taken to this work.
I'm too ashamed to face Amami-dono now...
Our costumes match.
Let's both do our best.
All right...
A warrior ghost!
Roll-call samurai's overdoing it!
Can someone go pick up lunch?
Okay, I'll take care of it.
I'll help you.
Maybe we'll run into my dad on the way.
So he is coming, then?
Yes.
I'll be really happy if I can show him
the project we all worked so hard on together.
Hey, Amami-san, you did tell him
that it's a haunted house, right?
Haunted House
Are you trying to kill him?!
A culture festival...
It sure is packed.
Here.
Thank y—
Huh?
Cursed garden
Haunted House
Cursed Garden
What?
That hair, and those clothes...
Is that you, Hibiki?
What?
You're totally different from yesterday!
Manga Club
Exhibit
Manga Club Member       Yoshida
Original Manga for Sale
Original Goods Crafting
Cosplay
He's taking it all in
I finally got them all handed out.
It's been like this all the time lately...
You're Inoue-san, right?
The other kids told me
a little about you yesterday.
Huh?
Pardon me.
Hairline Color Check
You're still safe.
From what?
Sorry, I just felt bad that this is
all putting so much strain on you.
I-It's no one's fault...
I just hate being made fun of.
I see...
Of course you wouldn't say
it in front of her father,
but I know you never place the blame
on Hibiki or the ghosts she sees.
You're a nice girl.
What are you smiling about?
Oh, it's nothing. Shall we get going?
Sure. I'm finally done with
handing out these flyers.
Are you gonna be okay at
the haunted house, though?
O-O-O-Of course!
Uh... You don't have to force yourself...
It's been such a long time, you know.
Since Hibiki was last part of something at school with her friends, that is.
So I want to see it, no matter what.
She tried really hard!
She worked as one with the whole class
and took everything super seriously.
She worked her hardest,
and she was really happy.
So please go see it!
See what we and Amami made together!
I'm sorry, Asahi-san.
What are you apologizing for?
For leaving you behind because
of my own selfishness...
I don't care how little time we have.
Just having spent it with you
makes me the happiest man on Earth.
But our baby...
It's okay.
I've seen what will happen.
She'll have to endure some pain and sadness,
but she'll find many kind people
who will take her by the hand.
Really?
Yes!
Well, let's head home.
We'll practice making fried eggs tonight.
Just go easy on me.
U-Um...
What is it?
Thank you.
Really, thank you.
Oh, um... uh...
L-Let's just get going.
Oh, I'll take that. You can get the door.
No, I can handle it.
Wh-Why did the door open by itself?
Usually they reserve that service for Amami...
Wait, are they...
mistaking me for her?!
I'm with her actual dad, too.
That just makes it more misleading...
N-No, it couldn't...
You've done well.
Lunchtime!
Hey. What's up?
You dropped your box.
No!
Stop!
Yoo-hoo, Amami-chan!
Have you had lunch?
White with pink stripes!
Okonomiyaki
I bought lunch!
Oh, thanks.
I was waiting for this!
These are for all of you.
Yay.
Yippee!
Oh, it's Noritama!
Dad, you're here!
Is that... What? Inoue-san?!
What happened to your hair?!
Don't tell me you got so terrified, you...
No, it's...
And that's why.
I see... Thank goodness.
Inoue-san, that's awesome!
What the hell is so funny?!
Today's Quitters
Uh-oh, run for it!
Yamada!
Stupid
Yamada
Another one for the quitter list.
And thus, after leaving us with
many memories and traumas,
our haunted house became
a culture festival legend.
I am so sick of ghosts!
Wow!
Mysterious fluffballs!
Wow! Wow! Wow!
We won't tell the adults!
Have you noticed it? Do you feel it?
See with the mind's eye.
I want to get possessed and stay possessed.
An after-school sensation.
Common sense means nothing to high-school girls
with a "que sera, sera" attitude.
Out of our way, ghosts!
Abracadablovelove!
Wow! Wow!
You should join us too!
Smile! Smile! Smile!
Let's have a blast!
We only have one chance to be young,
so we should enjoy it to the fullest.
Evil spirits, vengeful spirits, all welcome.
Yeah!
Nothing's impossible in this world.
There are all sorts of strange events and phantoms.
Yeah!
Come what may, we'll never back down.
What does it mean to be ordinary?
Yeah?
If only the gods know the answer,
Yeah!
they can keep it to themselves!
After all...
Ignorance is bliss.
Next Time
Yo, Uehara Kana here.
My blog got a ton of hits again today.
I wonder what I should post next...
Whoa, Amami, what is that?!
That is too good!
Looks like these new people are pretty wild!
There's never a dull moment around you guys.
Next time on Re-Kan!:
"A Super Awesome Holy Night."
A Super Awesome Holy Night.
Well, anyway, let me just upload this...