Blue sky! White clouds!
Summertime means...
...beach time!
Summertime Means Beach Time.
Wow, it's cold!
Hurry up, everyone!
C'mon, you're getting too excited.
Gotta say, I'm impressed you found this place.
We've almost got it all to ourselves.
Well, you see...
Something touched my leg!
Sheesh, don't scare me like that.
Shadow Leaps from Cliff
A Ghost?!
Monthly
Adventure
This beach is famous as a haunted place.
Monthly
Adventure
Tell us that sooner!
Monthly
Adventure
Now that's a good haul.
I wanna go home! No!
Summertime means beach time!
Our story is starting, now let's walk together
so that these miraculous days never end.
Yes! Let's go now.
After our boundless dreams.
When I lay out the map of my future,
my heart starts throbbing, telling me to make my move.
Sometimes I'll inevitably end up
shedding a few tears,
but let's keep our eyes on the future.
The curiosity that's driving me
right at this moment is still a mystery,
but I do know that I want to find out the answers with you.
Our story is starting, now let's walk together
so that these miraculous days never end.
Yes! Let's go now.
Our harmony resounds throughout the world.
We'll never forget to wear our smiles
with everything that makes this moment shine.
Yes! Go my way.
We'll keep dreaming on and on.
Before Summer Break
Why don't we go hit the beach
during summer break?
Before Summer Break
The beach?
It has been really hot lately.
I'd like to go, but if we go that far,
won't we need a chaperon?
You get really serious about
the strangest things, Inoue.
What of it?
And what's with you?!
We're all set there.
Do you know someone?
My big brother...
The police officer!
And he's your brother?!
So this is...
my big brother!
Hi, everyone!
Nice to meet you.
Thank you for coming today.
I didn't expect him to be so laid-back.
What's wrong, Esumi?
Look at all the spunky high school girls!
I wish I could take one of you home with me,
but it's against the law, so no hope of that!
He's well-known for being an open book.
They're definitely brothers!
So you have a white swimsuit, Amami?
Yes.
Got a little adventurous, didn't you?
Check out that navel.
I think you look great!
Thank you.
We went to pick them out together for today.
New Collection
I picked out a few for you.
Thank you.
Here are your choices!
New Collection
That angle!
Leopard print?
New Collection
String?!
Good.
Th-That one's perfectly normal.
You don't have to act so bashful.
Right!
Let's get a shot to remember this by.
They're all the way out here, too?!
She has impregnable ghost photo defenses.
But you know, some might say...
Having them there to cover her...
...makes it look even sexier!
Look at all the fish!
The water's pretty deep, huh?
It's kinda scary that we
can see down to the bottom.
Hello!
Something's down there!
What was she talking to?!
Bet ya didn't expect to see me here!
I'm gonna take full advantage
of your being distracted.
What?
Buzz off.
Cut it out already!
What the hell are you guys?!
Here it comes!
And... there!
O-Okay!
Don't hit that thing to me!
Coming back!
No more!
Esumi, what's with you today?
You're being so reclusive.
It's nothing...
Oh? What's this?
Police Officer
Former Gangster
I hope he doesn't remember...
Seashell
What'd you do back in the day?
And what are you doing right now?!
Underwater might be off limits...
But they can't lay a finger on me in this boat!
Summer in Japan is gonna be the
summer of sexual harassment!
Hey!
That's against the rules!
Let's split a watermelon!
Yay!
You too! C'mon!
What's up?
Oh, uh, it's nothing...
Did he forget?
I wonder how a watermelon
split by a high school girl tastes.
Thank goodness he's a moron.
Huh? Um...
Go for it, Amami!
Okay...
Um...
I call foul.
We know it's you, roll-call samurai!
Yum!
So good!
So you're the girl with the sixth sense?
Oh, yes.
Can you predict the future, too?
The future?
No, I'm afraid not.
Really? Well, it's still cool that
you can see ghosts and stuff!
It's like you've got a superpower.
Doesn't that seem like the kind
of power a hero would have?
A hero, you say?
Yes, a hero!
Every little boy wishes he could be
a hero at some point in his life.
I was no different!
But...
I didn't have any powers...
Um...
That's why...
I decided to become a hero
using the powers of the law!
Stupid brother is stupid.
Well...
I can't predict the future, but I can ask the locals
if there's been any suspicious activity.
The locals?
Shadow Leaps from Cliff
A Ghost?!
The thing in the paper!
Several Minutes Later
I got some great info!
First of all,
ride the train home leaving at 7:18 PM.
And secondly,
look out the train window at that cliff,
and you'll see a very interesting sight.
Would you say...
it's a more interesting sight than I am?!
No more schemes!
Direct assault!
Whoa, wha— Stop!
Stop that! Hey!
Ready to call it a day?
Aww...
Well, this was only a day trip, after all.
We've gotta make that 7:18 train.
Oh, yeah.
Okay... Then let's stay the night next time.
C'mon, we're leaving.
Give me just a second.
What are you doing?
What do you
recommend?
Asking for advice on souvenirs.
What is that?
What do you
recommend?
The sea bass is great this year
What?!
Take these as souvenirs
Pink heart-shaped shells!
Wow...
Looks like they were eroded into this shape.
They're beautiful.
Look, we match.
Take it back!
No...
Don't be shy
Shut up!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
You're not joining in?
I-I'll do it later.
Okay, we're on the 7:18 train home!
I wonder what'll happen...
I've never thought of my
sixth sense as a superpower.
The cliff will be there when we exit the tunnel.
We just need to look at it out the window, right?
But if it brings a smile to someone's face...
A local fireworks show?
Perfect timing!
How is she always right?
Amami, you're amazing!
Wait, what was so interesting about the cliff?
What's this place so famous for?
LIFE
Not convincing at all!
Second Term Starts Tomorrow
I guess I'll call her about tomorrow.
Hello? Amami?
You have reached the voicemail service.
She's not home?
Please leave your message after the tone.
I'm right behind you, listening.
Answer your damn phone!
Hanazuka Prefectural High School
Huh?
Is everything okay?
You seem down.
Ah, sort of...
But I'll get over it.
Hey, Flame-Haired Messiah!
Is she over it?
Um, Flame-Haired—
Don't repeat it!
It's finally been brought into the light, huh?
Flame-Haired Messiah was Esumi's street name
in her gangster days!
I said, don't repeat that!
More like a flame-haired demon!
Remember when we met Yamada's
older brother over summer break?
I actually knew him back then.
Police Officer
What?!
Since I'm your chaperon...
He pretended he didn't remember me,
I'll need all of your email addresses!
and got our email addresses...
And then he sent me a fan letter!
What kind of relationship did they have?!
Here's a shot of her from back then.
Don't show them that.
Esumi was a legend in her own right.
And don't start telling stories.
What should we do tonight?
Eh, whatever.
Uh, um...
Come with us.
Sorry, something came up.
Yeah, okay.
Um... Please, just stop!
Hey, what's the big deal?
Hang out with us.
'Kay?
No way!
Somebody help me!
What the—
Cut the crap, you scum!
Who's there?!
Red hair like flames...
You can't be...
The almighty Flame-Haired Messiah!
Don't call me that!
So as she rescued the weak and crushed the strong,
Esumi became a legend.
And she lived happily ever after.
There's no happy ending here.
But... "Flame-Haired Messiah"?
People just started calling me that!
Me... Messi... Messiah!
Messiah!
Just laugh out loud already.
Well, everyone has things in their past
that they find hard to talk about.
Even you, Ogawa?
Tell us!
No way!
I bet Amami has some stories like that!
Any embarrassing tales from your past?
Huh?
What? Amami's embarrassing stories?
I, Yoshida, have kept my notepad on my person
24/7 in anticipation of just such an event.
All for my new manga!
No, that doesn't matter!
I wanna hear about Amami's
embarrassing moments!
Now, out with it! Spill! Out with it already!
Well... When I was little...
Uh-huh?
It's embarrassing to say,
but I got so lonely at night, I couldn't sleep alone.
Ah, that's common.
But then everyone came and stayed with me.
Hi!
It's okay. Don't be scared.
Would you like to talk for a while?
Okay!
It's still a wonderful memory for me.
I take back what I said.
They'd even hold my hands until I finally fell asleep.
Thank goodness it didn't turn into eternal slumber.
Hands...
That reminds me, I had a spiritual
encounter back then, too.
For real?
Yeah.
I was in a fight in this alley...
Damn you!
Don't mess with us!
S-Save me...
Please... Save me!
This way!
Stop right there!
Outta the way!
Hey, you all right?
W-Weren't you scared?
Nah.
Back then, people scared me more than ghosts did.
So after that...
Hey, you there!
Messiah?
You're Messiah, right?
I've finally met the Flame-Haired Messiah!
Man, I hear rumors about a heroic
young girl all the time at the station!
I became a police officer because
I wanted to be a hero, you know?
I never would've believed it if I hadn't met you!
I've been wanting to meet you forever,
but I've had zero luck.
Every time I heard that Messiah was nearby,
I rushed out to the scene.
You don't know how happy I am to meet you!
Hey, do you think we could
exchange numbers and emails?
Oh, but first, I've got to get a shot of us together.
Say "cheese!"
People can be punched,
and I'm damn glad about that.
Bro!
So, well, it's like...
If there's a hand there that no one notices but me...
Then before I can think about it...
I just take hold of it.
Caution
Slasher
Murder
Site
So I can understand, sort of.
Esumi...
1 New Message
From: Yamada Masaki
Another email!
You're too polite. You could just ignore him.
If I don't respond, he'll come for me in person!
He already has!
Hey.
Seeing her responding to him makes it seem like the ghost arm brought them together.
Damn it...
Indeed!
What a pain.
Send
Cancel
Sending
Sent
I was trying to avenge my own death by turning that punk in!
Do your job, you dumb cop!
Wow!
Mysterious fluffballs!
Wow! Wow! Wow!
We won't tell the adults!
Have you noticed it? Do you feel it?
See with the mind's eye.
I want to get possessed and be loved.
An after-school sensation.
Common sense means nothing to high-school girls
with a "que sera, sera" attitude.
Out of our way, ghosts!
Abracadablovelove!
Wow! Wow!
You should join us too!
Smile! Smile! Smile!
Let's have a blast!
We only have one chance to be young,
so we should enjoy it to the fullest.
Evil spirits, vengeful spirits, all welcome.
Yeah!
Nothing's impossible in this world.
There are all sorts of strange events and phantoms.
Yeah!
Come what may, we'll never back down.
What does it mean to be ordinary?
Yeah?
If only the gods know the answer,
Yeah!
they can keep it to themselves!
After all...
Ignorance is bliss.
Next Time
Hey. It's Esumi Kyouko.
Amami and the gang had a good time,
so it was a good summer break.
But I'll never forgive the Yamada brothers!
I think I'll help get ready for the culture
festival to get myself in a better mood.
What's our class gonna do?
That's a silly question.
Next time on Re-Kan!:
The Legendary Culture Festival.
"The Legendary Culture Festival."
Hey, you! The one who just said "Messiah"!
Step outside with me for a sec.