Let's All Play Together.
But...
Our story is starting, now let's walk together
so that these miraculous days never end.
Yes! Let's go now.
After our boundless dreams.
When I lay out the map of my future,
my heart starts throbbing, telling me to make my move.
Sometimes I'll inevitably end up
shedding a few tears,
but let's keep our eyes on the future.
The curiosity that's driving me
right at this moment is still a mystery,
but I do know that I want to find out the answers with you.
Our story is starting, now let's walk together
so that these miraculous days never end.
Yes! Let's go now.
Our harmony resounds throughout the world.
We'll never forget to wear our smiles
with everything that makes this moment shine.
Yes! Go my way.
We'll keep dreaming on and on.
Mr. Moriya.
Miss Kimura.
Congratulations...
...on your marriage!
Kimura, the Japanese teacher,
and Moriya, the health teacher.
They've really got guts.
Especially Moriya.
He has... guts?
Any questions so far?
All right...
How long have you and
Miss Kimura been together?
Did pistil meet stamen?
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Had a visit from the stork yet?
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Have you brought a bundle
back from the cabbage patch?
Uh...
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
Health Administration
- General Health Administration
- Environmental Administration
- Industrial Health Administration
- Educational Health Administration
When are you guys having kids?!
That's par for the course, I guess.
Talk about anarchy...
Tell us, Miss Kimura,
how did you and Mr. Moriya start dating?
We both grew up in the country.
We got to talking about that,
and we hit it off, I guess.
You had similar origins, then.
Indeed.
Oh, Mr. Moriya!
Would you like to eat lunch together?
Ah, but...
Let's go.
They're so in love!
In love...
You can't help but envy the bride-to-be.
Isn't she lucky?
Indeed!
I-I don't...
Not my thing.
Wasn't it your dream in grade school
to be a bride someday?
When the hell was that?!
When we were learning our times tables!
There's someone who looks like a bride over there.
Morya!
She's so cute!
Wh-Who is it?!
It seems as though she can't speak.
Morya!
Being so young, her consciousness is hazy.
She recalls very little about her life.
Things could take a bad turn, at this rate.
What do you mean?
Ghosts exist on this plane because they have
a lingering attachment to someone or something.
But I believe this girl is losing
even her memories of that.
Then...
With the passage of time,
she may one day vanish
before her last wish is fulfilled.
O-Oh no! What should we do?
Morya?
Then let's change that!
Let's have her make new memories with us!
I said something good though, didn't I?
Yeah, but it just...
...pissed me off for some reason.
Okay!
Let's teach her to speak!
Huh?
It's better if she can talk to us, right?
And maybe...
Big brother.
...she'll even call me that!
That's the doofus Yamada.
Morya?
Amami!
Ogawa!
Doofus Yamada!
Doofus?
She's a quick learner!
And this is the Flame-Haired Messiah!
I really like that humans can be punched.
Uehara!
That's Inoue Narumi.
Hey—
Narumi!
That's Miss Narumi to you!
I'm older than you!
She got all sweet with her back turned.
Looks like she's really taken to her.
On my honor... On my honor... On my honor...
What are you trying to imprint
on her mind, topknot?
I'm in the minority. I couldn't resist...
Hommer!
Let's learn how to greet people today.
'Kay!
Hello!
Very good.
Narumi!
Inoue!
Wh-What? Quit staring at me!
F-F...
F-F-F...
Farewell!
Farewell?
That's another way to say goodbye.
Oh.
Farewell!
I bought some for her, too.
Now we say "thank you."
Thank you.
Oh, shoot! That was coffee.
My bad.
Don't teach her that! Say "I'm sorry"!
I'm sorry.
She's being taught instead?
Sheesh...
I didn't mean any harm.
Be more careful.
Hey!
Word Chain Tournament
Let's have a word chain tournament!
What starts with "M"?
Morya!
Animal!
Lather!
Rum.
Morya!
They're too easy on her.
It's fun being with everyone!
Yes, it is.
Everyone's so big!
Like, tall?
Well, we're grown-ups.
She's really learned to speak well.
Yeah.
She still can't remember
anything, though, can she?
No.
Morya!
We still haven't figured out what that means.
Who cares if she can't remember?
She's got us as her friends now!
I said something good though, didn't I?
Yeah, but it still...
...pissed me off for some reason.
Look, it's the teachers.
They're as lovey-dovey as ever.
Mori...ya?
Moriya!
Moriya. Moriya...
Moriya. Moriya. Moriya...
So, how does she know Mr. Moriya?
Moriya's actually possessed.
She was actually his secret love child.
Sh-She's actually his guardian angel...
Has she remembered anything else?
No, not yet.
Maybe we should just let her
meet Moriya face-to-face?
I cannot recommend that course of action.
Why not?
As we do not yet know who the girl truly is,
we cannot predict what will happen.
In the unlikely event that
Master Moriya were to be harmed...
How is this gonna harm anyone?
Moriya!
I said it was unlikely!
Y-You're right.
Mr. Moriya and Miss Kimura
are preparing for their wedding.
We shouldn't make a fuss.
Then I'll do some research!
I'll find out how Mr. Moriya and she are linked!
I didn't find a thing!
Don't try to gloss over it with that grin.
At least act a little bit apologetic.
S-Sorry...
Nothing, huh?
W-We'll go and try to find something out.
What?
But...
I-It's not for you or anything.
It's for Mr. Moriya and Miss Kimura.
Drama queen! Drama queen!
Don't teach her words like that!
Well, let's get to it.
Keep her company, Amami.
Oh, sure.
Everyone's busy?
Why don't the two of us play together?
U-Um...
Amami?
Is something wrong?
You look upset about something.
Moriya!
Faculty Lounge
Da-dum, da-dum...
Da-dum...
Shut up!
You'll blow our cover.
Sorry, I couldn't resist...
Will you guys be quiet?
If the teachers catch us,
we'll be in a whole world of trouble.
In trouble for what?
Dinner's almost ready.
O-Okay, thanks...
I-It really is a ghost...
Yes. I'm sorry to have you spend time with her.
Oh, it's fine. I mean, she's not exactly scary.
Besides...
She seems familiar, for some reason.
All done! Eat up!
A little girl's ghost wants to see Mr. Moriya?
Y-Yes.
She keeps saying "Moriya. Moriya..." over and over.
Do you know what she looks like?
She's got long hair and wears a white dress.
No, it's not a dress.
It's more like those gowns you wear at a hospital.
This is her.
It can't be...
He... Mr. Moriya was actually
quite sickly as a child.
He spent a lot of time in the hospital.
One of his hospital stays was a long-term stay.
At that time, he shared a room with a little girl.
They were about the same age,
so they became friends quickly
and played together a lot.
But sadly, she was much sicker than he was.
Thank you for dinner.
My pleasure.
Mr. Moriya, thank you so much for today.
Oh, don't mention it.
It was fun experiencing something so unusual.
Moriya.
What should we play tomorrow?
I'm sorry. I can't play tomorrow.
Why not?
I'm getting married.
Moriya, you're getting married?
Yep.
Oh, yeah.
You're big now, aren't you?
You're all grown up.
You can eat your carrots now.
Huh?
So she...
She said it must be the girl Mr. Moriya
met in the hospital when he was little.
If her ghost is still a child, then...
Yeah.
A-Aren't we gonna play with her today?
I'm saying I'll play with her!
Inoue...
She's trying so hard.
And trying not to show it.
What should we play, then?
Okay, let's play kick-the-can!
You're it!
Go get it!
We're starting already?
Amami?
Would you like to play with us?
Narumi.
Ogawa.
Uehara.
Messiah.
Don't call me Messiah.
Doofus Yamada!
Don't call me Doofus!
Let's all play together!
Cut it out!
We played a lot today, didn't we?
Yeah!
Did you have fun?
Good.
Um...
Listen...
If...
If you don't mind...
Can...
Can you...
Can you stay here forever?
Promise?
Yeah. Promise.
Was that...
That's how she sleeps?!
Shall we go back to bed?
No...
I must bid you farewell.
Take care on your way.
Amami.
Thank you all for playing with me.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Congratulations!
Moriya!
When we grow up...
You're all grown up.
When we're...
...grown up...
You're so handsome now.
We'll meet again!
I'm sorry I couldn't keep our promise.
But...
I still love you, Moriya!
Bye-bye! Farewell!
We'll take it slow.
We'll make lots of stops on the way,
get lots of souvenirs...
And someday, we'll go and see her.
Yeah... Someday.
Definitely.
I've gotta get to work.
Skip work! Let's all have a blast together!
We're all best friends, right?
Shut up.
Have some tact!
Come on.
Let's go have some fun.
I don't like it when anyone is missing.
Okay, let's go have fun!
Oh, fine.
Really? All right!
You're paying, Yamada.
What? Why?!
You have to learn words
before you can use them.
She didn't need to learn "farewell"...
But she still said
"thank you all for playing with me."
Why would she say that?
We could've played more!
She was just a kid...
Inoue.
Amami, Inoue, come on!
We'll hang out tomorrow,
the day after that, and beyond, too!
Wow!
Mysterious fluffballs!
Wow! Wow! Wow!
We won't tell the adults!
Have you noticed it? Do you feel it?
See with the mind's eye.
I want to get possessed and be loved.
An after-school sensation.
Common sense means nothing to high-school girls
with a "que sera, sera" attitude.
Out of our way, ghosts!
Abracadablovelove!
Wow! Wow!
You should join us too!
Smile! Smile! Smile!
Let's have a blast!
We only have one chance to be young,
so we should enjoy it to the fullest.
Evil spirits, vengeful spirits, all welcome.
Yeah!
Nothing's impossible in this world.
There are all sorts of strange events and phantoms.
Yeah!
Come what may, we'll never back down.
What does it mean to be ordinary?
Yeah?
If only the gods know the answer,
Yeah!
they can keep it to themselves!
After all...
Ignorance is bliss.
Next Time
Man, I have to do the preview? What a drag.
This shouldn't be a gal's job.
Anyway, Valentine's Day doesn't change much
from one generation to the next, huh?
Oh, crap! Does that make
me sound like an old lady?
I wonder who the secret admirer
sending Hibby chocolate is.
Next time on Re-Kan!:
"The Secret Valentine."
The Secret Valentine
Maybe he's hoping it'll be paid back triple?