Ouch!
I'm off.
I'm off!
Manaria Friends
Anne and Grea
Was first period transliteration?
That looks good!
I thought it was healing magic.
Princess! Good morning!
Good morning.
Morning.
Good day.
Good morning.
A wonderful morning to you.
Grea!
Morning!
I finally found you!
Morning.
Thanks.
Um... Princess Anne...
Just call me Anne.
You're the Dragon Princess, after all.
Anne!
Anne.
Yeah?
Do you remember the book
we borrowed together before?
The one I recommended?
Yeah.
I'm still partway through it,
but I'm learning a lot about Manaria.
Or rather, about you. I'm enjoying it.
That's great!
The library here has so many books
in all sorts of languages.
Don't you just want to read them all?
Y-Yeah.
Oh yeah, I found a book about
the land of the dragons the other day.
What kind of place is it?
Um...
There's a lot of big animals, unlike here, I guess.
That sounds lovely!
So what made you decide to come to this academy?
Um... Well, my mother was once a student here.
And, you know... I'm also a half-dragon.
Oh, so your mom is an alumna!
Anne!
Ann—whoa!
Lou?!
Are you okay?
Thank you so much, Anne.
There's trouble in the library! Come quick!
Huh? Wai—
Sorry, Grea!
Just give me a minute!
O-Okay.
How did it get in here?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
You okay, Hanna?
Princess?
I'm sorry for stepping on it...
Everyone, get back!
The princess is amazing!
We're saved!
Is it fine if I seal it?
Y-Yeah.
Okay.
Ice Bind!
Sorry...
Don't be...
Achoo!
It's not your fault, Princess.
I was the one that asked you
to seal the Lord of the Library.
But Hanna, you—
I wasn't even strong enough to help you.
I'm a failure of a president.
I'm so weak.
I'm a disappointment.
I'm not cut out for this.
Thank you.
Um, I can help out if there's anything else you need.
We should be fine for today.
Thank you for your assistance, Princess.
G—
Grea?!
Anne.
Uh...
Are you all done now?
Y-Yeah.
It got encased in ice when I sealed it.
The Lord of the Library was really mad.
It was going berserk.
And, well...
I stayed behind to help everyone clean up after me.
But I still...
You did well.
Were you waiting for me this whole time?
Yeah.
I think that was quite a long minute, though.
What's wrong?
Oh, uh...
Are you hungry, Anne?
Oh, now that you mention it,
I haven't eaten since this morning.
Should we get something to eat?
Yeah!
Do you prefer sweet or spicy food, Grea?
Um... Sweet.
I thought so! I do too!
- Episode 2 -
The Anguished Dragon Princess
Manaria Friends, Episode 2:
"The Anguished Dragon Princess."
Drawing: Oda Takeshi