You really do play beautifully, Grea.
It's nothing special.
I'd love to practice more.
Why don't we come again tomorrow then?
We have exams coming up.
I want to focus on my studies,
so I probably won't be coming for a while.
Okay...
Manaria Friends
Exam Period
Since the exam period is coming up,
I'll be staying back later to answer any questions!
Can you help me with this part, Miss?
Can you teach me too, please?
You'll find that right here in your textbook...
Oh, that's strange.
I could've sworn it was here somewhere...
Where?
Where are you headed?
Everyone looks pretty busy with exam preparation,
so I was thinking of going to borrow
the next volume of this series.
Hanna?
...and that's how the ancient trees native to
Manaria can be used to make any kind of elixir,
although getting the mixture
right requires very precise calculations.
You really are amazing, Princess.
But the method you used to deduce
the results might be a little too advanced.
Oh, really?
Now with Anne's explanation in mind,
let's start from the beginning and use a simpler method.
Thank you, Hanna.
We'll start with these inscriptions.
Does anyone have any questions before we begin?
Um...
Hm...
Grea!
Anne?
Do you need a hand?
Don't worry, I'm fine.
You sure?
I'm sure you have enough on your plate already.
See you later, Anne.
Oh...
Sure...
Who's that?
Don't you want to check your answers, Anne?
All correct again!
Anne...
How did your exam go, Anne?
I was so lonely!
I know.
Why don't we try playing a duet?
I dunno...
It's been ages... I wonder if I can still play.
So everything after this is just
practical applications of basic theories.
Nothing I don't already know.
I wonder if Grea is still up studying...
Let's soldier on for a little longer.
I got full marks!
I hope I'll be able to chat with Grea tomorrow.
Good night.
- Episode 5 -
The Academy Surrenders
Manaria Friends, Episode 5:
The Academy Surrenders.
Illustrator: Kanzaki Hiro