What are you doing for your vacation assignment?
I still haven't decided.
Hey, wanna hang out in town before heading home?
Sounds good!
I wonder if everyone's going to start leaving today.
I'm gonna have to help out
with the chores once I get home.
I've gotta look after my brother
and stuff. It's such a pain.
Probably, since there's lots of people with bags.
All of the seniors are gone now too.
It feels a bit lonely.
Yeah, it does.
I wonder how much time we have left together.
Huh?
Grea.
This is for you.
What is it?
Princess.
The attendants are awaiting
their instructions, so we'd best be off.
Oh, right.
Sorry. Let's chat again later.
Sure.
See you.
What could this be?
Their Promise
I'll be leaving the keys to the dormitory
with you over the break.
We're leaving tonight, so if anything happens,
please see the staff at the contact tower.
I will. I know it's been a while since
you've been able to go home, Hanna.
Have a good time.
I will!
So Anne is leaving today as well?
She was dreading all of the formalities she'll have
to deal with once she gets back to the palace.
Oh, was she?
But she'll be back when
the next semester starts, right?
Oh, haven't you heard?
President.
The carriage has arrived.
All right.
I'll have to excuse myself, Grea.
Have a safe trip.
You enjoy your break as well.
Take care, dude.
See you later.
Please board this carriage
if you're headed to the East!
Is this the last of them?
Sorry! We’ve got one more!
Be extra careful with those, okay?
Please gather over here if you'll be
on a campus committee over the break.
Oh, sorry.
It's fine.
All right, we're heading off now!
Wait for me!
Do you need a hand?
Oh, Grea!
Have you packed all your things yet?
No, I won't be going home.
May I visit your store over the break?
Oh, I'm sorry. I was thinking of going on
a shopping trip to the East during the break.
Oh, I see.
Anyway, I have to finish tidying up.
Take care, Grea!
You too, Ms. Mira.
Everyone's leaving.
Please line up over here
if you have materials to return!
Wait over there if you're checking things out.
Think we'll make it to the carriage in time?
Can't you work any faster?
Sorry.
Maybe I'll come back later.
We're closing up now.
There won't be anyone around during the break,
so you'd best hurry if you want to borrow anything.
Oh, right.
See you.
Anne...
Anne?
Are you here?
Anne...
Dragonkind Princess?
Where have you been, Grea?
I looked everywhere for you!
But I thought...
There's no way we'd never see each other again, silly.
Then why was your dorm empty?
Oh, haven't you read my letter yet?
Huh? Oh.
Can I open it?
Of course.
Roommate application?
You mentioned it this morning, right?
You were wondering how much
more time we had together.
I want to stay with you.
But I don't think we can be
together after we graduate.
I want to make the world
a happier place for everyone.
We're princesses, after all.
So let's spend as much time together as we can.
We can wake up together in the mornings,
and chat until late at night!
And we can run to class together when we sleep in.
I'm sure we'll have an even more wonderful time.
So...
That's why.
Don't you agree?
Anne...
Do you feel differently, Grea?
Not at all.
It sounds wonderful.
I promise to write.
Good.
Are you sure you've got everything, Anne?
If you find anything I missed, just leave it there.
Yeah, okay.
It's gotten so late already.
Sorry for making you clean.
It's fine.
You'd better hurry.
See you soon, Grea.
Have a safe trip, Anne.
You won't grow nice and big
if you only eat the things you like.
Make sure you get your nutrients,
and chew your food properly.
Got it!
I heard Mr. Heinlein is going to assign a research
presentation right at the beginning of the semester.
He sure is strict.
Though it's kind of refreshing how thorough he is.
Ms. Mira is as kind as ever, though.
Yeah, like how she gave us
extra time to hand our homework in.
Good morning, Grea.
Good morning.
We had a tea party last week with the new students.
They all loved the tea you recommended!
Please do keep giving me your advice.
Really? That's good to hear.
Also, your application has been approved.
Thanks.
When the princess returns to the academy,
please come to the student council office together.
We'll give you a rundown on the
important aspects of room-sharing.
All right.
Well then, have a nice day, Grea.
Excuse us.
Grea!
Welcome back, Anne.
Manaria Friends
Magnificent work, Owen.
I, Owen, swear on my life and honor to continue
to do my utmost to protect you, Princess.
That's a wrap on ceremonies!
I can go back to school now, right?
But Princess, the king said
he wanted to have a word with you.
Again?!
It was dark by the time he finished
having "a word" with me yesterday!
I'm already two weeks behind schedule.
I'll never be able to go back at this rate!
They keep coming up with more
formalities for me to sit through.
I'm leaving!
Princess, the king calls for you.
I can't take it anymore.
Cover for me!
The princess is still changing.
Would you kindly wait a moment?
Thanks!
My life and learnings as a student
are way more important right now.
I'm going where my heart takes me, Your Highness.
It took you quite a while to escape this time.
It smells like Grea!
Have I left her hanging too long again?
I'll be back soon, Grea!
See you next time!
Illustrator: Ponzu