Why's the new song a ballad?
No good?
Not for a diversion...
Excuse me, what do you mean by diversion?
Weren't you listening during Operation Tornado?
She gets her band together inside the school,
and they get the attention of all the regular students.
We don't put them directly in harm's way,
but we use them occasionally, and when they're
in the way we need to remove them from the scene.
That's when we use the girls as a diversion.
They're pretty trendy for NPCs...
At any rate, that's the merit and appeal of her band.
I see...
So? It's still no good?
A ballad won't quite do.
If everyone's quietly listening to it, we won't be able to move openly.
I see.
Well I guess that's out.
Okay, let's regroup and I'll start the briefing.
Otonashi.
Hm?
Close the curtains.
Our next operation will be "Operation
Revenge for the Angel Area Infiltration Plan."
It will commence in three days.
It's that operation, is it?
But last time—
This time he'll be accompanying us.
Nice to meet you.
From behind the chair?!
An egghead.
Yurippe, what kind of joke is this?
How are we gonna use a weakling like that?
Now now, don't say that.
In that case...
Let's test him!
You don't really have friends, do you?
3.1415926535897932384626433832795028841971693993751058209749445923078164062862089986280348253421170679821480865132823066470938446095
Stop that!
No way! He's reciting Pi?!
What an egghead.
Please stop him!
Noda's a moron!
That's right. Our weakness is that we're all stupid.
The leader shouldn't be saying that...
The last time we attempted this operation,
our intellectual deficiency was exposed.
However!
This time we have a boy who aspires to the name of "Hacker Genius"!
Handle name: Takeyama.
He's now part of the planning team.
He'll conduct a thorough investigation of the area.
That's not his real name?
Please...
...call me Christ.
Look at that. She was ignoring his cool handle name.
That's Yurippe for you.
So, what's this "Angel Area"?
Angel's residence.
Angel's residence?
Wh-What kind of place could she live in?
Wait a sec. Do we really need a hacker for a place like that?
The core is controlled by a computer.
It's mechanized?
And it'll surely contain a means of contacting God.
This plan sounds huge!
It's our second attempt, though.
Angel will be more alert than the last time.
We'll need GirlDeMo to be especially showy for us.
Roger.
Get chance and luck!
All right. Doing good.
Wait, aren't I getting a little too into this?
Ah, well. Those guys aren't as bad as I first thought.
So this is part of that showy distraction, huh?
Ah, sorry. Did I startle you?
Oh, it's you.
Huh? You know me?
Yeah!
That guy who's always carrying a big axe around
says you bring disaster, and that I should be careful around you or something.
That idiot, huh?
But wait, using the gym? Is that really okay?
It's totally dangerous! It's totally unprecedented!
And it's not their usual guerrilla concert. It's scheduled, and everything.
The teachers probably won't let this go unpunished, so we don't know what obstacles we'll face.
But I heard this operation needs
a lot of people to gather together.
Girls Dead Monster, huh?
By the way, um...
It's Yui!
I'm still just an underling in the diversionary squad...
But I couldn't be any happier!
After all, I'm helping out the great GirlDeMo!
Do you know about them?
Girls Dead Monster are amazing! Shortened to "GirlDeMo".
They're all girls, and they're incredible performers.
And no matter how you slice it,
Iwasawa on vocals and guitar is stunning!
She even writes the music and lyrics.
My favorite is "Crow Song".
The climax of that song is just so passionate. I love it.
And the lyrics, too!
They're surely about Iwasawa.
And another thing that's great, too...
Alchemy! Alchemy!
Hey, I'm not done yet!
Alchemy is...
Do I look like I need to hear all this?!
Go get back to work for your precious GirlDeMo!
Oh! That's right!
Okay, see ya!
Oops.
Sorry. I'll fix it up quick.
All right, let's take a break.
You guys were really fired up.
It's no wonder that the students love you guys so much.
Before I even realized it, I had stopped to listen.
Thank you.
You don't have any memories, right?
Something like that.
You must be happy.
Are you memories like... uh...
Did you hear about someone's memories?
Yeah. Yuri's.
Yuri's, huh?
That was just horrible.
Mine aren't nearly as bad.
Not as bad?
I'm saying it wasn't anything big.
I couldn't sing the song that I wanted to...
That's all it was.
My parents were always fighting.
I didn't have a room of my own to hide in.
In the midst of all the shouting,
I'd curl up in a corner and cover my ears.
All I could do was retreat into my own shell.
There was nowhere else I could rest.
During those hard times, I discovered a band called "Sad Machine".
I heard that the vocalist had been raised in a broken home much like my own.
When things got rough, he would cover his ears
with his headphones, and escape into a world of music.
I tried the same thing.
It was like everything just flew away.
The vocals were shouting out in
the way I couldn't. Singing for me.
All the common-sense people were wrong.
It was those who cried out that were right.
It was the lonely ones like us who were truly human.
That music shouted back and fought against the injustice of the world for me.
That music saved me.
When I first found this guitar,
it had been thrown out in the rain.
I began to sing for the first time.
In a life I thought was so empty, I had music.
Are you sure? With your grades, you could go anywhere...
No.
I don't want to rely on my parents.
I worked different jobs to save up money,
and auditioned at countless record studios.
I thought for sure that when I graduated,
I'd get out of that house, leave it all behind,
and live for music.
That's what I believed.
Huh?
I must be tired...
If this keeps up, I won't be able to play the guitar...
I'd better take tonight off and rest...
The next time I opened my eyes...
I could no longer speak.
Cerebral contusion.
An aphasia from a stroke.
The cause was a chance blow from one of my parent's fights.
I cursed my fate.
There was nowhere I could run.
And just like that, my life had ended.
Iwasawa?
Ah, Hisako. Okay!
We were getting sick of waiting.
No memories!
Take it.
That story just now...
That's why she's rebelling against the unfairness of life.
She too had a sad life.
Nobody's afraid of becoming a water flea.
Everybody here... everyone...
They're choosing to fight against God.
They're fighting against...
...accepting their cruel lives.
Come on, President.
You can overlook something like this!
That's right! GirlDeMo concerts
are all we have to look forward to.
Don't take that from us!
That's right! Yeah?
Huh?
Where'd she go?
It's like I'm the bad guy...
Understood?
We'll be going in with minimal people this time around.
We strike tonight at 1900 hours.
Operation start!
Too few people.
You get a front row seat.
It's time.
All right.
Let's rock it out!
Clear!
Okay. Infiltration successful.
Huh?
We've infiltrated Tenshi-area.
Close the door already!
Takeyama, you take care of the computer.
Please, call me Christ.
Wait... uh...
Isn't this just a normal girl's room?!
This is criminal activity!
What are you doing?!
This is the girl's dorm! Kill the lights!
And what do you mean by
"controlled by a computer"?!
It's just one little PC!
Password?
Nobody was able to crack it the previous time.
I see.
It's time for me to show my power.
Analyzing now.
Huh. I guess he's useful after all.
Come on, haven't you heard of privacy—
Hey, wait up!
You're too loud.
If you keep this up, I'll slit your throat.
What the hell?!
I was just starting to change my opinion of you guys, too!
Why?
Why won't more people come?
Alchemy? Already?
Yeah!
Alchemy!
Hey! What do you think you're all doing?!
Behave, and go back to your dorms!
No way! We've got to see this!
That's right! You're the ones who should go!
Yeah!
She's here.
Everyone, give us more!
No. Nobody can do that for us.
It's something only we can do!
Angel has appeared.
Roger.
Takeyama?
Right now, I'm running
high-speed cracking software.
It'll be done soon.
Also, please call me Christ.
We're in!
Well done, Takeyama!
All right, copy all the data!
That'll take too much time.
At least an hour.
Also, please call me Christ—
Should we take out the hard drive?
We'll be discovered!
What do we do then?
At any rate, at least show us
anything suspicious, Takeyama!
Call me Christ!
A list of students?
Only the NPC's? No, we're in here too.
It's just a regular student registry!
There's nothing suspicious about that.
This is nothing but criminal activi—
Shut it!
The Diversionary Squad has been suppressed.
Angel is returning.
This is as far as we go, huh?
And we didn't get anything this time, either.
We're dispersing.
Damn it! You've gotta be kidding!
Stop it, please!
They're doing it for us! Let them go!
Their music is what keeps us going! Please!
We've been lenient up until now.
Don't push our patience!
We're seizing all the instruments.
This isn't a damn school festival.
You won't be doing this again.
You won't mind if I toss this out, right?
Don't touch that.
Huh?
I said...
I said, don't touch that!
Stop her—
Stop!
A new song?
Takeyama!
Got it!
But please, call me Christ!
This is my life.
Continuing to sing like this...
This is the reason I was born.
Just as I was saved...
I'll be able to save someone else.
I've finally...
finally...
found it.
Iwasawa?
So what have we learned, Yurippe?
Angel developed her powers on her own.
It's the same as how we make our own weapons.
So what does that mean?
I'm not sure...
I can't say yet.
Why not? You're being secretive, Yurippe.
If she needs to use the same methods as we do,
then the only thing we can infer is the worst case scenario.
God doesn't exist anywhere.
If Angel really does live up to her namesake,
why didn't she get her powers from God?
Why does she need to develop them herself?
Well, then. There's another matter of concern.
Where did Iwasawa disappear to?
Wasn't she erased by Angel?
In the middle of a concert?!
Then, what happened exactly?
Just who would do that to Iwasawa?
Nobody.
She consented.
That's all there was to it.
In order to disappear, one does as Angel instructs, and leads a normal student life.
It wasn't actually that simple.
Play ball!
I'll be an asset to your team!
It's baseball.
Don't stop dancing!
Let's fight, kid.
This girl's supposed to be
Iwasawa's replacement?!
I'll put together the
strongest team ever!
Even though nobody knows what
the hell you were doing when you died!
Yui!
Just who are we fighting...?
You're definitely fired.
Your team is not registered to participate.
You'll have to face a penalty worse than death!
You're shaking.
That would feel incredible.