Oh, how bothersome.
This pink lovey-dovey aura...
Is this first love?
Is this what first love is like?
What's going on?
She just confessed, an' he said yes.
Way to go, Luluco.
That's my daughter.
They're so lovey-dovey...
Shit!
Love is justice, Keiji.
Shaddup!
Luluco's still only a mid—
Shut up, hyper-geezer!
This is where it gets good.
A Pitter-Patter Stone, born from a
Nothingling with an empty heart...
And an Extra Aflutter Jewel,
born again from a middle schooler
with an empty head.
The two combined to form, what,
a Lovey-Dovey Diamond?
Right! This is first love!
This is requited love!
First love is invincible!
Requited love reigns supreme!
The two of us are unbeat—
Nova?
I prepared for an occasion like this
and installed a micro Black Hole on his forehead!
Oh, the irony.
The Big Bang in Nova's brain earlier
activated the micro Black Hole,
and now it's grown big enough
to consume him entirely.
What? What now?!
The pink aura is flowing into her?!
This reaction...
The being who acts as the spark
plug for the entire universe...
The budding chosen one who has the
power to patrol across dimensions?
Lalaco...
You finally pulled the trigger, Luluco!
You're kinda awesome, Luluco!
Damned middle schooler who's somehow
combined various powers into one absurd power!
I can see everything!
I can see Nova! He seems okay!
I can see that the Blackholeian
is weaker than I thought!
His Black Holes aren't too massive yet!
I can beat him!
Awaken: Deep Love Gun Morphing!
Eat this! Black Hole Knuckle!
Fight for Nova!
Impossible!
You put a lid on my Black Hole?!
A mere middle schooler obtained
the power to distort dimensions?!
Evil Blackholeian who meaninglessly
keeps stealing things people hold dear
and causing them grief!
People die when they're shot.
I'll teach you that normal fact of life right now!
I am Black Hole incarnate!
A mere middle schooler could
never hope to defeat me!
Fight...
F-F-F-Fight...
Black Hole, my foot!
At the end of it all, you're only
taking pleasure in shoplifting!
F-F-F-F-Fight...
Fight!
You're worse than a normal middle schooler!
Fight for Nova!
Worse than a middle schooler?!
I'm a Black Hole, and you call me
worse than a middle schooler?!
You crossed a line that must never be crossed!
Black Hole Double Knuckle!
Luluco?!
Yo, is she in a rough spot?
Black Hole Double Knuckle!
Luluco, we're coming to save—
How do you like that?
I'll shoplift you, starting with
that wicked arm of yours!
I'm getting sucked in!
I'm out of ammo?
I don't have enough energy!
I can't win alone! I really can't do this alone...
Use me, Luluco.
Nova! You're alive...
If you shoot me into him,
the micro Black Hole and Black Hole
will you-know-what each other
and vanish from this universe.
No! Don't go!
Don't leave me alone again!
Either way, I can't live on
in this dimension anymore.
This was fated to happen all along.
If you knew this was gonna happen,
then why did we meet?
Why must we part?
So we can meet again!
I'm searching the entire galaxy for you
Got it!
You'd never lie to me, after all!
That's right.
Going from one planet to the next
Let's meet again in another dimension.
I'm broadcasting my feelings of love to you, beep, beep
So please receive them!
They float gently
No way!
You measly middle schooler!
Not yet!
In this endless universe
Don't think this is over, you rotten humans!
Come. It's time for us to exit the stage.
There will be a second, and third—
Goodbye.
I've locked on to that heart of yours
So you will never be able to run away
The brainwashing wore off!
The HQ is back to normal!
It's all thanks to those guys
from the Ogikubo branch!
Thank you!
Yay!
Hell yeah!
Justice prevails!
You didn't do jack shit!
Justice is invincible!
What are ya even talkin' about?
It's finally over.
Chase him to the ends of the
universe and arrest him again.
That's what I'd do.
You're supposed to introduce
your boyfriend to your dad, right?
Normally, that is.
Right!
Look. The shoplifted Ogikubos are
returning to their places in the universe.
I'm Luluco.
This is the story of my first love.
And this is how everyone's
been doing since that day.
Both the big-brained and the bird-brained
There!
Good morning, Dad!
Good morning, Luluco!
Are singing out loud because they want you, cock-a-doodle-doo!
We bring you a live feed from the
Space Patrol Galaxy Command HQ.
Space
They need to do it before their life runs out
How does it feel to be the
new Commander-in-Chief?
All of your dreams can come true!
Okay, join me, everyone.
Common sense is a good morning call
Chief Over Justice
Appointed Commander-in-Chief
of Space Patrol HQ
Jus—
Midori
Oh, Midori?
To keeping the status quo, cock-a-doodle-doo!
Luluco, everythin's normal here in Ogikubo.
So plan out your life and sew out the mysteries
Milady! Milady!
Should we put this table here?
Every Friday is my birthday!
I keep tellin' ya, call me Chief Midori!
Justice!
This planet is still blue today?!
Midori
Appointed Chief of
the Space Patrol's
Ogikubo  Branch
Appointed Chief of
the Space Patrol's
Ogikubo  Branch
Justice!
Both SOS and celebrations require the same thing
Space Pirates detected.
Space piracy underway.
They're the times when you have to shout your loudest!
Space Piracy Task Force requested to sortie.
Lalaco
Godspeed
Stole Money and Goods from Space Patrol HQ and Fled
Still a Space Pirate
Found you, Lalaco!
You need to use everyone you can, even idiots!
I'll chase you to the ends of the universe!
Keiji
Joined the Space Patrol's
Space Piracy Task Force
Wait, I'm going a different
direction, so I need out!
You have to be like me, so don't give up now!
Have a nice trip,
Miss Trigger.
I'm off.
The universe is so big and yet
Luluco
Super-Dimensional Special Officer
Codename:
Miss Trigger
A whole lot has happened,
Everyone is so slow at dreaming
but I love Ogikubo and this universe,
where the abnormal is the norm!
If they're so serious about everything
And, until the day I meet him
in some other dimension...
We'll attack their ears with these resounding lyrics!
To be continued!
Even the purest of the pure
SPACE PATROL LULUCO
Sing out loud because they want you, cock-a-doodle-doo!
So let's sing Les Misérables and drive us to our fateful encounter
SPACE PATROL LULUCO
Common sense is a matter of opinion,
So what is yours worth? Cock-a-doodle-doo!
SPACE PATROL LULUCO
Hold on tightly to all the light we can!
Both the directors and people behind the scenes
Don't want to learn this, cock-a-doodle-doo!
This radiance has started overflowing
Who will accept it now?
Everyone is normal, but if feelings are born
Everyone will go cock-a-doodle-doo!
Pending crash while we're being flooded
By important information
Everyone dies and everyone lives
Good morning to you, cock-a-doodle-doo!
You just have to accept that everything is simply weird
All of your dreams can come true!
Both the big-brained and the bird-brained
Are saying "nice to meet you," cock-a-doodle-doo!
Suddenly you pretend to be a lantern
And throw important information at me!