We've come a really long way by believing in ourselves
Even the most impossible dreams can come true
Luluco
Humanity and their lives depend only on them!
We learned that only waiting doesn't lead to anything
Alpha-Omega
Nova
Now it's time to see the greatest outcomes with our own eyes
Midori
There's nothing better than experiencing it ourselves
So let's go! Keep trying our best!
You are the future!
SPACE PATROL LULUCO
Uh, my name is Luluco.
Badger Planet SVM-Z
I've been wandering all over the
universe looking for Ogikubo,
and I came here because I heard that
the detective agency on this yellow
planet could get me any info I need...
Badger Game
Detective Agency
Would you happen to know
where I can find Ogikubo?
Welcome, welcome!
Get her tea, tea!
Se'chan, get her some tea!
Hurry up and get her some tea!
Right away.
Here's your tea.
Se'chan
Welcome...
Violence
Machspeed
I wonder where I can find Ogi—
I'm a detective! Shall I look for it?
It's gone? Want me to look for it anyway?
Okay, sure, but I came here to ask
about something else as well...
It's fine! Bring on as
many as you like! Hurry!
Uh, I need relationship advice...
What? Relationship?!
So, um...
I have this colleague, Nova,
who's kind of a handsome boy.
We've gone as far as kissing,
but when I try to talk to him...
He keeps going on about how
"that Ogikubo is fake,"
and just sits there surfing
the web with Midori...
Wait, are you even listening?
Yeah, I heard all of it!
Get her tea, tea, tea!
Right away. Here's your tea.
So I got mad and came to
this planet all by myself.
I mean, isn't it weird?
It's not, it's not! I heard you out!
Pay for counseling! Pay for detective work!
Pay up, right now!
I listened to you! Pay up!
You seem to have lots of experience.
Bring out the dough! The dough!
How does one deal with
boys at times like these?
Bring out the dough right now!
Money?
The chief said we didn't have any...
Pay up, damn it!
Shark Detective Machspeed!
I hear you laid yer hands on the
honey pots of the gals at my shop.
I'm here to collect, punk!
Don
What? This?!
Shit! The T-Bone Syndicate
was backing that shop?!
Damn, I couldn't have picked worse
honey pots to lay my hands on!
Fire the Se'chan Missile!
Missile...
Fire! Fire!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
Run! Run! Run!
Hey, detective restless shark!
How could you throw Se'chan like that?
What's so bad about doing that?
You ain't gettin' away!
Get back here!
Fire the Se'chan Missile!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
The don got hit!
He died instantly! He died, damn it!
The hell?!
Revenge for our don!
Which gang's raidin' us?!
Kill 'em!
How awful!
The town is filled with nothing
but mafiosos and gang warfare!
This is insane!
Of all the planets I've seen,
this one is the most dangerous!
Why did I come to such
a horrible place by myself?
I'm scared!
Fire the Se'chan Missile!
Fire...
Stop it!
Fire!
I will avenge my husband!
Don's Wife
I will avenge the don!
Don's Mistress
Sliced apart!
Se... Se... Se...
Se'chan!
He grew totally enormous!
Se'chan, are you okay?
I'm okay.
How cruel...
Rubber doll or not...
Men are shy creatures.
You killed one hell of an important woman!
They might usually treat you like crap,
but if they truly care about you,
This ain't a woman! It's a goddamn sex doll!
they'll dive headfirst into any
kind of danger to save you.
No, she's a woman!
One of them's still alive?!
Die, full-color girl!
Nova!
You came to this dangerous planet
to save me. Does that mean...
That's right.
You are very precious to me, Luluco.
Nova! Are you saying
what I think you're saying?
I've been waiting for this
moment for a long time.
Waiting...
Hng!
Thank you, Se'chan!
Look at him.
He's fighting so hard for my sake!
For my sake!
Luluco, we've figured out
where the real Ogikubo is.
There are as many Ogikubos
as people in this universe.
But the ones in space were all fakes.
There's only one original Ogikubo...
When I tried a different search term,
I found that everything was gathered
at the center of the galaxy.
Those coordinates will lead us... here.
That's the Space Patrol's Galaxy Command HQ.
Space Patrol Galaxy Command HQ
Wow.
So many Ogikubos...
Are these all personal Ogikubos?
What's the meaning of this?
HQ seems a bit different
from how I remember it.
Congratulations!
Space Patrol Galaxy Commander-in-Chief
You are heroes!
You did well to protect the original
Ogikubo from space pirates,
and to get this far!
I shall hand out commendations to each of you!
Uh, Commander, what is going on?
First, the chief gets a special,
three-rank promotion!
Huh?
Yay! A special promotion!
Midori gets a bounty of one million space yen!
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Space Patrol HQ
Space Yen
Winning Prize
Yay, money! Money! Money!
Space Patrol HQ
Winning Prize
The secretary gets a six-month paid vacation.
Space Cruise
This sleeping brain gets a mannequin body.
And Luluco,
you get the original Ogikubo!
Hooray!
We did it, Nova!
It's the real Ogikubo!
Congratulations, Luluco.
Thanks!
Let's take a picture, guys!
Say...
Justice!
Our long journey has finally come to an end!
At last, I can go back to
Earth—to a normal life!
This is the best feeling ever!
So...
To be continued!
I'm searching the entire galaxy for you
Going from one planet to the next
I'm broadcasting my feelings of love to you, beep, beep
So please receive them!
They float gently
In this endless universe
I've locked on to that heart of yours
So you will never be able to run away
I want you to hold my hand
To make my head spin like a merry-go-round
To make my heart skip a beat
The world will be dyed in the colors of my love