Both the big-brained and the bird-brained
Are singing out loud because they want you, cock-a-doodle-doo!
Luluco
They need to do it before their life runs out
All of your dreams can come true!
Alpha-Omega
Nova
Common sense is a good morning call
To keeping the status quo, cock-a-doodle-doo!
Midori
So plan out your life and sew out the mysteries
Every Friday is my birthday!
The planet is still blue today?!
SPACE PATROL LULUCO
I'm Luluco.
I live with my dad in the
one-of-a-kind town of Ogikubo,
a Space Immigration Zone
where humans and aliens co-exist,
and go about my life as a totally
ordinary middle school student.
To be honest though,
I hate this weird town.
I want to live a normal life,
like people in other towns do.
Take that!
Good morning, Dad!
Good morning, Luluco!
Let's eat!
You handle all of our household
chores in such a normal manner!
That's my Luluco! You're so admirable!
I wouldn't say that.
I'm just doing normal things in a normal way.
It's nothing to get excited about.
Luluco...
I'm so proud of you!
In this abnormal town, with abnormal parents,
you've still grown up to be such a normal girl!
I guess so.
You're part of the Space Patrol, upholding order
in Ogikubo, and you hardly ever get time off.
We're also living in this run-down apartment now
because you and Mom had a fight,
and she took all the furniture with her!
Yeah, we sure are normal, aren't we?
The slab bacon you make is so tasty, Luluco!
But still, it's because you gave
me such a normal upbringing
that I can be so normal despite
living in such an abnormal environment.
Anyway, hurry up and eat. It's not often
we get to leave together in the morning.
We don't wanna be late—
This is... space stuff he confiscated at work!
Do Not Open   Do Not Open   Do Not Open   Do Not Open
Dangerous and prohibited space-time capsules...
Confiscated Article
ID:
Instant cold-sleep capsules for aliens.
For official use only.
Confiscated Article
ID:
Instant cold-sleep capsules for aliens.
For official use only.
Confiscated Article
ID:
Instant cold-sleep capsules for aliens.
For official use only.
Confiscated Article
ID:
Instant cold-sleep capsules for aliens.
For official use only.
Confiscated Article
ID:
Instant cold-sleep capsules for aliens.
For official use only.
Confiscated Article
ID:
Instant cold-sleep capsules for aliens.
For official use only.
And he ate one by mistake?!
This is so not good!
Dad, Dad, Dad!
Dad!
Dad, Dad, Dad, Dad, Dad, Dad, Da—
Oh, no! He broke!
This is bad!
Normally, when something bad happens,
you call the cops or the Space Patrol!
That's where Dad works, though!
Anyway, ice cube or otherwise,
he still has to punch in at work!
Space Patrol
E-Excuse us!
Uh...
Good morning.
I am the chief of the Space Patrol's Ogikubo branch,
Over Justice!
N-Nice to meet you.
Thank you for taking care of my father.
So, uh, my father...
Hm?!
Are you in middle school?
Yes. I'm Luluco. I'm a middle school student.
You're under arrest!
B-But I haven't done anything wrong!
You're free to go!
Anyway, my father...
He was forced to swallow
one of those capsules again?
He swallowed one by accident during breakfast.
Who made his breakfast?
I did.
You're under arrest!
But I didn't put it in his food!
Then you're free to go!
Should the Space Patrol really be acting like this?
This place sucks!
You should work here, Luluco.
D-Don't wanna...
Having your father defrosted and returned
to normal will cost us a pretty penny.
He doesn't have any more
advance pay available, either.
I don't wanna!
Right now, mysterious space crime
is running rampant in your middle school.
However, we're powerless because
adults can't interfere there.
I want to send you in as a
temporary undercover space agent.
I'll get approval from HQ.
Wear the Space Patrol Suit
and mete out justice!
Justice!
Good morning! This is Space Middle School.
Today's lucky sign: Leo
Schoolwide assembly at 9:00 AM.
Good morning! This is Space Middle School.
I ended up leaving Dad with
that flaming skeleton guy,
but thanks to that, I got to school on time.
Perfect attendance, no tardies,
my uniform and book bag follow regulations,
and I don't stand out in any way!
I promised Dad, after all.
Being normal is the best!
Midterms
My grades are holding at
just below average, though...
I've gotta work harder!
Wh-What's going on?
Something's echoing in my head!
Identifying Offender
Match
What is this?! What's going on?! Help?!
Space crime detected.
Activating Patrol Suit in Auto mode.
Wait, what does that mean?
I can't! Put me down! Stop!
Wait! Stop! I can't do this!
Who's making all that noise? Luluco?
Put me down! Put me down! Put me down!
We're in the middle of an exam.
She's showing off her curves!
Earthlings are total exhibitionists, huh?
Offender
Space cheating offender detected.
Space
Cheating Offender
Arrest at once.
This guy
Offender
(probably)
Midterm Exam
Answers
Damn! They found out I was space cheating!
Offender
Time to make a run for it!
Offender attempting to escape.
Begin pursuit.
Awaken: Judgment Gun Morphing!
Huh? Wh-What now?!
Wait, what? What's going on?
Not good! This is bad!
No way is this happening!
Not good! Send help! Do not want!
Stop! No! What the heck?!
This is really bad...
So lame!
What the heck?
That's lamer than a southern hick
from a galaxy in the sticks.
What is this?!
Is that supposed to be a gun?
So Earthlings like exposing
the insides of their bodies?
Wait, are you Space Patrol?
What a creepy shape!
Okay, Luluco,
please drop by the staff room later.
Offender attempting to escape, again.
Begin pursuit, again.
Fight for Justice!
The normal life I'd spent thirteen years
building up came crashing down with a bang.
To be continued, though!
I'm searching the entire galaxy for you
Going from one planet to the next
I'm broadcasting my feelings of love to you, beep, beep
So please receive them!
They float gently
In this endless universe
I've locked on to that heart of yours
So you will never be able to run away
I want you to hold my hand
To make my head spin like a merry-go-round
To make my heart skip a beat
The world will be dyed in the colors of my love