The Hero Association has been greatly weakened,
and our greatest weapons are yet to be unleashed.
The Monster Association is poised
for an overwhelming victory,
O Monster King Orochi!
The only question is, now they are off balance,
how will the Hero Association respond?
The power lies in my hand
You'll know now, ONE PUNCH!
Through the one-time tranquil town
Thunderous roars begin to fill the air
Watch out! Freak out! Monsters!
DRAGON
WOLF
TIGER
DEMON
Who will stand to take the lead
When we slay the evil ones?
Mayhem, mix-ups, morons!
We know we are
Heroes!
(Ah) Why on earth were you
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
(Born to be) destined for villainy?
(I know why) If you too wish to know
(If you ask) Then I shall tell!
This night the fist of justice is coming for you
And your fate is a punch straight into hell!
(HERO) That word exists for you, indeed, for you alone
(Go! Go!) Thrust forth your silent fist, raise it to the sky!
(HERO) The solitude is borne by the apostle for
(Go! Go!) A peace not built up from hatred and fear
All to defend the world!
(HERO)
Raise your power!
ONE PUNCH!
Charanko!
I'm going to pound true martial spirit into you!
Come at me!
Charanko finishes it with a single blow!
Our four semi-finalist fighters are now set!
Which one will take the championship?
The Class S Heroes
Huh.
Wearing this makes my head itchy.
Hey! You're up!
Huh?
Why're you holding your head?
Are you nervous?
Oh, yeah.
If I hadn't dropped my guard in our bout,
I'd be trying to keep my head from trembling, too!
The semi-final you just missed was incredible.
Suiryu won again with a single kick!
But the guy you're up against is dangerous, too.
I have him as the dark horse of the tournament.
Watch yourself, Charanko.
He's suddenly acting like a friend to Charanko.
Might help to learn what he looks like.
Watchdog Man...
Class S, Rank 12
Watchdog Man
...here I come.
Just you and me.
Emergency!
A group of monsters is attacking Watchdog Plaza!
What?!
Other cities reporting monster attacks as well!
Ahaha!
Let's party!
Stop!
Release those heroes!
I, Dogman, will fight you!
Is that all your poison can do?
You're not a living creature, are you?
Now that you know...
Self-destruct!
The pilot must be somewhere nearby!
Where's the antivenom serum for City Y?
No word yet.
Damn it.
It'll be okay.
They're on the move.
Huh?
Class S, Rank 9
Drive Knight
Monsters are appearing in all theaters
while the Hero Association lacks intel.
Choose.
My tactical transformations cause
your death by maximum excruciation,
or you die quickly and easily
by revealing all you know.
You interrupted my concert.
The price is your life.
Found you.
Class S, Rank 5
Child Emperor
You're the one controlling the robots.
The toxin analysis is complete.
If only I had my backpack on...
Class S, Rank 10
Pig God
Pig God!
I heard explosions and figured I'd come help.
Any who interfere must die!
No! She's poisonous!
I'll save you!
Hork
Pig God! The venom...!
No problem. Pretty tasty.
Buuuu...rp.
Child Emperor has sent the antivenom formula!
Good. We can treat the poison now.
Class S truly works miracles.
We've come to the second semi-final match!
Semifinals
Match 2
This is a must-see matchup!
Semifinals
Match 2
Choze, whose relentless attacks
have demolished opponents,
versus Charanko, who has advanced
by winning every match with a single blow!
Hmmph!
Any vulgarian can finish
an opponent with a single blow.
I execute my opponents at my own leisurely pace
to showcase my infinite superiority!
I come from a bloodline of chosen people.
For generations, my ancestors bred only
with those who possessed superior genes.
I am their culmination, a genetic masterpiece!
I exist as a breed completely
beyond mere homo sapiens.
Today I declare my dominance for all to see,
but ultimately,
this world will be mine to rule!
You sure got a lot to say.
So you're kinda like GMO corn or something?
I will murder you.
How exquisite to see your eyes filled with tears,
your mouth contorted in pain!
Begin!
Another single-hit knockout!
Charanko advances unscathed to the finals!
The tournament's already ending?
Charanko's power knows no bounds!
We've lost contact with the Class A heroes in City I!
Understood.
Summon a Class S—
Hold it!
I've been hiding under the rubble,
waiting for reinforcements to get here!
Now we've got all these Class A heroes.
We can handle this.
No. You'll do no good.
To fight a foe with inadequate force
only heightens the damage to one's self.
Class S,
Rank 13
Flashy Flash
You saying we're inadequate?
Shut up and watch.
So that's Class S power...?
Isn't this causing even greater damage?!
You stop it?
Just pecked at its wounds.
This may call for my ultimate technique.
That's...
Terrible Tornado!
You there!
Why're you all screwing around
when we're shorthanded?!
We were fighting this octo—
You especially!
"Flashy Flash", was it?
You're supposed to be Class S,
so start acting like one!
Useless jerks.
Says the air-headed woman
who dropped in to steal my kill?
You presume you're stronger than me?!
Yo, what if she hears you?
Don't get us in trouble with her!
Such an arrogant brute.
We were no help at all...
As I predicted, Class S heroes are most troublesome.
It is of no consequence.
We can make any number of monsters.
You're probably all aware
of why I've gathered you here.
It involves the hero hunter, Garou.
Silverfang is currently pursuing him.
However,
it's possible Garou might defeat the old man.
Granted, Silverfang's skills are beyond reproach.
But he is up against his former student.
He might go easy on the boy.
Therefore,
we of the Holy Order of the Sword
will find Garou first, and kill him.
To find him, we need numbers.
I'm asking for your help.
You are the strongest swordsmen we have.
He must be quite a threat for you to ask this...
All right.
I'll send out my disciples.
Amahare...
You were right to ask us.
Zanbai...
Consider it as good as done.
Nichirin...
Thank you all.
I'll make it up to—
Since when is the Holy Order of the Sword
a neighborhood watch?
Haragiri...
Our aim is to achieve true skill.
Improving our art is all
that concerns the Holy Order.
Enough, you're drunk. Let's—
Quiet. I'm not done speaking.
I have something special here.
Monster cells.
By incorporating them into one's body,
one obtains power surpassing human limits!
In other words, we can be monsters ourselves!
He's gone mad.
Where did you get these?
The monsters have formed a Monster Association.
They approached me.
By surrendering my humanity,
I was allowed to join them
and was given strength beyond
what this flesh could offer.
Tell me you didn't...
Of course I did!
I am no longer some mere human.
The power flowing through me is unbelievable.
Gentlemen, you must become monsters too!
You've fallen from the path, Haragiri.
With my quick draw,
I can sever all four of your heads at once.
Any who refuses, dies!
Such a pity.
A pity indeed, Atomic Samurai.
For I was told to kill you, regardless.
You have three seconds!
Eat the monster cells!
3! 2! 1!
The rest of us aren't fools like you.
We're going.
But we've got a new target:
the Monster Association.
Welcome to the Super Fight final match!
The seedings had Charanko
as an overwhelming underdog,
but we might have an incredible upset on our hands!
By the sound of it,
the fans in the stadium sense something, too!
But this man will have no part of it!
It seems unthinkable that
he'd struggle against anyone!
Suiryu of the Dark Corporeal Fist,
versus Charanko's
Fist of Seltzer Water on the Rocks!
Is this guy on to my rug?
Who will emerge victorious?
Oh! Suiryu is grinning!
Has he sensed he's got his opponent outclassed?
Charanko seems to be trying to hide
his nervousness by looking like a doofus!
This is how I always look.
Take your stances!
Let's enjoy ourselves, Charanko.
Huh?
Begin!
The fight begins!
Watch it!
Suiryu takes the offensive!
But for some reason, he stops just short!
H-He's attacking with such speed!
Since it's the finals, I wanted to see his moves,
but that wind is gonna be a problem.
Is he doing that on purpose?
What's the matter?
I know you can see it coming.
Kick after kick!
But he's stopping just short every time!
All Charanko can do is guard his head.
Has he already lost the will to fight?
The ring announcer is clueless.
I was just warming up.
You're strong.
I can tell since I'm strong too.
So he's not trying to blow the wig off?
It's your eyes...
They aren't seeking rank or glory.
Your eyes are looking for something fun.
Well...
you might be right.
Why'd you enter this tournament?
I'm in it for the prize money.
That's what I'm after too.
And I got one more reason.
I want to fight good opponents.
Of course, in the end I'm gonna win,
but the process is fun, you know?
Fun... you say.
Yeah. It's fun being strong.
I see...
I came here to experience martial arts.
I heard the fighters here were strong,
but if I fought back even a little, the match was over.
What're they gabbing about?
Probably the road full of hardships
it took to come so far.
I was starting to think
coming here was a waste of time,
but you seem different.
I see.
Then how about we do it this way?
I'll let you experience martial arts,
and you do your best to make it fun for me.
Oh, I like that.
Okay, then...
Shall we begin?
Here goes!
Th-That was even faster than before!
Suiryu's getting serious!
I won't let up!
Charanko's been launched!
Safe.
D-Down he goes!
Is Charanko okay?
Will he even be able to stand up?
Ch-Charanko!
Their ability levels were too far apart.
Did I go too hard?
That last one had me scared.
I thought for sure my wig was coming off.
All right.
This is how it should be!
H-He's really hanging in there!
If he holds on, his chance might come!
No...
Look at Suiryu.
He's only been using leg techniques.
He's holding back and toying with his prey.
That means...
...he hasn't gotten serious yet.
Your weapon is your punch, right?
C'mon, hit me.
Make it fun.
He read that I was going for a countermove.
He may be a white belt,
but he has real fight experience.
The way he protects only
his head shows sharp instincts.
What's your day job?
My day job?
Uh... going for walks, defeating monsters...
What?
You fight monsters?
It's almost as if you're doing hero stuff.
W-Well...
I figured I might be a hero someday.
Another one aiming to become a hero...
Doesn't seem like a job for a quality fighter.
I fought a few Class A heroes earlier,
but they were so weak!
They're heroes in name only.
Their job is just flaunting virtue and
justice to make people feel indebted.
At their level, no matter how hard they try,
they're not gonna save the world.
Fine intentions, noble thoughts,
lofty morals, heroic justice...
They're impurities that create boredom
in the life of fun that I seek.
You're strong like me,
so why not live free and easy
without that crap holding you back?
Huh?
Hit too close to home?
I offer advice because I see
you're one of the strong, but...
A clean hit!
Wait...
Impurities?
What's that got to do with it?
You're not the only one doing what he wants to do.
Suiryu, was it?
Here's some advice from me.
If what you're after is having fun,
don't get any stronger.
Dang, I keep doing that...
I almost ended it too quick again.
Wh-What the heck happened?!
Did you see that?!
A-Amazing!
M-My goodness!
A shocking development regarding Charanko!
He's been outed as wearing a wig!
The referee is conferring with the judges.
Could this mean...
I will now explain the stoppage.
After the "Wolfman Incident"
of the last tournament,
the rules have been changed
starting with this tournament.
Masks and other head coverings are now prohibited.
His wig has been ruled a head covering.
Accordingly,
Charanko is disqualified!
A-Amazing!
The match has ended!
Suiryu has secured victory!
This is a joke!
Let the match continue!
Charanko's so young to be
carrying such hidden tragedy...
No, that's probably an imposter.
Saitama? What's he doing here?
You know him?
We'll confirm later you're who you claim to be.
Time to go.
Playtime's over.
Now, we fight for real.
What?!
I still haven't shown you what I can really do!
The ring split in two!
You're not going anywhere!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Whoa!
They're still fighting!
I thought we were having fun?
Nothing's fun about losing!
Yeah!
Keep going!
Finish him off!
The crowd loves it!
Suiryu seems a man possessed!
I've never seen him like this before!
Now you'll understand. This is martial arts!
Dark Body Flying Dragon Fist!
He's kicking, punching, unleashing pure fury!
Th-There's no stopping!
I'm not getting to him.
The ring cracked!
That power stance...
He's gonna kill him.
Get away!
That didn't...?!
I see... I think I'm beginning to understand.
So I've given you an inkling
of what martial arts truly are?
Martial arts are essentially...
...moves that look cool.
Such...
...shallowness!
After everything I threw at you,
that's your conclusion?!
I might try that spinny thing you did.
Defeating a monster like that would be sweet.
Don't mock me!
A hip attack gets him!
Oops.
My belt...
Well that wasn't very cool-looking...
Now! Grab him!
Uh-oh.
H-He's making a run for it! Stop him!
Quick, the back exit!
Catch him!
For the first time in my life,
I lost.
Our dreams of future feats, our sorrows of the past
That we all have etched deep down inside our souls
Will they help us along or will they hold us back?
We may never know until the end of time
Still, we hope that finally days of serenity will come
When we'll find it in ourselves to forgive each other's sins
Even if we tried to split apart, we're so important to each other
That we never could forget, no matter what
Our bond can teach us that our kindness is another kind of strength
That you can use just by reaching out your hand
It's something dear to us we couldn't bear to live without
So I swear I'll make it back to you
I swear that I’ll come back here to you
I was defeated...
And I stood no chance.
Among the enemy are monsters
beyond anything seen before...
Gouketsu
Threat Level :
Dragon
The Resistance of the Strong