This is your last chance to surrender, Garou!
Not how you figured you'd be going out, huh?
Well that's just too bad, hero hunter.
Every hero here is a veteran
who's faced down death countless times.
I brought in the heroes
I personally know are the best
just to hunt your ass down!
"The best", you say?
Am I the only one who feels
something's off about that term?
Where are the Class S heroes?
Doesn't the Hero Association
understand how dangerous I am?
These bargain-basement
mediocrities barely get my blood up!
So even a criminal like you
only cares about Class S, eh?
Hmm?
They sure are popular, the Class S heroes.
They get paid off the charts
by the Hero Association,
and they get let in on secrets
that we're not privy to.
Even though we're all heroes, the gap is huge!
Having a ranking system
that credits only those at the top
denies many capable heroes
the recognition they deserve.
They may not be Class S,
but they're still tough as hell.
And you!
You've gotten all this attention
for taking out Class S heroes.
That makes you the perfect
target to prove my point!
So that's why there's no Class S here.
You guys want to take all the credit.
Any kid who heard you would be so let down.
It's hard to breathe...
I feel dizzy, too.
Is it the poison?
I heard there's some
"Monster Association" kicking your teeth in.
You sure a loner like me should be your priority?
What about that hostage who needs rescuing?
Once you're dealt with,
the Monster Association comes next.
We'll be the ones to take
all you upstart monsters out.
These guys are just steps
on my path to becoming a true monster.
I'm not backing down!
The poison's taken effect.
He can't take much more.
If I just keep moving forwards,
I can make it to the top!
The power lies in my hand
You'll know now, ONE PUNCH!
Through the one-time tranquil town
Thunderous roars begin to fill the air
Watch out! Freak out! Monsters!
DRAGON
WOLF
TIGER
DEMON
Who will stand to take the lead
When we slay the evil ones?
Mayhem, mix-ups, morons!
We know we are
Heroes!
(Ah) Why on earth were you
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
Hero
Almanac
Complete Edition
(Born to be) destined for villainy?
(I know why) If you too wish to know
(If you ask) Then I shall tell!
This night the fist of justice is coming for you
And your fate is a punch straight into hell!
(HERO) That word exists for you, indeed, for you alone
(Go! Go!) Thrust forth your silent fist, raise it to the sky!
(HERO) The solitude is borne by the apostle for
(Go! Go!) A peace not built up from hatred and fear
All to defend the world!
(HERO)
Raise your power!
ONE PUNCH!
Did you see Justice Man yesterday?
He finally used a new attack!
Justice Fire Kick!
Yeah, it was so cool!
But you know the best part?
The way Crab Demon died!
Remember his face when Justice Man
saw the egg he was trying to hide?
But Crab Demon almost had him...
When Mach Woman and Little Justice joined in,
it was three vs. one,
but he still held his own! It was so cool!
What the...?
Why're you rooting for Crab Demon?
Crab Demon was only trying to stop ocean pollution.
And he was fighting all by himself.
If he'd been a little stronger, he would've won.
I feel so sorry for him.
Notions of Self Worth
Now!
Ankle Noose!
Earth Rotation of Doom!
Wh-What's he doing?!
Chain Toad!
He's down...
The snake's got a blade or something!
Like I'm not allowed to have one?
Talk about discrimination.
He's been hit in the leg and poisoned, but still...!
Look out!
I've got him.
Bison Pile Driver!
Keep your distance!
What?! When did he...?!
Damn it!
He's figured out our timing,
but he's wide open from the front.
No!
Put me down, damn it!
Roar, Bamboo Shoot!
Shit.
Halfway there...
Death Gatling...
He might get us all at this rate.
Let's forget about taking him alive.
Agreed.
He made his choice.
He still can move at that speed?!
He should be completely worn down by now,
but somehow he has us fighting his fight.
It definitely doesn't feel like we're fighting a human!
Stinger!
Fight me one-on-one!
I accept your challenge! Everyone, stay out of this!
Don't! We have to fight together!
I'll shred him to the bone!
What the—?!
Lucky for me you're as dumb as they say, Stinger!
You tricked me...!
Out of the way!
I'll do this!
Garou can't dodge my rapid fire in his condition!
Move away from Garou!
Hey, what's the matter?!
We were so close a second ago...
Why run away from me now?
I'm gonna be all lonely!
I can't shake him!
He's using Glasses as a shield!
I don't have a shot...
With our formation busted,
am I just holding them back now?
The new guy's just holding us back.
I don't want to share the credit with him.
I-I don't need credit... You all take it.
This is it...
I'm gonna be killed...!
I'll never be a hero...
I'm just an ordinary guy...
I've reached my limit!
Limit?
Who decides what your limit is?
Instead of overthinking setbacks,
just move forward.
That's when I decided to remake myself.
To be like him!
I won't be used as cover.
I'd rather fight to the—
Oh ho! That's the spirit!
You've got lots of stamina, right?
Bastard!
Stinger! It's a trap!
Maybe it is, but I can't ignore it!
Gigantic Drill Stinger!
You took out your meatshields.
Now I don't have to worry about friendly fire.
You're dead, Garou the monster!
There's a kid inside the shack.
He'll get hit if you shoot from there.
Trying to talk your way out
with a lie so completely obvious?
See this now!
The moment the monster wins!
The winner will be justice.
Time to die!
Death Shower!
Impossible...!
Not a single shot hit?!
M-Mister...
Only an idiot would let loose like that.
Don't bother with the act.
See, I know.
That was "Death Shower",
where you use up all your ammo.
He goaded me like he did the others.
"Monsters it hits are turned
into mincemeat and obliterated."
But not quite, eh?
I'm grateful!
You proved I can't be defeated by guns.
Not how you figured you'd be going out, that it?
Too bad for you, but that's how foils work.
You shoulda called in some
Class S heroes like good little Class A's.
If even one of them had joined you,
things might've been different.
Screw Class S!
You think the rest of us are just second string?
Class S heroes are incredible.
But
we fight through blood and death, same as them!
Look at me!
I cornered the hero hunter!
I am the class A hero,
Death Gatling!
You got issues, brother.
I, not them, will defeat you!
To show that we deserve to have our place!
Seems the one most obsessed with rankings
is you, dumbass!
You disgust me.
Idiots...
M-Mister...
Oh.
You're still alive.
Hey!
Somebody help!
W-Water...
I received a call for assistance.
From the look of it, you are that hero hunter.
I will eliminate you.
Machine Gun Blows!
Fist of Flowing Water Crushing Rock!
Die!
Bastard...
He let me bury him to lure me in.
This man...
He defended using
Fist of Flowing Water Crushing Rock.
I understand now...
This is why the other heroes struggled.
Okay! I'm gonna do this!
You got like a millimeter of health left!
Guess I've gotten better than you!
Oh? Still got some fight left?
Hold on a sec. Stay calm, Saitama...
One more hit and I win.
It'd take a miracle for him to comeback n—
So how was that?
I set up for a last-gasp, come-from-behind win.
Hope you had a little fun, at least.
I wouldn't let you win, but I'll let you get this close.
I mean, your moves are always the same.
I gave you a chance,
but all you do is spam the same button.
I could beat you with my eyes closed.
This puts us at 81-0.
I'll loan you the console, so try practicing a bit.
Games stress me out!
If you ever win, it'll all go away.
Don't break anything, okay?
Your thing's going off!
Oh, you're right.
Is it monsters?!
I am so ready to kick the friggin' snot out of 'em!
It says other Class S heroes
headed there immediately.
By the time we get there, it'll probably be all over.
Aww.
Speaking of which, Saitama,
all those dead monsters near your place scare me.
It seems kinda unsanitary...
Oh, I'll have Genos incinerate them later.
But I wonder,
CITY Z HAZARDOUS AREA AHEAD
ABSOLUTELY NO TRESSPASSING
why do so many monsters appear around here?
CITY Z HAZARDOUS AREA AHEAD
ABSOLUTELY NO TRESSPASSING
They're why no one lives in this area anymore.
CITY Z HAZARDOUS AREA AHEAD
ABSOLUTELY NO TRESSPASSING
If monsters start to show up
everywhere like yesterday,
there might be more neighborhoods like yours.
Where is Genos anyway?
He hasn't been home since yesterday.
What? Is he all right?
There's this Monster Association thing now.
Maybe they got him.
It's Genos. He's probably fine.
Maybe I'll have a look.
A Class S...
Thank goodness.
This one's strong...
His speed is the real deal
and he's got Tank-Top Master's power.
He fires those incineration
cannons without hesitation.
Busted up like this, it'll take a lot to beat him.
Damn it...
Give it up.
There is no way you can escape from me.
That's what I need...
I have to remember the way he moved!
He changed his style.
He's moving on all fours!
Shake.
I've always been good with precision machinery!
Mainly at breaking it!
Meaningless.
One after another...
I must've really gotten the attention of you heroes!
Makes me happy to be so popular!
The appearance of an evil organization
has thrown the world into chaos.
The Hero Association must work
as one to deal with that threat.
We do not have time to waste on nobodies like you.
You think I'm a nobody?!
Then help me change that, Demon Cyborg!
Once I've beaten you,
the world will fear me more, won't they?!
Tell them all.
No hero is a match for me.
I'm an all-powerful monster.
No one can defeat me!
No such thing exists.
Now!
Rescue the hero hunter!
What the...?
The Monster Association, at your service.
We've come to bring you back with us, Mr. Garou.
You're in a tight spot, right? We will help you.
You guys again?
Our superiors say they'll
offer you an executive position.
Isn't that wonderful?
Don't want it.
Piss off.
I'm afraid we can't, not this time.
We're here under orders.
This can't be...
The hero hunter,
in league with the Monster Association?
Huh?!
Yesterday, I was defeated.
But I learned there are monsters
more powerful than I could imagine.
Now, no matter what threat may appear,
my guard will never be down again.
Plus, I am stronger than I was yesterday.
Master Saitama said to aim for
a higher level and train my spirit.
I am beginning to understand what he meant.
It will take more than this to defeat me.
Master Saitama?
There is a hero stronger than all others
whom no monster can match.
Incinerate.
Genos.
Bang?
Would you mind letting us handle this?
Fist of Whirling Wind, Slashing Steel!
Let me handle the monsters, Bang.
You take Garou.
Thank you, brother.
Now, then.
We meet once more, Garou.
That voice...
The world's most annoying
old geezer is here for me?
What the hell happened to you?
I'll end it for you.
On your feet!
Are you strong?
Who is this cocky kid?
Master, shall I toss the brat out?
No.
When he wakes up, feed him until he's full.
Fist of Flowing Water Crushing Rock!
Our dreams of future feats, our sorrows of the past
That we all have etched deep down inside our souls
Will they help us along or will they hold us back?
We may never know until the end of time
Still, we hope that finally days of serenity will come
When we'll find it in ourselves to forgive each other's sins
Even if we tried to split apart, we're so important to each other
That we never could forget, no matter what
Our bond can teach us that our kindness is another kind of strength
That you can use just by reaching out your hand
It's something dear to us we couldn't bear to live without
So I swear I'll make it back to you
I swear that I’ll come back here to you
Cleaning Up the Disciples' Mess