Earthdoom Prophecy Emergency Countermeasures Team
Introductory Briefing
That's what's going on here?
We're asking criminals for help?
Has the Association approved this?
It has!
Mankind is on the cusp of a period of crisis
that we cannot overcome unless we unite as one.
Introductory Briefing
Earthdoom Prophecy Emergency Countermeasures Team
Our current heroes:
390 in Class C,
101 in Class B,
38 in Class A,
and 17 in Class S,
are clearly not enough!
You won't be working for free.
We will duly compensate you
for every monster you defeat!
What a crock!
That's a total waste of cash.
You can't count on trash like this
when things go south.
And you're so high and mighty?
I've killed more people than you've met.
Wanna try me?
These wimps...
...have no heart!
B-But—
Well now, look at this!
She's good—her prophecy's spot on.
She knew a God-level threat like
no one had ever seen was coming.
That old meathead's right.
All these nobodies put together
couldn't take me down.
Huh?
Who are you?
Name's Garou.
I've busted up tons of martial arts dojos
and you could say I've got a thing for monsters.
Now what's the hold up?
All of you, come at me.
Let's find out who's strongest.
You see, that's what I came for!
Stop this foolishness.
Foolishness?
We don't need you. Get lost.
That how you treat a guest,
Earthdoom Prophecy Emergency Countermeasures Team
Introductory Briefing
Mister Big Shot of Justice?
Hell, you've made up my mind.
To each and every coward here
I'm gonna mete out some evil.
A little slaughter party!
You three, there's a job for you.
Toss him out.
With pleasure.
Well, gramps?
You forget to put some "heart" behind your punch?
With or without that bullcrap, the strong...
...are strong!
Old fart!
Whoa! Not bad!
Yeah! That's how you do it!
Huh?
What're you worms cheering about?
You're gonna die, too.
Wh-What'd he say?!
You're supposed to be on our side!
No!
Heroes are always late to the party,
while monsters take the initiative.
They appear suddenly, out of the blue.
Listen up. You're on the humans' side.
I'm with the monsters.
A human calling himself a monster?
Foolish scum!
I'll burn your body to ash!
These little tricks liven things up,
but once you see through 'em, they're ugly.
He just...!
This is central tower, 7th floor multipurpose hall!
Send every hero in the facility, stat!
All of them!
Taking on several Class S punks at once
might be bit much right now.
That should be enough to make quite
the name for "Garou the Monster".
This has been my declaration of war.
In six months, I'll be even stronger.
Then I come back in through the front door.
'Til then.
The power lies in my hand
You'll know now, ONE PUNCH!
Through the one-time tranquil town
Thunderous roars begin to fill the air
Watch out! Freak out! Monsters!
DRAGON
WOLF
TIGER
DEMON
Who will stand to take the lead
When we slay the evil ones?
Mayhem, mix-ups, morons!
We know we are
Heroes!
(Ah) Why on earth were you
Hero
Directory
(Born to be) destined for villainy?
(I know why) If you too wish to know
(If you ask) Then I shall tell!
This night the fist of justice is coming for you
And your fate is a punch straight into hell!
(HERO) That word exists for you, indeed, for you alone
(Go! Go!) Thrust forth your silent fist, raise it to the sky!
(HERO) The solitude is borne by the apostle for
(Go! Go!) A peace not built up from hatred and fear
All to defend the world!
(HERO)
Raise your power!
ONE PUNCH!
Orders understood?
Yes!
Class B, Rank 3
Wild
Monkey
Class B, Rank 2
Eyelashes
And if the target shows the slightest resistance?
We physically punish him to the point
that he never behaves brashly again!
Very good.
Thank you, Miss Fubuki!
Human Monster
Master Saitama, your rank
has risen to Class B, rank 7.
I have also risen to Class S, rank 14.
All I did was defeat monsters I bumped into.
I've gone up that much?
It is because nowadays
monsters appear almost daily.
You defeat monsters,
but do not report it to the Association.
The fact that your rank is increasing despite that
means witnesses are reporting your work for you.
In other words, your identity as a hero
is gradually becoming known
to the citizenry, Master.
Before long, fan clubs for you might spring up.
What? No way.
Even you, a Class S, don't have a fan club.
I do have a fan club.
Seriously?
High-speed object detected!
That is beyond human speed.
A monster?
Ooh, an item.
Master appears preoccupied.
Guess I'll go...
I will be able to test out my new upgrades.
Show yourself!
A human?
What do you want?
Get Saitama out here.
I obtained information saying he lives here.
Are you a friend of Master Saitama's?
We've met somewhere before...
I am Speed-o'-Sound Sonic, Saitama's rival.
Today is the day I settle the score.
Now, out of my way.
Speed-o'-Sound Sonic!
So it's you, the pervert.
You dare call yourself Master's rival? Shameless!
One more step and you will be eliminated.
Always trailing Saitama like shit on a goldfish...
You will be "eliminated".
O-Oh crap.
20 Minutes Later
I overwrote King's save data.
And after I brought it home without asking...
It'll probably be fine.
No, it won't.
Aw man.
Class B, rank 7 hero Saitama!
Come out here!
Class B, rank 1 Blizzard from Hell would like a word.
Oh, I've already got a subscription to the newspaper.
We are not salesmen!
We're heroes who outrank you!
How do you do, new hero Saitama.
I am the Blizzard from Hell.
Perhaps you've heard of me?
Huh?
Not even once.
Who are you?
She is the Class B, rank 1 hero!
Oh, I see. Keep up the good work!
So?
Bastard sure is cocky...
I doubt you can take a hint, so I'll be clear.
All who ascend to Class B customarily
pay their respects to the Blizzard from Hell.
Emergency Alarm
Pay respects?
Yo. I am Saitama.
Howja do?
Well, that'll do.
Now, are you aware that there are
various factions in the hero business?
Factions?
In this industry, if you aren't part of a group,
Emergency Alarm
you don't survive.
I don't get it.
Emergency Alarm
I'm saying it's impossible to raise your rank alone.
Why not?
Obstacles in your way.
Like what?
Like rivals.
I don't really understand.
But anyway, I'm kinda busy—
I'm not done talking!
Align yourself with me.
If you do, I'll ensure you never
drop out of the top of Class B.
Oh?
Huh?
Ah!
What you're saying is,
if I refuse, you'll stand in my way?
Do you make threats like this to every Class B?
Like a gang leader?
I only make offers to heroes who catch my eye.
Are you afraid that I'll take your rank 1 spot?
Don't worry about it.
I'll make Class A soon enough.
Come to think of it,
why haven't you moved on to Class A?
Hurry up and give me your answer.
Obviously the answer is no.
There shouldn't be a pecking order among heroes!
Eyelashes! Wild Monkey!
Yes, Ma'am!
Rough him up so bad he
never works as a hero again!
You won't survive like this,
Blizzard.
So you're trying to push me aside.
Is this...
...telekinesis?
Exactly.
You don't seem surprised.
Are you gonna fight me with rocks and stuff?
Better not.
Think you can mock me?
You'll regret it.
I'll beat you to an inch of your life.
Hellstorm!
Flesh peels away, bones crack and rupture...
The cruelty and brutality
break your will in an instant.
It's your own doing, though.
You deserve it for thinking you can surpass me!
No one is better than me!
All my enemies—
You'll never make top-rank
throwing tantrums like that.
—will be crushed!
You don't get what it means to be a hero.
The world is full of super-strong bad people.
Standing up to them is what heroes do.
Even if you've gotta do it alone.
Someone like you, who gathers the weak
so she can feel strong, can't understand.
It'll come back to bite you.
Factions?
Newb crushing?
Rankings?
Who'd care about them?!
Show heroes some respect, poser!
Shut up!
What would you know about me?!
Wh-What happened?
Oww!
My hunt for a rat...
...has led me back to Master's apartment.
That's Genos, a Class S...
What's he doing here?
Master Saitama, I apologize for
kicking up dust near your home.
This is a little more than "dust"!
I caught a glimpse of Sonic just now.
What were the two of you doing?
Y-You have connections with Class S heroes?
Huh? You mean Genos?
I am Master Saitama's disciple.
D-Disciple?
A Class S, to a Class B?
You are Class B, rank 1
The Blizzard from Hell.
I see.
You have targeted Master Saitama
as your latest newcomer to "crush".
And now you are near death
from fighting him, correct?
No,
she got caught up in your attack.
Is that so? Then I apologize—
Exploding Shuriken!
A monster?!
Not really.
I've got enough on my plate, get lost.
You could throw 100 more
and I would still be unscathed.
Tough talk, but you haven't even hit me,
Puppet-man.
Saitama!
Watch me!
After I turn your disciple into scrap, you're next!
Such intense malice...
And even just standing there,
I sense his extraordinary combat ability...
This man is dangerous!
Master, this stalker's persistence is an affront.
I will rid the world of his existence.
No way a slug like you could get rid of me.
Sure you still want to fight me
when that's all you've got?
When did I show you all I have got?
You lose, fool.
Accelerate.
He's gotten a bit faster since we sparred.
Oh.
Maybe he got an upgrade?
I can barely see them.
Why does he bother going around behind me?
Does this child think he's faster than me?
I picked some lint from your hair.
You little—!
Dropped your guard, did you, Sonic?
Machine Gun Blows!
He dodged?
Wait!
You're hopeless.
Such confidence, yet your punches
meet only air. How's it feel?
This master technique uses special footwork and
my super-fast movement to create after-images.
Fourfold Funeral!
Now die.
Scatterflash Slash!
I cannot follow his movement.
So I will lay waste to the entire area!
Incineration Cannons, maximum intensity!
It's over!
I won?
No, he dropped before I slashed him...
Saitama...
Trying to save your disciple?
You're too soft.
I don't need my whole neighborhood exploded.
Besides, the two of you have no reason to fight.
Genos...
Were you built for petty fights like this?
And Sonic, I thought you were after me.
Since you won't leave it alone,
I'll take you seriously this once.
Menacing
Come at me.
I've been waiting for this moment.
And to kill you,
I've perfected the ultimate technique!
Okay, let's see it.
Ultimate Master Technique!
Tenfold Funeral!
Ten clone images?
He's trained hard enough to stop being a joke!
His combat skills are clearly Class S level.
As a Class B, Saitama doesn't stand a chance.
Even so...
Why is it that when I face you,
I feel as if I'm doomed to lose every time?
Until I wipe away this hang-up by beating you,
I will never break through my limits!
Killer Move: Serious Series.
Serious Line Hops!
Whuaowethaofuoaakkk??
Wh-What was that?
I just line-hopped past him.
He beat me with shock waves?
Countless afterimages...
He was faster...
Next time, we—
Is he dead?
I wasn't trying to kill him.
Such power.
He's not normal.
I could never make it to number one.
I had intelligence, stamina, street smarts,
and I was born an esper.
I should be standing at the top!
If only it weren't for her.
My older sister and the world's most powerful esper,
Tatsumaki.
Class S, Rank 2
Tornado of Terror
Because of her, I'd never been
number one in anything my entire life.
So when I became Class B, rank 1, I got to thinking.
If I remain in this position and control
the heroes of Class B and below,
Sun-man
I can surpass my sister,
who only works alone.
That little—
The Tornado of Terror is Class S.
Why don't you aim for Class A, rank 1?
Class A is out of the question.
It'd be no problem climbing the ranks of Class A,
but I could never become rank 1.
Never.
Class A, rank 4 Bushi Drill.
Class A, rank 3 Okama Itachi.
Class A, rank 2 Iairon.
Class A, Rank 2
Iairon
Class A, Rank 3
Okama Itachi
Class A, Rank 4
Bushi
Drill
Even these three swordsmen,
disciples of the Class S hero Atomic Samurai,
cannot break into the ranks of Class S. Why not?
Because no one can surpass
Class A, rank 1 Handsome Mask.
The primitive savage found frozen
in an ice floe and revived, Suppon.
You escaped from the research facility
and accosted those who
tried to help you. You are evil.
The Association instructed me to capture you alive,
but I'm not that merciful.
Class A, Rank 1
Handsome Mask
Enough!
Handsome Mask!
You're wonderful!
He's so tough!
This world is rife with unimaginable monsters.
You're quite a monster yourself,
but not to the level of Handsome Mask or my sister.
There's also King,
who they call the world's strongest man,
and Blast, who stands atop the hero world.
They're monsters even among monsters.
For us, it's difficult to advance on our own abilities.
So what's wrong with banding together?
Sun-man
Nothing, really.
But I don't think I'll become one of your underlings.
Because you're strong?
You'll never move up the rankings, you know.
Oh well. I tried to get you into my faction.
Yo, Saitama!
Hey, did you take my game home with you?
K-K-K-K-K-K-King?!
S-Sorry, I did take it.
I knew it. Hand it over.
No, I'm really sorry.
No big deal, as long as you give it back.
I deleted your save.
Huh? What'd you say?
Why?
Why is a Class S so happy to see a Class B?
Master does not team up with others.
Does not antagonize anyone.
Ignores rankings.
My bad.
Nah, don't worry about it.
Oh, the button's smooshed in.
Yet powerful heroes are drawn to him.
If only I were one of them.
It is because...
...he is strong.
Our dreams of future feats, our sorrows of the past
That we all have etched deep down inside our souls
Will they help us along or will they hold us back?
We may never know until the end of time
Still, we hope that finally days of serenity will come
When we'll find it in ourselves to forgive each other's sins
Even if we tried to split apart, we're so important to each other
That we never could forget, no matter what
Our bond can teach us that our kindness is another kind of strength
That you can use just by reaching out your hand
It's something dear to us we couldn't bear to live without
So I swear I'll make it back to you
I swear that I’ll come back here to you
Class S, rank 14 Genos
and Class B, rank 7 Saitama.
We are agreed upon their hero names?
No objections!
For aggressively attacking numerous
monsters with dauntless courage,
Genos's hero name will be "Demon Cyborg".
And based on his appearance,
Saitama's name will be...
"Caped Baldy".
A hero name is something
every aspiring hero dreams of.
No doubt these two will be overjoyed to hear theirs.
"Demon Cyborg" and "Caped Baldy".
They'll work even harder now!
Two hours of chitchat about some useless nicknames,
while the meeting to deal
with Garou ends in 15 minutes?
Damned good-for-nothing optimists!
You mean that crazy fellow
who calls himself a monster?
No need to panic, Sitch.
Class S, rank 3 Silverfang is already in pursuit.
We can trust that old man.
If need be, Tornado and Blast are also available.
He's just a man, Sitch.
He likely has nothing to do with the prophecy.
Damn!
Will that really be enough to deal with Garou?
What the crap...
Wh-Who the hell are you?!
I'm a Class A hero!
Why'd you attack me?
Class A, rank 9 Tank-Top Vegetarian.
I happened upon you, so you're my next prey.
But I'm stunned by the lack of challenge.
Brace yourself, then.
You'll find out what it's like
to throw down with a hero.
Oh, I'm looking forward to it.
Whenever I can battle a true monster-class hero.
The Hunt Begins