What are you looking for?
A getaway car?
A hideout?
Some clean cash?
Well, I won't stick my nose where it doesn't belong.
Just tell me what you need.
Tell me, "Assorted Goods Retailer",
Mr. Department Store,
is that also for sale?
Is that what you're interested in?
I'm afraid it's not available for purchase.
My punching bag—
Woah, there.
My deposit.
I've also been a bit worked up
since picking up this stupid job.
Just so you know, you owe me 7 million if she dies.
What do you want that brat for anyway?
Oh, right.
I think you've got the wrong idea.
I'm not buying her.
I'm buying you.
A Certain Magical Index
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
Carrying a ticking time bomb
The Earth keeps on turning, so hurry up!
No one can pretend it's not their business anymore
Suddenly common sense is out the door
Opposing fates fail to reach each other
Drenched in the rain of resentment
But why? Fear and doubt keep building up heavy in my heart
My racing heart is flooded with ambition
Ready!
Everyone that's drawn to this place
Has gone beyond the meaning and color of desire
My heart wants to stay strong
I feel it deep inside me
With all my soul, this one thing
Dive into a heart
Spark Signal
I took care of it.
This job was so shitty I almost died of boredom.
Huh? What I need?
Someone to collect a pile
of meat that's still breathing
and a set of women's clothes.
What size? How should I know?
Also, send only women.
If I see any guys, I'm going to bust their balls.
Live however you want.
Whether you succeed or fail
in the rest of your life is up to you.
Who are you?
A villain.
A shithead villain.
And you know what?
Today's dinner is stewed hamburg steak,
says Misaka as Misaka reports
the results of her reconnaissance.
So Yomikawa's mastery of the rice cooker
now extends to dishes that elaborate, huh?
You said we could meet on the weekend, right?
Says Misaka as Misaka tries to receive confirmation.
So long as plans don't change until then.
Oh! Yomikawa has brought
the stewed hamburg steak!
Says Misaka as Misaka reports
on top-priority real-time developments.
Is that so? It seems like your life
is always full of side-tracking.
Did something happen?
Asks Misaka as Misaka is puzzled
at the sound of a telephone ringing.
Nothing special.
Just confirming my room service order.
Are you okay?
I don't want you doing anything dangerous.
Says Misaka as Misaka tries asking nicely.
You don't need to worry about
a dude who can survive a nuke.
The times have really changed for the better.
You can't call those pro maids.
M-Maika...
What I'm saying is, wearing the clothes
and gathering lustful glares is not the point.
What did you say?!
What meaning is there to the
existence of non-sexy maids?!
I would seem my shitty brother needs to
be taught what being a maid is really about.
I'll go get some mechanical pencil leads.
Oh? I'll join you then.
Are you going to help your beloved
brother with his homework?!
Together, we should have it done by dawn!
Okay, I'm not going to your place today.
What?
Adieu.
You have no heart!
So, what's today's homework?
One day, I'll get out of this city.
I'll beat this impossible game!
Musujime!
Today we're going to work hard until you
learn to make sautéed vegetables properly.
My tummy and I are waiting for you!
Sautéed vegetables!
I'll be straight. I have some urgent business,
so I can't sauté vegetables tonight.
Today too?!
What about the heaps of veggies that I bought?!
Good for you. Vegetarians live longer.
This is a camper, so it has a kitchen, right?
I see that you're still fond of that face, Etzali.
And I see you're still sour, Xochitl.
You've taken possession
of the original Grimoire, right?
It's right here.
What happened to you?
I messed up.
To make up for it,
I had to let them tinker with my body.
Wasn't there anyone to stop them?
What about Tochtli? She was on your side, right?
My side, huh?
I've never met any of the people
who are on your side now, have I?
Don't try to deny it.
Whatever the reason, you switched sides from
the Aztecs to Academy City and defeated me.
Right, Eztali?
Brother?
Unabara, you lowlife!
What was that just now?!
Stand back, Etzali!
He must be from our organization!
No, he may be a pervert, but he's an ally.
You get infatuated with a Level 5 middle-school
girl despite having a little sister at home?!
A middle school girl?
Wait, what are you talking about?!
Etzali, don't tell me you
betrayed us for such a reason?!
Calm down!
First of all, she meant "brother" figuratively!
We're more like teacher and student.
So step-siblings, then!
What else could you wish for?!
Every human at some point falls
under the influence of a younger kid.
Oh my, is everyone in GROUP
other than me a pedo?
Your obsession with little boys doesn't
leave you in any position to call me a "pedo".
He has a point.
He does.
Wh-What would ever make
you think that about me?!
So what's this job that requires
convening all of GROUP?
It's just a regular job.
We have to wipe out some people
calling themselves Spark Signal,
who have taken some hostages.
They said I'm fine now
and they'll discharge me soon.
That's good,
You can't use Body Crystals anymore,
but I'm relieved that you're not any worse off.
But I'm super-surprised you brought flowers.
I super-thought you'd get a bunny suit.
Drop that already!
It's not like I—
Ta-da!
This is our place's famous super-bunny girl Rikou!
Hamazura, are you that super-into bunny girls?!
Th-This is because of Kinuhata's foot massage!
Don't worry, Hamazura.
We're in a hospital,
so a nosebleed can be easily fixed.
You're the only one who
cares about someone like me.
Don't worry, Hamazura.
This hospital also treats diseases of the mind.
When Takitsubo is super-out,
what are you going to do?
Good question.
ITEM is de-facto super-dissolved.
I'm waiting for another team to be formed,
but there's no point teaming up with Takitsubo,
who's lost her combat power,
and you don't have a reason
to help us anymore either.
I don't know if I'm capable of doing anything myself,
but I have to do something to bring
Takitsubo back from the Dark Side.
In other words,
you're going to super-pour your whole soul
into figuring out how to make
Takitsubo wear a bunny suit, right?
Come on, am I now stuck being
treated as the bunny guy?!
Stop looking at me as if you're
super-staring at a bunny girl, Hamazura.
Now, let me be straight with you,
a bunny suit won't suit you!
Now let me tell you something!
I may be a middle schooler,
but I have a better figure than Takitsubo,
who's in high school.
You're so wrong!
I expect that when Takitsubo
will really shine is without clothes.
And that there won't be any
surprises if you take yours off.
I'm going to super-murder you, okay?
You don't seem to mind being super-killed!
That was a super-close call.
I nearly gave you a super-useful
visual aid for your handiwork tonight.
That definitely makes the top 5
worst things I've heard in my life.
Also don't think that the sight of
your panties is worthy of being my—
Hamazura, look how it super-flutters.
I-I can see them... almost...
Once more, flutter!
B-But I can't see them!
I want to see them, but I can't!
It's no use.
I want, but can't!
And flutter!
Takitsubo, give me strength!
That's cheating!
Hamazura, you're super-dead!
Have you no mercy, you demon?!
As long as we can blow up
their largest particle accelerator,
we can prevent the Board of Directors
from making any open moves.
I doubt anyone could do much
if we're this far down underground.
It's time.
Show him a bit of compassion.
Put a blindfold on him.
This plan is never gonna work.
What?
You'll never get away with your evil deeds!
I believe that there's a hero who'll catch you!
We'll all be saved!
Someone's going to come and save us!
Really?
Even if such a hero exists, it doesn't look like
he can reach a depth of 200 meters in time.
I believe!
How did you find us?!
Finding you using Move Point
is a piece of cake, you piece of shit.
A-Are you a hero?
I'm a villain.
A shithead villain.
Good work.
That was pretty well done.
There's one thing that bothers me, though.
It's what those shithead terrorists
were demanding from the higher-ups.
Did they say anything about their demands?
DRAGON.
Their only demand was for all information on
DRAGON to be immediately released to the public.
We just went along with
what the higher-ups told us to do,
and crushed an important lead
that was right under our noses.
How is Sunazara Chimitsu doing,
Stephanie Gorgeouspalace?
His treatment is proceeding smoothly.
He hasn't regained consciousness,
but they say his life is no longer in danger.
It's all thanks to you.
Please, it makes me sad to see him like this.
So, who's the person you want taken out?
The first-rank of Academy City, Accelerator.
Can you do it?
If that's what I need to do.
You need not consider who else
might get hurt in the process.
For example, I won't mind if some stray bullets
hit ex-ITEM members, like Kinuhata Saiai,
who put Sunazara in his current state.
That's nice to hear.
Then let me also get the person who implanted
a transmitter in Sunazara's body along the way.
Wait!
This is yours.
If you had just handed Sunazara over,
I would have been fine with doing your dirty work.
If you had just done what I told you,
you could have avenged him!
Oh, I forgot to mention something.
The object of that revenge
is everyone in Academy City.
A Certain Magical Index
Huh? Did you forget we're having
a discharge party for Takitsubo?
What? A job?
We're finally forming a new team,
so we're going to go super-wipe out
the remnants of a terrorist group.
Huh? What sort of game is that?
Takitsubo's waiting for us.
We're meeting at the salon in District 3, okay?
Does it bother you?
If you want to avoid unexpected misfortune,
you should never let your guard down.
That's also why I never meet you in person.
You're probably hiding in something
like a nuclear bunker.
Faced with abilities like Musujime's,
the thickness of your walls doesn't matter.
Mr. Shiokishi, why are you,
a Board member, contacting us directly?
I'd like you to take out the remnants
of the "Spark Signal" terrorists
you dealt with the other day.
Do you know what DRAGON refers to?
Sounds like the name of an old video game.
Deal with this boring task quickly so
that you can return to your regular lives.
There are twenty remaining members.
We can easily kill them,
but are we just going to do what the Board tells us?
This might be our chance
to get a glimpse of DRAGON.
Are you suggesting we join
forces with the terrorists?
Make no mistake,
if you're prepared to get civilians involved,
that would be the end of our little quartet.
So weren't you going to form
a new team and fight terrorists?
Yeah. But it only took a few minutes
to meet the others, and then I came back here.
We're creating a new team from the remnants
of ITEM, SCHOOL, BLOCK, and MEMBER.
You all tried to kill each other before,
but I'm sure you can get along just fine now.
Wait a minute! That's so shady!
Oh, yeah, that girl in the dress, Measure Heart,
said she's super-looking
forward to working with you.
That girl...
Wait, should you be here now?
Aren't you ignoring orders from the higher-ups?!
I super-shouldn't be doing it.
So, Hamazura,
I want you to help me with something.
What?
I just have to wipe out all the terrorists,
before I get dragged back to this new team.
What?!
So I guess you're the type of person
who relies on help from acquaintances.
Did you super-say something, Hamazura?
Hey! Something crazy-looking is coming after us!
Are you stupid?!
You're stopping us from attacking them!
They got away.
Our pack of villains goes in, does a fat lot
of nothing, and barely plucks off half of them?
Maybe I'll just go finish off
the rest of Spark Signal on my own.
Wait! Please wait!
Stop! Don't use meds!
But she won't make it to the hospital without it.
She's pregnant.
Please save them both!
I'm begging you!
Move.
Sex: female.
Weight: 244 grams.
Heartbeat: 60.
Stimulus-response rate: 5.52.
Prepare 2.5 grams of Ectrin.
Administer via transdermal chip over
the carotid artery, delivering five 20-second doses,
with 10 seconds between them.
That will keep her alive.
Wait! What would that do to the child?
I just said that will keep her alive.
Hey, wait!
Hey!
Thank you. You saved them.
Get lost already.
I'll never forget what you did for us.
I'd like to be able to return that favor one day!
So—
Get lost.
It's a Six Wings.
Why would it be after us?
Don't tell me it's because you ignored your orders!
I think you're super-jumping to conclusions here.
It's shooting at us!
Six Wings missiles are guided by infrared sensors.
That was a super-flare!
Nice work.
Hamazura, hold the wheel super straight!
Are you crazy! It'll hit us! We'll die!
Look super-straight ahead and drive!
Yes, but your panties—
I mean, you can't do it!
You can't get through a military
chopper's armor with that!
Who said I'm trying to get through its armor?!
Yes! I was super-awesome.
I figured the clay shot would break into
super-many pieces and clog the air intake.
Nice panties!
Damn it!
Kinuhata, use your Offense Armor!
Wait! What about you?!
Okay, I should pick up Kinuhata
and go meet Takitsubo.
Unknown Caller
It's been a while.
I'm one of the ex-SCHOOL members,
Measure Heart. You remember me, right?
Where did you get my number?
First, tell me, is Kinuhata Saiai with you?
So that was you people's doing, was it?!
If you have a way of contacting her, tell her this:
The terrorists who you said
you'd take care of yourself
have occupied the salon in District 3.
The salon in District 3?!
When I least expect it, you're gone
And loneliness hits me hard in the chest
In the night filled with signs I look up at the stars
I bite my lip and pray
Every time the dawn comes I run to you
You try to hide behind a smile that you're covered in wounds
But I notice, because I'm not a child
I'll protect you even if I have to make an enemy of the entire world
This strength comes from the light you've given me
I don't want to just wait for a miracle
I want to start a revolution that changes who the two of us are
And this is the night before it starts
Next Time
Even if I become a villain,
even if I have to grovel on the ground,
even if I have to sacrifice someone,
there's a person I'm going
to protect no matter what!
Next time: "The Board of Directors".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.