We managed to make a clean
escape from the Knights.
What?! Clean?!
You call hitting the water spinning
and bouncing off seven times "clean"?!
But, come on now, we're both still alive, aren't we?
It's all good.
What do you mean "all good"?!
That's not the point!
I hear hoof sounds!
Are they after us?
You?
The Third Princess?!
We found the Third Princess.
Good work.
Take her into protective custody.
Also...
The Imagine Breaker is with her?!
What in the world is happening there?
A Certain Magical Index
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
Carrying a ticking time bomb
The Earth keeps on turning, so hurry up!
No one can pretend it's not their business anymore
Suddenly common sense is out the door
Opposing fates fail to reach each other
Drenched in the rain of resentment
But why? Fear and doubt keep building up heavy in my heart
My racing heart is flooded with ambition
Ready!
Everyone that's drawn to this place
Has gone beyond the meaning and color of desire
My heart wants to stay strong
I feel it deep inside me
With all my soul, this one thing
Dive into a heart
Curtana Original
Have you heard of the Scandinavian
warrior named Thororm?
They say he used magic to blunt
the weapons of his enemies.
Could... you... have...
Based on that legend,
I developed a spell that allows me
to nullify the offensive power
of anything I deem a weapon.
That's after the horrible surprise
attack on me in Dover.
Reduce to zero!
I already reduced that to zero!
Don't you have anything else?
History is already in motion.
Unless you can turn back time,
it's clear who the best choice
of ruler for this nation is.
So why do you keep clinging
to the powerless Third Princess?
Do you still not understand?!
No!
It can't be!
The three animals in the crest represent
the Royal Family, the Knights, and the Church.
The blue patterns of the field represent England,
Scotland, Wales, and Northern Ireland,
the countries of the United Kingdom.
Are you serious?!
Do you really mean to take that stand?!
Are you trying to achieve complete harmony
on the level of Britain as a whole
without siding with any of the three
Princesses or the Queen?
I've told you already.
There is no point in talking about this.
You should just take action
in accordance with your beliefs.
Reduce to ze—
He launched it into the air?!
But as a long as I notice it and
deem it a weapon, it's useless.
Reduce to ze—
Can I make it in time?
Reduce to zero!
You had another hidden blade?
And I meet the same end as Thororm.
In the end it's just like ten years ago.
You won using a surprise attack.
After all, I'm nothing but an ex-mercenary brute.
That means that unlike you strict Knights,
I can fight any way I see fit.
Unfortunately, I don't have any
blades fit for killing old friends.
H-He beat the commander!
Get back!
I'm getting a really bad vibe from this.
But I have to do something.
Good thing the Amakusa Church took
the Third Princess under their protection.
That is a face I never wanted to see again.
Acqua of the Rear?!
So he survived.
Index!
If you wish to reclaim her, be quick about it.
This place may be more dangerous than London,
where the insurgents have gained control.
So the Knight Leader was defeated.
Look at all the work he left for me!
He was supposed to clear the small fry
out of my way, but now I have to do it myself.
Worry not, I shall free you from your work
by putting an end to your
coup d'état right here and now.
I'm stronger than you think.
Don't forget that I hold
Curtana Original in my hand!
This was originally meant to cut off
Britain's territory from the planet Earth,
putting it under the control of the wielder.
But I can also put its power to
a more immediately practical use.
If you cut a three-dimensional object,
the cross-section is two-dimensional.
For a two-dimensional object,
the cross-section is one-dimensional.
And if you cut something with
more than three dimensions,
the cross-section becomes a
three-dimensional object in this world.
In other words, the cross-section
is expressed as this sort of scrap material.
The All Dimensions Severing Spell.
If I were to point out a flaw,
I guess it's that it ends fights too easily,
so it's not much fun.
Damn it! If you can keep her occupied
in one place for just a moment,
I can use that chance to destroy her mystic artifact.
Ooh, I'm so scared.
I hear your specialty is called Imagine Breaker.
Let me show you the
appropriate way to deal with it!
Shit!
What do I do now?!
Index!
Grab on to me if you want to live.
That hurt.
Take your friend.
Why did you save us?
The one currently managing the alliance
between Roman and Russian Churches
is a man called Fiamma of the Right.
Fiamma of the Right?
What Fiamma wants
is your right arm, and the knowledge
of how to manifest its true function,
which is contained in the
Index Librorum Prohibitorum.
Therefore, if I had allowed the two of you to fall,
Fiamma would have lost the crucial elements
of his plan, plunging him into turmoil.
I was worried that could lead to even more
widespread and meaningless destruction.
In the end, the only proper way to go about this
is to remove the root cause of the problem.
But before that, this little quarrel sprung
out of the core issue, and it needs to be curbed.
Little quarrel? You mean the coup d'état?!
Is there a way to stop it?
The relationship between Carissa and the Knights
is centered around Curtana Original,
which makes that its weak point.
However, it's not my style to strike at that.
I fight head-on without using tricks.
Acqua of the Rear, huh?
Index! Are you all right?!
Does anything hurt?
Did you save me from the Knights?
You'd think that, right?
But the truth is a bit more complicated.
Wait, don't tell me you came here
together with another strange woman?!
You'd think that, right?
But the truth is a bit harsher.
I'm relieved to see that you're your usual self.
Touma, I think I want some dinner.
That's a bit too much like your usual self.
A Certain Magical Index
Disable Curtana Original?
We got a report that the Second Princess
has returned to Buckingham Palace.
We assume she's there to tune Curtana Original,
which is unstable due to its immense power.
The Second Princess and the Knights only
work together because of mutual interests.
So an opportunity has opened up now
that the Knight Leader has been defeated.
If we managed to destroy Curtana,
the coup would fall apart.
Now that I think about it,
Acqua also mentioned that the deal between
Carissa and the Knights is centered around Curtana.
But even knowing that, can we actually do it?
The Buckingham Palace subway.
In one of the normally-unused branches
of the Underground system,
there's a rail car with a special magic circle
always waiting on standby.
If the car is moved directly
under Buckingham Palace,
it can stop the sword from overloading.
We think that's also the reason
why Carissa returned to Buckingham.
We can use that to our advantage.
The Church of England's
flying fortress, Coven Compass,
stores enormous amounts of magic power
used for its large-scale flash spell.
We should be able to use that to interfere
with Curtana Original, causing it to overload.
That makes sense.
Well, not really, but I'll take your word for it.
We're somewhat relieved
to know you feel that way.
In truth, there are very few people
who can actually execute this plan.
So what's up with this restaurant anyway?!
I've never been here before,
but is this the land of huge busts?!
Wait a minute!
If basically everyone who eats here is like that,
maybe the food here makes your boobs bigger!
Kamijou Touma
ANSWER
TRANSFER
VOICEMAIL
Wh-Why?! Why is he calling?!
I can't believe that dummy is finally calling me.
Hello.
Sorry to bother you, Misaka.
I need to sneak into a subway.
Do you happen to know how
to open electronic locks on shutters?
Sorry to bother you, Misaka.
I need to sneak into a sub—
I heard you fine, and was trying to ignore you!
Take a hint, you moron!
What in the world do you need
to get into a subway station for?
Where are you?
In London.
What?!
Do you even realize how much red tape
there is to get out of Academy City...
Wait, wasn't he in France not that long ago?
Well, I really am in London.
And I also really am standing in front
of a shutter and don't know what to do.
Tell me what the lock looks like.
Seeing how far we got without a hitch,
it seems all of London's security measures
really are concentrated on detecting magic.
It would appear so.
I understand how Index and I get by,
since we don't use magic,
but you're a princess of Britain.
I am aware that I should undergo that
education as a member of the Royal Family,
but when it comes to magic,
I've had a strong aversion to acquiring
knowledge and techniques that could cause harm.
I'm sorry.
It's fine. You just need to open the barrier
that only a member of the Royal Family can control.
I shall do my best.
With the aid of Index, even an unskilled
mage such as myself should manage.
W-We're counting on you.
Touma, this place has markings made with magic.
They're probably here to show the way
to sorcerers who come to service the mystic artifact.
What?!
Touma!
Touma, get back!
That's a mystic artifact
fashioned after Mokkerkalfe.
It's a constructed giant from Norse mythology.
Shit! Did that work?!
You've got to be kidding me.
Oh, shit! I can't move.
Touma!
To my elder sisters, this trap would probably
seem like an insignificant child's toy.
But even with my meager combat ability...
...if someone is trying to hurt
those who stood up for me...
...I shall fight!
I shall fight right until the last moment!
CAO! MARATTR!
Motion Adjust: Right Arm To The Right!
Change Attribute: Orientation!
Obey the command of one of the true blood!
Open the gate immediately!
Sorry.
And thank you, Villian.
You can leave the rest to me.
I'll get it this time!
It's over.
Thank goodness, I got through!
Itsuwa, is that you?
The plan worked!
After Villian and Index opened the magic barrier,
we managed to access the rail car's engine.
So please,
move away from there as soon as possible.
I managed to suppress it, but just barely.
P-Princess Carissa!
I'm fine.
That was an attack from Coven Compass.
Retrieve the special railway car and restore its seal.
Yes, Your Highness!
It seems to have gone well.
Curtana is now weakened.
Once the anti-coup-d'état forces we summoned
have gathered, we can storm Buckingham Palace.
When we bring down Carissa,
the coup should fall apart.
It's the grand finale.
You know what that means?
What?
H-Hey, you ate it, didn't you!
That was my meatball!
No, I didn't.
This is not the time to just have a light salad!
Everyone, please think of what's ahead of us—
Seconds!
I demand seconds and
I won't take no for an answer!
The proper thing to do before a battle is,
of course, to have a hearty meal.
Aren't you going to eat anything?
I'm just a bit dazed
by everyone's intensity about this.
Geez! I'll take over, go talk to him already!
No... Um... I'm fine, thanks.
I'm all ragged and sweaty after all the fighting.
I can't go looking like this.
That's why I've prepared
Operation Cinderella for you!
Ta-da!
The pre-sale roadshow!
The revealing Great Spirit maid costume!
T-Tatemiya-san!
Why do you have that ultimate weapon?!
By the way, I'm also taking proper care
of the Priestess's precious bridal attire.
Wh-Why are you doing that?!
I don't need that thing!
You don't need it?
Could there be a Hyper Fallen Angel
Super Sexy Maid costume coming?
Y-You don't spare any effort.
That's not what I meant!
Sister Agnese, the Far-East sect
seems to be up to something
involving squandering excessively large breasts.
Who in our camp would be most
effective to enact countermeasures?
Don't even think about it!
I'm never doing that!
What?
I thought it would look good on you,
so I brought it along with the pedestal.
I don't want either!
Gothic isn't that simple!
I see, that leaves me no choice
but to wear it myself, since I brought it.
Wait, you fool! Stop!
Curtana Original got overloaded.
Was that your doing?
No, it was probably the work
of this country's magic specialists.
I see.
It's caused the Knights to nearly fall apart as an organization.
Still, if you were to return,
the matter should be settled.
Are you having second thoughts?
Let me give you a warning,
since you're heading to your death.
In the bout we just had,
I could only control one pattern at a time.
That was the cause of my defeat.
But Second Princess Carissa
and Curtana Original control them all.
Her deadly strike cannot be dodged,
nor blocked, nor prevented by a counter-attack.
You need to be truly prepared for that
if you really plan to defeat her.
Acting Pope!
Coven Compass has reached
the designated coordinates.
The time has finally come!
Let's go.
Yeah.
Oh, my. It looks like we're a bit too late.
Are they leaving me behind? Damn it!
Even though I somehow ran into my
scheming daughter I didn't really want to see.
You don't have to call me "scheming"!
I just took the most rational
and level-headed course of action,
preparing for the eventuality of Carissa
unlocking the full potential of Curtana Original.
That's the definition of "scheming"!
Can you do it, horse?
I have to get back to London as soon as possible.
Tell me, is the banner in the
British Museum prepared?
It's a coin toss, I'd say.
Few people would notice that there is a mystic
artifact among the items on display in the museum.
As long as Charles Conder is doing his job well,
we can probably use it.
Good grief.
It might be for the future of the Kingdom,
but those fools are running
straight into the decisive battle
without any trump cards,
relying only on their own willpower.
Your face betrays that you're
pleased with that, though,
Mother.
Next Time
Are humans powerless before
this overwhelming power?
No, they're not!
Tonight, everyone fights for Britain!
Next time: "The Heroes".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.