A Certain Magical Index
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
JSOIDJBSJDBAD
NKDNF
OSKDKSNASDKND
JBSJDBJAKSNDA
NKDNFSNDKANDASKDN
KSNKDNAKD
ASVJ
JKXNAS
SNFK
BNSDIBF
YVSUAD
KSBD
Carrying a ticking time bomb
The Earth keeps on turning, so hurry up!
No one can pretend it's not their business anymore
Suddenly common sense is out the door
Opposing fates fail to reach each other
Drenched in the rain of resentment
But why? Fear and doubt keep building up heavy in my heart
My racing heart is flooded with ambition
Ready!
Everyone that's drawn to this place
Has gone beyond the meaning and color of desire
My heart wants to stay strong
I feel it deep inside me
With all my soul, this one thing
Dive into a heart
Dark Matter
Geez!
Why won't you let me get out
when I'm telling you I want to get out here,
says Misaka as Misaka tries objecting
profusely with her hands on her hips.
I have already received the fare to the destination.
It would be inappropriate to—
Misaka uses this opportunity to enact her escape!
M-Miss!
Excuse me, is everything okay?
Um, what was her name again?
Frizzy!
Hey! Misaka's identifier is Last Order,
says Misaka as Misaka...
A lost child?
I think he's that way,
says Misaka as Misaka
expresses her estimation of facts.
It's like something's clicking in my head,
says Misaka as Misaka provides
supplementary sensory information.
Um, so who's this lost child?
Can't get me any closer?
Fine. Now get lost.
So there're still a few kilometers
to go until the satellite antennas.
Look who's here.
This is your weakness.
You can't use your ability
if you can't get to your switch.
Are you from BLOCK?
No.
I'm with MEMBER.
I'd hate to lose a Level 5.
Someone from GROUP, huh?
Or ITEM?
I'm with MEMBER.
Kakine Teitoku and Accelerator.
Two Level 5s at the same time.
Is MEMBER the best, or what?
So you're a teleporter who
can only go behind people.
That's some shitty ability.
Proper teleportation is beyond you,
so you can't even use it without the help of
someone else's positional information.
Says the dude who can't do
anything without his electrodes.
Hey, you two! What's going on?
You're lacking.
Lacking in the aesthetics of evil.
My ability has precision
far beyond the sights of a gun.
No matter where you run to,
my next move will pulverize you.
Now run, swine!
And burn this terror into your memory.
It's a lesson in the beauty of evil.
This is what a real top-grade
villain is like, you shithead.
I call this little invention of mine Mimosa.
They're minuscule reflective alloy particles
that respond to a certain frequency.
Controlling them allows me
to tear through concrete,
or, say, pluck off a human body's cells one by one.
I felt despair for art in
the winter when I was twelve.
I had been fascinated with European architecture.
But it was difficult for a child's mind to grasp
the scale needed to create such works of art.
And so numerical formulas caught my fancy.
They were so efficient and parsimonious.
Their beauty was like poetry...
Time for another moment of despair.
D-Damn it!
What's wrong?
They got the professor and Saraku!
And I'm locked in!
What do I do?!
I have my own enemy to pursue.
I have no time to wipe your ass.
Wait! Please!
What the hell?!
Come on! Let me out!
Someone help!
All right.
If I just destroy that computer, my job will be done.
There's movement in District 23.
Several Anti-Skill members
who were there got taken down.
Whoever's there seems to be headed
towards the ground-based antenna.
What do we do?
We pray for their success.
We got their motive wrong.
They don't want to take control
of the laser weapon on Altair II.
They want to obstruct Academy City's
surveillance abilities.
Let's go.
The 5,000 mercenaries outside the city walls
are waiting for the signal to move in.
The security measures are quite rigorous.
Can't we just force our way through?
No, if they detect anything,
unmanned attack choppers will be here in no time.
They're the newest Six Wings model.
It won't be pleasant if they find us.
The guard drones will be
rotating out in ten minutes.
Now that they don't have aerial surveillance,
that leaves a window for us.
What's the matter, Yamate?
Anything bothering you?
5,000 mercenaries.
Where exactly do they plan to attack with them?
I can't afford to wait any longer.
What happened?
Yamate!
Shit!
Scatter!
We should pick up the mercenaries and withdraw!
We brought in 5,000 and it still wasn't enough!
So they couldn't quite stop all of them.
Venus is at an optimal angle for my obsidian knife.
Accelerator!
You just let them stroll in.
You really are completely useless.
Well, I did use my Spear of Tlahuizcalpantecuhtli
to reduce the number of intruders
to about a hundred.
Drive this into your thick skull:
A Certain Magical Index
a miss is as good as a mile.
We can't cancel the operation now.
All right, I have a question for you.
Where are BLOCK going?
The Reformatory in District 10.
Why would you raid that?!
Our target is Move Point.
We got info that friends of the person
with that ability are in there.
We want them as bargaining chips
to negotiate with Move Point.
You want someone to get you
into the Windowless Building.
Yes.
BLOCK found out that Move Point
is the guide to the Building.
We want to know where supplies are
being brought into the Building from,
so we can blow it up with
a Synchronous Multilayer Bomb.
Oh, is that it?
Do you know who's standing in front of you?
No way!
Let's go. We have work to do.
This is the only detention facility
for espers in the world.
It's packed full of AIM jammers.
Basically, we can't use abilities inside.
It's not that we can't, but if we do,
we can easily lose control of them.
So we should go easy on the abilities if possible.
I see.
That's why this place was weirdly quiet.
They've all killed themselves
with their own weapons.
Found you.
If you're here, that means
you're with BLOCK too, huh?
No, I'm with MEMBER.
Though I was just using them.
Etzali!
I came here to find you!
This is Xochitl.
She's an Aztec sorceress from
the organization I was in before.
A sorceress?
You traitor!
I sacrificed everything to come
here and take you out!
I'll handle this.
You three go on ahead.
We're wasting time. BLOCK are already inside.
You two go on ahead.
I can't move quickly,
but I can keep these goons occupied.
Tsuchimikado.
You're going to support Musujime.
Let's go.
Won't the shockwave from the blast get us too?
Don't worry,
I'm arranging it so the shockwave
only goes towards the inside.
There are 38 of them.
We can afford to lose one or two.
That's not what I signed up for!
What? You getting emotional over these brats?
Damn those useless goons.
Hold on.
You barged in so I couldn't
finish tuning the explosives.
I can't guarantee any of the brats inside will survive.
Don't touch the detonator.
You're Musujime Awaki,
also known as Move Point, right?
That saves us some time.
Say, GROUP,
what did the experience
of the 0930 Incident teach you?
What are you saying?
I thought that this entire world
was ruled by Aleister,
but there really is a way to escape his grasp,
and there are places he can't reach.
Using people as stepping stones to get
to a new world is nothing to brag about.
Striving to get to a better place,
to a paradise, is what all mankind—
Enough!
Don't move!
What are you up to?
I also have my reasons to kill Aleister.
However, I'm not using hostages!
I'll just beat the information out of you directly!
A pro doesn't need eccentric abilities or tricks.
All you need is to combine basic tactics
in the best way to defeat your enemy.
Etzali, what have you been doing all this time?
She controlled the enemies' weapons,
turning their destructive power back at them,
killing them all without getting her hands dirty.
It must be some kind of suicide spell.
You dropped something.
Aren't you going to pick it back up?
How? You're not supposed to know such spells.
And you made it to a position where
you wouldn't have to do any dirty work.
What happened to you?
What's going on in that organization?
A macuahuitl, huh?
Such a weapon doesn't suit you.
And what you're doing now suits you?
You left the organization, hid your face,
and now you're just indulging in peace and quiet here!
Shit!
You're dead!
You tricked me.
A sword of the Aztecs, who had no
technology to shape metal into weapons,
isn't too sharp.
So if you're prepared to get cut
to the bone, you can block it.
I told you already, weapons don't suit you.
I don't wish to kill you.
Please just go away.
Feel like telling me how to get
into the Windowless Building yet?
Why are you so hellbent on killing Aleister?
I experienced something of a tragedy in this city.
I want to ask Aleister if he's involved with that.
That's all.
I used to be obsessed with that "truth" thing, too.
But chasing that doesn't help
one regain their peace of mind.
True.
So what are you going to do?
Because of my mental trauma,
I can't teleport myself.
I can't shoot or fight hand-to-hand either.
Yes, it's because I think that way
that I can never protect anyone!
You intend to use it?
Yes.
I'm sorry, but I intend to go all out.
I'll overcome!
I'll overcome this frustrating scar,
and everything else!
You even held back.
Sorry, but this is the leadership
that's expected of me.
Xochitl! What in the world is that?
I tried to compensate for my lack
of power by using a grimoire,
and this is the result.
I hope this teaches you a lesson.
You read it!
No, I went further.
N-No way!
You merged with an original grimoire?
No, you became a part of it in order to gain power?
You must know that inevitably
leads to a rapid breakdown!
If I'm able to kill you as I'm being consumed,
the organization's goals will be fulfilled.
They were pretty cruel while I was still there,
but what in the world happened after I left?
I'm not going to let you die!
An original grimoire gives knowledge
to those who seek that knowledge.
If I take over the grimoire,
I should be able to tear it from her.
It's never been done.
And if I fail, I'll die.
I believed in you.
We really were right to trust you.
Thank you for coming for us.
You've done enough for us.
Now go.
Go.
Are you fine with this?
Yes.
It's for the best.
Sure took your time in there.
Let's head back, then.
Into the darkness.
Come on.
I have no business with you,
but you keep pestering me.
Maybe I need to do some spring cleaning.
Okay, I'll tell you everything.
Oh,
that's a pretty fancy hideout.
When I least expect it, you're gone
And loneliness hits me hard in the chest
In the night filled with signs I look up at the stars
I bite my lip and pray
Every time the dawn comes I run to you
You try to hide behind a smile that you're covered in wounds
But I notice, because I'm not a child
I'll protect you even if I have to make an enemy of the entire world
This strength comes from the light you've given me
I don't want to just wait for a miracle
I want to start a revolution that changes who the two of us are
And this is the night before it starts
Next Time
The strong survive.
White wings spit on normal principles
and mock common sense.
Next time: "Espers".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.