We've passed the assigned point!
Target is within range!
Commencing large-scale flash attack!
All witches evacuate the line of fire!
I repeat! Evacuate the line of fire!
Here we go!
Target: Buckingham Palace!
Fire!
That's some serious bombardment!
Are you sure there won't be any collateral damage?!
The palace is surrounded by a large park.
Even if the aim is a bit off, it should be fine.
More importantly, we need to be prepared
in case this attack fails to defeat Carissa.
And I'm heading straight into battle
with nothing but my amateur fist.
Pretty reckless, even for me.
Why do you fight?
Why dive into a deadly battlefield
and risk your life to fight for Britain,
a country you have no allegiance to?
No reason in particular.
If all the people getting caught up in this coup
were just disposable game enemies
created to get mowed down,
I would already be on my way
back to Academy City.
But they're not.
Everyone living their life has something precious
that they're desperately fighting to protect.
I can't just stand back and watch them die.
So you're a mercenary
of a different kind than William.
That must be material from Curtana Original's spell!
Grab on to something!
Shit!
Index!
Kanzaki! Itsuwa!
Shit! Where is everyone?!
A Certain Magical Index
The Heroes
Please stop this!
Oh,
I didn't expect you to be the first to come,
my foolish little sister.
But you can't kill me unless you
nock an arrow and pull the trigger.
Weapons have no power if you don't use them.
Let me show you how it's done!
Carissa!
Congratulations. That was a commendable move.
The final boss already?!
And we don't know how many
Knights are hiding nearby.
Don't worry, I don't have any
Knights waiting in ambush.
I had to make a bit of an example of them.
Don't tell me—you killed them?!
They were comrades who fought by your side!
You can't—
Spare me.
High status and abundant
taxpayer funds are rewarded to those
determined to work themselves
to the bone for the nation.
Being consumed for the sake of their country
is surely a Knight's most cherished desire.
And thanks to them,
we have rebuilt our strong union.
Unless the coup succeeds,
both the country and the other Knights
shall perish in terror!
The mobile assault fortresses, Gryphon Sky!
They're unmanned mystic artifacts,
but that makes them our best option
for coordinated combat operations.
I guess they're too powerful to use on
just one person. The AI doesn't know what to do.
You were supposed to have been cut in twain.
Second Princess Carissa!
Die!
I'm alive.
I finally came up with
a decent way to repay my debt to you.
Kanzaki!
I'm not alone.
Index, I request that you analyze
the spells related to Curtana.
You need to take control, or seal them, right?
I'll try.
You nobodies who couldn't even
arrive in time for the final battle
think you can suddenly be the stars of the show?
I have no intention of resolving the situation myself
because now I have friends that will watch my back!
If you don't come at me with everything you've got,
you'll perish!
They're moving so fast!
But if I can distract Carissa for just a moment...
How heroic of you.
But stay out of this!
Kamijou Touma!
I'm fine! Get her!
You all came!
God damn it!
You're making me spend more than I should!
It seems we need to rely on your right arm after all.
I'll give it a go, but I can't guarantee anything.
When Curtana severs the dimensions,
there is a small delay before the scrap material appears.
I conjecture that you could nullify the slash itself,
but you can't destroy the scrap material it produces.
So I just need to get as close as I can
after she slashes, before the scrap appears!
Isn't this a befitting position for you,
who can't even properly use magic, princess of virtue?
I can't afford to grovel any more!
I've made up my mind to stand
on my own two feet as a princess,
for myself and for the one who risked his life for me!
Hogwash!
What?!
A shot from the Coven Compass?!
Did they coordinate this?!
Damn your trickery!
This is the power of cooperation, my dear sister.
It won't even graze me with that trajectory.
BAO.
CD.
Begin adjustment to object! Curve downward!
Are you kidding?!
Not even a scratch after getting hit by that?!
I was planning to save this for after I'd lured
out Mother by having you wallow in despair.
Calling destroyer Wimbledon,
currently patrolling at Dover.
Fire a cruise missile with a Bunker Cluster warhead.
Target: Buckingham Palace!
Bunker Cluster?
Surely you know of it?
Everything within a 3-kilometer radius
will be blown to smithereens.
We won't allow it!
We'll intercept it in the air with a protective barrier.
If you can make it before a cruise
missile traveling at Mach 5 arrives.
That's rather careless of you.
You didn't think I'd expect this?!
Kanzaki!
Oh, my.
Any sorcerer in this country
should be aware of how dangerous
the sovereign is when wielding Curtana Original.
Hey, Missy, it played out just like you said.
This is definitely a burial site fit
for the ruler of an entire civilization.
I'm sending you the data.
I see.
That explains why she hasn't killed them yet.
My nimble and reckless little sister,
I've now uncovered your entire plan.
Heed my word! I am First Princess Riméa.
Her actions, insane as they may seem,
were all for the sake of Britain!
A Certain Magical Index
France and the Roman Catholic Church
are using the EU as their pawn,
and there's been pressure from
the Russian Orthodox Church.
The dignity of our nation is being violated.
In the face of that humiliation,
she resolved of her own will to wield Curtana Original
as a powerful weapon
against those external threats.
And at the same time, she also resolved to seal
that extremely powerful ultimate weapon for eternity,
so that it can never be used for malign purposes.
She's also resolved that after the battle is over,
she'll spend the rest of her life,
together with the destroyed
Curtana Original and the fragments of Second,
in the cave she has chosen as her tomb.
Calling destroyer Wimbledon.
Launch another Bunker Cluster.
She plans to become the tyrant
who used the heinous power of Curtana
to slaughter numerous
external and internal enemies,
thus taking all the blame for it upon herself.
If anyone has compassion for my sister,
if any knight wishes to save a lady,
I would ask them to take up their sword once more.
You think I've given up?
But what are you going to do?
The second Bunker Cluster is almost here.
Blow away these fools!
This is the true might of our military!
Reduce to zero!
You!
You can have my head
when this coup attempt is over,
but let us first prepare the way
to reach that outcome.
I hope that the Royal Family
can combine their strength again
to justly face France and the Roman Church.
Forgive me for leaving the fate of
our country and princesses in your hands.
It's fine.
I'll help you stop her.
Knight Leader?
Did my sister get to you with her sly speech?
It only strengthened my desire to save you, Your Highness.
It annoys me to do this, but I suppose
I'll have to use all of the Bunker Clusters.
My Thororm spell may be no match for Curtana,
but it can reduce Bunker Clusters
to zero without a hitch.
Do you plan to waste them despite that?
I have, of course, accounted for that.
24 missiles from Wimbledon,
26 from King Henry VII, 15 from Sherwood.
If I use an illusion to hide even one of them,
you can't defend against it,
because your spell requires your awareness.
Calling all destroyers standing by.
Fire all cruise missiles!
Wha—
An antenna?!
This should prevent you from
sending reckless orders to the military.
I see.
You just had to interfere.
Acqua!
Am I late?
Science is not my strong suit.
It took me quite a while to destroy
all of the military antennas in the area.
I never thought the day would come
when I would fight beside you once more.
Try not to get in my way.
Count on it.
Let's go!
Let's see how much we've managed
to improve in the past ten years!
Off with your head!
They're not the only ones you're fighting!
Lone Flash!
Incredible.
So you've finally overcome
the narrow notion of just dodging them.
Three Saint-level monsters are
actually rather irksome to deal with.
You shouldn't think that you can accomplish
anything just because you're slightly special.
The reason we can exhibit our power
is because we have others who support us.
You might be right.
But haven't you considered that you've
given yourself too much to defend?
The more of you there are, the more targets I have!
You can bring hundreds,
thousands even, and I won't budge an inch!
You finally show yourself, Mother!
You, who are the root of all our problems!
If you want to have your way,
you need to have a better plan than mine.
But since it's looking like yours is going
to lead to an inferior outcome, I came to stop you.
Nonsense!
Are you that unwilling to part with the throne?
No, I'm just appalled at your narrow-mindedness.
Daughter, if you really wish
to change this country, you need...
What are you planning to do?
...a revolution.
This is another one of the country-level
spells that only the Royal Family can use.
Union Jack, I order you!
Release all of the enormous power
gathered by the union of the four countries,
and redistribute it equally
among the citizens of Britain!
The power filling Curtana Original is disappearing!
I, Queen Regnant Elizard, am addressing all citizens!
I'm sure many of you have been hurt for no apparent
reason since the start of this coup attempt.
But you now have the power to fight back.
Tonight, and only tonight, each of you
has an equal opportunity to become a hero.
And knowing that, I want you to choose
who you fight for and with.
Decide for yourself and follow the justice,
valor, and courage you arrive at.
I hereby open the general
elections for national heroes!
Me...
A hero?
So we can fight too.
To Buckingham!
Head to Buckingham Palace!
Yes!
Everyone, this way!
Get a grip, Itsuwa.
Miss Tsushima?
Curtana!
Look around.
Queen Elizard used her secret weapon.
You can feel it, right?
The power distributed to every citizen.
Let's join them.
Do you think that's enough
to cause Curtana Original to falter?
But it's a 90-million-against-one tug of war.
If you lose concentration for even a moment,
that power will slip from your hands.
Incredible!
With so many protagonists,
Index, Kanzaki, Acqua, and I
are getting overshadowed!
What's the deal with this country?!
How can everyone be a protagonist?
She must know that.
And that's why she's prepared
to sacrifice herself for the country.
I'll protect her.
I'm going to pull her out
of this ridiculous vicious cycle!
CTOOCU.
Change trajectory: Orient object "Curtana" upward!
SAARTST.
Slow angular acceleration; reset torque, speed, and trajectory!
Acqua!
Is it over?
That was a rather flashy show, if I do say so myself.
If I may be so insolent to say,
it was too flashy, Your Majesty.
Was it?
I think the people will fail
to comprehend what really happened
and form their own explanations
and some fond memories.
But it's possible that some realize
it was the work of magic.
Well, if that happens, we can just admit the truth.
There is no law that says magic
should only be done in secret.
By the way, where is the boy
that's to receive the commendation?
This is awesome.
I didn't even imagine it would be that fun to watch.
Wh-Who are you?
Does the name "Fiamma of the Right" ring a bell?
You have my thanks.
Using the Catholic Church to make France
put pressure on Britain paid off really well.
I was able to obtain what I wanted.
What was so important that you
had to ignite a war just to steal it?!
I don't know if you weren't told,
or if you just don't recall,
but your role is over anyway.
Now die!
Now that's the unique right hand I was after.
Who the hell are you?!
Fiamma of the Right.
The de facto leader of God's Right Seat.
Let's leave it at this for today.
Wouldn't want you destroying
the mystic artifact I went to all this trouble for.
A mystic artifact?!
It's really awesome. Wanna see?
Index?!
Yes,
I am the grimoire library of Necessarius,
the 0th parish of the Church of England.
My official designation
is Index Librorum Prohibitorum.
Index!
What's this? Poor maintenance, perhaps?
What did you do to Index, you bastard?!
How should I know?
If you wish to know,
contact her customer service department.
Now then, I have to make a quick trip to Russia
to collect the material I need to call down an angel.
I'll let you take care of Index Librorum Prohibitorum
and that right hand until I'm done.
When I least expect it, you're gone
And loneliness hits me hard in the chest
In the night filled with signs I look up at the stars
I bite my lip and pray
Every time the dawn comes I run to you
You try to hide behind a smile that you're covered in wounds
But I notice, because I'm not a child
I'll protect you even if I have to make an enemy of the entire world
This strength comes from the light you've given me
I don't want to just wait for a miracle
I want to start a revolution that changes who the two of us are
And this is the night before it starts
The stolen mystic artifact was a safety device.
It was what allowed this girl,
who has memorized 103,000 grimoires,
to lead a normal life.
This is our fault.
We'll take care of
Index Librorum Prohibitorum here.
But she'll never be safe until Fiamma is defeated.
Russia, huh?
Stiyl! Is it all right to leave
Index with you for a while?
I'm gonna go punch that bastard Fiamma!
Next Time
A brief moment of peace?
There's no such thing.
What we have are empty shell casings,
screams of pain, and the smell of burnt gunpowder.
A new darkness rears its head.
Next time: "Spark Signal".
When science and magic collide,
a saga is born.