We're of opposite hearts
You and me
Yet we share this single feeling
How strange
I sometimes wish
You smiled when we met
Showed you're interested
You'd see nothing
But my angelic side
But before I knew
You were testing my heart
With strategies so mean and just not fair
Since you picked a fight
I simply can't back out
I will play this game with you
Come, now
The battle has begun
Throw me into disarray
And as a deciding blow
Whisper softly in my ear
The sweet words of love
We're of opposite hearts
You and me
But can love change what's between us?
Lost in this relationship
I can't let you catch me off-guard
When our eyes meet it's enough to
Make me all embarrassed and shy
I can't open my heart
You do it, please
Take the first step now