Welcome to Virtual Town.
I'm a horse.
A humanoid horse.
Neigh, an equine human.
Either way, I'm a talkative horse.
This virtual world is full of unique people like me.
You might find a talkative peanut,
some old dude pretending to be a cute girl,
a guy who's always blasting away with missiles,
a grandma, a gorilla, a tanuki ninja,
Hello Kitty, a strangled Hamtaro—
Oops, I'd better stop here,
before I get in all sorts of hot water.
Now, the girl you see running past is Mirai Akari.
Mirai Akari
She's a cheerful, sexy lady who
often pervs on those new to town.
Hooray for puberty!
This is Electronic Girl Siro.
Electronic Girl Siro
She is by no means a crazy,
psychopathic, combat AI dolphin,
but rather an extremely cute and wholesome idol.
You won't believe what I found!
The one walking strangely is
HimeHina's red half, Tanaka Hime.
Tanaka
Hime
A cackling girl who can't stop talking.
Super-dee-duper crab running!
Chasing after her, in the somewhat
provocative, midriff-exposing outfit,
Suzuki
Hina
is HimeHina's blue half, Suzuki Hina.
Hime! You're flashing everyone! Cover up!
Or they'll pull us off the air!
The one who just faceplanted is the
lethargic tomboy Nekomiya Hinata.
Nekomiya
Hinata
Her skill at shooter games is top-notch,
but her tank top droops low.
Ouch...
My video games are waiting for me!
Last is the class representative
with long, black hair, Tsukino Mito.
Mito
Tsukino
Though she tries to assert dominance
over everyone else in Virtual Town,
she is, alas, hopelessly weaksauce.
People, you mustn't run.
You have to walk properly,
with your toes pointing in, as I do.
Here, let me demonstrate.
Looks like fun things are in store
for the virtual world today.
Hey!
Okay, everyone, gather around!
Virtual Cyber Academy Dormitories
Mee-ting time!
We're holding a meeting!
Huh? A meeting?
What kind? A panty-flashing meeting?
Yeah, right, Tanaka!
Oh, I know!
It's a meeting for us to share in Akari's lusts!
Great idea!
Is it really?
It's true that I've received overwhelming
wholesome praise in the V world as
the most wholesome of the wholesome,
It's true that I've received overwhelming
wholesome praise in the V world as
the most wholesome of the wholesome,
but if interacting with an embodiment
of lust like Akari would allow—
me to reach new heights,
a love scene or two is a small price to pay.
True, I too have received overwhelming Comaneci
praise in the V world as the best Comaneci
poser to ever do the "Comaneci" pose,
True, I too have received overwhelming Comaneci
praise in the V world as the best Comaneci
poser to ever do the "Comaneci" pose,
but interacting with an embodiment
of lust like Akari is a small...
It's true that I've also received extreme killer
praise in the V world as the queen of killers—
Okay, enough!
Guys, I get it already, so calm down.
You see, I have an important
announcement to make.
Believe it or not, we're—
Is it about the anime?
Oh, of course.
Akari, you're lagging way behind.
We're already rolling. See the camera over there?
Hello! Can you see us?
Hey, isn't it about time?
Oh my, already? Everyone, gather round!
Wait, hold on...
Okay, here we go.
One, two...
Virtual Friends Are Watching!
I want more, I want more, such a wonderful surprise
Hey who says, hey who says, I've had enough?
All I see is like a dream that goes on and on and on
Pittery pattery and away!
Ready, and!
Come on and clap, and play this melody
But how come? But how come?
Who needs a reason why?
To all the ha-ha-ha-ha-happy folks at home,
I blow one, I blow two naughty smooches to you
Hey, we can keep on keep on going, don't stop!
Dizzy tizzy waiting for my smashing debut
Splishing splashing showering with love raindrops
AI love AI love AI love
I want more, I want more, such a wonderful surprise
Hey who says, hey who says, I've had enough?
All I see is like a dream that goes on and on and on
And to you, and to you, how are you?
Here we go!
Ready, and!
AI AI AI
M-More more more
A-AI AI AI
V-V-V-V-Virtual Friends Are... Watching!
It is a time of galactic war in the virtual world.
Who will conquer all the V nations
and unite the galaxy?
Why, us, the Game Club!
Shut up, Harutrash! I'll turn you into space debris!
You want me to land a kill on you, Pinky?
Come on, you two. Don't fight.
President, are we really going to try
to conquer the galaxy like Haru says?
Yes! We need to raise our rating and
become top among all the V nations!
Wow, there's a rating system?
Kaede, I've come up with a plan!
Really? Tell us about it!
I call it "Game Club Titans Conquer the Galaxy"!
Game Club Titans
Conquer the Galaxy!
So your plan is for us to turn into titans
and beat everyone with brute force?
Not bad for you, Pinky.
Strength is everything.
With strength on our side, we can't lose!
How do we turn into titans?
Well, I discovered the other day
that if you bite your own finger
here in space, you'll turn into a titan!
What?! Could it be that simple?
Then without further ado...
Congratulations!
It worked! I grew larger!
I'll try it, too!
Congratulations!
Will it work for me, too?
I got big!
Congratulations!
Way to go, guys!
My turn, now!
Felicitations.
Perfect! Just like last time I tried.
It looks like we're ready to go.
Now that we're big, let's launch some invasions!
Thank you, and see you again.
What?! My body is...
Huh? Why did you all shrink?
What is this, mutiny?
That's odd. Seems like it's in our blood.
Maybe it's 'cause you're well-born?
I can't believe you'd leave me alone like this!
Kaede!
Felicitations.
Miria!
Pinky!
I don't want to be the only one like this!
Change me back!
Hold on, President!
Felicitations.
Impossible! She's annihilated us in only two strikes?!
P-President, please, calm down!
They're gone... and you're going with them, right?
No! Please, stop!
S-Stay away!
Happy New Year.
Everyone's gone...
The Game Club's quest for
galactic conquest is far from over!
The quest for galactic conquest continues...
Virtual Grandmother!
"Ryuugen Higo."
Today's Expression
Ryuugen Higo
It's a Japanese expression.
It means, "baseless rumors
that are carelessly spread".
Let me talk about the toilet paper crisis of 1973.
As a result of the oil crisis, the government
instituted a paper conservation initiative.
People took that to mean that paper would run out,
resulting in a mad rush to stock up on toilet paper.
As for myself, at the time...
I must have just turned 20.
It was not uncommon to find store bathrooms
or public restrooms devoid of toilet paper.
You can imagine the shock
of entering such a bathroom.
Some of us grew so desperate for toilet paper,
we were prepared to "pay per" wipe.
For toilet "paper", you see.
What? It's not like your virtual friends
are always watching or anything!
You're watching
Let's Go! Classroom
Man, why can't it be spring break already?
Winter break just ended!
Don't get ahead of yourself.
Yeah, but when one break ends,
you can't help but start looking forward to the next.
Exactly! I thought I'd gotten enough relaxation,
but I'm already thinking about the next break.
It's so hard to avoid lazing around during breaks.
But aren't you always lazing around?
Am not! I'm just practicing video games in my head.
I kept a proper, regular lifestyle during
winter break, so I'm the same as always.
You're watching
Let's Go! Classroom
A wholesome lifestyle?
Indeed.
Ahh, the sound of wholesomeness...
Such a role model! And runway model!
Wha—You think so?
That much should be normal.
You're watching
Let's Go! Classroom
What's going on?
What was that tremor?!
Not to mention, it feels hot!
Hey, look outside!
Isn't that a volcano?
It's so hot!
I can't stand the heat...
It's too much...
Why is there a volcano outside the classroom?
We'll die from this heat!
We have to get somewhere safe!
But where?
There's nothing but lava outside!
We'll die if we go out there!
What do we do?
Huh?
Wha?
Class rep?!
You realize what's going on, right?
What of it? Just another normal day.
No, no, no! This isn't even remotely normal!
That's a volcano!
So what if it's a volcano?
You're watching
Let's Go! Classroom
You see them all the time in movies!
So hot! Dying!
Just think of it as a sauna.
The volcano's erupting!
It's a volcano. Of course it will erupt.
I say, you're all overreacting.
Just act like it's any other day in the classroom.
Okay, just like any other day...
Hello!
Good morning!
Let's do our best today, like we always do!
As if!
It's so hot I could die!
Is that the best you can do, Akari?
H-Hey, isn't that lava coming toward us?
That's right, Siro.
The volcano erupted and spewed out lava,
so that's only to be expected.
I'll heat you up real good!
Oh no!
It's headed straight for us!
My K/D ratio!
Quiet! The volcano erupted,
spewing out lava, which is headed for us.
It's only natural that we'll die!
Er, wait. Naturally, we'll all die?
You're watching
Let's Go! Classroom
Th-That's no good!
I'm coming for you now!
To be continued
Grandmother Is Watching.
One, two. One, two. One, two...
Right. Right. Right.
Gorry, you're in high spirits today!
Right.
Good news?
Right!
Did you win the lottery?
Right...
Or your total came out to exactly
777 yen at the register?
Right...
I know!
Did you lose weight? You seem pretty light today.
I swore off bananas yesterday. I'm on a diet.
Gorry, you're what all girls dream to be!
Fuji!
Fuji Aoi Park
Aoi!
Right!
Ya gotta see this!
Ya gotta see this, Akari!
Akari, ya gotta see this!
Hi-yah!
What's wrong, Hime?
Miss Mirai, ya gotta see this!
What? What?
We got a letter from a "Takeru",
who's having trouble!
Here, give this a read!
Wha?
Hello, Akari.
Hello.
I was supposed to meet a friend the other day,
but overslept an hour,
which made that friend furious.
We haven't spoken at all since then.
What should I do?
What a hottie!
Well, you know, oversleeping
happens all the time, if you ask me.
That's true.
Maybe give the friend a box of snacks?
A box of snacks!
Overslept?
Bring a box of snacks!
Akari Advice
Overslept?
Bring a box of snacks!
Akari Advice
Overslept?
Bring a box of snacks!
Akari Advice
Overslept?
Bring a box of snacks!
Akari Advice
Overslept?
Bring a box of snacks!
Akari Advice
Overslept?
Bring a box of snacks!
Akari Advice
Buying forgiveness!
But the question is, what type of snacks?
Overslept?
Bring a box of snacks!
Akari Advice
Huh?
How about a rice bag?
Oh, so one bagful.
One bagful!
Well, Takeru should probably
bring at least two bags.
That's true!
But Takeru is trying to patch things over, right?
Oh yeah, that's right.
What can he do?
Yes, that's right.
Hey, Miss Mirai?
Miss Mirai!
Yami
Hikari
Come now, the answer is clear!
Yami
Hikari
He's the one at fault, so he should apologize!
Yeah, whatever.
Hikari, why do you care so much?
Oh, shush! Stay out of this!
Just forget the guy.
We can't!
Don't put ideas like that into her head!
Pout!
Hey, nothing a one-night-stand can't fix.
You shouldn't give yourself away that easily!
Well, I'll leave the rest to Akari.
Akari, you can do it!
Hello?
Miss Mirai!
Sorry, I was lost in thought.
Welcome back.
Listen up, Takeru!
To get your friend back on your side...
Is this it?
The backside talk?
To make up for last time,
promise to meet up one more time,
and oversleep an hour again!
What a twist!
Then, as your friend turns to leave in anger,
you go in for the embrace!
"I'm sorry. It's just, seeing you standing there,
your beauty froze me in place, just like last time."
Or something?
Gosh, that's so romantic!
Are you sure? Maybe it's too direct?
Virtual Red Light District
And then they'll get into the mood
and start XXX and △△△ing,
and disappear off into the red light district at night!
Virtual Red Light District
How shameless.
My, but isn't it, Tanaka?
Although, it just says "friend",
so it might be a guy friend.
Virtual Red Light District
Ah...
W-Well, that's all I came for. Later!
Sure, come again. Take care.
I'll prepare some tea next time!
Ya gotta see this,
Akari!
Hinata's Heading to
School
Almost won my chicken dinner!
Hinata's Heading to
School
Almost won my chicken dinner!
This is bad.
It's the endgame,
with only four survivors, including me.
Based on the sound of gunfire,
there's someone at both 1 and 11 o'clock.
In the middle is a field with no cover.
I can't pin down the last player...
Are they in this house?
If I move into the field now,
I'll be shot at from three directions.
The End.
What do I do?
How do I taste that sweet, sweet chicken dinner?
Think!
Hinata!
Chicken dinner!
What's wrong?
O-Oh, no...
You were glaring.
Uh, well... chicken!
I'm in the mood for some chicken...
R-Really?
Well, who doesn't love chicken?
See you!
See you...
I guess I'll have some chicken for lunch...
Hinata's Heading to
School
Virtual Friends Are Watching!
I'll blow you to smithereens!
La-di-da! La-di-da!
Oh! Tsukino Mito! Have a seat!
I've had it up to here!
Barkeep, give me a shot of chocolate trivia.
Coming right up!
Trivia, go!
Trivia
Oh, chocolate.
It's said the first European
to discover chocolate was Columbus.
But this "chocolate" was an unpleasant-tasting
drink, which didn't interest Columbus.
Also, chocolate has a number of effects.
There was a woman who lived to be 122
who was a huge chocolate lover,
and ate around 900 grams a week.
By the way, if you eat chocolate and gum together,
the fat in the cocoa butter will melt the gum,
so I'd advise against it.
Wow, really?
I learn so much from your trivia.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Tsurumaki Kazuya
Pen Name
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Tsurumaki Kazuya
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Tsurumaki Kazuya
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Watching
Tsurumaki Kazuya
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Tsurumaki Kazuya
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
I'm Mikurira Rara.
My favorite foods are prosciutto and strawberries,
and I'm good at vaulting box exercises and singing.
It's nice to meet you all!
Tsurumaki Kazuya
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Class Rep,
It's 3 O'Clock.
Now, who could be visiting today?
Class Rep,
It's 3 O'Clock.
Oh!
You must be Kenmochi Toga.
That'd be Toya.
Oh, I'm sorry, they look similar written down.
Class rep, what do you want, locking me up in here?
Yes?
Quiet, Kenmochi.
Let's get right to it.
The Ultimate Would-You-Rather
Committee is in session.
You'd better pick correctly, if you can.
Do I have any say?
Today's topic is...
AGENDA
What
What incident would you choose as a streamer?
AGENDA
What
incident
AGENDA
What
incident
AGENDA
What
incident
AGENDA
What
incident
would
What
incident
would
What
incident
would
you
incident
would
you
incident
would
you
choose
incident
would
you
choose
incident
would
you
choose
would
you
choose
would
you
choose
would
you
choose
would
you
choose
as
you
choose
as
you
choose
as
a
streamer
as
a
streamer
as
a
streamer
?
A: Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
The game you were streaming turns into gay porn.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
The game you were streaming turns into gay porn.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
The game you were streaming turns into gay porn.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
The game you were streaming turns into gay porn.
B: The game you were
streaming turns into gay porn.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
The game you were streaming turns into gay porn.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
The game you were streaming turns into gay porn.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
The game you were streaming turns into gay porn.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
The game you were streaming turns into gay porn.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
The game you were streaming turns into gay porn.
AGENDA
What
incident
would
you
choose
as a
streamer
?
Your drunk mother barges in during a stream.
The game you were streaming turns into gay porn.
Didn't B actually happen to you?
Exactly. What I thought was a standard typing
game suddenly cut to this crazy gay sex scene.
With that in mind,
which do you think is more tolerable?
Good question.
Probably A: My drunk mother
barging in during a stream.
That's your choice?
It was not uncommon on Niconico
streams back in the day.
That's right.
Yeah, and it sometimes becomes
the highlight of the stream.
Sometimes, it even goes viral.
Exactly.
You don't often end up getting banned
from your mother barging in.
That's true, and like...
For the gay porn, if it gets explicit,
you run the risk of getting banned.
That's right.
In what situation could
your mother get you banned?
I guess, if she's so drunk
she starts taking off her clothes.
There are no winners in that scenario.
That's the 3 o'clock bell,
so I'll present the correct answer.
The answer is B: The game you
were streaming turns into gay porn.
Answer
The game you were streaming turns into gay porn.
Did my opinion even matter here?
Quiet! I went viral with this!
How are you supposed to stream
if you're afraid of bans?
Class Rep,
It's 3 O'Clock.
Virtual Friends Are Watching.
No! Horses don't need to watch!
I won't stop!
Virtual Friends Are Watching.
Hello, I'm Ootori Kohaku, 17 years old.
People call me Unity-chan.
As for why I'm called Unity-chan, I'm...
Stay away!
No, not a bamboo spear! No!
Huh?
UNITY-CHAN LIKES TO ROLL AROUND
I'm live?
Kerin Slayer.
Kerin Slayer
utysdjkcn
Hey, Hime.
Will we really find a dark elf in a cave like this?
Villager A said he saw one coming out of this cave.
Did you ask Villager B?
B kept walking into a wall, so I left him alone.
If one is lurking so close to town,
the villagers will be in danger.
We better take care of it.
Hime, wait!
Over there!
It's a Keblin!
Idiot! He noticed us!
Oh, no! What have I done?
Due to production difficulties, this segment
will be presented as stills.
Please enjoy the full animation next week.
Crap, this is bad!
Nin-thingy!
Hina, that's amazing! How did you do that?
Just pretend you know what you're doing!
Look, another one!
All right.
will be presented as storyboards.
Nin! Nin!
You suck at this!
The Keblin!
Let me go!
Don't try to steal Hime's panties!
What do you think you're doing?
Th-That voice!
I'll blow you to smithereens!
Look forward to next week!
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Ekakima Kuru
Pen Name
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Ekakima Kuru
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Ekakima Kuru
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Watching
Ekakima Kuru
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Ekakima Kuru
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Master, I'm your wife, Ekakima Kuru.
Do you want me to provide for you
with my fantastic drawing skills?
Just kidding.
Bye-bye.
Ekakima Kuru
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Please
Sister!
!
Please listen, Sister.
What troubles you, Mr. Horse?
I am here to confess my s—
Listen to this, Sister!
What is it?
When I did my laundry, the tissues I left in
one of my pockets got all over my clothes!
Sister, what should I do?
A dryer cycle, or a rinse and spin cycle with fabric softener,
can make the tissue easier to remove.
Oh, really?
You could also use a lint roller,
or, as a more unconventional method,
pat the clothes down with fruit netting.
Please give it a go.
I will! Thank you!
The grace of V be with you.
Sister!
Please
!
I'm honored.
Virtual Friends Are Watching.
Now, let's answer some viewer mail.
From "Smooth-Talking Slick".
Thank you for writing.
Thank you!
"Hello, everyone.
You're all pretty and very popular online,
but who's the most popular out of you six?
Please tell us."
So he says. What do you think?
Most popular?
Popular...
Our popularity matches the size
of our squishy melon buns!
Oh, so who would be number one, then?
Melon buns?
Wait, but...
We'd have to compare to know.
What?
Everyone, stand up front.
Line up, everyone.
No, don't look yet!
Look away, look away!
I'm a little girl, so have mercy.
Have fun, guys.
All right, it seems we have a winner.
The most popular one among us six is...
The Electronic Girl, Miss Siro.
Hang on! I smell some brown-nosing here!
Not at all!
This is the end of the show!
What's "brown-nosing"?
Well, that's all for this week!
Tune in again next week for...
Virtual Friends Are Watching!
You know we're not a doll
We alight in this human world for one night
to watch as our imperfect forms meet their destinies
Hear us cry to humankind with all our might
Our drive for life is why we chose these hollow bodies
Glowing with the light of life
Cry out and fight, shine in the night
From ashes arise, by love united
Us twisted humanoids
You know it's naughty virtual virtualize a life alive
Humanoid incarnation, celluloid imitation,
can't avoid obfuscation, reborn of illumination,
cardioid light creation, take the pain, become human
Inhuman simulacrums, sing their lives, sing this anthem
_
"Humanoid"
Her_
Here's_
Here's to_
Here's to th_
Here's to the A_
Here's to the Adva_
Here's to the Advance_
Here's to the Advancement_
Here's to the Advancement of_
Here's to the Advancement of Vi_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtu_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual _
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual Sub_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual Subcul_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual Subculture_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual Subculture
Hello!
I'm Mochi Hiyoko, a virtual YouTuber
who was reborn as a little girl.
Hiyoko
Mochi
You've all wanted to become a little girl
at some point in your lives, right?
Well, do I have the medicine for you!
This magical medicine will turn you
into a little girl the moment you take it!
Wouldn't being a little girl make you all happy?
May everyone become little girls!
Next time:
"The legendary medicine. Ooh... I feel hot."
Virtual friends will be watching next week, too.