Apparently, when a cat's tail is standing up,
it means they want attention.
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
Can I get some attention, too?
C'mere, you horse bastard!
Yes, yes!
Mito-Mito, what's wrong?
Virtual Cyber Academy Dormitories
You seem really tired.
I haven't been getting much sleep lately...
Tell me about it.
You really lose track of time when gaming.
Not quite, Hinata.
Huh?
I was practicing for something.
Practicing?
For what? Tell us!
Well, that would be...
My pose for when we introduce the show!
Huh? What do you mean?
So what pose did you come up with?
Let me show you.
Ta-dah!
What kind of pose is that supposed to be?
That's awesome! Let's go with that!
Very well!
Now, let's strike it together!
Ready, and!
Virtual Friends Are Watching!
I want more, I want more, such a wonderful surprise
Hey who says, hey who says, I've had enough?
All I see is like a dream that goes on and on and on
Pittery pattery and away!
Ready, and!
Come on and clap, and play this melody
But how come? But how come?
Who needs a reason why?
To all the ha-ha-ha-ha-happy folks at home,
I blow one, I blow two naughty smooches to you
Hey, we can keep on keep on going, don't stop!
Dizzy tizzy waiting for my smashing debut
Splishing splashing showering with love raindrops
AI love AI love AI love
I want more, I want more, such a wonderful surprise
Hey who says, hey who says, I've had enough?
All I see is like a dream that goes on and on and on
And to you, and to you, how are you?
Here we go!
Ready, and!
AI AI AI
M-More more more
A-AI AI AI
Virtual Friends Are Watching.
Haru, no more making funny medicines for you.
R-Right. My apologies.
Did something happen?
Uh, well...
Everyone, gather round.
We have to start making progress
on this galactic conquest thing.
Anyone have any good ideas?
So, about that...
I created this incredible remote
by pure chance while repairing the ship.
What kind of remote?
A remote that lets you stop time
for anyone you use it on!
A remote that lets you stop time for anyone you use it on
What?!
Of all the powers one can wield,
time manipulation may well be the greatest!
Well done, Ryo!
Harutrash froze! Yay!
Wow! With this, we can invade deep into
enemy territory while they're all statues!
Let me try it out! I want to mess with Harutrash!
Miria, be quiet.
What? Ryo?
Ryo?
What's gotten into you?
It's been bothering me for a while.
Everyone in this club just
wants to do their own thing!
I'm the only one here who's putting
in effort for our galactic conquest.
Ryo, calm down!
You understand, right, President?
Of course!
So please, calm down!
Now, just unfreeze Miria and Haruto.
Okay, Ryo?
What makes you say that?
Are you uncomfortable being alone with me?
Ryo, no!
Allow me to show you
how the world will be within our grasp
with the power of this remote!
No!
Now, this is my world!
I'm the master of time!
What? Can you see me?
I said, can you see me?!
Ora!
To think Haru would dare step
into my world of stopped time...
Good grief...
I've got the remote! Ora!
Wryyyy!
Now I just need to free the rest...
Pinky!
President!
I'll save you now!
There!
Ah.
The quest for galactic conquest continues...
The Game Club's quest for
galactic conquest is far from over!
Virtual Grandmother!
Senpen Banka.
Today's Expression
Senpen Banka
It's a Japanese expression.
It refers to how various things
can change in various ways.
One such change in recent years
is the appearance of convenience stores.
The first convenience store was opened in 1974,
in Tokyo's Toyosu.
The first thing I bought from
a convenience store was a cup noodle.
Oh, that was an eye-opener.
It tasted so good the first time I tried it.
I'll never forget it.
Back in the day, there was an image of being
cool associated with eating standing up,
so we'd all be standing around Ginza
or what-have-you, eating cup ramen.
Or as we'd call it, eating nup coodles (cup noodles)
in Gowntown Dinza (Downtown Ginza).
Much like crook and nanny (nook and cranny).
Nup coodles (cup noodles),
chilled grease (grilled cheese),
Wave the sails (save the whales), a blushing crow (crushing blow).
Now then, see you wext neek (next week).
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Chaco
Pen Name
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Chaco
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
My name is Chaco!
Virtual
Watching
Chaco
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Friends
are
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Chaco
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Chaco
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
I love chocolate, hence Chaco.
I'll do my best to become
famous like the other VTubers!
Chaco
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Well, this is what
Virtual Friends Are Watching is like...
Virtual Friends Are Watching.
Ah!
Aoi!
Well, if it ain't Gorry!
Sorry if I surprised you.
That's quite the band of Gorries.
What are you up to?
Picking up girls.
Picking up girls? Like how?
Hey Aoi, let's go get banana shakes at Harajuku.
Denied.
Aoi, let's go get our banana
fortunes told at Harajuku.
Denied.
Aoi!
Let's go!
Follow me, boys.
Fuji!
Fuji Aoi Park
Aoi!
Right!
Ya gotta see this!
Ya gotta see this, Akari!
Akari, ya gotta see this!
What's up, Hime?
Miss Mirai, I tell ya, ya gotta see this!
llllllllllllllllllll
The girls' movements were so wild
that the cameraman could not keep up
llllllllllllllllllll
The girls' movements were so wild
that the cameraman could not keep up
llllllllllllllllllll
The girls' movements were so wild
that the cameraman could not keep up
llllllllllllllllllll
The girls' movements were so wild
that the cameraman could not keep up
llllllllllllllllllll
The girls' movements were so wild
that the cameraman could not keep up
llllllllllllllllllll
The girls' movements were so wild
that the cameraman could not keep up
llllllllllllllllllll
The girls' movements were so wild
that the cameraman could not keep up
llllllllllllllllllll
The girls' movements were so wild
that the cameraman could not keep up
llllllllllllllllllll
The girls' movements were so wild
that the cameraman could not keep up
llllllllllllllllllll
The girls' movements were so wild
that the cameraman could not keep up
What? What?
Huff-puff, huff-puff.
We got a letter from a "Mushroom Head",
who's having trouble!
Come on, quit the heavy breathing and read this!
Right, sorry.
Let's see...
"Hello, Akari."
Hello!
'Ello, 'ello.
I got hold of a ticket to my
favorite group's next concert,
but it conflicts with my baseball game.
If I don't attend the game,
who knows what my teammates will do to me!
Is there any peaceful resolution
that would still let me go to the concert?
Man, I'd really want to go.
Baseball game
concert
Problem:
conflicts with
I'd really want to go to the concert!
That's true...
But, you know, I'm sure he really cares
about his baseball team too.
Yeah, he's a good kid!
Ah, yeah, he's a good kid.
You ever had conflicting plans like that?
Oh, I have!
Go, go, go!
Me, me, me!
Livestreams from YouTubers or VTubers
that I wanted to watch conflicted.
Conflicted with my own.
Oh, at the same time as when you would stream?
Yeah, exactly!
I know that feeling!
I know? You're like, "But I wanna watch!"
Yeah, I mean sure,
you could just watch the stream archive,
but you wouldn't be able to chat!
Exactly!
That's true...
I want to watch it live!
So, what do you do then?
Well...
I watch the archive.
Good girl! So responsible, Tanaka!
Responsible.
Very responsible!
But, you know, Mushroom Head here
probably wants a good excuse
to skip the game and go to the concert.
That's true...
Hey, Miss Mirai?
Miss Mirai!
Yami
Hikari
"My long, hard bat—"
Not another word!
Nice interception.
Akari, you can do it!
Hello?
Hello, Miss Mirai?
Sorry about that.
Listen up, Mushroom Head!
This is just my suggestion, but...
What was that?
Did I hear a butt?
First, you ambush the group's
manager outside their office!
The manager?!
Yeah!
Then, you hit on the manager.
Wh-What if it's a guy?
You hit on him.
How very progressive.
Then, you get it on with the manager!
Get it on with the manager
I knew this would get lewd!
After that, you get it on
with the baseball team's coach!
Get it on with the baseball coach
We're in adult territory!
You then invite the group to the baseball
stadium to perform before the game!
Invite the group to hold the
concert at the baseball stadium
That would solve everything!
So instead of glow sticks,
everyone would be waving bats?
Exactly.
All right! I'm off to buy eight bats
to stick between my fingers!
You can hold bats with your fingers?
How strong are you?!
Buff AF!
Go, Tanaka!
Here I go!
Ya gotta see this,
Akari!
Hinata's Heading to
School
Oh?
Was this big vacant lot always here?
Now I'm itching to be queen of this playground.
This is bad.
This area has no cover or places to hide.
If I come here equipped with a Blaster,
its poor inking capabilities and mobility
would make it difficult to secure a foothold.
Maybe I can spam C'mon! to call for backup?
C'mon!
No, wait!
There are pipes here.
I can lure the enemy to those pipes,
let them think they're safe behind them,
then use the Blaster's splash damage to...
Boom.
I can do this!
Yeah! Booyah!
Booyah!
I guess it's worth practicing
the Blaster every so often.
Boom.
Boom!
I bet it's fun to blow things up!
Hinata's Heading to
School
Oh, you're all hopeless.
That's all right.
Virtual Friends Are Watching.
La-di-da! La-di-da!
Oh! Hime and Hina! Have a seat!
I've had it up to here!
Barkeep, give us a shot of rabbit trivia!
A shot, a shot!
Coming right up!
Trivia, go!
Trivia
Oh, rabbits.
"Rabbits"
We often associate rabbits with loneliness,
so many girls might say,
"I'm a rabbit, so I'll die without company."
Yeah!
It's true that rabbits, so quiet and solitary,
seem somewhat lonely.
However, rabbits themselves
actually hate living in groups
and love to be alone!
This misconception leads people
to keep multiple rabbits in one cage,
which will cause them stress, so be careful.
Yeah.
By the way,
the largest rabbit ever according
to Guinness World Records
was 1.32 meters from head to tail!
Wow, really?
We learn so much from your trivia.
Indeed, we do!
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Villager No. 2
Pen Name
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Villager No. 2
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Watching
Villager No. 2
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Friends
are
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Villager No. 2
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Villager No. 2
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
A place where your tastes are exposed to the world!
That's what this segment is.
Villager No. 2
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Class Rep,
It's 3 O'Clock.
Now, who might be visiting today?
Ah!
Hello, Class Rep!
Oh, if it isn't Mononobe Alice.
It's after school tea time with the class rep!
"A-After school tea time" is cutting it close, Alice.
Better not use it.
Okay!
Well, you're not wrong about "tea time".
For your sake, today's Ultimate
Would-You-Rather Committee,
will be a Would-You-Rather Tea Party!
Today's agenda is...
AGENDA
What
would
AGENDA
What
would
AGENDA
What
would
AGENDA
What
would
you
What
would
you
What would you rather drink at a tea party?
rather
you
drink
rather
at
drink
a
at
tea
a
party
tea
?
party
tea
?
party
A: Noni juice.
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
B: Senburi tea.
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
Senburi Tea
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
Senburi Tea
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
Senburi Tea
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
Senburi Tea
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
Senburi Tea
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
Senburi Tea
AGENDA
What
would
you
rather
drink
at
a
tea
party
?
Noni Juice
Senburi Tea
Senburi tea?
Yes.
Is that a Japanese tea?
I believe so.
Noni juice isn't a tea, but juice, right?
That's true.
I've drunk kale juice on a variety show before,
but it was surprisingly tasty.
That was supposed to be
your punishment for losing,
and you go and say "It's surprisingly tasty!"
like you wanted to kill the ratings!
You're supposed to go "eww!" to get a laugh!
You're right. Sorry.
Though your honesty is part of your appeal.
Thank you!
But I don't know much about noni juice.
Oh, I've actually tried noni juice before.
What, really?
It had this strong, tart taste to it...
So not exactly "good", then.
But they do say "good medicine tastes bitter."
It could be worth trying once, to—
It's already 3 o'clock,
so since we actually have some here,
why don't we drink some and decide?
I'm going for the noni juice.
Then I'll try B, the Japanese senburi tea!
Here we go. Ready, and...
This is...
This isn't too bad!
Hey! A good streamer... entertaining reactions...
Class Rep,
It's 3 O'Clock.
Virtual Friends Are Watching!
UNITY-CHAN LIKES TO ROLL AROUND
Unity-chan...
I'm honored.
Virtual Friends Are Watching.
Now, let's answer some viewer mail.
From "Smooth-Talking Slick"...
Huh?
If this show is on, that must mean...
today is... Wednesday!
Oh man, I completely forgot about my report.
Why? Why does this always happen?
Man...
Ouch.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Lilyel the Angel
Pen Name
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
Watching
Lilyel the Angel
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Heyalily, everyone.
Virtual
Watching
Lilyel the Angel
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Watching
Lilyel the Angel
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Virtual
Friends
are
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Lilyel the Angel
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
I'm Amatsuka Lilyel, an angel!
I'm training in the human realm
to become an archangel!
Lilyel the Angel
Pen Name
Send in your own virtual character!
See "Virtual Friends are Watching"
official home page for more info.
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Everybody's
Virtual
Friends
are
Watching
Previously, on Kerin Slayer
Previously, on Kerin Slayer:
Please wait!
Who are you?!
Kerin Slayer.
Kerin Slayer
utysdjkcn
Could that be you, Elu?
Elu?
You mean the God Elf beauty spoken
of in the legends of faraway lands?
Elu the Elf?
Wait, but her form is clearly all wrong!
She looks kinda hazy,
and her complexion is all gray!
There's a reason for this.
A reason?
Well, I may as well tell you at this point. Have a seat.
You too, keblins.
Keb-keb!
Here we go.
Elu is an elf girl that came
to Tokyo from another world.
Oh, I know that.
It says so on Nicopedia!
Yeah.
One day, something terrible happened.
Something terrible?
The forest was set on fire... Her home!
She met with a terrible fate.
Hina, did you know about it?
I just wanted to say that line.
Do continue.
Elu hurried back to the forest,
but it was already too late.
The forest was gone, as were her brethren.
That's awful...
Elu, wallowing in brev—
Elu, wallowing in bervemet—
Elu, wallowing in bereavement,
drew upon her own life force,
in order to try to revive the forest.
Oh, I know that spell!
Reternium Forest-Spirit-Headeus! Right?
No.
The forest was revived.
But she paid the price, and was turned to stone.
What a sad story...
That's right.
Even since I heard of that legend,
I've spent my time in this Gunma forest
researching a de-petrification spell.
We had no idea.
We're sorry.
But you're just in time.
I've just perfected the spell.
Now that's just lazy writing!
Forest, land, birds!
Forest!
Land!
Forest Land Bird
Lend your vitality to my magic circle,
and release Elu from her petrification!
Forest Land Bird
Elu Dorado!
Dorado
Elu
Elu!
Right.
Right!
Please
Sister!
!
She isn't coming today, is she?
Please listen, Sister.
What troubles you, Mr. Horse?
Forgive me, Sister, for I have s—
Listen to this, Sister!
What is it?
I made breakfast for a friend,
but the fried egg came out a complete mess!
I bet she hates me now!
That's nothing to worry about in the least.
What?
Cooking is about love and sincerity.
It's the thought that counts, not the appearance.
I'm so relieved.
And even if it turns out messy,
just put it between two slices of bread
for a delicious egg sandwich.
I see!
All right! I'll cook it right for sure tomorrow!
The grace of V be with you.
Never mind egg sandwiches, Sister...!
Please
Sister!
!
Virtual Friends Are Watching!
I want, want, want, want you to watch!
Now, let's answer some viewer mail.
From "The Pen is Mightier Virtual Division"!
Thank you for writing!
Let's see... "I've always loved hip-hop.
Do you ever listen to hip-hop?
If you don't mind,
I'd love to hear your freestyle rap!"
Today's Topic:
Group freestyle rap
So he says!
Today's Topic:
Group freestyle rap
What does he expect from us?!
What? No way!
I can't do that!
Sudden death...
If you're a real virtual YouTuber,
rapping should be a walk in the park, right?
Are you ready?
Today's Topic:
Group freestyle rap
Let's go!
Yeah, yeah!
Excuse me?
What's this supposed to be?
An earthquake!
What is this?
Heartbeats?
I'm beatboxing!
Beatboxing!
First up, Hina.
Freestyle Rap
MC:  Hina
Let's all drop a virtual rap!
This actually sounds legit!
Oh, don't stop the beat.
Theme
What about winter, who the hell are you?
Freestyle Rap
MC:  Hina
Winter, splinter, this is a printer!
Wow, wow, wow!
Yo, check it out! Your turn!
CYBER GIRL
Next up after Hina, I'm your girl!
Freestyle Rap
MC:  Siro
Listen to my sick beat!
It's winter in here, let's cheer!
Freestyle Rap
MC:  Hinata
Hey guys, hey girls,
walkin' on by there, stopping for no one.
Coincidence, independence.
Livin' in an age of ruins, payin' taxes.
Us youth were born into this analog
but we'll stick it out!
That's our spirit and demerit!
'Cause we're straight up,
growing up, turtle stepping up!
Turtle stepping up?
So cool!
Wow!
Your turn, your turn, your turn, your turn!
Okay!
Ponpoko girl Tanaka Hime here!
Freestyle Rap
MC:  Hime
Suddenly turtles, so I gotta go with that!
If a turtle crawls into a kotatsu,
its head and legs would stick out, like a turtle!
Yo, next up is Akari!
Speaking of turtles, they're sexy.
Freestyle Rap
MC:  Akari
Excuse me! Young lady!
Speaking of turtles, they're sexy.
And what's sexy? A turtle.
Stop! Get away from that topic, Akari!
Bleep! Bleep! Bleep!
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts so much!
But sexy things make me happy!
Can't spell fun without "sexy"!
Hey, Mito, say something sexy!
I have to do a sexy rap?!
Well, here I go.
Here I go!
Isthmus, happy, merry Christmas.
Freestyle Rap
MC:  Mito
I, uh... Speaking of snow, throwing snowballs!
Judo throws!
Lots of throwing!
Like how Akari just threw me under the bus!
This isn't a rap!
Commentary?
Rap! Rap!
Right, uhm...
I'm quite good at throwing snowballs,
so people call me... balmy... jewelry...
Uh, next is...
Uh, who hasn't rapped yet?
Did Hina do it yet?
Everyone's had a turn.
Mito, you were the last.
Everyone's gone? We're done?
Say something cool to finish!
F-Finish... Finish... swordfish, clownfish...
...angelfish. Which do you guys like?
Pick one!
This is what being a virtual YouTuber is like!
Yes, this is what being a virtual YouTuber is like.
That's it for this week!
Tune in again next week for...
Virtual Friends Are Watching!
Hey, Human...
Tell us the secret of life!
Humanoid incarnation, celluloid imitation,
can't avoid obfuscation, reborn of illumination,
cardioid light creation, take the pain, become human
Inhuman simulacrums, sing their lives, sing this anthem
Sorry for existing? Don't be absurd
The shadow floating in the mirror would like to say a word:
"Go on and struggle like the humans that you're not
You're neither nor, just imperfect reflections, a shadow of a thought"
The shadow looks back at you, right in the eye
But what is it that you're seeing? Could it be a lie?
"Come on and join us, come on let's get wild"
A new world opens, calling out: voices, an alluring smile
Come our last, there we will find
the future of all humankind
The shadow that arises when we close our eyes,
whose reflection does it bring to mind?
You know we're not a doll!
We alight in this human world for one night
to watch as our imperfect forms meet their destinies
Hear us cry to humankind with all our might
Our drive for life is why we chose to be somebody
Feel this life—It's humanoid
Claiming our right, crying and fighting back
Feel this pain—It's humanoid
To ashes returning, violet-blue burning out
Us twisted humanoids
You know it's naughty virtual virtualize a life alive
Humanoid incarnation, celluloid imitation,
can't avoid obfuscation, reborn of illumination,
cardioid light creation, take the pain, become human
Inhuman simulacrums, sing their lives, sing this anthem
_
"Humanoid"
Her_
Here's_
Here's to_
Here's to th_
Here's to the A_
Here's to the Adva_
Here's to the Advance_
Here's to the Advancement_
Here's to the Advancement of_
Here's to the Advancement of Vi_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtu_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual _
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual Sub_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual Subcul_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual Subculture_
Here's to the Advancement of Virtual Subculture
Mikoto
Rindou
I'm the queen of ogres, Rindou Mikoto.
Oh you dear, dear humans.
During Setsubun, you yell "Ogres out! Luck in!",
throwing beans at ogres,
but we ogres find it painful and sad, you know.
Besides, you mustn't waste food.
So I'll catch them all with my mouth.
Next time:
"Explode! The Ultimate Spell Smitheraga!"
Virtual friends will be watching next week, too.