I feel your heart beat on beyond the hands of time
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Believing that our bond will last until the end
The fervor to protect you growing day by day
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they'll never fade
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they’ll never fade
In the fragile, tender kindness of your bright eyes
There's a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
There’s a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
All the wonderful times that we spent side by side
Will live within my memories eternally
As my mind overflowed thinking of you
More than I could ever hope to explain
I turned the pain of the loss that I felt
To power I'd never known
To power I’d never known
And I keep rushing into the light
No one can stop this phase
Now that we're hand in hand
Now that we’re hand in hand
I etched a vow into the fabric of my mind
So I can keep you safe whatever perils come
I take your hand in my own and never let it go
The time that I have spent just standing by your side
Is all that I have ever wanted to recall
Until at last the day comes when I see you smile
Know that I’m never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
Know that I'm never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
Before you go cold, I'll have you give me
the details on the virus you gave that poor girl.
Oh. I had no idea.
I am in no state to carry her while teleporting.
I should call Uiharu to have her transported.
What's happening to Misaka?
Stop there.
Sogiita! You can move?
No big deal. All it takes to stop bleeding
and mend your bones is some guts.
You were gonna dash right into that, huh?
Something changed about her just now.
I figured that person who gave me hints
must've succeeded with their plan.
Really? It doesn't look any better to me.
She still can't seem to control the power.
I have to help.
I don't know how your right hand works,
but she's a whole different kind of trouble now.
Earlier she was like compressed energy,
but now that seems like something
incomprehensible, or otherworldly.
Leave this to me.
I might be able to suppress it
with some crazy suicide move.
No.
I told you, I know her.
I want to help her myself.
But, come on!
You're right about how
I probably can't do this alone.
I still don't understand what's going on,
so I can't say if this is the best option.
But I guess if it's not enough,
I'll have to fill the gap with some gutsy move!
Right?
I like you, really.
All right.
Give it a blast!
A path!
Hurry!
You stay put!
What is this? It's not my power.
I can guess, though.
If I let this thing go, it won't just be
Academy City that gets wiped off the planet.
I can't let that happen.
If I compress it enough to cover it with my body
and then blow it up, then maybe...
Him?!
Is he trying to stop this?
Wait! It's not an ability!
It's a mass of my desire to crush and erase
everything I hate about Academy City!
I have to—
No!
I know that Academy City
has a horrific dark side to it.
And that powerful people
beyond our reach are pulling the strings.
But even if you wiped
all that away with brute force,
I don't think you'd end up
with the world you wish for.
I'm sure you can think of a good number
of people who've tried to help you.
You should try changing the world
one step at a time, with them.
I'll help too, of course.
Wait, your arm! You need a hospital!
Huh?
It works just fine.
What are you even made of?
Hmm...
There we go.
That was quite the show!
I didn't expect the dragons!
That's the guts I like to see!
Let's spar someday.
Wait, what's that metallic stuff?
Was it there all along?
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Dragon Strike
She'll be all right, then?
I'd say so, yes.
Soon after she was taken here,
I received some data on the virus that infected her.
I was able to make an antivirus for it.
She'll take a few days to recover,
but she'll be good as new.
That's a relief.
Also,
I think one of my Tokiwadai friends
was taken here today as well.
Come in.
Misaka!
Your sister is okay? I'm so glad to hear.
Is something wrong?
I'm sorry!
I got you involved in this mess,
and you got hurt because of it.
I know words can't make up for it...
Please! I promised you I'd bring
your sister back, and look at me!
I feel pathetic.
Still,
you could've been hurt much worse...
That's true.
But even if such a fate befell me, I can safely say
I would feel no regret for my actions.
Kongou...
I am not so outstanding a person as to
thoughtlessly rush to the aid of just anyone.
I myself wanted to help you,
and so I would have no regrets.
Has anyone ever called you a "lighthouse"?
Huh?
"You are the lighthouse in someone's storm."
It means that without going out of your way,
you provide a guiding light for those around you.
I cannot say I understand it thoroughly, but I feel
that in seeing how you look after your friends,
I myself may have become
a better person, who cares more for others.
I'm really nothing so great...
Alas, that is not for you to decide.
Even if you fancied yourself great, it would mean
nothing if those around you disagreed.
This I can attest from experience.
That's not true!
It's not only me who looks up to you!
Don't forget Wannai and Awatsuki!
Wannai and Awatsuki? Why do you mention them?
It wasn't me who saved you...
I see...
They went so far for me...
What should I do, Misaka?
I should feel guilty for
involving them in such danger,
but instead I feel only honored!
Excuse me!
Visiting time will be over soon.
Oh, okay.
I'll come tomorrow too!
Thank you!
Misaka!
I am so glad to have enrolled at Tokiwadai!
Yeah.
Saten Ruiko
Wanna watch the fireworks?
Hey, Misaka!
Wanna go to that nice spot
to watch the fireworks again?
REPLY
Inbox
Uiharu and Shirai are coming,
so let's all go together!
Hey, Misaka! Wanna go to that nice spot
to watch the fireworks again?
Uiharu and Shirai are coming,
so let's all go together!
The Judgment girl's gone?
Handcuffs?
I could easily break free with my ability.
But why bother?
I'm not dead. That means the plan failed.
Guess I could just let the rats eat me here.
Shokuhou Misaki?
Misaka!
We're over here!
Darling!
Good to see you!
Look at this, Misaka!
Uiharu got some weird food again!
Strawberry tacos aren't weird!
At least call them "unique"!
Does the word make a difference?
Uiharu, will you just eat anything with strawberries?
Not anything!
Thanks so much...
Did you say something?
No, nothing.
Would you like a bite?
I'll pass.
Their suppressed memories of me were back again.
In their memories of today's events,
they went after a terrorist
targeting the Starlight Games.
Which isn't really that far from the truth anyway.
I also apparently have a cover story
for why I missed some events.
Shokuhou didn't do that for my sake,
but to keep the existence of the Exterior a secret.
Still, it's definitely thanks to her that
my "little sister" was cured of that virus.
I used to despise her—
No, I still do...
but if she has her own ideals and a sense of justice,
then maybe one day we can get along.
Just maybe.
By the way, Misaka,
are you feeling better now?
What do you mean?
Didn't you get a stomach bug
from some bad street food?
So you spent the whole day
locked in the restrooms...
You made violent threats to
Shokuhou's people on the way.
Huh? The bathroom?
Unless you're willing to fight
to the death here, get out of my way!
The whole school was talking about
how close a call it must have been.
Or maybe I'll kill her after all.
STARLIGHT
GAMES
DAY
III
I'm too dizzy to use my ability...
You win, Saten!
I'm unbeatable when a baseball bat's involved!
STARLIGHT
GAMES
DAY
V
So light!
STARLIGHT
GAMES
DAY
VII
The Gods of Wind and Thunder are back!
The Starlight Games are ending...
Not sure if they felt too long or too short.
In the end I couldn't participate at all.
If only I hadn't been injured the second day,
perhaps I could've joined my darling in the end...
You got hurt stopping a terrorist.
Plenty worth it, I'd say!
Consider it a badge of honor.
Indeed...
But when I think of that day,
I cannot help but feel I am forgetting something.
You too? I've felt the same, actually.
I'll go grab something to drink.
What would you like?
Oh?
Really?
Yeah. Call it an end-of-the-Games treat.
Coconut soda, then!
Habanero pineapple juice!
Watermelon tea please!
All right! I'll be right back!
Look at that! Folk dance!
Looks fun.
I feel like dancing too.
Though I have no one to dance with.
I feel your pain.
If only I weren't injured...
Oh!
Saten, was it?
Oh, Kamijou!
Hey!
Glad to see you.
I never got a chance to thank you for your help.
All... right?
Let me buy you a snack. Just nothing too expensive.
You really don't have to.
I'm back!
Wh-What?
What are you doing here?
And since when are you friends with Saten?
Yeah, she let me borrow her good-luck charm.
A good-luck charm? Huh?
I needed one for the scavenger hunt.
She let me borrow hers.
Scavenger hunt, I see...
Yeah! She totally saved my butt there.
Hey, Kamijou,
if you really want to treat me to something,
how about a dance around the bonfire?
Oh?
Huh?
What?
Is that it? I don't mind...
Great!
Oh, just go on ahead for now!
I'll follow you after I finish my drink.
R-Right...
Now then.
This must be the obstacle course getting to me!
Are you okay?
I think I sprained my knee!
It hurts!
Oh no! Darling, she's—
I can't move around much like this.
Misaka, would you dance in my stead?
Wh-Why me?! You should be the one dancing...
Don't worry! I never said he has to dance with me...
I-I can't! M-Maybe some other time!
You'll dance in my stead, right?!
Yes, ma'am...
Huh?
Misaka?
Wh-What's going on?
She's so stiff.
Don't get in the way.
What comes after raising the right hand? I forget...
You saved me again.
Oh, yeah.
I just helped a little in the end.
There were others helping you too.
Yeah.
I caused trouble for so many of my friends.
I...
I can't ignore how Academy City
treats espers like lab rats.
But I've also made so many friends
in the time I've been here.
And I treasure those friends more than anything.
So next time, it's my turn to protect them.
That's the least I can do for you after all this.
Sure.
That's what I wanted to say!
So... then that means you think
of our relationship as a treasure!
It sure sounded like you were including me in that.
I see, I see.
Huh?
I'm waiting for your snappy retort...
Time's up!
Ah, there she goes.
She lasted longer than expected.
Do you know, can you recall, about the promise that we made so long ago
After it's done, wonder if I will fade away into the dark
I know we've gone well past the point of no return to living righteously
But I still feel just a little freed
I need to reach through to the world that lies beyond that lingering memory
As I fall into a slumber
Flashing back to that day
Fighting to hold back the tears that I can't bear to shed
I'm doing whatever it takes just to fight through to my destiny
I could never just believe that fates are predecided
Yet, somehow, people still find their meaning
As they struggle through this story without a name
In this cruel world of suffering
I find myself just trying to bring back those days again
They can't come back
Next Time
Sucking up to scientists is the best way
to get ahead in Academy City.
Promise
But they ended up having me
babysit that girl. I didn't expect that.
Stop reading my thoughts out aloud!