You can't burn this all up,
nor break it all apart.
What will you do when you're faced
with such overwhelming mass?
That was really something.
First time I've had to both dodge and
push back with my full power at once.
So, what will I do against overwhelming mass?
Well...
Mass versus mass!
I had never found any meaning to my life
'Til you came along and opened up my eyes
Staring deep into the heart
of the being drifting on the wind that we think of as "you"
Burning these fleeting sentiments into ever-lasting memories
A Certain Scientific Railgun
As the city moves into yet another season's end
And the newest friend that I've made
brings a measure of happiness
On a certain evening, feeling not a bit of fear
I knew that I could trust
in the path my heart had told me that I should walk
Knowing that if I'm searching through
someone's counterfeit fantasies
I can never approach the light that I've been looking for
Still, I can only press ahead
This illusionary world
shines a light I somehow feel is equally lonely and soft
Searching through my beating heart
for a firmer cognizance of reality
Even knowing that the days
keep advancing seems like an illusion that's slipping away
Knowing this power deep within
gives me fervor like a searing flame
It's too hard! My iron-dust blades can't cut it!
An iron-dust puppet?
It can change shape and recover just like me.
But isn't it weakened by the small size of the grains?
I am stronger.
Now to finish before you can regenerate.
It's dangerous to touch now.
The iron dust it's made of builds up electric charge
from the friction as it swirls inside.
And if I use that built-up charge
to shoot a bullet of iron,
it can pierce even your armor.
I see. That is impressive power.
However,
I will simply regenerate again.
The grains are small enough to get inside of you.
As I thought, you can't control all these
individual sharp grains of iron dust.
I can feel them tearing you apart from the inside.
Now, one more shot!
What now?
A high-pressure gas tank?!
It's full, unlike the one I threw at you earlier.
What will happen if I drop this on a populated area?
Your power is impressive,
even at a range of kilometers.
But what about multiple at once?
Three?!
Are you trying to exhaust me?
It's been a while since the last time
we had dinner and a sleepover.
Is something wrong?
Didn't you hear that noise? Like some big fireworks.
Huh?
I don't know of any events like that today.
See?
You're right. I wonder what that is.
That couldn't be...
Well, I suppose it could...
But she still hasn't called.
You'll be the first to know if something happens.
Darling! I cannot stay put!
And here goes...
...the last one!
Wonderful control.
She aims carefully to make them explode upwards,
thus minimizing collateral damage below.
The lumps of iron dust she uses as projectiles
disperse throughout the sky above the city.
It's not even close to the thickness
of volcanic dust after an eruption,
but the dust lofted to the stratosphere
will rain down on any aircraft over a wide area.
No matter how ingeniously hidden,
the interference with the solar wind
will produce magnetic fluctuations,
and reveal where Cinderella is.
Found you!
I got your... gas... tanks?
What?!
It split up?
No...
Copies made of junk?
Where's the real one?
What was that I just saw?
Is it gone?
No...
Ouch!
Doppelganger!
I have an offer for you! Listen to me!
We need to talk!
Very well.
Come, then.
Wai—
I thought so. They're barely visible,
but there are strings in the air.
What are these?
Kuriba?!
D-Doppelganger!
If the Doppelganger is only after the airship,
then it just fought me to help find it, and the giant
monster thing was just a way to manipulate me?
What does it really want?
Either way, right now I need to save Kuriba!
Reach!
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Dispersion
Now, then.
I appreciate that you showed up willingly.
Let me hear this offer of yours.
Wait two months, please!
This is Indian poker.
It's a learning device I'm spreading
that utilizes dreams.
If my calculations are correct,
in about two months,
someone will find a way to erase a soul.
Once that happens—
You hope to safely extinguish my soul,
which would otherwise spill out uncontrolled
when my vessel is broken?
I thought I understood your thought patterns,
so I'm surprised you're moronic enough
to come up with such an irrational idea.
You come telling me you intend to erase me
and you hope I'll just say, "okay, fine"?
Even if you're just trying to buy time,
come up with something better.
You're wrong!
I'll have my soul erased!
If I died, that wouldn't just erase my soul,
but also destroy my body.
That would be inconvenient
if you want to become human.
Here I was wondering what you'd come up with.
You seriously expect me to trust you?
Even if someone comes up
with a way to erase a soul,
why should I believe you'd just give up your body?
Why should I believe you won't
turn that power against me?
Let me make this clear:
I have no interest in your body.
I just want to erase you, the one capable
of creating me, from this world.
If you're so willing to devote your body,
then go ahead and die right here and now.
I was going to burn you along
with the city, but this works too.
I live a borrowed life, even now.
Now that I know how to save
my mother, I have no regrets.
Kuriba!
I lost her!
How to catch her?
How to find her?
How long until she crashes?
Leave that to us.
North-north-east. Distance 1600. Altitude 2000.
Are you both ready?
All good!
The wind caught her.
Correct 4 degrees counter-clockwise.
Distance 800.
500.
200.
Gotcha.
Got her!
Thanks! Perfect timing.
Just repaid what I owed. No need for thanks.
We were supposed to be cooperating.
You don't sound so cool when
I can hear the blush in your voice.
What do we do with her?
We found out who our client was, remember?
Guess we should just take her to them.
I see!
The Doppelganger is on top of the airship.
I'll keep you up-to-date with its location.
Thanks!
You're having fun out there, aren't you?
I'm clinging on to that airship you mentioned.
Oh my!
I was looking at Kuriba's research papers
from before she underwent the experiments,
since all the more relevant data
is locked away on that airship.
Is it no longer necessary?
Misaka Mikoto
No, it's actually perfect timing.
This "possession by a soul" stuff sounded too fishy,
so I considered around 20 alternative
theories on how it's controlling matter.
Misaka Mikoto
You figured something out?
Are there any papers about artificial muscles?
W-Worry not.
The airship which holds most of the data is,
in a sense, a part of the cyborg.
Therefore the safety mechanisms apply
and it cannot crash it willingly.
Destroying it shouldn't cause the soul—
I mean, lead to further casualties.
I understand.
This is bad.
If the anti-air defenses take it down,
all my life's research goes down the drain.
Why is this happening?
What's that?
So, what do you think?
It sure feels like that kind of thing,
but that doesn't explain all of these capabilities.
Would you send that image to me?
When I first found the Doppelganger with my ability,
it was using material from
a closed factory to make something.
The shape looks different, but there are similarities.
It self-replicates and infiltrates matter
on the microscopic level to control it.
This artificial muscle shares features with
ant parasite microbes and slime molds.
That definitely sounds like what's happening,
but could a cyborg's AI come up with that?
It's not just any AI.
It fused with the brain of a human
talented at developing cyborg tech
and learned her creativity and
imagination over a whole year.
Not to mention how it can calculate
and simulate much better than any human.
I don't know at what point
it realized it wasn't human,
but it was certainly a carefully plotted escape.
If we assume that it surmised Kuriba's soul theory,
its actions served not only to strengthen it in battle,
but also to deter people from destroying it.
Connected
Shokuhou Misaki
Call Ended
I knew your possession wasn't that mystical.
This is just me guessing,
but I think you felt despair not
when you realized you aren't human,
but when you became certain that you have no soul.
I shall welcome you now, Railgun.
Isn't it well made?
It combines features from a kind of slime mold
with the muscle structure of a large herbivore.
It grows explosively given water, air,
and a minimal amount of light.
Though once it reaches maximum size,
it starts decaying and it falls apart in a few hours.
If you were after Kuriba Ryouko's life,
what else is it you want now?
Should I say, revenge against humans?
I've taken control of more than 20 other gas tanks.
I prepared them to burn that woman,
Kuriba Ryouko, along with the whole city.
You took out my main trunk,
but I still have some connections.
My strings will take another 20 minutes or so
to grow strong enough to support the mass.
In your eyes I may be nothing but
a vain AI that mistook itself for human,
but as a creation, I have both envy
and hatred for my creators.
Complain to the researchers who made me
learn this foolishness called "emotion".
I'll have to fight.
Airships shouldn't move like that!
I won't be able to get back on if it throws me off.
Multiple?
Decoys again!
From your location, bandits at 1, 2, and 7 o'clock!
Two more at 9!
Thanks!
Again?
Two at 3!
Five o'clock!
That's probably the real one!
Wait! Your line of fire goes—
I watch you as you walk off calmly beneath the morning sun
And your image fades from my eyes
As you slowly blur into the distance
It feels as if a breeze of summer has blown us far apart
And I head off on my way home
Through these ever-sprawling deserted urban streets
As the stars fade into the brightening sky
The scent of twilight lingers in the air
I wonder what we could become
And what our stories' pages might have in store
And whether these warm days might never return
Even if decades pass and we still don't meet again
I know that there's one thing I never could forget
The vow we made each other
With hand in hand so long ago
A lukewarm breeze announces
The end of summer fast approaching
I feel as if I'm taking on the warm red glow of the sky above us
Next Time
Some days I'm sad and feel down.
My Dear Friends
Sometimes I feel powerless.
Some nights I lie awake for hours.
I'm not alone!
I've got my dear friends!