What's the sigh for?
Are you surprised?
I finally got released from the hospital,
only to have to spend even more nights without you.
Complaining won't change that.
It's Tokiwadai's tradition that we stay
in hotels with family during the Starlight Games.
Yes, I am aware...
I will somehow endure these long and lonely nights.
And then once the Starlight Games are over,
we'll get to share our burning passion...
You're making no sense.
Excuse me!
One large serving please!
Sure!
One large serving! Just a moment!
Food Voucher
I wonder...
what she ended up having.
Darling?
Sorry.
Oh, right, want something to eat?
It'll be my treat for the occasion.
I should get something for Uiharu and Saten too.
Something they could nibble on...
A-Anything from you would delight me.
But if I get to choose, I'd like to have your—
...Made it!...
...Made it...!
Uh, was there a war here or what?
Uiharu,
I'm told they won't be using this field today.
I can look around as much as I like.
I'm counting on you for the intel!
Sure. I'm on it already.
Any idea how it might look?
Could it be tiny lumps like gold nuggets?
Have you found anything about its color or shape?
Well, wherever I search it's all fuzzy nonsense.
But there's a huge amount of it.
Well, where there's smoke, there's fire.
If there're so many people talking about it,
there must be something to it.
You're so optimistic.
Time to hunt the shadow metal!
There's something fishy about this.
I feel your heart beat on beyond the hands of time
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Believing that our bond will last until the end
The fervor to protect you growing day by day
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they'll never fade
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they’ll never fade
In the fragile, tender kindness of your bright eyes
There's a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
There’s a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
All the wonderful times that we spent side by side
Will live within my memories eternally
As my mind overflowed thinking of you
More than I could ever hope to explain
I turned the pain of the loss that I felt
To power I'd never known
To power I’d never known
And I keep rushing into the light
No one can stop this phase
Now that we're hand in hand
Now that we’re hand in hand
I etched a vow into the fabric of my mind
So I can keep you safe whatever perils come
I take your hand in my own and never let it go
The time that I have spent just standing by your side
Is all that I have ever wanted to recall
Until at last the day comes when I see you smile
Know that I’m never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
Know that I'm never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
There's nothing metallic.
No way this burned rock
would be the shadow metal.
No news here either.
Actually, I can't seem to find
the site you were talking about.
That's weird. It wasn't even a week ago I read it.
Do you know what this means?!
It's a conspiracy, my dear Kazari!
Conspiracy?
I read some mysterious organization
targets those who go after the shadow metal.
If that's true, then we might be getting close!
Are you working?
I brought Kuroko.
Oh, good.
Can we stay until the next event?
That must be it!
If we don't hurry, they'll take all of it!
But if there are people like that,
aren't you in grave danger?
You're up to something weird again.
Grave danger?
If an organization with that much power
tracks down the shadow metal,
and they found you looking for it right now...
Uh, Uiharu,
stop saying stuff like that.
I'm kidding, I'm kidding!
It's my revenge for the usual skirt flipping.
Why, you...
Huh?
Who are you?! Hey!
Saten?!
Saten, what's wrong?
Did something happen?
I think someone attacked Saten.
Uiharu! Where is she?!
The Kirigaoka stadium in District 18!
We're flying, Darling.
Me too!
You stay here, Uiharu.
Depending on the situation,
we might need you to call Anti-Skill.
But—
Uiharu,
we've got it.
Ouch!
Okay, okay, just let me go!
That hurts.
That hurts!
Those are—
What are they doing?!
D-Darling?
What do you think—
We're terribly sorry!
Our job is to guard and thoroughly clean
the changing rooms and the fields after events.
Waiting Room
There are people out there
after the DNA of high-level espers.
They've been thwarted multiple times in the past.
It's but natural we detain any trespassers we find.
Then you come and attack us.
I can't apologize enough.
I'm terribly sorry!
If you learned your lesson,
then we'll let you off the hook—
By the way,
have you heard about the shadow metal?
Huh?
Saten...
Not even they've seen any shadow metal.
The fields are guarded tightly to prevent genomes
from getting stolen. That seeded the rumors.
That seems to be the truth about the shadow metal.
I told you to stop running
after unfounded silly ideas.
I'm sorry.
You too, Darling!
I learned my lesson.
Are you sure? It feels like you two
are totally ignoring all of my advice.
This is gonna be long.
I'm glad she's all right.
Saten never fails to spice up the day.
But...
these results really bug me.
Did someone seed dummy information
so no one could find the site Saten talked about?
Maybe to hide something inconvenient there?
No way. That's just Saten's influence talking.
But if these dummies were all machine-generated,
then I might be able to restore
the original site by analyzing the patterns.
It's a bit overkill, but here we go.
My, would you look at that.
This is what Saten was talking about.
Shadow Metal (Nullus Metallum)
But there's nothing suspicious about this.
The details on the shadow metal
are mostly as Saten said.
"A very valuable orange",
the "Disciplinary Guides",
a DNA computer that creates esper abilities...
Oh? I know this person.
We're back!
I've been waiting for you!
I'm so sorry, Misaka.
I took off without thinking too. We're both at fault.
Sorry about the trouble, Uiharu.
I'm just glad you're all right.
Did you find anything new?
Hey!
Did you learn nothing today?!
I just...
I looked around myself, but nothing really turned up.
The file has been deleted.
But I did find something exciting!
It's the absolute best spot to watch
the fireworks at the night parade!
Really?
I sure hope it's legal to go there.
Absolutely! I checked!
That sounds nice. Let's go!
It's so pretty.
They do these every night
during the Starlight Games, right?
Yeah, they do.
Then let's make sure to see another one.
Sure!
I can't sleep properly without my usual pillow.
Where is the Queen?
I haven't seen her since last night.
Oh, Misaka. Good morning.
Good morning.
So the Queen hasn't been here at the hotel?
Shokuhou Misaki's groupies?
Misaka!
Wannai! Good morning.
Good morning.
I really don't mean to trouble you,
but when would you return my gym clothes?
Gym clot—
She hasn't returned them yet?
Excuse me?
Ah, sorry. I mean...
Coffee! I spilled coffee on them.
It wouldn't come out at the cleaners'.
I'll pay you back for them!
I'll make sure you get new ones.
Ah, you don't have to go that far.
Tabigake...
She didn't return the clothes for a whole day.
Maybe she wants to have
more fun pretending to be me?
No, that's not like her.
Something
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Manipulation
feels wrong.
This is the area I last saw her in yesterday.
I should be able to find something
if I carefully go through the cameras.
Not this one. Next.
I have plenty of time today.
Maybe I'm worrying too much.
But they need to get regular checkups.
I'd really rather not take chances.
An ambulance?
There! That's her!
She's out cold?
Sick?
Wounded?
I need to calm down.
Which fire department serves this area?
District 7 Fire Station 3
There.
It's the same license plate as on the recording.
Excuse me!
Who was driving this yesterday?
Yesterday? Him and me.
Around noon, did you transport a girl
who had brown hair tied up on one side?
Her?
Yeah, we did.
She's a friend of mine. Could you tell me
which hospital you took her to?
Right over there. You see?
There? Doctor Real-Life Gekota works there.
He knows about the Sisters.
Thank you!
If she was taken here, then she'll be—
Huh?
She's not here?
There are no records of any
emergency arrivals at that time.
But the ambulance crew said they brought her here!
They must've meant another hospital.
No, I'm sure.
Yeah, we definitely brought her to that hospital.
But the records say—
No. Something's wrong.
She was wearing Tokiwadai gym clothes.
We got a call and went to the scene...
Whatever hospital they took her to,
they'd call the school straight away.
Right, and we picked up the girl,
who was unconscious.
It's weird that even though a night
passed there's nothing from the school.
Are you sure?
Then can you tell me which doctor saw her,
and anything else that happened?
Of course.
It was... huh?
Who was it?
Come on. Are you playing dumb? Huh? Wait.
Hey, wai—
I should check the car's internal records.
As I thought. They didn't take her to any hospital.
They went to an underground
parking lot then turned back.
Get out of there!
They took her to a parking lot in the ambulance,
then put her in another car.
Then, where would she be right no—
Hey!
Get out already!
Look at this!
The records show that you
went nowhere near a hospital!
I'd love to see you try to explain that!
But that's...
There's proof! You can't talk yourself out of this!
But... you're that girl.
What's going on?
You were the one we transported.
Why would you tell us that you're missing?
No! That's—
Hold on.
I thought I knew you. You're that Level 5 girl.
You can use electricity.
Manipulating the driving records
shouldn't be hard for you.
Why would I do that?!
I'm sorry I lied about who I am.
But stop lying and tell me the truth!
Hey, stop!
S-Somebody! Somebody, come here!
We're not lying!
If it's not a lie then
what's wrong with your memories?!
Stop going on about—
Manipulating... Memories...
Is it her?
You! Let go of him now!
She seems a little under the weather.
She realized she has five more nights
to spend without Misaka.
She's lost her will to live.
I see.
Uiharu.
This isn't a patrol route.
What?
That can't be. It must be this way.
Look for yourself.
You're right.
Geez. Keep yourself in shape
before saying anything about others.
But why would I make a mistake like this?
Who cares if we patrolled an extra corner?
Excuse me!
You're with Judgment, right?
No, I mean, yes!
I'm a spectator visiting the city.
I was mugged just now.
That's horrible.
What did they take?
Also, please tell me whatever you can about
the suspect's appearance, and which way they ran.
Guess this was the right route to take after all.
That's inappropriate.
I can't...
move...
or teleport...
What they took, huh?
Hmm...
Well, the memories of Misaka Mikoto.
I am deeply sorry.
Let's get going.
What is wrong with you?
You threatened public services for a prank?
They were kind enough
not to make a fuss about this.
What got you so worked up?
I asked them tough questions
until Miss Watanabe showed up.
They didn't seem to be lying.
Then it must be her.
I believe Shokuhou Misaki
abused her powers to hide a crime.
That would be a grave situation if true.
Do you have any basis to force such a conclusion?
I...
Damn. No matter how I explained,
I'd have to mention the Sisters.
I can't say precisely.
That would be a tough charge to press, then.
We are in the middle of
the Starlight Games, Miss Misaka.
The whole world is watching Academy City.
You are a level 5 representing
not only our school, but the whole city.
I understand that the pressure
can sometimes be too much.
Please refrain from careless actions
even more than usual.
I'm sure you understand.
Yes.
I don't get it.
Why would Shokuhou control
the ambulance crew to kidnap her?
Not that it matters now.
Once the events start I should take off
and get to that underground parking lot.
That's my only lead.
Oh, perfect!
May I ask your help?
Miss Misaka is a bit emotionally unstable right now.
Would you please watch over her?
Of course.
Guards? And Shokuhou's people at that?
Ah, Misaka.
I have long wished to have a good chat with you.
Glad today is the day.
R-Right...
Don't cause too much trouble for the teachers.
You're such a tomboy.
This is just so awkward.
Misaka!
A telepath?
We're watching you, so I opened a connection.
As long as we're connected,
I'll know roughly where you are.
Misaka?
If you choose to flee, we will go all out on you.
Go.
As you wish.
I am truly sorry, Miss Misaka.
It saddens me to cast clouds over your Games.
But Queen Shokuhou's optimizations are absolute.
I could lose them if I tried.
At least, I think I could.
But gathering intel with them on my heels
would be a bit too much.
They wouldn't threaten me outright.
I doubt Shokuhou told them anything.
That's Kuroko! And Uiharu and Saten!
Mind if I talk with my friends?
I won't run away or anything!
S-Sure...
I'm out of options.
I'll ask for their help as much as possible
without getting them in trouble.
Kuroko! Can I ask you...
What is it?
I didn't think we were on such close terms.
How presumptuous of you.
Do you know her, Shirai?
No.
She is my senior, Misaka Mikoto.
Oh! She's famous!
You're called the Railgun, right?
K-Kuroko,
is this... some joke you're pulling?
What are you talking about?
Uiharu? Saten?
Why do you know our names?
Have you mentioned us to her, Shirai?
No. We are not acquainted.
I don't know why you know about us,
but if you require assistance, we may help
as members of Judgment.
No,
never mind.
You crossed a line there, Shokuhou.
You went after my friends.
This isn't
just a prank anymore.
Do you know, can you recall, about the promise that we made so long ago
After it's done, wonder if I will fade away into the dark
I know we've gone well past the point of no return to living righteously
But I still feel just a little freed
I need to reach through to the world that lies beyond that lingering memory
As I fall into a slumber
Flashing back to that day
Fighting to hold back the tears that I can't bear to shed
I'm doing whatever it takes just to fight through to my destiny
I could never just believe that fates are predecided
Yet, somehow, people still find their meaning
As they struggle through this story without a name
In this cruel world of suffering
I find myself just trying to bring back those days again
They can't come back
Next Time
Why would Shokuhou manipulate my friends' memories?
Trust
Then she sets her henchmen on me
so I can't do any recon.
I have to figure this out!
Misaka, just leave it to me, Kongou Mitsuko!
Huh?