September 27th
What I foresee is pretty much
guaranteed to happen.
Even if I try to change it,
I can only induce some minor differences,
never changing the outcome.
So basically, you can't escape fate?
I don't know if there's some higher plan out there,
but this may be a case of the principle of causality.
Foretelling the future is still
a barely-researched field.
But today I saw something
that had never happened before.
The future I foresaw was avoided.
The researchers say my ability is probably
based on calculations limited to three dimensions.
Normally that's enough to be considered absolute.
Shirai's teleportation operates on
11-dimensional calculations.
So you think it can avoid outcomes
that would be inescapable in 3 dimensions?
That's just my theory.
What's that?
Just a normal pen light.
I use it to improve my focus
when I utilize my ability's second stage.
I understand that hearing my story
won't be enough for you to believe me.
So I'll make a prediction that's not in the app yet.
Try loading this photo into the app.
All right.
There it is!
It's about a kilometer south-southwest from here!
Let me see that too.
It should happen in 40 minutes.
I had never found any meaning to my life
'Til you came along and opened up my eyes
Staring deep into the heart
of the being drifting on the wind that we think of as "you"
Burning these fleeting sentiments into ever-lasting memories
A Certain Scientific Railgun
As the city moves into yet another season's end
And the newest friend that I've made
brings a measure of happiness
On a certain evening, feeling not a bit of fear
I knew that I could trust
in the path my heart had told me that I should walk
Knowing that if I'm searching through
someone's counterfeit fantasies
I can never approach the light that I've been looking for
Still, I can only press ahead
This illusionary world
shines a light I somehow feel is equally lonely and soft
Searching through my beating heart
for a firmer cognizance of reality
Even knowing that the days
keep advancing seems like an illusion that's slipping away
Knowing this power deep within
gives me fervor like a searing flame
That's dangerous! Let's call an adult!
It's fine! Just a little more!
See, I got i—
Chisa!
Good call bringing floaters since
we knew it was going to be at the river.
Was that enough to prove my ability?
And you could reconfirm that
teleportation can interfere with it.
I'd say knowing who to help beforehand
would come in handy for Judgment.
That's true.
Maki?!
Tokkie, you were cheating on me after all!
Hold on there a second!
This chick just started clinging onto me!
What?!
Hey!
I understand your pain,
but there are lines you shouldn't cross.
At this rate it's going to end up
worse than I'd predicted.
A crocodile escaped its transport!
But y-you walked into me...
What's what?
Who do you think you're talking to?!
We're, you know—
Introduce yourselves to Anti-Skill later.
Well done.
Impressive work.
Well thank you.
Next, regarding the recent mass fainting incident.
Mass Faintings - Cause still unknown
rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr
Anti-Skill says the people involved
show no particular complications,
but the cause is still unknown.
Your ability couldn't predict that?
They say continued efforts
to reveal the cause will be made.
I guess because they just fell asleep
but weren't otherwise hurt.
Also, my ability tends to detect
things physically close to me.
It may be a form of danger detection.
Not that it's any use if I can't
avoid the danger anyway.
Here.
Excuse me?
Your leg.
I must have grazed it earlier.
You'll need to wipe yourself off
before using antibacterial ointment.
You may appear emotionless,
but you're actually quite the little gentleman.
I try to be as nice to women as possible.
Even if the woman in question is you.
Did you really need to add that last part?! Jeez!
Why did you join Judgment?
I... I guess it was for the safety of Academy City.
So for justice, then?
Do I have to spell it out?
I don't understand such things,
because they have no clear logic or resolution.
I got a new prediction.
You look unwell.
I have light anemia.
Is that a park?
10 / 4
16:54
It's projected for tomorrow afternoon.
Is something wrong, Miyama?
Look at this.
10 / 4
16:57
16:54
Two events in the same park.
We've never seen that happen.
I made this prediction before meeting you.
The two incidents are at about the same time, too.
Maybe two people getting
caught in the same accident?
But the two are hundreds of meters apart!
The first image's been analyzed in a lab already.
While not very clear,
it appeared to feature a wildly burning fire.
Fire?
Can we see that processed image?
Sorry, they don't just let me
take the research pictures home.
If both predictions concern the same incident,
that would mean the fire will reach a wide area.
An accidental fire, explosives, pyrokinesis...
Could be any of those, off the top of my head.
Considering how wide the area is,
many people could get caught up in it.
In that case, we cannot handle this alone.
We'll try to reveal as little about you as possible,
but we need to get help. Is that all right?
Yeah.
May I have a moment?
We're emphasizing crime prevention this month.
Could you show us your student ID please?
Here.
Thank you.
Nothing looks dangerous or explosive.
This is all in order.
Thank you for your cooperation.
We're watching every entrance to the park,
checking people's abilities in the student records,
looking for dangerous possessions,
and searching for hazardous materials.
Including people from other offices,
there are 40 Judgment members here.
I'm surprised they're all cooperating
based on that fuzzy explanation.
I can guess the real reason behind it though.
They've been there at so many
incidents preventing damage recently.
Some people in Judgment were asking
why we wouldn't lock the park down,
but there must be a reason for that too.
We don't know at what point your ability
interferes with the predictions.
If we lock the park down and the fire starts
in a more distant area, we could not handle that.
Two more hours.
All right.
Shirai, try putting this on!
What is this?
A satellite image.
It shows people's locations in the park in real time.
My!
How did you get permis—
Did you hack something?
Saving lives takes priority!
Asking around, it seems recently there are
more stray cats and dogs going after the trash.
Is something wrong?
No... Just the cherry trees are blooming.
Can that happen in October?
Well, maybe if it warms up again after
a long chill, the trees think it's spring?
Does that happen?
Not really...
Is something wrong?
I got two new predictions.
Both locations are within the same park.
Not in line with the previous two,
but spread elsewhere in the park?!
Thank you! This is really useful.
If we reorganize based on this, we could—
Miyama!
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Precognition
His red blood cells are deformed?
Yeah.
As a result, they can barely carry oxygen.
We see this occasionally when
someone overuses their ability.
He has to stop using it for a while.
Otherwise, it could even be fatal.
Why would you go so far?
Hey!
Ookawachi?
Your ability sees others' misfortune, right?
Creepy!
Disgusting.
Licky!
There you are.
Map
My ability may only see misfortune,
but I think it could be useful one day.
An ability to protect others.
Maybe?
These are the recent analysis results.
Is that...
Ookawachi?
Is that me?
I think so.
I-I'm sorry about being so mean!
Do something about this!
Yeah. That's why I broke the rules and copied it.
Let's come up with something
and change the future.
Get out!
Ookawachi...
I'm sorry. I couldn't change the future.
Change the future?
It's because of your prediction that
this happened! You bring the misfortune!
No...
It's your fault that I ended up like this!
Get lost and never come back,
you walking calamity!
It didn't work out, Licky.
I really tried as hard as I could...
Guess I can't protect people after all.
Oh no...
Licky...
Not again! Why?
Is it really my ability's fault?
Got a headache?
No, it's nothing.
Try to grasp that feeling from earlier.
Interfere with predictions?
Some abilities might be capable of that.
I found someone.
She's with Judgment. They work to help people.
But who would care about a stray dog?
I have to—
Where am I?
Damn it!
It's almost time.
I know.
There were no explosives.
No suspicious people.
There are no underpasses or gas pipes either.
But it is also unlikely to start outside the park.
What, then?
It's started!
Konori!
I know! We'll take care of the people
she teleports out, as we agreed!
Calm down!
I will teleport you to safety.
Follow the orders of the Judgment officers nearby.
Where next?
It's already spread that far?
I saw fire in the distance.
I started filming it, but it spread to me in a flash!
The blaze is spreading too fast!
Something is wrong with this fire.
The fire is only really intense on the cherry trees.
The cherry blossoms... Something is off.
They're blooming out of season.
But why?
Fertilizer ampules?
Yes! That material at the roots of the
cherry trees might be highly flammable!
If that's the case, then between
the ground and the trees,
the entire cherry grove
could become one giant torch!
Got it! I'll predict the spread
of the fire based on that.
You should rescue people based on the predictions!
Licky!
Shirai!
She was the last one.
We've retrieved some of those
ampules from nearby trees.
It doesn't match any commercial product.
Your suspicions were correct!
But who would do this?
Kuroko!
Miyama?
It's dangerous! Stop!
Teleport me to the center of the park.
That might let me infer something.
Calm down and explain.
A stray dog?
That was the first prediction?
But he's my friend...
Any characteristics?
Uiharu! Check the satellite image!
The smoke is too thick, but I might get
some clear shots of limited areas.
Konori!
Right.
Let's go.
Good grief! I figured he was hiding something.
He thought we wouldn't help a stray dog.
He acts mature, but he's just a child after all.
Shirai! I've narrowed the area down!
Next!
Kuroko! Come back and send me there!
This was all because of my selfishness!
Teleportation can interfere with the predictions,
but that doesn't mean it's always a positive change.
You weren't supposed to be here at all,
but at this rate you'll become a victim!
This is a whole different scale
than anything before. If you—
Miyama.
If you working yourself half to death
for that dog was your selfishness,
then not pulling out here is mine.
Found it! It's limping away from the fire!
I believe
our selfishness is what one calls justice!
Kuroko!
Licky...
Oh no...
Welcome back.
That was close.
I teleported ampules behind
the flames as they approached us,
which changed the direction of its spread.
Is this your dog?
Other than his left leg, he seems to be unhurt.
Then again, he might have breathed in smoke.
Let's take him to the hospital too.
Boys shouldn't show their tears so easily.
Shut up. Don't look at me.
October 5th
Those ampules were indeed the cause of the fire.
The people who developed the compound
just wanted to make the flowers bloom all year.
They didn't expect it to turn the trees into
stockpiles of explosive nitrogen compounds.
Are they fertilizer chemistry specialists?
No. They said they learned
how to make it from Indian poker.
You're always welcome to come play with him.
I'd be happy for the opportunity to apologize.
Ookawachi Megumi
I hear you found someone to take Licky.
Yeah, one of my classmates agreed to.
Are you going to be lonely?
A bit.
But as long as he's alive,
I can still see him, even if it's not as often.
A life you saved.
You were the one who saved him.
No.
If not for your ability, we couldn't have
rescued Licky or any of those people.
Really?
Really.
But my ability...
Yes. Don't exceed your limits ever again.
However,
abilities grow.
Follow your curriculum, and if one day you learn
to use it without such a strain on your body,
you should come see us again.
Even if my ability developed,
I'm not sure it'd be helpful for someone
who's not as close to me as Licky.
I think it would.
You are very similar to me.
To you?
Yes.
I always admired the heroes of justice too.
I see.
I-I was little!
I'll give it some thought.
Like a gust of summer wind blowing through fresh leaves
The image of you walking away
Dissipates from my blurred vision
I walk back home on the empty streets
The morning star is fading
The smell of night is still faintly in the air
Even if tomorrow we are not who we are today
Even if we can never go back
Even if ten, or twenty years pass
I'll never ever forget it
The promise we made as kids with our hands joined
As the lukewarm wind blows
Announcing the end of summer
I'm taking on the color of the slightly reddish sky
Next Time
You wish to grow in many ways, don't you?
Let me introduce you to the perfect product!
Bust Upper
Indian poker!
I'll pass.
You can acquire skills and knowledge while asleep!
I said I'll pa—
Wait, Bust Upper?!