You should be grateful I'm doing this for you.
I really am, Konori.
I'm not good enough to use
the hospital's chairs for Judgment missions.
Geez.
Your wound hasn't even closed up yet.
Looks painful.
D-Don't use your Clairvoyance on me!
That aside, you really shouldn't
push yourself too hard.
Uiharu's worried about you.
I think she feels responsible for my injury.
She was navigating for me when it happened.
Probably.
All the more reason to recover as quick as possible.
I don't want to put even more burden on her.
You two are so similar.
Come again?
It's nothing.
Never mind.
Starlight Games
Opening Pledge
We did it!
Yeah, we did.
Good job, people.
But...
why do I have a bad feeling about this?
The Starlight Games are finally on!
Starlight Games
This is one of the few occasions
when Academy City is open to visitors.
Starlight Games
Here in the main stadium, we can see many visitors
in addition to the competitors' families.
Ms. Watanabe!
It's been so long!
It's that time of the year again.
Ms. Tsukuyomi.
What's the occasion for your outfit?
I'm a cheerleader now!
Your enthusiasm is clear, but—
Oh, I almost forgot Shokuhou's
doing the pledge of fair play.
Yes. They wanted Level 5s to do
the ability demonstration this year.
Starlight Games
Which is fine, but still...
The pledge of fair play!
We pledge
that every one of us
will carry ourselves with sportsmanship.
We will take strength in our
courageous dreams and fiery enthusiasm
Starlight Games
llllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllllll
to build new and ever-lasting friendships that...
Friendships that...
how did that go again?
Whatever. We'll build ever-lasting friendships
and handle all that with our great guts!
We'll express our gratitude to our families
We'll show off the power of guts
by showing the results of our studies
and how much we've grown.
and prove our youth and worth to all the assholes.
We'll make the Games full of great gutsy memories!
Whatever obstacles or difficulties
may stand in our way,
we pledge that we'll go at it
with the best of our guts!
What the heck?
A bit of a mess, I'm afraid.
Sadly.
That concludes the opening ceremony.
Dammit.
I feel your heart beat on beyond the hands of time
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Believing that our bond will last until the end
The fervor to protect you growing day by day
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they'll never fade
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they’ll never fade
In the fragile, tender kindness of your bright eyes
There's a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
There’s a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
All the wonderful times that we spent side by side
Will live within my memories eternally
As my mind overflowed thinking of you
More than I could ever hope to explain
I turned the pain of the loss that I felt
To power I'd never known
To power I’d never known
And I keep rushing into the light
No one can stop this phase
Now that we're hand in hand
Now that we’re hand in hand
I etched a vow into the fabric of my mind
So I can keep you safe whatever perils come
I take your hand in my own and never let it go
The time that I have spent just standing by your side
Is all that I have ever wanted to recall
Until at last the day comes when I see you smile
Know that I’m never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
Know that I'm never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
The Starlight Games are an
annual event held in Academy City.
Starlight Games Management
It's a large-scale sports event lasting seven days.
Unlike your usual school sports days,
every student in the city takes part
competing in the colors of their schools.
And it's broadcast on TV all around the world!
The biggest difference, though,
is that all the players are espers!
That's the coolest part!
They say the clash of espers causes stuff
to happen you can't see anywhere else!
You bean dat urban wegend aboud
dat whadeber-ids-cawwed meddal?
Not just any metal! The shadow metal!
It's a metal that's only created
by the clash of hundreds of abilities!
That can only happen at the Starlight Games!
It's super rare, so it sells for insane prices!
We've gotta look—
Saten!
You're taking silly rumors seriously again!
Come on, of course I'm joking.
Even I can tell when a rumor is just a rumor.
Strawberry fried noodles, please.
We both know that's not true!
Coming right up!
It's one thing to have a curiosity,
it's another to go overboard like this and—
Look!
Misaka's on TV in gym clothes!
Darling!
The fourth duo is Misaka Mikoto and
Kongou Mitsuko from Tokiwadai Middle!
Academy City Starlight Games
Three-legged race
The third event of the seventh block
is the three-legged race!
Three-legged race
Academy City Starlight Games
Seventh Block - Third event
Three-legged race
Academy City Starlight Games
Seventh Block - Third event
Three-legged race
Academy City Starlight Games
Seventh Block - Third event
Three-legged race
Academy City Starlight Games
Seventh Block - Third event
Three-legged race
Academy City Starlight Games
Seventh Block - Third event
Three-legged race
Academy City Starlight Games
Seventh Block - Third event
Three-legged race
Academy City Starlight Games
Seventh Block - Third event
Three-legged race
Allow us to explain the rules.
Seventh Block - Third event
Three-legged race
They get disqualified if
the strap binding their legs breaks.
Abilities may not be used
to directly injure other players.
High-level espers have additional limitations,
so Misaka may not use her lightning strike ability.
Does that mean she can use all other skills?
Take your marks!
Is Tokiwadai the favorite in this race after all?
If it was simply a clash of their abilities, probably.
But as this is a running race,
there can be surprising strategies to turn the tide.
As if such tricks would work against us.
We are Tokiwadai's Gods of Wind and Thunder.
We practiced a lot.
And fell a lot.
Where did that pair name come from, though?
Bringing you today's live commentary,
it's Pirate Radio DJ and—
Bare Navel Headband!
We're moments away from the race's start!
Ready!
What is this?!
Off we go!
Right at the start, the Airin Girls' School
contestant's bandages
have bound the other teams like snakes!
They're the only ones running! What just happened?
Acccording to our documents, she's a telekinesist.
She can control anything she touches.
Her partner is able to break objects
down into their components.
It seems she broke down the concrete of the road.
So the bandages turned black with asphalt!
It must be gooey, and it'll solidify too...
It's not a bad idea to do it at the start.
What do you mean?
Apart from a few exceptions,
abilities generally have a range.
Stopping their opponents and escaping their ranges
turns this into a contest of speed.
I see!
I see the other teams have freed themselves.
My clothes are heavy with goo.
See you at the goal!
What just happened?
An accident?
H-Hamsters? Why?
I figure it's a trap set by
the Ninoude Middle team.
They can use telepathy limited to rodents.
How would that stop anyone?
I think they're after the strap binding their legs.
I see!
If the hamsters cut it, that'll disqualify them!
Not a chance!
Wait, no! Where are they going?
They got their underwear instead.
Give it back!
They seem to be unable to proceed!
Good job, hamsters!
Habatobi High and Tokiwadai are up next.
The rodents attack again!
As expected.
What are you doing to my little Koutarou?!
Piss off! Don't make it jump at me then!
Oh? What's gotten into Misaka?
I guess she's hurt that the hamsters
avoided her because of her electricity.
100m race - Competitor Meeting Place
Academy City Starlight Games
Look at that! Everyone living out
their youth to the fullest in all its chaos.
Then again,
I can just Mental Out the other contestants
and judges to get it over with in a flash.
You may not bring anything unrelated to the race.
I'll take this for now.
The Starlight Games
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Huh?
The three-legged race, the third event
of the seventh block, is nearing its finale too!
This is the last turn,
and then it's straight to the finish line!
The Habatobi High boys are nearing the turn.
Will they have the juice to last to the end?
Tokiwadai and Ninoude are after them!
It's not over! I'm confident in our final rush!
Bring it on!
Bring it oon!
Bring it ooon!
Bring it oooon!
Bring it ooooon!
Bring it oooooon!
Bring it ooooooon!
Bring it oooooooon!
Bring it ooooooooon!
Bring it oooooooooon!
Bring it ooooooooooon!
Bring it oooooooooooon!
Look at that! What did they slip on?
Misaka's magnetism is carrying Tokiwadai ahead!
Habatobi's Amime can control
the friction of objects he touches.
Enjoy that! I touched the road in the curve!
It won't last, but it doesn't need to now!
Tokiwadai are using the
centrifugal force to catch up!
Guess it won't be that simple.
Or maybe!
Amime used his ability to allow
them to accelerate like skaters!
My ability collects and combusts
the hydrogen in the air!
It's a handy rocket boost!
It's a straight line to the finish. We win!
Team Habatobi loses control
and flies out of the course!
Shit.
Amazing! A safety mat caught them in the air!
The heroes of the day are
of course the Tokiwadai pair!
Misaka lifted up the mat with her magnetism,
and Kongou made it fly with her Aero Hand!
What amazing teamwork in the face of danger!
Damn, and we were so close, too.
What's this?
What?
Is this iron dust?
At the start when we were held by the bandages,
I mixed in iron dust before the asphalt could set.
I'd have stopped you if you were
going to reach the finish line first.
It saved you though, so no hard feelings, okay?
They got us good.
Is this what the ladies call fair play?
We never had a chance, huh?
Tokiwadai Middle wins the race!
Maybe if the other schools united
against Tokiwadai, they'd stand a chance.
Awesome!
No subwizes dere.
If only I wasn't injured,
I'd be standing there with her!
Kongou Mitsuko, you're in the way
and I can't see my darling!
Damn, how do you pick this up?
This phone's so weird.
I don't care if it's the latest model.
I could use a normal phone...
You can pull out its side to show the screen.
Then you can call back from the call history.
Oh, you're right! Thanks a lo—
Is something wrong?
Uh...
Nothing...
Saten, let's go!
Be right there!
Wh-What?
Have I met you somewhere before?
N-No! You must have me
mistaken for someone else.
Of course.
Saten!
Coming!
What's wrong? Did you get into trouble?
No. I was just in the middle of something.
I take it you've successfully
infiltrated Academy City.
Yes.
This is your first mission since you joined MEMBER.
You must succeed, young Aztec.
I know.
What a shock!
Nagatenjouki Academy breaks ahead of the pack
and is first across the finish line!
They haven't lost an event yet!
Misaka can't take part in the Starlight Games,
since she's not a student.
Let's head back to the hospital.
Misaka!
We saw the three-legged race!
You were amazing!
It's nice we won, but I'm a dirty mess.
I've seen you run before,
and it's amazing how fast you are.
You could outrun boys of the same age! So cool!
Really? I've been quick since I was little...
Mikoto's been really fast since she could walk.
Mama?
Starlight Games
Hey.
What are you doing here?
We were supposed to meet—
"Mama"?!
I called her the way I did when I was small without
thinking but it's not that I'm still a mama's girl—
"Mama"? Are you Misaka's mother?
Not her sister?
You look like you're in your early twenties!
Oh. That?
You're Mikoto's friends?
Thanks for the compliments.
But looking at you close, I recognize hints of Misaka.
Except the bust.
Saten, I think we'll have a nice chat
later all alone, just the two of us.
I'm just kidding! Just kidding!
Geez.
Where's Kuroko?
She's patrolling with Judgment.
I can call her if you need her.
Ah, never mind.
I thought she could teleport me back
to Tokiwadai to change clothes.
Yeah, you're covered in grease.
I won't make it back for the next event like this.
Why not ask someone to run in your place?
Well...
I'll have to compete with that moron,
so I'd rather not...
That moron? Who would that be?
Mama wants to know!
I-I didn't mean it like that!
Oh, him?
You know?
He's helped Misaka a bunch of times.
Details.
I was watching the scavenger hunt race.
There was this spiky boy!
Spiky?
Oh, him!
You know?
I saw them together in the morning.
She was chatting with a high school-looking boy.
Something about how the loser
would do whatever the winner says.
Whatever the winner says?!
All three of them...
Starlight Games
Oh, my!
Such brutish, wild force. I'm getting goosebumps.
Awatsuki...
Yes?
Have you ever been in a fight?
We are taught that our opponent is within ourselves
and that we are not training
to prove our supremacy above others.
As I watch other schools' students,
it feels like competition is firing up their spirits.
Indeed,
I don't think I could put
so much power and spirit in a race.
I understand that it's bad to hurt
or cause problems for others.
But I feel that our lack
of fighting spirit may be a problem.
I don't think I've ever gotten angry,
let alone in a fight.
So that's why you asked earlier.
I think I haven't eith—
Oh right!
Would you get angry at me please?
Uh, um...
H-H-How dare you!
Beat Tokiwadai!
Who cares if it's an elite school!
They're just girls, and middle-schoolers at that!
Don't let them get ahead!
Yeah!
My, my!
It's good to be brimming with energy.
Alas, we are one of the five favorite schools
competing for the Starlight Games.
We cannot let you win just like that.
We'll plant such fear of Tokiwadai in your hearts
that even your descendants will tell the tales!
Amazing, Kongou!
How can she stand up to the boys like that?
Wonderful!
We can't lose!
Go, Tokiwadai!
G-Go...
I can't hear you! Once more!
Go!
Once more!
This is bad. What should I do?
Is something wrong?
The event is starting soon,
but Misaka is nowhere to be seen...
Oh, no.
"Here to watch again."
Starlight Games
"I-It's not like I'm sad
I can't take part in the events."
—says Misaka like a played-out trope.
It is undeniable there is a feeling of alienation.
Misaka!
Yes?
Why are you not wearing gym clothes?
Starlight Games
Oh right, your gym clothes got dirty
during the three-legged race earlier.
You didn't bring a change?
I'll lend you mine.
Crap!
I figured I'd make it in time if I used my abilities
to speed myself up, but it's almost time.
Sorry, I had to—
Does it fit?
It does not limit my movements.
I feel extra room around my chest.
I'll take the cat.
Oh?
Is something wrong?
I could've sworn there was someone there.
Wh-What is she doing?!
So, what do you think?
I'm well prepared. It shouldn't be an issue.
As you wish, I'll neutralize her, no problem.
We're starting, Baba.
Sorry! I'll be right there.
You're sure full of confidence.
Not surprising from a member of MEMBER,
the secret government-run organization.
Show me what you're capable of!
Do you know, can you recall, about the promise that we made so long ago
After it's done, wonder if I will fade away into the dark
I know we've gone well past the point of no return to living righteously
But I still feel just a little freed
I need to reach through to the world that lies beyond that lingering memory
As I fall into a slumber
Flashing back to that day
Fighting to hold back the tears that I can't bear to shed
I'm doing whatever it takes just to fight through to my destiny
I could never just believe that fates are predecided
Yet, somehow, people still find their meaning
As they struggle through this story without a name
In this cruel world of suffering
I find myself just trying to bring back those days again
They can't come back
Next Time
"Oh my."
Balloon Hunter
"Misaka was mistaken for her sister
and now she has to compete in an event."
"But she must work hard not to let everyone down!"
—says Misaka to explain her determination
as if in the episode preview of a show.
That's, uh... Commendable.