Besides...
He humiliated our friend.
You are not the only one here
with something to be angry about.
You're angry that your friend was humiliated?
Is psychological dependence the latest fad?
If you try to look cool by acting for others,
then when it eventually comes back to bite you,
you'll just regret your actions and blame them for it.
But apparently people lacking in imaginative power
can't understand that
unless they actually experience it.
Water?
I'd heard that unconscious
people were heavy, but still...
Oh! She feels lighter.
Is this your ability, Awatsuki?
It won't last very long.
Please make haste.
Come on now. Do you think I'll just let her leave?
That hole isn't nearly wide enough
to stop a Great Dane-type.
Damn it! I lost the only lead I had!
Or did I?
The nanodevice-packed Mosquito-type
is also useful as a GPS tracker.
I can find her later. It's not a big deal.
The matter at hand now
is dealing with these two.
I feel your heart beat on beyond the hands of time
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Believing that our bond will last until the end
The fervor to protect you growing day by day
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they'll never fade
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they’ll never fade
In the fragile, tender kindness of your bright eyes
There's a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
There’s a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
All the wonderful times that we spent side by side
Will live within my memories eternally
As my mind overflowed thinking of you
More than I could ever hope to explain
I turned the pain of the loss that I felt
To power I'd never known
To power I’d never known
And I keep rushing into the light
No one can stop this phase
Now that we're hand in hand
Now that we’re hand in hand
I etched a vow into the fabric of my mind
So I can keep you safe whatever perils come
I take your hand in my own and never let it go
The time that I have spent just standing by your side
Is all that I have ever wanted to recall
Until at last the day comes when I see you smile
Know that I’m never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
Know that I'm never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
I have to call an ambulance and Anti-Skill.
I hope Wannai and Awatsuki are okay.
Yes?
Hi there, Baba. How is the plan going?
Everything is going smoothly.
Great Dane-types, attack more intensely!
What's that?
Are you fighting someone?
Unfortunately, yeah.
It's just going to delay me a bit.
Are you all right? Need reinforcements?
That won't be necessary.
Are you sure?
I'm so worried about you,
I can't think of anything else.
Yeah, right.
Can I at least run down any new leads for you?
Unfortunately, I still don't
have anything useful to go on.
The one thing you could do is
a bit of cover-up to delay Anti-Skill.
How stupid do you think I am?
I'm not letting you steal my thunder.
Now then. These two weren't
in the Balloon Hunter event,
so I haven't researched their abilities.
The brown-haired one's ability is Hydro Hand.
If they get into water, even the
Great Dane-types are in trouble,
but it doesn't seem to cause that much
damage when she's fighting on land.
The one with the braids uses telekinesis, I guess.
But seeing that she can't just
pin down the Great Dane-types,
she can't be that powerful.
They both seem to be Level 3.
They don't seem to have much combat experience,
but they're making up for it
by working together really well.
I don't really have an endless supply of robots.
You two are better than I expected.
I'm looking for Misaka Mikoto's... sister.
You, with the brown hair. You were talking
to that girl, Kongou Mitsuko if I heard right,
about a lead on the whereabouts
of that sister, weren't you?
Won't you tell me what that lead is?
Of course, I'll make it worth your while.
This is filled with nano-devices.
It's an exceptional item that
can be used to incapacitate anyone.
I used one on Kongou Mitsuko just now.
It's true.
The mosquito-shaped robot injects them.
When I touched Kongou, she was burning up.
There is a chance he is telling the truth.
Removing the nano-devices
from a person's body is not easy.
But if you had this, you might
be able to find their halt command.
So would you be willing to
trade your information for this?
You want to help your friend, right?
We cannot divulge information to a person like you.
However, we shall be taking those nano-devices.
Even if we have to use force.
Oh, dear. I see there's no chance to make a deal.
You leave me no choice.
One of these two is already used, and it's empty.
The other one still has its nano-devices.
Which one do you think it is?
Awatsuki!
Yes!
They know it's a trap, and they still split up.
Pampered girls are so easy.
Where are you going?! Stop!
Come on. I'm getting away.
Aren't you coming after me?
Apparently Kongou partnered up with Misaka
for the balloon sandwich event.
Tokiwadai Middle School wins Balloon Sandwich event!
Starlight Games News
Were those two friends?
The Railgun.
When I think of that girl, my chest tightens up!
I don't even want to think about someone like her,
acting so arrogant off of nothing but a pretty face!
If you can't get her off your mind,
then maybe that was a fateful encounter.
You two might become a good pair.
M-Me and a girl like that?!
Th-That would be out of the question.
Really?
Hey, wait for me.
I can go by myself.
Let's split up and patrol separately.
Emergency Department
The taxi stand had such a long queue.
Academy City Buses
Bus Stop
There are a lot of tourists everywhere.
Let's just wait for the bus.
I can't let Kongou deal with everything.
I have to get away.
Oh, my. I wonder what happened.
Academy City Buses
Bus Stop
I've heard that there have been
a lot of heatstroke cases lately.
Academy City Buses
Bus Stop
We should be careful.
Getting enough water and electrolytes is important.
Emergency Department
But that's...
Saten!
Misaka,
please wait!
Oh, uh, Misaka?
What happened? Why were you in the ambulance?
Hold it!
Interesting. Even some distance from the pond,
she can still control a good quantity of water.
When one of the Great Dane-types absorbed some water
she was controlling, it was destroyed from the inside.
I guess once she has control over some water,
losing sight of it doesn't hinder that control.
I think my analysis is just about done.
With this type of ability, the mass one can control
and the range are limited by the user's power.
Now that she's away from the pond,
she can't replenish her supply of water.
And if I pretend to create an opening
within her range of control...
You almost had me there.
As I suspected, she loses control
over water that's scattered.
The other limitation a Hydro Hand user has is
the number of distinct items they can control at once.
Attacking her water may seem futile at first glance,
but every time it splashes,
pieces of her water armor are chipped away.
The little princess, incapable of anything
but frontal attacks, is starting to fall to despair.
I'm going to enjoy this so much.
Emergency Department
I saw Kongou lying unconscious in the park.
Wannai and Awatsuki were confronting
a sinister-looking boy controlling some robot dogs.
This is my fault.
I didn't take this seriously enough.
I thought it was just a regular
squabble between cliques.
That she was just trying to mess around with me.
I never thought she'd go so far
as to hurt a student from our school.
We're ready.
Please wait over there.
Okay.
Huh?
Um, Misaka?
It would seem you have some things going on, but—
Out of my way.
We should wait for the others to join us.
Unless you're prepared to kill to stop me,
get out of my way!
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Hell Breaks Loose
Misaka?
I had estimated that you'd run
out of steam with two of them still up.
I'm impressed you got all of them,
even if it took all your water to do it.
However, you no longer
have any water to protect you.
Now what?
As a student of Tokiwadai,
I have some training in self-defense.
If you are unarmed, I am also prepared
to fight you without my ability.
How valiant of you.
But I dislike such barbaric ways of fighting.
I'll have my reserve troops do their job.
Being prepared for all
eventualities is simple prudence.
It's not trying to shake me off,
but just maintaining the distance between us.
Its purpose is clearly to separate me
from Wannai and buy time.
I need to hurry.
I can use this.
I managed to cut that corner nicely.
This is where Kongou used her ability.
We must have circled back at some point.
You see, I'm actually pretty strong.
Looks that way, doesn't it?
If you had any water left, you'd be able
to send it up to about this line, right?
For a person as discerning as me,
determining that your range
is about 18 meters is but a triviality.
And that's not all.
I've also estimated that the maximum
volume you can control is about 300 liters,
and that it can't be split into
more than three accumulations.
What are you going to do now?
Bravely fight until your last breath?
Bow down and beg for your life?
Or will you pray to god for rain
from these lovely blue skies?
No, you can't do any of that.
The only thing you can do is regret
your rash decision to get involved in this.
Time for you to suffer the same fate as your friend.
Rain.
What?
Didn't you notice?
This park has a network of buried drainage ducts
to lead the water into the pond
when there is heavy rain.
What?
Your analysis of my ability was impressive,
but you should have also paid attention
to what you cannot see.
W-Water?!
Where'd it come from?!
The drainage duct!
Has she been leading this water
through the pipes all this way?!
I can control up to four separate accumulations.
"Being prepared for all eventualities", wasn't it?
I also possess the guile for that.
I can't grab it!
I'm drowning!
I'm going to die!
Great Dane-types! Suck up the water!
Suck up all this water!
Oh shit!
Were those all the robots you had?
Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit!
I don't have any more Great Dane-types!
I have no choice.
I'll have to use up the last robot
the professor allotted me!
Do you accept your defeat?
I did say I dislike fist fights,
but that doesn't mean I'm bad at them.
I've been trained in a special
assassination technique since childhood.
Family circumstances, you see.
It's a horrible technique that
I've been forbidden from using,
but faced with an opponent as
powerful as yourself, I have no choice.
I'll distract her with this bluff,
so I can have the Mosquito-type
inject the nano-devices!
Almost there!
I almost have her!
It fell?!
Is it out of power?
Impossible! I just activated it!
No! Those movements are strange!
I'm glad to see you're all right.
Awatsuki!
The case I went after was empty,
so I figured he'd use the nano-devices
once you got the upper hand.
Apparently my decision to reduce the
buoyancy of the surroundings to zero paid off.
Buoyancy?!
The one with the braids wasn't using telekinesis?
It was buoyancy manipulation?!
P-Please wait!
Are you, two espers,
going to beat up an unarmed person?!
I-I'm just doing what I was hired for!
There's the Mosquito-type with the nano-devices!
I may have gone a bit too rough on your friend,
but let me off wi—
This may be meddlesome of me to say,
but you only scorn the trust
people have for one another
because you have no one you can trust yourself.
And that is the result of you looking down
on everyone and closing your heart to them.
Unless you make friends you accept
and are willing to meet halfway,
no one will be there to help you.
I feel I was somewhat unqualified to say such things.
Not at all.
What you said was something he needed to hear.
I hope he uses it as an opportunity
to change his ways.
Shit!
Shit! Fucking bitches!
How dare they look down on me!
Information is the key!
If only I had information
on their abilities from the start,
I never would have lost!
Mantis-type!
It's quite conspicuous, so I was reluctant to use it,
but its power is on a different level from
the Great Dane-types, meant for investigation.
Now that I understand their abilities,
my victory is ensured!
Go, Mantis-type!
Death isn't enough to pay for this humiliation!
I'll beat you black and blue, capture you,
and make you regret being born women!
I'm going to spread the images
of you disgraced on the web!
After I destroy your bodies and minds,
that'll also destroy your public image!
I'll make you beg for me to kill y—
The GPS signal from the Mosquito-type
I put on Kongou Mitsuko?
Why is it here?
It's coming up straight ahead.
Wh-Why?!
Why is Misaka Mikoto here?!
Impossible!
She's supposed to be
incapacitated by nano-devices!
I see! Someone who looks like Misaka Mikoto!
It's the Sister!
I'm in luck!
If I capture her, I'm redeemed!
Punishing those two bitches can wait!
Mantis-type, capture her!
It's—
It's the real one?!
S-Stay away!
I know you can hear me.
I made sure to leave the communication device intact.
I've determined your location
from the control signals.
I-It's not opening!
Has she already taken control of all my systems?!
I'll be right there to make you look like this thing.
Or at least that would be my impulse.
But considering that you were controlled by her,
I'll let you off this one time.
However,
if I ever again see a robot of yours
near me or my friends, even for an instant,
no matter where you are, I'm going to find you,
and crush you.
Oopsie.
What's wrong?
Oh dear.
Baba's out.
Out?
He said that all his underlings are gone,
so he's going to find a place to hide.
Go figure.
He also said he failed at
incapacitating Misaka Mikoto.
I guess I'll have to take things into my own hands.
She's tough.
What?
Do you know her?
I've seen her fight once from up close.
Well, it's not like we have to beat her in combat.
If we can do everything we need
before the day is over, we'll be fine.
Do you know, can you recall, about the promise that we made so long ago
After it's done, wonder if I will fade away into the dark
I know we've gone well past the point of no return to living righteously
But I still feel just a little freed
I need to reach through to the world that lies beyond that lingering memory
As I fall into a slumber
Flashing back to that day
Fighting to hold back the tears that I can't bear to shed
I'm doing whatever it takes just to fight through to my destiny
I could never just believe that fates are predecided
Yet, somehow, people still find their meaning
As they struggle through this story without a name
In this cruel world of suffering
I find myself just trying to bring back those days again
They can't come back
Next Time
The key to the mystery
is auribus oculi fideliores sunt!
The Eyes Are More
Trustworthy Than the Ears
Auribus oculi fideliores sunt.
Everyone say it with me!
Auribus oculi fideliores conto.
Did someone say something different?