The next event is:
Balloon Hunter
Balloon Hunter!
.
Balloon Hunter
Each school competes
with a team of thirty students,
.
Class 1-3
Hazamaya Kana
using balls to pop the paper balloons
on each other's helmets.
Class 1-3
Hazamaya Kana
Players whose balloons are popped are eliminated.
Class 1-3
Hazamaya Kana
Whichever team has more survivors
when time runs out wins.
Class 1-3
Hazamaya Kana
The field of play is large, but players aren't allowed
to enter roads or areas open to the public.
And just as with other events,
direct attacks with abilities are not allowed.
Let's go, shall we, Misaka...?
It's starting, Kongou.
Is everyone ready?
I'll give you credit for not giving up straight away.
Let's see who laughs in the end.
All right.
Ready...
Run as if your lives depended on it!
If we all survive it's a draw!
H-How passive can one get?
After them!
"It's dangerous to go alone."
"We should form platoons of three."
—suggests Misaka...
Oh well.
How did it end up like this?
Starlight Games
Actually, I think I can imagine how.
I'm not sure if I should feel relieved or annoyed
that no one realized she's not me.
Well, what's done is done.
You're playing in my place, so go wild, will you?
I feel your heart beat on beyond the hands of time
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Believing that our bond will last until the end
The fervor to protect you growing day by day
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they'll never fade
Holding on tightly to our hopes so that they’ll never fade
In the fragile, tender kindness of your bright eyes
There's a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
There’s a light that guides along my fast-beating heart
All the wonderful times that we spent side by side
Will live within my memories eternally
As my mind overflowed thinking of you
More than I could ever hope to explain
I turned the pain of the loss that I felt
To power I'd never known
To power I’d never known
And I keep rushing into the light
No one can stop this phase
Now that we're hand in hand
Now that we’re hand in hand
I etched a vow into the fabric of my mind
So I can keep you safe whatever perils come
I take your hand in my own and never let it go
The time that I have spent just standing by your side
Is all that I have ever wanted to recall
Until at last the day comes when I see you smile
Know that I’m never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
Know that I'm never letting go of this warm, gentle hand
You're not going to patrol?
I'll be handling internet duty in a bit.
During large-scale events like this,
cyberattacks of various sizes can be expected.
You're really good with that kinda stuff.
Three minutes into Balloon Hunter,
neither team's lost anyone so far!
Which team will break the balance first?
Isn't that the event Misaka
said she was taking part in next?
I think so too. I hope she made it on time,
having to change clothes and all.
Being Misaka and all, I'm sure it worked out.
That's Kongou!
Let's split up!
Okay!
They have to pop each other's balloons?
Tokiwadai has plenty of strong espers
even without Misaka, right?
I bet they'll win easily.
I wouldn't be so sure.
Give up already.
A telekinesist?
You lured me here?
I feel bad for doing this to a girl.
Don't worry! I won't hit your face!
It seems you are not even Level 3.
I'm a telekinesist too.
And I'm much stronger than you.
Shit!
Do you really think I'll let you escape?
Omoshi's out!
If you're all this level,
I can easily handle you all by myself.
Don't worry, it won't be long—
Kirifu's out!
What?
Wait, he attacked me after I took him out.
That's against the rules!
If it was me.
H-Hi.
She used telekinesis to hit you with the ball.
That's where being so full of yourself got you,
Level 4 telekinesist Kirifu Megumi.
Why do you know my full name?
Because we're a lot weaker than you.
We did our research and planned out how to win.
Is everyone in position?
At least five of the opposing team's
members entered this area earlier.
We've covered all three exits of the area.
Move in on my telepathic mark.
Ready? Three.
Two.
On—
K-Kobayashi, calm down...
A telepath's scream is an unblockable sonic weapon
that rings directly in your brain.
It's a toy, don't worry.
Personality: Leader
Kobayashi Satori
3rd-year
Telepath
Can't stand bugs (especially spiders)
How far are you going to run?
I am getting tired of this!
M-Mud?
Do we have to go this way?
That'd ruin my shoes.
Let's go around, shall we?
G-Good idea.
There they go,
naïvely running straight into our trap.
This is amazing.
We're toying with the great Tokiwadai.
It's all as you said, Baba!
I just gathered the data
and made some suggestions!
But how did you get this much data?
All their details, even their secret fears...
I've got a friend at the
Garden of Learning. I had some help.
What next?
Lemme see.
Wars turn on advanced intelligence
and a leader able to use it.
Let's see... Next, we move.
We rendezvous with Nomura
and the others at Point 5A.
Where is Point 5A again?
With enough details on the enemy,
even losers like these can be useful.
That would be...
The storage room in the second block.
There?
Let's go...
Baba?
Yeah, let's go!
It's going well. We've got a huge lead.
Don't let your guard down.
They've got Misaka Mikoto.
She's a natural radar station. We can't ambush her.
A real stronghold.
But we don't need to take them all out, right?
Yeah, no need to take unnecessary risks.
Let's be careful to avoid her.
Here we go.
It took a lot of work to get these
underdogs to agree to this plan,
but now that they're ahead, they might bail on it.
What a drag.
How do I flare them up for this?
No way! Why did I have to run into the level 5?!
Sh-She's gone?
Experiments have been held in this alley before.
I know all the paths,
the hiding and sniping spots too.
Crap! No chance!
Careful, that roof is dangerous—
"Told you."
—observes Misaka.
Misaka took two down!
Can Tokiwadai turn this around
in the remaining time?
Did you see that, kitty?
Miss Misaka is amazing!
What an adorable kitten.
Thus I fall, in the end.
Don't forget to feed Ekaterina... one mouse a day.
Thanks for the performance.
Now get out of the battle zone quick.
Oh, we need to?
You're so strong. There were seven of us.
This is what you deserve
for challenging the great Kongou Mitsuko!
She's a transfer student,
so we barely had any data on her.
You should be proud that you
managed to beat me at all!
Do all transfer students act that high and mighty?
This is bad! Nomura's team are all down!
Crap!
This is bad. We've lost most of our lead.
Our only Level 3 as well.
Perfect!
We should target Misaka Mikoto.
They're all split up now,
but once time starts to get tight
they might team up.
If they coordinate, we won't be able
to maintain the small lead we have.
If we take out their ace, that'll confuse them
and make it harder for them to unite.
That makes sense, but still.
How are we supposed to do that?
Don't worry.
There's a stupidly easy way
to take her down.
A Certain Scientific Railgun
Balloon Hunter
I lost them.
I'm with Judgment!
You're under arrest for the charge of theft—
Huh?
Better not annoy me now.
I am in a bad mood.
After all, so far today...
I have still been unable to see my darling.
What is this?! Damn it! Pull them out!
She must be taking part in an event right now.
Where was the biggest screen in this area?
"This is strange," thinks Misaka, her head tilted.
She does not appear to have any willingness to fight.
Yet she is not just running away aimlessly either.
She's escaped to such an open area.
This is either of benefit to her ability,
or perhaps...
it's a trap.
If thrown balls can't hit her,
then don't throw them.
Huh?
The rules only say that we have to
pop the balloons with the provided balls.
You can pop a balloon with a ball in your hand.
If Misaka Mikoto tries to use
her ability to deal with the balls,
it'll count as a personal attack
and she'll be disqualified.
We can block her lightning
by holding on to the balls.
Without her abilities, she's just like us.
Then...
Got you!
"I faced someone who can kill on touch
over ten thousand times."
"It is not easy to catch Misaka."
—warns Misaka.
Go!
All together!
Misaka is dodging everything!
A duck!
A lunge!
A slide!
This is just amazing!
Finally.
It took ages to arrange for this situation.
Misaka Mikoto constantly emits
a weak electromagnetic field.
If she focuses on it, it functions as a radar.
It's close to impossible for any electronic device,
no matter how small, to approach her unnoticed.
But if the rules block her ability
so she has to focus on her opponents,
there's a chance!
Listen!
Go in all at once and—
A hole in the wall.
Time to—
Misaka goes down!
No way! I did it!
We win!
Did they... get me?
Mission complete.
That was a weird order.
"Neutralize Misaka Mikoto."
Balloon Hunter is now over!
A favorite for winning the games,
Tokiwadai has lost it by a small margin!
Their first defeat in the games.
I feel this is the biggest reason
to take part in the event.
Indeed, there is plenty to be learned from defeat.
It must serve as a painful lesson for those
whose level or family make them haughty.
We can't have them worry more about
dirtying their clothes than winning.
True.
Should we make them take turns
cleaning the toilets in the dorms?
That is indeed a good idea.
"Due to insufficient vigilance,
I fell victim to the other team's scheme."
—reflects Misaka on her own mistake.
Even though I was representing you—
Did you have fun?
Did you have fun taking part in the event?
Y-Yes.
Then don't worry about it.
It's against the rules to switch places like this,
but it was an honest mistake.
And it's my fault too, for running late.
I thought you handled that last bit
way better than I could have.
Good job.
It's almost lunchtime.
Have you had lunch yet?
No.
Here. These are coupons for the food stalls.
Food Voucher
Can be exchanged during the Starlight Games at any affiliated shop
I'm having lunch with Mama. You can have them.
Food Voucher
Can be exchanged during the Starlight Games at any affiliated shop
Food stalls?
It's not every day we have
an event like this. Let's enjoy it.
You borrowed those clothes from Wannai, right?
Return them quick.
It's one thing to bring your own food,
but bringing a gas burner and
having a cheese fondue is another.
But having a hot pot with your mom
on a sports day is just great!
Which part of it?
It's gonna take a while for the cheese to melt.
I should've cut it finer.
I'll get some drinks then.
Mama'd like some wine!
They don't sell that here!
Ugh.
Bleugh.
That's quite the queue.
Hey!
Huh?
Fancy seeing you here.
You too?
It sucks that there are lines everywhere.
Tell me about it. I almost wet myself, at this age!
What are you talking about?
The restrooms are crowded too,
I almost didn't make it.
I just came to get some drinks!
Oh, that?
You really have no tact.
I'll get some for you too then.
What my mom got won't be enough either.
Just a sec.
Yet still so weirdly kind.
See? Just as I said.
Indeed.
How did you know from the broadcast?
There are plenty of ways to use Mental Out.
I'm not telling, though.
I see. Level 5 secrets, I figure?
Keep your comments to yourself,
and your eyes wide open.
Look who's there!
Ugh.
Misaka! Having a lazy lunchtime?
Lazy?
How've you been spending your lunch?
Off training in secret or what?
No way.
I canceled all my afternoon events with my ability.
What?!
The morning tired me.
Now seriously...
Is this gonna do?
It's all tea though.
Who might that be?
A schoolmate in my year. Sadly.
In your yea...
I see, in your year!
I saw where his eyes just went!
Hello, Kamijou!
I'm Shokuhou Misaki, Misaka's friend!
Nice to meet you!
I'm no friend of yours!
So scary!
You know, I think she hates me!
She doesn't have a spark of kindness for me!
Uhh, yeah...
She's all sparky around me, too.
Oh, so it's sparks all the way down!
You two just met...
Don't start giving me weird nicknames together!
See you, Misaka!
Fill in for me in the rest of the events!
What's wrong?
It's not like you to ponder like that.
Are you done with work?
There were a few larger-scale server attacks,
but they were total amateurs
so I've already sorted it out.
Wow...
What about you?
See...
Where do you think we could find shadow metal?
Are you still going on about that?
If it's produced by the interference
between esper abilities,
it should be in areas where strong schools clashed.
Shirai scolded you about this too.
Are you having financial issues?
Nah.
Not like I'm rich or anything,
but this is about the adventure.
Finding something beyond common sense,
something extraordinary...
It's the same as the deal with Level 5s.
I see.
I'll help you too.
Shadow metal, was it?
I'll try looking up some details too.
Thanks a lot, Uiharu!
Why are you wearing gym clothes underneath?
So I can get ready for events quickly.
Please stop flipping my skirt...
Cotton candy.
Candied apple.
Food Voucher
I wonder how they taste?
Fried noodles often comes with onions,
so that is not an option.
Food Voucher
"Even cats can have fried squid,"
—says Misa—
This is... bad...
I borrowed these clothes.
Now they're all... dirty...
Do you know, can you recall, about the promise that we made so long ago
After it's done, wonder if I will fade away into the dark
I know we've gone well past the point of no return to living righteously
But I still feel just a little freed
I need to reach through to the world that lies beyond that lingering memory
As I fall into a slumber
Flashing back to that day
Fighting to hold back the tears that I can't bear to shed
I'm doing whatever it takes just to fight through to my destiny
I could never just believe that fates are predecided
Yet, somehow, people still find their meaning
As they struggle through this story without a name
In this cruel world of suffering
I find myself just trying to bring back those days again
They can't come back
Next Time
Darling, we are finally all alone!
Manipulation
It's no big deal.
No! It's been 23 episodes since
the two of us did an episode preview together.
So we should let passions blaz—
You're not even going to make a quip first?