Even the purest of the pure
Are singing out loud because they want you, cock-a-doodle-doo!
Luluco
So let's sing Les Misérables and drive us to our fateful encounter
Alpha-Omega
Nova
Common sense is a matter of opinion
So what is yours worth? Cock-a-doodle-doo!
Midori
Hold on tightly to all the light we can!
Wait, is that really a heart there, too?
SPACE PATROL LULUCO
I'm Luluco.
This is bad.
My mom suddenly came back from space
and shoplifted our hometown of Ogikubo!
Current Bid:
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Buy It Now:
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Seller
Current Bid:
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Buy It Now:
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Seller
Current Bid:
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Buy It Now:
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Seller
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Buy It Now:
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Seller
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Buy It Now:
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Seller
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Buy It Now:
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Seller
Is it brand new?
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Buy It Now:
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Seller
Is it brand new?
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Seller
Is it brand new?
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Seller
Is it brand new?
Used. Shows signs of usage.
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Seller
Is it brand new?
Used. Shows signs of usage.
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Seller
Is it brand new?
Used. Shows signs of usage.
Seller
Is it brand new?
Used. Shows signs of usage.
Does it come with all original accessories?
Is it brand new?
Used. Shows signs of usage.
Does it come with all original accessories?
Is it brand new?
Used. Shows signs of usage.
Does it come with all original accessories?
Is it brand new?
Used. Shows signs of usage.
Does it come with all original accessories?
Not all.
Is it brand new?
Used. Shows signs of usage.
Does it come with all original accessories?
Not all.
Used. Shows signs of usage.
Does it come with all original accessories?
Not all.
Used. Shows signs of usage.
Does it come with all original accessories?
Not all.
This new? Does it come with a box?
Used. Shows signs of usage.
Does it come with all original accessories?
Not all.
This new? Does it come with a box?
Used. Shows signs of usage.
Does it come with all original accessories?
Not all.
This new? Does it come with a box?
I've always thought that I hated this weird town,
but I would hate losing it even more!
I have a good idea.
Place Keiji here, Luluco.
Okay.
Look.
While he may be unconscious,
waves of justice are still
running through his brain.
If we keep stimulating those,
his brain should start functioning again, if only temporarily.
Wow.
Gross...
Hang in there, Dad!
That was a shocker!
Dad! I've missed you so much!
Oh, Luluco!
The slab bacon you make really is tasty—
Wait, what?
My body's gone!
The only slab here right now
is a slab of your brain, Keiji.
Is that you, Chief? It's been a while.
Long time no see.
I see.
This is no normal situation!
Yeah. Try to think of a way to stop Mom.
Y'know, I've been thinking...
If we bid, like, 1... 10... 100... 1,000...
Current Bid:
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Buy It Now:
Space Yen
(Tax Free)
Seller
10,000,000,000 space yen and buy it now, wouldn't that fix everything quick?
Nice idea, Midori!
No, it's not.
We can't bid on it knowing
that it's an illegal auction.
We have no money for criminals!
And no money, period!
So much for justice.
We do have justice!
Wow...
Wait, this is your place, Luluco?
Tiny!
Run-down!
Lame!
Who cares about that right now?
Here!
What, your closet?
I had no idea this was
packed away inside our closet...
Since I'm missing half my brain,
it took me a while to remember about it.
You're lacking in brains, Keiji.
Can you really pilot in that state?
Forgive me, Luluco!
To return Ogikubo to normal,
I'm going to give up on being
a normal parent and a normal person!
Ow, hot!
That's a lot of adrenaline!
Space Patrol Rocket: Bullet Unit 1...
Fire!
Listen up!
We of the Space Patrol will hereby
shoplift the shoplifted Ogikubo back!
Minus times minus equals plus!
A crime for a crime equals justice!
So it's a crime...
Normally, justice is about upholding the rules!
But sometimes, you can't mete out
justice if you play by the rules!
Nobody is allowed to break
the rules or pervert justice!
But you can twist it!
Yes!
This is how...
...we adults...
...bring about justice!
That is some messed-up reasoning!
Nailed it!
Justice...
Ow...
I think we're just stuck on the side of the ship.
So...
What now?
I'm out of hands to play.
Same. I have no hands.
That was weak. I'll kick ya outta here.
Mom!
Lalaco!
Long time no see, ex-hubby.
Oh? That explains why your brain was missing.
You've got some nerve if you're trying
to trick your own mother, Luluco.
It's not too late, Lalaco!
Give Ogikubo back!
And go back to normal!
Like Luluco and me!
Go back to normal!
Normal! Normal! Normal! Normal!
Speak normally, Dad!
Lalaco!
Quit calling me that!
Right now, I'm the very incarnation
of true, unfettered freedom,
Space Pirate Empress Godspeed!
If you want Ogikubo back,
let's see you try and take it back!
Oh, too bad.
Looks like some fat cat bought it now.
Congratulations!
Buy It Now
Your item was purchased
at the Buy It Now price of
10,000,000,000 space yen (tax free).
Finalize
Transaction
And that's the end of the auction.
Start shipping.
Perishable
Don't place
anythingon top
This
Side
Up
This
Side
Up
Perishable
Don't place
anythingon top
This
Side
Up
Perishable
Don't place
anythingon top
This
Side
Up
Perishable
Don't place
anythingon top
This
Side
Up
Perishable
Don't place
anythingon top
This
Side
Up
Perishable
Don't place
anythingon top
This
Side
Up
Perishable
Don't place
anythingon top
This
Side
Up
Perishable
Don't place
anythingon top
This
Side
Up
Perishable
Don't place
anythingon top
This
Side
Up
W-Wait, Mom!
What do we do?
At this rate, we're really gonna lose Ogikubo!
Long story short,
we just gotta shoplift it back, right?
Midori?
Yo, it's me. We still got those left, right?
Send 'em over.
What?
Just listen to what I'm telling ya!
Send every last one we got!
Now! On the double! Pronto!
Th-This is the quasi-legal...
...Black Hole app from back then?
Midori, you were still hiding these?
Ya can't always do that justice thing
if ya only play by the rules, right?
If ya want twisted justice,
you've come to the rigblubglu.
Well said, Midorblurrgh.
I'd noticed that justice within you
right from the get-go!
Really, now?
Get ready! It's gonna keep comin'!
Detecting a huge and unidentified
green energy source directly above us!
Th-This is a massive...
middle school girl's hand!
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What?!
Don't tell me they're planning
to shoplift this entire ship?!
To hell with that!
We can't break free!
We're gonna get shoplifted along with the gate!
Oh, no! The two warps
are gonna you-know-what
and distort this whole space!
Come on, Mom! Stop doing these bad things!
Did you forget?
If I see that someone else
is gonna destroy something,
I can't rest easy until
I destroy it with my own hands!
I'll make you regret ever
picking a fight with us Space Pirates!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Damn it all!
Don't come cryin' to me later!
Little shit!
Out of the frying pan and into the fire!
Where are we?
A faraway galaxy?
The normal life I seek is growing
even further out of my reach!
But I won't give up!
To be continued! To be continued, I say!
I'm searching the entire galaxy for you
Going from one planet to the next
I'm broadcasting my feelings of love to you, beep, beep
So please receive them!
They float gently
In this endless universe
I've locked on to that heart of yours
So you will never be able to run away
I want you to hold my hand
To make my head spin like a merry-go-round
To make my heart skip a beat
The world will be dyed in the colors of my love