Both the big-brained and the bird-brained
Are singing out loud because they want you, cock-a-doodle-doo!
Luluco
They need to do it before their life runs out
All of your dreams can come true!
Alpha-Omega
Nova
Common sense is a good morning call
To keeping the status quo, cock-a-doodle-doo!
Midori
So plan out your life and sew out the mysteries
Every Friday is my birthday!
The planet is still blue today?!
SPACE PATROL LULUCO
I'm Luluco.
During what was supposed to be
a normal breakfast on a normal day,
my dad accidentally froze himself,
so I ended up having to work
at the Space Patrol in his place.
I just wanted to live a normal life, though...
Damn...
For real?!
I don't believe it.
Crazy.
All right, settle down. Don't make a fuss.
We're in the middle of an exam.
Thank goodness! He's alive!
I didn't have a choice.
They...
They made me an offer I couldn't refuse!
Save that for later.
Man, what should I do?
Normally, at times like these,
you call the cops or the hospital...
Oh, right. I totally forgot...
I forgot to mention this,
but a new student is joining us today.
Alpha-Omega Nova
Hello.
I'm Alpha-Omega Nova,
and I'm transferring in from space.
Alpha-Omega Nova
Pleased to meet you all.
So that meteorite was carrying a transfer student!
All right. You'll be sitting next to Luluco.
Alpha-Omega Nova
Okay.
And Luluco, clean up that mess already.
Alpha-Omega Nova
Oh man, I forgot!
I should do that, shouldn't I?
Alpha-Omega Nova
But how? What do I do?!
Wouldn't taking space criminals to the
Space Patrol HQ be the normal thing to do?
I can tell from your amusing appearance.
You're Space Patrol, right?
Right.
I'm Space Patrol Luluco.
I knew it.
I'm Space Patrol, too.
Chief Over Justice summoned me here,
so I need to report to the station now.
I have to...
take this offender there, too, so...
Would you mind showing me the way, then?
If you don't mind being second priority...
This is such a strange town.
It's still hard to believe humans
and aliens live together here.
You think so?
I've lived here all my life, so I can't really tell.
It is rather strange.
Apparently, it used to be part of Japan,
but back in the Showa
or Heisei era, I'm not sure which,
Japan sold Ogikubo off because they were broke.
Receipt
Code
Item
Quantity
Price
Comments
Ogikubo
No Box,
Slightly Faded
Apparently it wasn't worth all that much, though.
It's even mentioned in our
third-year Social Studies textbook.
My dad said that a ton
of aliens moved in after that
and there was chaos everywhere.
Those people there,
the owner of that shop, and that dog...
They're all aliens.
It's a town full of aliens,
and it appears completely bizarre to me.
Wow.
You can tell at a glance whether
someone's an alien or not?
You can't?
You're an extremely amusing girl.
I am sure that you are someone who
can see more than what is in front of you.
Are you from somewhere out in the universe, too?
If you're asking whether I was
born in this universe, then yes.
Just like you, I'm a child of this universe,
which in turn was born from the Big Bang.
Space Patrol
Well done, Luluco!
Such a brilliant arrest! It's hard to believe
you're only thirteen years old.
It looks like Judgment Gun
Morphing worked well, too.
So that was one of the suit's functions?
It's not just the suit's power.
It's a manifestation of your own justice.
Sorry to interrupt your pointless discussion,
but I've been assigned to the
Ogikubo branch as of today.
I'm Alpha-Omega Nova.
Oh, hello there, Alpha-Omega Nova.
Thanks for coming all the way here.
Sorry to put you to work right away,
but could you interrogate that offender?
Understood.
Awaken: Judgment Gun Morphing!
It seems he's still breathing,
so I'd like to finish him off.
I'm sorry!
I'll spill the beans! I'll tell you everything!
Go right ahead.
Our school is being controlled by
a terrifying alien called Save the World.
They made a quasi-legal Black Hole app,
which they're distributing to the students!
A quasi-legal Black Hole app?!
They were using that to enable space shoplifting?
Shoplifting
I knew your middle school
had something to do with that case!
Shoplifting
Luluco! Nova!
Annihilate the evil residing in your school
with the might of your justice!
Understood.
Just the two of us?
Fight for Justice!
So we'll be working as a team from now on?
Justice!
Let's do our best.
'Kay...
Awaken: Judgment Gun Morphing!
Fight for Justice!
Justice!
Just as the Big Bang is the universe's origin point,
the boy standing before me might well be my own.
If this emotion expanding
faster than the speed of light
was born from me,
a normal middle schooler
of just thirteen years of age,
then it might be a Big Bang in its own right.
To be continued...
I'm searching the entire galaxy for you
Going from one planet to the next
I'm broadcasting my feelings of love to you, beep, beep
So please receive them!
They float gently
In this endless universe
I've locked on to that heart of yours
So you will never be able to run away
I want you to hold my hand
To make my head spin like a merry-go-round
To make my heart skip a beat
The world will be dyed in the colors of my love