Everyone thinks and everyone lives
Good morning to you, cock-a-doodle-doo!
Luluco
You just have to accept that everything is simply weird
All of your dreams can come true
Alpha-Omega
Nova
Both the big-brained and the bird-brained
Are saying "nice to meet you," cock-a-doodle-doo!
Midori
Suddenly you pretend to be a lantern
And throw important information at me
I'm going now, so get ready, future!
SPACE PATROL LULUCO
I see him.
I see Nova!
Emergency
What's going on?!
Don't move!
Move and we'll shoot!
Where are yer goin', Luluco?
Nova, I have...
Halt! Stop or we'll shoot to kill!
Fire at will!
...something to tell you!
What the hell's goin' on?!
It's those space pirates!
Huh? Luluco's nutjob mother is 'ere?!
What's this, Luluco?
I come all this way for your funeral,
and you're already back to life?
Yeah, just now.
Anyway, Mom...
I'm about to confess to the boy I like.
And I need the favor of a lifetime!
I don't need Ogikubo,
Dad's brain, or a normal life!
So please help me out!
Just once is enough!
You've come to have quite the spirited
look to you while I've been away.
Confess, eh?
You've come of age, I see.
I don't mind helping you out, then.
Mom!
Listen up, Luluco!
If you ask me, only after one dies and returns to life
do they become a normal person!
Luluco docked with her mom's ship?!
What is this?
The Jolly Roger turned
into the Space Patrol logo!
Justice!
I'll lend you my ship for now.
Now seek out that boy like
your second life depends on it!
Thanks, Mom!
Oh, and one more thing!
Take care of Dad, okay?
All right, I'm going, then!
Awaken: Judgment Gun Morphing!
She's gettin' pounded
right out of the gate.
Okay, you good-for-nothing Patrollers!
We're taking care of the scrubs!
Very well, Lalaco Godspeed.
By your not-justice and my justice combined,
we'll use that repelling justice energy
to blast those Blackholeians—
Shut it, geezer! Just do it already!
Ya hear?!
Over Judgment Gun Morphing!
Awaken: Judgment Gun Morphing!
Come on!
How long are you gonna sleep?!
Head!
Hands!
Space Patrol Keiji!
Awaken: Judgment Gun Morphing!
God Pirates Gun Morphing!
Wh-Where am I?
Where is Luluco?
Off to confess to some boy she's in love with.
What?!
No way! I won't stand for it!
It's too soon!
She's... Luluco's...
still only a middle schooler!
Yes, she's a middle schooler already!
Shit! Shit! Shit! Ya little shits!
She's old enough to make
her own damn decisions now!
Fire!
Secretary Final Fire!
I take my eyes off her for a second,
and she grows up into one damn fine woman.
Lalaco...
Today is the day our daughter confesses her love!
Nova?
Let's mark it with some massive fireworks!
Luluco...
We meet again.
Nova...
I was shocked when I thought you betrayed me.
I was so sad that my heart became
an empty shell, and I died because of that.
But then I realized that you never once lied to me.
You never betrayed me.
Yeah, it was all a misunderstanding on my part.
That doesn't matter.
But you also never told me the truth.
You never told me how you really feel.
If you want my heart, you can steal
it as many times as you want.
But if you take it without
my permission, that's a crime.
Feelings...
Crime...
None of that matters—
It does matter.
Because I'm Space Patrol Luluco.
And, Nova,
I'm placing you under arrest!
Nova...
I...
I love you!
Luluco?
What a riot!
So this is a middle schooler's
confession of love?
A completely pointless and
worthless waste of time.
That's a middle schooler for you.
Blackholeian!
Stupid middle schooler who
doesn't know when to give up,
nothing you say to him will have any effect.
He's a hollow Nothingling!
He has nothing in the way of feelings!
More importantly...
Nova?!
I don't know how you did it,
stupid middle schooler who gave birth
to something so big and worthless again.
But I seek only the unique!
The one and only!
I have no interest in mass-produced goods!
N-No way!
What?!
Give! Up! Already!
The universe? The void?
I'm just a middle schooler,
so I don't understand any of that!
But I do know that these are
my feelings of love for Nova!
Take it away all you want,
but these feelings will never, ever die!
Do you remember, Nova?
It made me so, so happy
when you said we should
do our best together!
That alone was enough to
give birth to these feelings,
feelings that are expanding
faster than the speed of light!
You changed the world for this normal,
thirteen-year-old middle schooler!
So now it's my turn to tell you.
Nova!
Let's go back together!
What is that light?
There's no way Nova
could develop feelings!
Stop your interfering, middle schooler!
Nova!
Nova?
So these are feelings?
Nova!
Don't you defy your owner, you hollow puppet!
Hollow, huh?
That word brings back memories.
But that's just who I was until a moment ago.
I'm neither hollow nor a puppet anymore!
Right now,
I'm just a normal Nova!
And I just fell in love with Luluco!
Ba-dump!
"Love," nothing!
Pointless! Worthless! Meaningless!
This is why I hate stupid middle schoolers!
And picking a fight against black holes?
That's beyond dumb! It's space dumb!
You're Space Dumbroll Luluco!
You won't get away with this!
I'm gonna shoplift you middle schoolers,
the galaxy, and the entire universe!
And in that new universe,
I'm gonna start my collection anew!
What do we do?
It's all right. We can get through this.
Let's do this together, Luluco.
Nova!
Yeah, let's! Together!
Blackholeian!
You're under arrest for super space shoplifting!
He held my trembling hand tight.
Just that is enough to make me
feel like I can do anything right now!
If wishes do come true,
then I ask for this moment to forever...
...be continued!
To be continued!