Ow...
You okay?
Okay.
My head very hard.
Booze after work?
I... no drink.
You adult, no?
Don't get drunk, so don't like.
About mindset. You, enjoy.
Food okay.
Deal.
There's a car.
Hey, new kid. Go check it out.
R-Right.
Made from spare parts.
A suicide bomber?
Shall we open fire?
Nah, let's wait and see.
We'll consider it hostile if it accelerates toward us.
Roger.
Overthinking it, huh?
Oh? Different convoy approaching.
Check it out.
Look out!
Return fire!
Bond! What are you doing?!
Bond, if it's too hard...
No, I'll do it.
On that day,
I killed someone for the first time.
Following the path of pain
kutsuu no michi wo tadori
Was too much to continue moving forward
ashi wo tometa darou
My time was frozen
kooritsuita toki mo
Keeping my distant memories out of reach
ima wa tooi kioku wo kasunde
If there are no sacrifices
nanimo gisei ni
Is that the definition of strength I can try to achieve?
sore wa tsuyoku nareru no ka to
But I lack even the courage to let go of your hand
nigitta mama no te mo mada hodoku yuuki ga motenakute
I'll become a hero
eiyuu ni naru
I've learned that
narenai kara
For me that's impossible
sono koto ni kidzuiteta
If nothing else, I'll wish for the strength I need to protect you
semete kimi wo mamoritai sou negau
I'll forge my body into a blade
kono karada wo tsurugi ni kaete
And take the path full of obstacles
are wo deta michi wo yuku
I moved forward by defeating even my own weak self
yowakatta jibun sae kiritaoshi susunda
I wonder if I'll ever reach
itsuka todoku no darou ka
The future you wish for
kimi ga nozomu mirai ni
I'll protect you until the very end, when we welcome that day
sono hi wo mukaeru made wa boku ga mamorinuku yo
Hurry up!
Episode 17
"Earth-Saving Hunter"
I was an awkward kid...
One who never really fit in.
And nothing changed, even as the years went by.
And that was friggin' hilarious, man!
What're you lookin' at?
Nothing.
I'd clearly failed to become
a functional member of society.
I felt like I was suffocating.
During those years,
I basically flailed my way through
each day like a fish out of water.
Just living felt like torture.
Though we're well aware our
environment is being damaged,
we can't even ascertain the exact cause.
The environment is far too complex a system.
For example,
consider a massive outbreak of insects...
Martel Group Japan,
a scientific organization focused
on environmental protection.
As members, my parents zealously
participated in its activities,
even bringing me along with them.
Kotarou-kun.
Iko-san?
Fuku Iko-san, caretaker at
an orphanage called House of Ties.
She'd asked me to help with something simple.
Late?
Yeah.
These kids kept dawdling.
Sorry.
I'm the only one around today.
So, what do you need me to do?
Just keep an eye on this one.
Pa.
I have to take these two to day care.
Thanks for your help.
Uh, what's your name?
Pa.
Not that.
Pa?
I'm not your pa.
I'm Tennouji Kotarou.
Pa.
Gimme a break...
I'm back!
Oh my, buddies already?
We can't even hold a conversation.
Normally she's almost too energetic,
but I see she's well-behaved today.
Is it because you're sitting with Kotarou?
She calls me Pa.
That's the only word she knows.
If it's not too much trouble, could you let
her sit with you during the seminar, too?
I guess.
Thanks.
Uh, what should I call you?
Iko-chan is fine!
Not you.
Her.
Oh.
This little one's name
is Senri Akane-chan.
How about the environmental
aftereffects of the H-bombs?
As of today, the islands' ecosystem
has almost completely recovered.
It's said that the radioactive effects
of H-bombs take centuries to dissipate.
You're going to fall.
We will now take questions from the audience.
Ask them something, Kotarou.
Not today.
I told you to prepare!
Come on, raise your hand.
I said not today.
As part of our family, you have to follow our rules!
Stop it!
Yes, the young man in the center.
So what you're saying is, mankind is the biggest
obstacle to protecting the environment, right?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Huh?
Your cheek...
Did they get mad at you?
My parents did, yeah.
And they hit me.
Thanks for everything today.
It's fine.
You weren't wrong, you know.
What you said back there.
Mankind is of pretty much
no benefit to the environment.
We've strayed too far from
Mother Nature's embrace.
Some say that eventually we won't
be able to live on Earth anymore.
Say, Kotarou-kun.
Have you ever gone through something painful?
Sure.
So many I can't even keep count.
If mankind gets culled in the future
and all the painful things go away,
wouldn't you feel a lot better?
Of course, life itself will go on.
But mankind may no longer be a part of it.
You're not getting away.
Hiding in here, huh?
Bloodsucking worm, are we?
A dangerous creature like you
can't be allowed to roam free.
Earth is in grave danger,
and it needs the help of the Earth-Saving Hunter.
That said,
this thing's just small fry.
I'll give you what you want.
Drink up.
It's like a tsuchinoko from the legends.
Is it good?
But that's it for you.
I can freely control my blood.
There.
You just swallowed a thousand needles!
Tonight's Earth Saving is complete.
What were those monsters?
Why do I have these powers?
None of that mattered to me.
I just eliminate UMAs as the Earth-Saving Hunter.
I'd gotten addicted to that thrill.
I figured out that most of the UMAs
could be found in the forest.
And so the Earth-Saving Hunter
moved his base of operations there.
Tonight's Earth Saving is complete.
I need to be stronger.
I guess I'll go with that.
Give me strength befitting the Earth-Saving Hunter.
For some reason, ever since I was a kid,
I had the power to do anything I wished.
What's this?
It's so pretty.
On the other hand, I'm...
I wish everything would just melt away.
Environmental activism, my ass!
Who the hell even cares?
Those... aren't ostriches.
Dinosaurs?
Huh?
Am I gonna die here?
Whatever.
That's fine by me.
I don't fear death.
Is he a civilian?
Looks like he's just a kid.
What do we do now?
Our team specializes in hunting.
We don't walk around with first aid kits.
Wait. There's something off about him.
The bleeding's stopped.
Sleep, boy.
This wallet yours?
Thank you! Let me offer you something in return.
Don't bother. Just get outta this place.
Uh, how did you get so strong?
Do you do martial arts?
What kind of rock do you listen to?
Sorry to summon you here.
Oh, don't be.
That aside—
Oh, that's right.
Here's your phone. We picked it up in the forest.
Thank you.
Uh, who are you people, Esaka-san?
We're investigating UMAs
at the university's request.
Like those dinosaurs?
Oh no, those were just large birds.
You were fighting with swords
and axes, weren't you?
Don't be preposterous.
The others were staff members
and vets from the zoo.
As for myself, I'm a bird watcher.
I'm helping them because
I'm quite knowledgeable about birds.
By the way...
What were you doing in the forest, Tennouji-kun?
I was out for a walk.
So late at night?
That's not safe.
I'm used to it.
But I strongly suggest you make that your last.
I will.
Good.
One more thing.
That forest is home to several new species.
I'd like you to keep that a secret
until we finish our investigation.
Sure.
My lips are sealed.
Not like I have any friends to tell, anyway.
There are no contacts on this phone, either.
I see.
In that case, add me.
Why don't you become email pals with me?
Esaka-san
Hello.
Thanks for having us.
They're our neighbors, the Kanbes.
Say hello.
Hey.
Sorry our son is so unsociable.
That's just how boys are.
Go on, Kotori.
Say hello.
I'm Kanbe Kotori.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah.
We've met in passing several times, though.
We're going out with them for a bit.
Take care of Kotori-chan.
Thanks for having me, Kotarou-kun.
Want something to drink?
Don't mind me.
Feel free to take whatever you want.
Thank you.
You're in grade school, right?
Yes.
Is that so?
Anyway, I'll be in my room.
Irresponsible brat.
I see you have good hearing.
Since you're so proficient at violence,
I suppose your senses are sharp, as well.
You saw me?
Yup.
I hate violence, so I found you to be scum.
They picked a fight with me, you know.
No, they didn't.
They were picking on another kid.
You stuck your nose in it yourself.
You...
Yes?
Is this what you're really like?
So what?
Nothing.
Seems like you really look down on others.
I don't seem like it.
I absolutely am looking down on you.
That so?
Well, have fun up on that high horse of yours.
I'll be in my room.
Don't call me unless you need something.
I won't.
Thank you for your time.
Next up...
What's up, Einstein Junior?
Don't call me that.
Which part? The "Einstein" or the "Junior"?
Both.
Tough customer, huh?
So, how about Martel, huh?
What about it?
What are your thoughts?
That seminar wasn't at all scientific.
They're basically saying we should accept
natural disaster wiping out civilization.
Calling it natural selection...
It feels like they're playing on anxiety
and questioning people's right to live.
This place is messed up.
Never thought we'd agree on something.
You should head back.
This is my exclusive box seat.
Why don't you take part?
Because it's a pain.
That's a lie.
You're running away, aren't you?
If you don't like it, just quit.
There's more to it,
like my relationship with my parents.
That's what you call runnin—
Yeah, yeah, keep talking.
You're wasting time running away
from making a decision.
I won't run away like you.
After that day,
the Kanbes stopped taking part in Martel activities.
She kept her word and did what she said she'd do.
What the hell is that filthy mutt?
Pero.
Make him move.
I can't go in.
I'm sorry.
He just won't move.
Fine. I'll make him.
Outta the way...
Ow!
You piece of shit furball!
Don't be rough with him!
Stop the damn dog, not me!
Please, Pero! Let him go!
I hope you've given him the rabies jab.
We have.
We'll pay for your treatment, too.
Forget it.
No, please!
Whatever you do, just please don't call the pound.
Do you really love that filthy,
violent mutt that much?
He's been through some horrible things...
Oh?
So I guess even Li'l Einstein Junior
can sympathize with dogs.
Well, I didn't get hurt too badly, so it's fine.
Just keep him away from my front door.
He's an eyesore.
Okay...
Apparently, that dog had been
abused by his previous owner.
And the Kanbes took him in.
He contracted food poisoning when his
old owner gave him something with onions,
and now he was wary of any food given to him.
Even so, Kotori did her best to take care of him.
Missing Dog
That mutt went missing, huh?
When was this?
Last night.
Looks like he ripped off his collar.
It had his fur and blood on it.
Talk about a great escape.
Please let us know if you see him.
He'll probably go back to the wild.
The forest's right there, after all.
Pero's been a pet all his life.
He can't find his own food.
His legs aren't in perfect condition, either.
When I told my parents to quit Martel,
they made me promise
to take care of Pero.
What do you want?
Hey.
I brought you something.
What is it?
What do you mean?
Seriously, what?
Horned beetle larvae?!
Are you going to say they look like chili
shrimp and make me unable to eat it?!
Stop it.
You're gonna make me unable
to eat chili shrimp anymore.
It's the thing you're looking for.
Whoa, there.
Hurry up and bring his collar.
Where did you find him?
I went on a stroll through the forest
and happened to find him occupying my box seat.
So I decided to make a complaint to the owner—
Thank goodness.
He ate it.
Maybe he likes his food a little wet.
I never tried that.
See ya.
My job here is done.
Wait.
Are you gonna give me a wad of cash?
I'm kidding.
I don't want any.
Thanks.
I said thanks.
Oh...
Well...
Shouldn't you look me
in the eye when you say that?
Not that I care.
When it comes to idly staying in one place,
I guess he and I aren't too different.
Pero didn't live long after that.
And, until the end, he never took to anyone.
Even after what happened,
my relationship with Kotori didn't change much.
But it did affect me in a way.
Looking at her love a dog that was
nothing more than a duty to her
suddenly made me anxious.
I'll quit Martel.
My instincts were screaming at me to move forward.
The world you live in
nemuru koto no nai
Is one that never sleeps
anata ga tatsu sekai wa
And it's still so pure
mada muku na mama de
If I can leave something
moshi kono daichi ni
In the ground here
nanika wo nokoseru no nara
Let it at least be some kind of a trace
semete omokage wo
I can't even do a simple thing like gaze at the sky
sora wo miageru sonna kantan na koto mo
So I close my eyes
yurusarezu hitomi tojiru
I was only ever looking
tada hitotsu dake
For one thing
mitsukete hoshii no
Sunken in memories
kioku ni shizumu
Feelings of love
itoshisa wo
At the ends of time
ikusen no hate
I hope you stay safe
tadoritsuku anata ga
Until we meet again
sukuwareru you ni
It's fine as long as my song reaches you
kono utagoe todoku kagiri