Should I have called you back sooner?
It's April now, so the cherry
blossoms have started falling.
Oh, it's fine.
Anyway, what's the situation like?
At present, neither we nor Gaia
are making any major moves.
The same goes for the Key.
The Key...
It always returns to where it was
born after its incubation period.
Our best bet is to cast a wide net over this area,
but we lack the manpower.
Sure you want me?
I was nothing but dead weight over there.
Haven't changed one bit, I see.
That said, you're fine the way you are.
Following the path of pain
kutsuu no michi wo tadori
Was too much to continue moving forward
ashi wo tometa darou
My time was frozen
kooritsuita toki mo
Keeping my distant memories out of reach
ima wa tooi kioku wo kasunde
If there are no sacrifices
nanimo gisei ni
Is that the definition of strength I can try to achieve?
sore wa tsuyoku nareru no ka to
But I lack even the courage to let go of your hand
nigitta mama no te mo mada hodoku yuuki ga motenakute
I'll become a hero
eiyuu ni naru
I've learned that
narenai kara
For me that's impossible
sono koto ni kidzuiteta
If nothing else, I'll wish for the strength I need to protect you
semete kimi wo mamoritai sou negau
I'll forge my body into a blade
kono karada wo tsurugi ni kaete
And take the path full of obstacles
are wo deta michi wo yuku
I moved forward by defeating even my own weak self
yowakatta jibun sae kiritaoshi susunda
I wonder if I'll ever reach
itsuka todoku no darou ka
The future you wish for
kimi ga nozomu mirai ni
I'll protect you until the very end, when we welcome that day
sono hi wo mukaeru made wa boku ga mamorinuku yo
Episode 21
"Reunion"
When Yasmin and I looked into the Key,
what we found was terrifying.
Once it is birthed from the earth
in the form of a human,
the Key travels the world with its own legs
and investigates humanity,
Earth's tenants, so to speak.
And when the time comes
for it to pass its judgment,
it causes massive destruction
with itself at the epicenter.
It couldn't be...
She's not here, huh?
Figures.
Wait, she called me here?
You're the Key, aren't you?
Kagari.
Kagari?
It was the first time I'd ever heard that name,
but for some reason,
it felt familiar, like music to my ears.
Tennouji Kotarou.
The planet's memories are all too
wrought with sadness right now.
If that doesn't change, all of it will fall to ruin.
Ruin?
W-Wait a minute!
It'll fall to ruin? All of it?
You mean all of Earth?
Normally, ruin would be followed by re-evolution,
but Earth currently lacks
the vitality to support that.
Re-evolution?
Starting over from scratch and
repeating history as much as possible
until intelligent life is born again.
However, as the consumption
of natural resources has increased,
the vitality of the planet has dwindled.
In this state, there will be
no re-evolution, even after ruin.
And what happens then?
The planet dies.
That's quite the bomb to drop out of the blue.
Why'd you choose to tell me?
Because you and I have formed a link.
Nobody else can see me.
Did it happen when I let you go?
We came in contact when I was sprouting, too.
That was the first thing I ever learned.
I believe what you did
was an expression of either love or devotion.
Th-That was...
In other words, you desire me.
Wait, wait, wait!
Uh...
You're the one who'll bring about
that "ruin" or whatever, right?
Is there any way I can get you to reconsider?
Ruin occurs naturally when I become
filled with sad memories.
There is only one way to stop it:
fond memories.
Fond memories? Such as?
I do not know.
All I can say is that they're
memories that I'd be fond of.
And I need a servant in order
to influence the Homo sapiens.
Servant?
I seek your help as my means to that end.
Bring me fond memories.
As your reward,
I don't mind satisfying your carnal desires.
Hey!
Don't go adding misleading adjectives.
S-So, like, would you let me fondle your breasts?
If you help save this planet,
I will even fornicate with you,
in the worst-case scenario.
Did you have to call it that?
Also, your name will go down in history
as "the man who saved the planet and
fondled Kagari's breasts as a reward."
I'd rather stay anonymous!
Save the planet, huh?
Help
Refuse
Sure, I'll help out.
Are you sure?
I won't go back on my word.
Where do we stand right now?
There's not a moment to waste.
We must find fond memories as soon as possible
and prevent re-evolution from starting.
Fond memories, huh?
I honestly have no idea what those could be,
but we've gotta do this.
Unfortunately, I don't understand
humans enough to define it for you.
However, I do feel like one of the
major causes of sad memories
is conflict between fellow Homo sapiens.
Conflict, huh?
Will stopping one bring you a fond memory?
What if it wasn't a small-scale conflict,
but one involving the whole world?
Like the one between Gaia and Guardian?
Can I really pull it off?
No, I'm the only one who can.
I've engaged with both groups,
but I have never truly felt like I belonged in either.
And I'm the only one.
Going up against such massive
organizations is positively insane.
But...
Kagari, how about you and I
try preventing the planet's death?
That has always been my desire.
Is that you, Tennouji?
Who else?
You seem like a totally different person.
I could say the same about you.
The important areas to keep an eye on
are the station and the main road
passing through the heart of the city.
Then there's the temple area.
There's plenty of targets to monitor,
but the most crucial one is, of course...
The Key.
I hear there's a superhuman who can see it?
Remember Oonishi from Team Mikuni? It's him.
Oonishi?
Oh, him?
Okay.
How about I handle this low-priority area?
Yeah, the forest area shouldn't be a problem.
But don't go around hunting daemons,
okay, Mighty Hero?
Imamiya.
I know.
I'm not a kid anymore.
I'll focus on keeping watch.
I'm pretty good at menial tasks.
You've grown in your own way, huh?
I'm glad I came here first, Imamiya.
I got permission to act alone
and gained some classified info...
Presents too good for a traitor like me.
I set the table so I could operate freely.
I even got a safe house in case I ever needed it.
Next up...
Gaia fanatics share several common features:
they lack confidence, hate the world,
and are passive folks
who find life itself oppressive.
Yeah, folks just like me.
As such, I didn't even need to put on an act.
You could say it was only natural that they picked me.
All of you here must have given up on this world
and entrusted your hopes
and dreams to your next life.
To that end,
your need to purify your life down to its very core.
And this is how you do it.
Behold this daemon,
which has taken such a ghastly form
simply because I offered it some of my spirit.
This is proof that all
of humanity's souls are corrupt.
So our souls really are tainted?
We can't keep living in this world.
But at the same time,
daemons are also a manifestation
of the noble desire to reform the world.
If they make the world a better place
and purify tainted lives in the process,
there is nothing you could
call it but genuine salvation.
My kindred spirits.
Join me in walking the path to salvation.
I began training in the summoning arts.
The first step toward becoming a summoner
is to connect your life to a daemon
through what is called a contract.
The contract link...
Proof that my life force took root
in something as a fleeting form of life.
The next step is gaining experience.
You form contracts with daemons and control them.
If the contract link snaps,
you lose control of the daemon.
An animal-type would die pretty much instantly,
but since insect-types are low-maintenance,
they go around doing as they please for a while.
I digress,
but the rumor that UMAs showed up in the forest
was caused by out-of-control daemons like these.
Anyway, it seems I'm not a very talented summoner.
I'm no match for Yasmin and the rest,
who picked it up all by themselves.
The final step is creation.
As its name implies,
it involves creating a whole
new daemon from scratch.
It's supposed to be far more difficult
than only controlling one...
But to even my own surprise, I actually pulled it off.
And with this...
I became an official member of Gaia.
I've infiltrated Martel... Gaia.
I'm going to start investigating
their internal affairs.
If possible, I'd like to get them
to stop investigating you.
You think we have time for that?
Prepare to eliminate Gaia at once.
Kagari, don't ask for the impossible.
I'm not some omnipotent hero.
Then strengthen yourself.
Do you think I'm blind?
I know you have the power to alter your abilities.
Do that and destroy Gaia, then Guardian.
Why do you ask for the impossible
time and time again?
Besides, that ability...
Then I shall bring judgment down
upon Gaia and Guardian myself.
No need to worry.
Homo sapiens cannot see me.
You think it'll be that easy?
There are humans and daemons
that can perceive you.
You may have great power,
but you're not suited for combat.
You don't even have a shred of battle awareness.
There's no time.
Why won't things go my way?
I'll work it out somehow.
It may take a little while,
but please believe me.
I won't ever betray you.
Of course not.
Betrayal is not an option.
Kagari,
what happened here?
These things took it out.
Just to make sure,
this is the first time, right?
I have 7,548 records of eliminating things
that dared to approach me.
Are you stupid?!
Don't go around killing Gaia's daemons!
It'll make it obvious that something's hidden here!
If they determine that the Key's here,
both Gaia and Guardian will
carry out special operations!
And everything will be over before you can blink!
Can humans really work together that quickly?
Do you have any idea how many times
the Key has been killed in history?
Humans are by far the best creatures at detecting
and hunting alien objects.
Please tell me you haven't killed any people.
I would never take Homo sapiens'
lives for no reason.
Got it.
Please try to hide from those things
or something from now on.
I fail to understand.
How can humans be so intelligent and perceptive
and yet fail to create fond memories?
Why have they stagnated like this?
Seriously...
Why, indeed?
I don't know the answer, either.
Suzaki Shuuichirou, 52 years old.
A Martel Group Japan leader who
controls all of its business interests
and is the major driving force behind its prosperity.
Most of the people who come to Martel
seek to escape from this world.
Aren't you the same, Suzuki-kun?
Yes, that's right.
B-But now that I know I have a power like that,
I, uh, think there must be something I can do.
You mean to say you wish to climb the ladder?
Oh?
Unlike the Saint faction,
Kashima Sakura's world-weary worshipers,
the Suzaki faction places importance
on making profits in this world.
Exploiting their nature made it easy to get
close to him, even as a complete newbie.
Martel has grown into quite a large organization.
And that has led to frequent leaks of information.
You want me to run an internal investigation?
I'm not about to ask an amateur
to do an expert's job.
All you have to do is pay attention to any rumors
and give me your frank opinions.
Of course, if you can figure it out,
nothing would be better.
So his target is the Saint faction.
He wants to weaken Kashima Sakura's
hold on the organization.
Got it.
I'll do everything I can.
Use these daemons.
They're plant-types whose
metabolism requires no oxygen,
so they won't reduce your lifespan much at all.
And use this to make your preparations.
Thank you very much.
The Saint faction and the Suzaki faction.
If I can use this divide for something...
Damn!
She really isn't here!
She usually shows up even if I don't say anything.
But there's no sign of her at all, which means...
Doesn't she realize it's game over
the moment she gets found?!
I didn't think I'd have to use these guys so soon.
They don't have the best eyesight,
but they have an excellent sense of smell.
They're perfect for the job.
Go after the greenest scent you can find!
That's Kagari!
I can't believe you did that!
Why would you go into town?!
It was to increase my
understanding of Homo sapiens.
I determined that it would
help me achieve my goals.
What's the point if you have to walk
into your enemies' crosshairs to do it?!
Do not get hostile with me.
I'm mad because I'm worried about you!
I'm hesitating right now.
I don't know if I should
go along with your decisions.
Don't you want to save the planet?
Yes, but we remain at a standstill.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Please!
Very well.
I'll wait.
Thanks.
Don't let me down.
I'm upset.
I know.
You never get back to me.
This is data of daemons,
from the contract phase to creation.
I want you all to investigate this.
Let me know if you find something, anything.
Everybody is worried about you.
I want you out of this.
We're a family!
I've paid you up front.
Please confirm the transaction.
I'm worried about you.
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
I want to see you.
I checked the data.
It contains information about
transforming life to suit humanity.
It's terrifying.
Can you analyze it?
If you say so.
But I'm scared.
I feel like getting involved
in this stuff is a very bad idea.
I'll keep that in mind.
Worried, huh?
What's this?
W-Wait!
Y-You're Kotarou-kun, right?
Is that you, Kotori?
Did you put up that barrier or whatever, Kotori?
Why are you two together?
Well...
Three years ago,
on the day I left home,
the Kanbes got into an accident in the mountains.
Kotori was the only one who survived it,
and she inherited the power of the druids,
ancient summoners who worshiped Kagari,
along with the duty of protecting her.
And then...
Kotori and Kagari met two years ago,
on the very same day I met Kagari, strangely enough.
She'd been regularly visiting her ever since,
but somehow we'd managed
to miss each other until this day.
Funny, isn't it?
Well, no.
Not in the least.
Is this...
I've been hiding Kagari-san within a barrier here.
But she never stays in one place.
So I was reinforcing the barrier today,
and that's when you showed up.
You've been protecting Kagari all this time, huh?
If I didn't,
I wouldn't have gained the power
to save Mom and Dad.
I see.
Hang on, Kotori.
Keisuke-san and Rikako-san
passed away, right?
Yeah, but they came back to life.
Though they're still a bit awkward.
Wait, don't tell me...
You contracted with them?
You turned human remains into daemons?!
What are you thinking,
you complete and utter moron?!
You can't call that coming back to life!
They're just daemons!
Zombies!
That's not true.
It'll take them some time, but someday...
The dead will never come back to life!
You're a smart girl,
so you should understand that
you're doing something wrong!
How am I supposed to understand?!
This girl will surely protect me.
That will allow you to throw yourself
into conflict free of concern for me.
Screw you!
Don't drag a god damn child into this!
Free Kotori right now and send her home!
If the planet dies, so will everyone on it,
be they adults or children.
That's not what we're talking about!
Anyway, I'm taking Kotori back ho—
I'm not going!
I don't know what your reasons
are for being with Kagari-san,
but I have my own reasons for being here!
You have no idea how dangerous this is, do you?
I do.
No, you don't.
No, you do not.
I do, too.
Forget it.
Get lost.
And don't bother responding.
Kotarou-kun?
You have no business being here.
If you refuse to leave, I'll drag you—
Why?
I've had to go through nothing
but one sad thing after another!
Why can't you be a little nicer to me?!
This is how we've always been.
Are you telling me to live with nobody by my side?!
Mom and Dad were the only ones
who were ever nice to me!
That was the second time I saw Kotori cry,
and I never expected it to hurt so much.
If Earth does fall into ruin in the future and we all die,
I just hope the last thing I see before I go
aren't a girl's tears.
The world you live in
nemuru koto no nai
Is one that never sleeps
anata ga tatsu sekai wa
And it's still so pure
mada muku na mama de
If I can leave something
moshi kono daichi ni
In the ground here
nanika wo nokoseru no nara
Let it at least be some kind of a trace
semete omokage wo
I can't even do a simple thing like gaze at the sky
sora wo miageru sonna kantan na koto mo
So I close my eyes
yurusarezu hitomi tojiru
I was only ever looking
tada hitotsu dake
For one thing
mitsukete hoshii no
Sunken in memories
kioku ni shizumu
Feelings of love
itoshisa wo
At the ends of time
ikusen no hate
I hope you stay safe
tadoritsuku anata ga
Until we meet again
sukuwareru you ni
It's fine as long as my song reaches you
kono utagoe todoku kagiri