I believe I am the one you've been looking for.
You're the witch?
People do seem to call me that, yes.
I'm Senri Akane, a third-year.
I-It's a pleasure.
You don't look awfully surprised.
And here I thought I was
putting on quite the show.
W-Well...
The thing is, I saw something
pretty ridiculous on the way here.
What exactly did you see?
Mysterious, talking creatures,
an unbelievably gigantic monster,
and a ribbon-clad ghost on top of that?
Wow!
Even witches have gone pretty
high-tech these days, huh?
Huh?
This is an FPS.
Play it later!
Allow me to get right to the point.
You're pretty much screwed.
At this rate,
you might even have UFOs coming
for you as soon as tomorrow.
Hey, I'm serious here!
Please don't mock me!
I saw your questionnaire.
Oh, that.
For the final question...
It's an intriguing answer,
Q23) When you brush your teeth in the morning, you start with your:
upper left teeth   upper front teeth    upper right teeth
bottom left teeth   bottom front teeth   bottom right teeth
other (    )
Q24) When you put on your shoes, do you start with the right leg or the left leg?
(1) Right        (2) Left
Q25) You have power and are discontent with this world. Tell me, do you wish to change this world? Or do you wish to change yourself?
(1)The World  (2) Myself
but did you take it seriously when you answered?
Wasn't that the one about
changing the world or myself?
I did, more or less.
Did you?
Um...
I'd like you to deal with this
right away if possible!
I'm one step away from being cursed to death!
I'll give you a charm, then.
I guess this will do.
You "guess"?
I hereby bestow upon you the Amulet of Venus,
within which dwells the magical
energies of the universe.
It's a paperclip!
A paperclip!
You're awfully hung up on its physical form.
Take these with you, too, then.
They're talismans.
What are you, an exorcist?
You won't have any complaints
as long as they work, right?
I guess...
However, we will need to schedule
follow-up appointments.
To that end,
I'll have you join the occult research club.
Huh?
Our stars are only an illusion of the shattered night
hibiwareta yoru ni ikuseisou no sora
On the sky many months and years old
utsuru bokutachi wa maboroshi
I wish to leave behind my past self
moshi kanau no nara kinou to wa chigau
Kanbe Kotori
And have my true self here instead
hontou no boku wo kono chi ni
The proof of our existence vanishes beyond the horizon
bokura ikitekita koto kanata e kieteku
Your life comes to a standstill like a rusted rail
sabitsuita reeru kimi wa tada tachitsukusu
So long as this blue fire flows through my arm
ima kono ude ni nagareru aoi hi ga aru nara
I'll be able to take your hand and stop you
furikaeru kimi no te wo hiite
Vowing to stars born of ashes never to let go
mou nidoto hanasanai to hai no hoshi e chikau yo
I will rewrite this poem
kakikaeru kono uta wo
Episode 2
Place of Youthful Beginnings
Where am I?
Tennouji-san.
Who are you?
I'm Tomoko, one of your talismans.
I've appeared in your dream
as a spirit in order to protect you.
For real?
The enemy is formidable.
I don't know how long I can
oppose her with my strength.
But don't worry!
I'll definitely protect you!
Thank you, Tomoko!
When...
When things calm down...
I want you to go on a date with me!
Okay!
Tomoko...
The ghost!
Tomoko!
What in the world was that?
Good morning, Kotarou-kun.
What's the matter?
Kotori, listen to me.
Last night,
I entered a different realm
from the basement storage area.
Like one of those
"seven secrets of the school" things?
I believe so.
There, I met some small, talking creatures,
a ridiculously huge monster,
and a ribbon-wearing ghost that kept chasing me.
Then, the huge monster and ribbon ghost
suddenly started fighting each other!
And then...
You shouldn't talk about
things like this out in public.
Kotori, Kotarou, good morning.
Oh, Chi-chan, morning.
Ohtori...
Watch out.
This school is rife with danger.
I don't really understand...
Special Offer
Free of Charge
Feecof
It's delicious!
Everyone's treating me like I'm crazy.
Special Offer
Free of Charge
Feecof
It's delicious!
The free part is nice. The taste, not so much.
Still, for the sake of this mission,
I must save as much lunch money as I can.
What are you trying to pull?
This is from the customer over there.
Don't sweat it.
It's on me!
Piss off.
I bet you poisoned it or something!
Perceptive bastard.
I see straight through your tricks!
Hey, are you implying I would stoop to such lows?
Why don't you eat it, then?
What's wrong?
Can't eat it? Huh?
All right, I'm gonna dig in!
Huh? It's sweet?
It shouldn't be...
Don't tell me they got switched?!
That's the one-day-only,
deluxe fruit parfait for you.
It smells fantastic.
I bet it's going to be sweet and delicious.
Now, don't mind if I do!
Wait!
D-Do you need something, Tennouji Kotarou?
N-No, not really.
Having someone stare at me
during lunch is quite unpleasant.
Turn around!
I-Is my eating a parfait that strange?
N-No, not at all.
What's going on?
I've got no choice!
Hey, what on earth are you doing?!
My half-eaten...
Filthy, filthy, filthy!
Pervert, pervert, pervert!
No, let me explain—
Die, you pervert!
Beast! Enemy of women!
Pathetic!
Ow...
Damn, would it kill our class rep
to pull her punches a bit...
Hey, Shizu, my girl.
She's asleep?
Lunch time's almost over.
Maybe I should wake her up?
What the hell's up with that alarm?!
Oh, Kotarou!
Do you always sleep here?
Not always.
Only on days with nice weather, if I feel like it.
I like this spot.
It's peaceful, calming,
and you can hear the birds sing and people talk.
There are all sorts of sounds.
So it's your favorite spot?
We should start heading back.
Sneaky deaky...
Huh?
Gotcha, Shizuru-chan!
Oh? So it actually worked?
Talk about a big surprise.
Tomoko!
What do you think you're doing?!
After she put her life on the line for me...
Isn't it great that this trashy scrap
of paper I had lying around
was more effective than expected?
Well, there are two left,
so you should be okay for two more nights.
Um, Prez.
Yes?
You're kind of mocking the occult, aren't you?
You're right.
I hate people who make a fuss about
magic and superpowers in a bid to escape reality.
This is the occult research club, right?
That it is.
What do our activities include?
We don't do anything in particular.
Even though you have a club room?
It's just a private room.
I simply took over this research club
that was on the verge of being dissolved
because I wanted its club room.
So Prez,
you don't believe in the paranormal
activity I'm experiencing,
or the monster I talked to you about yesterday?
Yes, although I'm sure something must have
happened for you to perceive it that way.
Understood.
Then let's investigate the occult to see who's right!
Investigate it?
This be the occult club.
You be the witch.
And I be the scrub
facing a paranormal glitch!
Everything's come together.
I'm not much for games like that.
If that's what you want to do, knock yourself out.
You look awfully convinced
that you've already won.
I'll admit that there are natural phenomena
yet to be explained by science.
However, spirits and superpowers
are closer to concepts of blind faith.
No, superpowers do exist.
Of that I am sure.
Oh, do elaborate.
Perhaps you have superpowers?
N-No, don't be ridiculous!
What's with the strange reaction?
A-Anyway!
I'll bring you some sort of proof,
so please look into spirit
countermeasures on your end!
Got it.
So, if you are able to prove that
paranormal phenomena exist...
That's right, do you have any requests?
Requests?
Requests...
Then, boo...
"Boo"?
Lemme touch your boobs!
A groper! Call the cops!
You're going to prison!
You're the one who told me to make a request!
Fine.
Huh?
If you can actually prove that
paranormal phenomena exist,
you may use me to satisfy
your primitive, carnal urges.
Seriously?
It's impossible anyway, so I'm not concerned.
Tomoko!
I'd like to recruit her as part of my search efforts.
Who is she?
She's in my class, and we go way back.
Kotarou-kun, what's all this about?
In return for getting help with my ghost troubles,
I joined the occult club.
So, I need to prove that
paranormal phenomena exist.
As part of your club activities?
Yes, that's it exactly.
Not going to mention the part
about touching my breasts?
Breasts?
No, um...
You're... going to touch... her breasts?
Well, not the actual breasts, y'know.
Just the gap in between.
Nothing erotic about it!
Is that what you meant?
Are you okay with that?
Hell no!
Which is it?!
You made such a pervy promise?
Look, it was just a joke.
This girl's rolling in money and power.
It can't hurt to get closer to her.
Dark!
Plotting to use another person like that...
Sounds good to me.
I think this suits you better than
those other, legitimate clubs.
I don't mind helping out.
You heard her!
Do whatever you want.
All right!
The Occult                             Research Club
Welcomes                             You
Our occult club blog is up and running!
Hip hip hooray!
First comes the introduction
and submission form...
This ought to jump-start our activities!
Hello!
Ugh.
Why are you here, Kotarou?
The real question is why you haven't been here.
W-Well, um...
Are you a member of the occult club, too?
Um, yes, I probably am.
I have a few ties to Akane-san.
Prez...
Boobs...
Crap!
I'm out of talismans!
W-Wait.
Wait I, uh, I groped a ghost?
They were soft?
No!
H-Hold on!
Um!
Right there!
Um, have you come up with
those spirit countermeasures yet?
Relax.
I found some additional talismans
and put them in storage for later.
Huh? Wh-Where?
Man...
I hope they haven't lost their exorcising powers...
Hi, Tennouji-kun.
Inoue, from the newspaper club?
I hear you joined the occult research club?
Nothing escapes your notice, huh?
So, I also hear you're investigating
the mysteries of Kazamatsuri?
Yeah.
Just some stuff about paranormal phenomena.
Guess that makes us rivals, then.
Let's play fair and square,
and see who can get the biggest scoop!
What's with that?
I'll be looking forward to the new-and-improved
occult club's future exploits!
A weirdo chick's got her eyes on me.
I'm Nakatsu Shizuru.
Pleased to meet you.
She's an underclassman who'll be helping
with our club activities starting today.
Um, I'm Kotori, a second-year.
Kotori-san.
Second-year.
What's wrong?
A younger girl calling me "Kotori-san"
makes me feel all squicky!
Kotori-senpai?
Yuck! Icky!
I'm not used to it.
I'm sorry.
Kotori?
Yeah, that's perfect!
And, this here is Chi-chan-senpai.
Chi-senpai.
There's no need to be so formal with me either!
Chi?
Yes!
I'll be in your care from now on.
And just like that,
we're starting to feel like a real club!
Something the matter, Prez?
I'm not keen on socializing
or being part of some motley crew.
I'm sure Shizuru will be of use!
In a soothing sense, too.
Excuse me.
It's me. Right now...
A nice guy called Tennouji Kotarou...
A nice guy called Tennouji Kotarou
is hosting club activities and I'm taking part.
Why?
I'm madly in love with him.
So much that I want him to just gobble me up.
Of course, I'm only kidding.
She hung up.
What?!
Who was that?
Lucia.
Konohana Lucia-san?
Wh-Why the class rep?
Lucia's been my best friend for ages.
Tennouji Kotarou!
Honestly.
If it's a joke, then say so.
You hung up before I could.
A-Anyway, what is this place?
What are you all gathered here for?
It's the occult research club!
Occult?
Why are you involved in that?
I'm helping.
We offer the pursuit of
knowledge, entertainment,
and take a scathing look into the
contradictions of modern society!
Also for breasts.
What?
Nothing. Uh...
We have mild recreation,
encounters with the unknown,
and look into other deep questions—
Also for breasts.
Specifically, touching my breasts, correct?
Tennouji Kotarou?
Kotarou.
Unfortunately, my breasts are of
insufficient size to please you.
No, it's not like that!
Besides, there's definitely some
demand for flat chests, and I...
Preying even on Shizuru, you degenerate?
Forget this depraved man's little group!
Let's go, Shizuru!
I don't think Kotarou is as
depraved as you say he is.
What?!
His lust knows no shame whatsoever!
Isn't it a given that adolescent boys
will be interested in boobs?
Shizuru just said something that
would win over any pubescent boy!
Besides, I've already accepted.
I don't want to call it quits midway.
Got it. Fine.
I don't understand why you
would support scum like him,
but if that's how it is,
then I have a duty to keep watch over you.
It's not your duty.
I feel like it is!
Tennouji Kotarou!
I will take part in this little group of yours.
Come again?
Got it?!
Uh, sure.
That's a cliché tsundere rival line if I ever saw one.
I don't completely follow, but essentially...
You could say, "Lucia has joined the party."
That's how it's going to be.
Looking forward to being with you all.
This means the class rep is one of us now, huh?
Are you okay with joining like this, Konohana-san?
My space for intellectual study
is being contaminated by carefree fools.
There's no way around it.
I can't leave Shizuru all alone.
Kanbe-san, Ohtori-san, I'm sorry,
but I'd like you to fill me in on everything.
Registration Form
Name:
Tennouji Kotarou
I hereby declare that I am now
a member of the occult research club.
Kazamatsuri Private Academy
Date:             year      month        day
Very well.
Welcome to the occult research club.
I hope this becomes a nice place
where you fit right in.
I hope I can become a somebody.
Of course!
We haven't really done anything
resembling a club activity yet, though.
Something just...
Well, whatever.
I wish my breasts were a little bigger...
I wanted to lead a productive life.
These guys are just what I need to do that.
I even won Kotori over.
Prez also seems interesting,
like there's more to her than meets the eye.
Ohtori's also a club member.
On top of that, we got Shizuru,
and even the class rep to join.
Not bad.
I could carve out a place to belong all on my own!
I'd never considered that before!
Sometimes, you don't need
to have a rough personality,
or be gloomy,
to end up all alone.
Like me and Kotori.
And maybe even Yoshino.
If we're left out,
then we should all just hang out together.
I'll bring us all together.
Because...
This is our precious youth here!
Thinking everything over,
I don't have too much free time left.
There are some things I can only
do during this stage of my life...
dekakegiwa no amazora kaerigake no kitakaze
Rainy skies when I leave, north wind blowing when I come home
itsudemo kimama ni subete aiseru tsuyosa ga hoshii
Give me the courage to cover every inch of this whimsical world with my love
kyou mo isogigachi na hitonami wo miokuru you ni
Fresh tree leaves sway, as if bidding farewell
osanai konoha ga yureteiru
To waves of rushing people
mata hajimaru yo
So it begins, once again
saa bokura mo sorosoro ikou
Come on, it's about time we went too
ikue ni mo kasanaru sekai de toki no nagare ni mi wo makasete
In this stratified world, we entrust ourselves to time's steady flow
kono saki mo itsudemo futari no ayumi wo tsudzukete ikou
Let's walk towards our future, step by step, always just the two of us
eien nante nozomi wa shinai tatoe chippoke demo kamawanai
I don't need an eternity, I'm happy with something small
tashika ni, ima koko ni bokura ga iru koto
But at this very moment, there's no doubt that we are here
sore ga shiawase
And what is happiness but this?