Transfer paperwork, done.
School uniform, ready.
Rules and regulations, checked.
Cockpit requirements, met.
Don't worry.
I filled out the forms for you too, Aerial.
T-minus 5 minutes before arrival at the 73rd Front,
Asticassia School of Technology.
This ship is now on course to dock.
Wow... a real school!
Mom, I finally made it!
I-It can't be!
No way no way no way! I gotta—
Bridge here.
E-EMERGENCY!
What?
A-A-A-A person! Th-There's a person out there!
Floating outside!
Bridge to Rescue Team.
A person is in need of rescue.
Prepare for EVA.
Ready!
Check the status of the target.
G-Got it, and that...
Any signs of a collision with debris?
Moving forward... gets you two.
Come again?
I'll swave them!
What're you doing?
Leave the rescue to us!
She's heading out?
Tch, what a handful.
Bridge to mobile suit pilot.
I'm opening the external hatch now.
Wait until it fully opens!
Th-Th-Th-Th-Th-Thank you!
Radio us when you find the target.
We'll come over immediately.
Roger!
Out of oxygen?
I'm coming to get you!
Are... Are you okay?
Hello? Anyone ther—
The hell do you think you're doing?!
Um?
I was almost done with that place for good,
and you had to go ruin it!
You better make up for this!
Okay?
Asticassia School of Technology
Episode 1
Suletta Mercury, right?
Y-Yes!
I assume this is your first practical?
I'm Nika Nanaura, a second year
in the mechanical department.
Feel free to ask me anything.
L-L-Lice—
L-L-Lice to—
Lice to moat you!
You're that nervous?
Th-This is my first time going to school...
Your first time?
Hey, did you really come from Mercury?
People seriously live there?
Y-Yeah.
What department are you?
Piloting...
We got an overachiever here!
Why here of all places?
Because my mom told me to.
Your mom?
Did your mom pick out
that dusty-looking headband too?
C'mon, that's mean!
She did!
Are you for real?
Miorine Rembran.
I heard about what happened.
You are to join the class immediately.
Understood.
I-I'll make...
I'll make up for my mistake!
I-I'll do anything you say!
Wh-Wh-What can I do for you?
Ah! You're the girl who ruined my plans!
She'll do anything?
What for?
Are you an idiot?
Someone's gonna get the wrong idea!
Doesn't sound like a bad deal to me, Miorine.
You wanted to screw off to Earth, right?
We're in class right now. Keep quiet.
Earth?
A magenta Dilanza...
It's Guel Jeturk.
Excuse us for interrupting the class.
This duel has been officially sanctioned
by the Dueling Committee.
I, Shaddiq Zenelli, shall be the arbiter.
I ask everyone present to not interfere.
A duel?
Hey, there's people behind me!
They headin' our way?
Guel!
Wreck 'em!
Suletta!
You numbnut! Do you want to get crushed?
Keep running!
How ya like me now, Miorine?
This is the face of a winner!
Everything will be mine, including you and the company.
They're in class, Guel.
Let's clean things up quickly.
This poor sod had the nerve to laugh at me.
Saying how my bride left me.
Bride?
You're the worst.
Wait up, Miorine.
I made a deal with the half-wit,
so now he has to grovel in the dirt.
Get over here and join in the fun, will ya?
I'm home.
U-Um!
What do you want now?
Th-Th-Thank you for s-saving me earlier!
Say what?
Wh-When your fiancé was dueli—
Shut it. I didn't agree to anything.
Then why's he going around
saying you're e-engaged?!
He won a duel.
The students in this school duel each other
with a range of matters on the line.
Whether it's money, rights, apologies,
even matters of marriage.
That's why you have to marry him?
Why is that a thing?
It was put in place by my shitbag father.
Benerit Group Front
Jeturk Heavy Machinery.
Peil Technologies.
Grassley Defense Systems.
These three are the Benerit Group's
highest earners for this period.
However, Parneo Company has been incurring losses
for three consecutive terms at this point.
Our group has no need for those who can't perform.
We hereby suspend all funding
for your company as a subsidiary.
Please rethink your decision, President Delling!
Without the group's financing,
our company will go under!
Exactly.
I'm burying you.
The report from their finance department
indicates that recovery is possible.
They've had their chances.
I have no need for anything other than results.
I sent two guards to watch over
your daughter. Will you be meeting her?
What would be the point?
Don't waste my time over trivialities.
Not a step closer.
S-S-S-S-Sorry!
What is it with you?
What are you holding?
What do you mean? It's a tomato.
That's what a tomato looks like?
What kind of food do Mercurians eat, then?
I've had tomato-flavored food, but...
Take it.
Th-Th-Thank you so much!
U-Um...
You just bite into it.
It's tasty!
Not all tomatoes taste that good.
These ones are special.
My mom created them.
She created tomatoes?
The particular variety, dummy.
Your mom made this.
We're kinda alike.
My mom sent me here to study
and to one day make Mercury a better place.
That's why I'm here.
Is that so.
So your mom is still alive, huh?
S-S-S-Sorry, I didn't mea—
Give me your student ID.
You don't know how to get back, right?
I'll download the school map
for you, so get lost already.
Playing with dirt again?
What's so fun about this Earth charade, anyway?
Guel.
Don't just waltz in here.
I had a great idea.
You're gonna live with us at the Jeturk House now.
Can't have you running off again.
I never agreed to this.
You know it's what your dad decided, right?
Ah yes, the word of the father is absolute.
Do you wag your tail when daddy calls, too?
What do you think you're doing? Stop it!
What a riot huh, Princess?
Hang in there!
St-St-St-Stop him!
If you care so much, do it yourself.
H-H-Help...
I was too easy on you.
As your future husband,
I'll make sure to thoroughly discipline you.
Now keep your mouth shut and do as I say.
D-D-Did your mom not spank you as a child?
You can't do that to a g-girl!
The hell do you think you are?
What's with you?
Do you have any idea who you're messing with?
Um, a pushy suitor?
I'm heir to one of the Benerit Group's Big Three,
and head of the Dueling Committee!
The reigning Holder!
Hol...der?
It's my title as the school's number-one pilot.
I dueled my way to the top.
E-Even so, what's wrong is wrong!
Apologize to Miorine right n-now!
Hah! At this school, right and wrong
are decided by strength alone.
Beat me in a duel and I'll think about it.
I'll do it.
What's this?
I challenge you... to a duel!
Stay out of this!
It has nothing to do with you!
Interesting. If you lose,
you have to leave the school. Deal?
O-Okay!
Are you out of your mind?!
Let's do it!
Move the carrier to Gate 2!
Don't forget to load spare packs!
Carrier moving to Gate 2.
Spare packages, loaded.
Another duel!
It's Guel!
Who's he up against?
It's the transfer student.
Path to Tactical Training Area, clear.
You're clear to launch!
Are you sure about this?
If Delling kicks the bucket,
my son Guel's engagement will be secured.
We have to do him in before any more
duels take place and change that.
Set the detonation for 10 minutes after launch.
Delling. It was nice knowing you.
13th Tactical Training Area
Obtaining environment settings
for the Tactical Training Area.
Coriolis correction, all green.
Bioinfo and identification confirmed.
Permet Link, sufficient.
KP001. Guel Jeturk.
Dilanza, launching!
Always so flashy.
Not interested, Elan?
Not one bit.
You didn't have to accept
a challenge from that bumpkin.
I'll make it quick.
I'm the future ace pilot of Dominicus, after all.
There you are, Mercurian bitch.
Tricolore: a flag of three colors,
particularly the national emblem of old France.
Her suit's quite fancy, too!
I don't see a logo. Was it made from scratch?
Arriving at the designated coordinates.
The duel will now commence
after consent from both parties.
The win condition is as usual:
first to take their opponent's Blade Antenna.
Combatants, face off!
Wait, that's the Princess!
It wasn't the transfer student?
How did Miorine get inside Aerial?
Oh...
Suletta?
What's going on?
What's the big idea, Miorine?
Why am I never the one in control of my own life?
This is my fight!
What a cheeky woman. Fine, then.
I'll put you in your place.
Guel, do you approve the change in opponent?
I approve.
The victor shall not be decided
by the performance of their mobile suit alone.
Nor will it be decided solely
by the abilities of the pilot.
Results are the one and only truth!
Commence duel.
Weapons, where are the weapons?
There's no way an amateur can handle a mobile suit!
Two more minutes.
My life is my own.
I make my own decisions!
The princess is from the management strategy
department. She doesn't stand a chance.
Know your place.
You're nothing but a trophy to me.
An alert? Someone's trespassing?
Who the hell dares?!
Exceeding speed limit. Please slow down.
Nika, why's your name showing up?
I'm just helping someone in need, no biggie.
What're yo—
What was that for?!
Give her back!
What?
Aerial is mine!
I told you, this has nothing to do with you!
Then fight with your own mobile suit!
Oh, come on! It's just a mobile suit!
What's going on?
They're arguing?
Aerial's not just a mobile suit!
We grew up together. She's family!
What? Family?
I'll make up for earlier by winning.
Aerial and I would never lose
to scrap metal like that!
Scrap, you say?!
Shaddiq! Change the duel opponent back!
Approved.
Secilia.
'kay!
Guel...
Time for your first lesson, you boor!
Eyes up!
My mom always says this:
"Running away affords a single blessing,
but moving forward gets you two."
What?
When you run, you avoid defeat.
But if you move forward...
You're saying you can win?
Winning isn't everything.
Even when I lose,
I gain experience, earn pride...
And now, trust!
A shield?!
You shitty bumpkin, try this on for size!
What the hell is that mobile suit?
GUND-ARM.
It's a Gundam.
What the hell are you?!
It's time.
Jeturk, sir.
It's too late to try and change my mind.
Not that, sir.
Your son was defeated in a duel.
Even if President Delling dies now,
Miorine will not be betrothed to your son.
Who defeated him?
Grassley? Peil?
Neither of them.
It was...
U-Um.
I... I won.
You sure did.
Suletta Mercury.
Huh? What's this?
This attire is proof of your victory
and bears the emblem of the Holder.
That emblem is also the mark of our engagement.
I told you before, right?
These are the rules my father established.
B-But I'm a girl...
Mercury's still behind the times, huh?
It's totally normal over here.
Here's to our future, miss bridegroom.
I saw you floating along like a star in the sky
Falling deep into sleep with a world passing by
No matter what lies ahead, lead the way, I will stay
So you will never be lonely again
Now your world has you and me
Every day, I see you wishing dearly
For memories long forgotten, tossed beyond the waves of time
You're stuck and you're left behind
Come with me and leap into the scenery
There's so much we've never seen, free from the gravity
'Cause you've been drifting all alone in the world
In a prayer, in a dream
Not a fret, not a care
In a sweet reverie
Now if you don't wanna hide and you're tired of the wait
Take a chance, and don't you dare look away
You'll live a life of all your own discretion
You'll live a life where time and place are all up to you
Take my hand and let's come up with the story
We'll make it so we never part till the end of time
Entrusted with the gift of life, we were born
We were entrusted with a planet's will to carry on
And share our love for each and every life out there
May each of us, alive, have every blessing there's to be
Episode 2
- Cursed Mobile Suit -
Next time on Mobile Suit Gundam:
The Witch from Mercury,
Cursed Mobile Suit.
Art: JNTHED